tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
DDC_FINAL,7 | 176,consider God repentance salvation despise proposition grace hour sake glory,god: 0.5; child: 0.5; word: 0.5; decree: 0.5; grace: 0.45; heart: 0.45; promise: 0.4; election: 0.4; reprobation: 0.4; man: 0.25; chapter: 0.15; father: 0.1; faith: 0.1; paul: 0.05; sin: 0.05; elder: 0.05; purpose: 0.05; saint: 0.05; christ: 0.05,"('Paul', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 7; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 7; ('two .', 'DATE'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('thirteen .', 'DATE'): 3; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 3; ('8', 'DATE'): 3; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('26', 'DATE'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'DATE'): 2; ('40', 'DATE'): 2; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 2; ('21', 'DATE'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('44', 'DATE'): 2; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('24', 'DATE'): 2; ('a late hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty-one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three .', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('twelve .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a very late hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Jacob and Esau', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Isaac', 'GPE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xxvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Esau', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('xxxiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('three .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('harden', 'GPE'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('10 , 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('xxviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('twenty-nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter twenty-five .', 'LAW'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter thirteen .', 'LAW'): 1; ('John viii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten .', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve . 39', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this thy day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('Homer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('odyss', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Odyss', 'GPE'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1"
DDC_FINAL,8 | 216,transcription page HTML make John thing thing encage Cor. say,person: 0.5; father: 0.45; god: 0.45; son: 0.45; essence: 0.45; reason: 0.45; christ: 0.45; thing: 0.4; john: 0.35; passage: 0.35; man: 0.15; heaven: 0.1; particular: 0.05; participate: 0.05; plurality: 0.05; place: 0.05; pharisee: 0.05; petition: 0.05; paul: 0.05; position: 0.05; scripture: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 26; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 8; ('thou', 'GPE'): 6; ('John', 'PERSON'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('John vi .', 'PERSON'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 3; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two .', 'DATE'): 2; ('three .', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ten .', 'DATE'): 2; ('xiv', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John xiv', 'PERSON'): 2; ('that day', 'DATE'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('xxiv', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thirteen .', 'DATE'): 2; ('36', 'DATE'): 2; ('HTML', 'ORG'): 1; ('93', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John i .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John viii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('more than one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xiv', 'ORG'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('20 , 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('xvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Syriac', 'LOC'): 1; ('Oriental', 'NORP'): 1; ('arabic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('viii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thess', 'NORP'): 1; ('three .', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Salome', 'ORG'): 1; ('Horace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Protea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luke xxiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('xxvi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('53', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('more than twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mark xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('luke xxii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('John twelve', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John xvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('seven . 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('herein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven .', 'DATE'): 1; ('twelve .', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
DDC_FINAL,14,penitent enjoin sin father Lev. iniquity iniquity father Nehem. sin,original: 0.5; sin: 0.45; man: 0.45; evil: 0.45; call: 0.45; parent: 0.4; heart: 0.35; rom: 0.3; iniquity: 0.3; bear: 0.25; father: 0.2; matt: 0.15; guiltiness: 0.15; act: 0.1; thing: 0.05; god: 0.05; ovid: 0.05; origin: 0.05; part: 0.05; pallasne: 0.05; pagan: 0.05; pelagius: 0.05; occasion: 0.05; offender: 0.05,"('17', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 5; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('twelve .', 'DATE'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('seven .', 'DATE'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('xvii', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nehem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sarai', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thucydides', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('I. Sect', 'ORG'): 1; ('126', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pallasne', 'ORG'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('ten .', 'DATE'): 1; ('three .', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James i .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('mar videt hanc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three . 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('viii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Job xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('livre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xlviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two .', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('three . 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xxiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('luke xi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty-five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John nineteeen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('uprightness', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luke xvi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
DDC_FINAL,16,CHAP. Xiii death body degree death call death body labour,body: 0.5; soul: 0.5; death: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; god: 0.45; resurrection: 0.35; whole: 0.3; lord: 0.3; day: 0.25; passage: 0.15; heaven: 0.1; life: 0.05; place: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 8; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('the day', 'DATE'): 7; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 7; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('David', 'PERSON'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 6; ('two .', 'DATE'): 5; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('21', 'DATE'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 4; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 3; ('14', 'DATE'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('three .', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('three .', 'DATE'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('that day', 'DATE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('35', 'DATE'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ten .', 'DATE'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 2; ('twelve .', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John xi', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John xiv', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('only two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('29', 'DATE'): 2; ('30', 'DATE'): 2; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Philipp', 'NORP'): 2; ('Vulg', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('52', 'DATE'): 2; ('Lazarus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Syriac', 'ORG'): 2; ('today', 'DATE'): 2; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Xiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three degree', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Job', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xxviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('viii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('xi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('xxxvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15 , 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('thirty-nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rachel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven .', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('tomorrow', 'DATE'): 1; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('three . 18 — 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the twenty-first', 'DATE'): 1; ('cxlvi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that very day', 'DATE'): 1; ('last', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty-one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hebr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('xxvi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John v. 28', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Thess', 'NORP'): 1; ('thirteen .', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four day', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('the quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('luke xxiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve .', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('532', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Beck', 'PERSON'): 1; ('599', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xxiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 Sam', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('thirty .', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dives and Lazarus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('luke xvi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou today', 'TIME'): 1; ('xxvii', 'GPE'): 1; ('53', 'DATE'): 1; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('resurrectionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forty-sixth', 'DATE'): 1; ('Stephen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 Thess', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('the three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Stephen', 'GPE'): 1; ('2 Cor.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 1"
DDC_FINAL,46,CHAP. class virtue connect duty man virtue desire advantage reference,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; jehovah: 0.5; king: 0.5; prov: 0.5; riches: 0.45; thing: 0.45; encage: 0.35; woman: 0.35; life: 0.35; matt: 0.15; day: 0.1; heart: 0.1; wine: 0.05; covetousness: 0.05; evil: 0.05; honour: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 18; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 14; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 12; ('two .', 'DATE'): 10; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('thou', 'GPE'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('twenty-one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('the day', 'DATE'): 7; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('ten .', 'DATE'): 7; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('thirteen .', 'DATE'): 6; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('three .', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('12', 'DATE'): 5; ('twenty-five', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('three .', 'DATE'): 5; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 4; ('Jehovah', 'GPE'): 4; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('seven .', 'DATE'): 4; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('24', 'DATE'): 4; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('twelve .', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Thess', 'NORP'): 3; ('xiv', 'PERSON'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('22', 'DATE'): 3; ('xxvii', 'GPE'): 3; ('twelve .', 'DATE'): 3; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('xi', 'PERSON'): 3; ('18', 'DATE'): 3; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('twenty-nine', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('xxviii', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8', 'DATE'): 2; ('49', 'DATE'): 2; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('xxiv', 'PERSON'): 2; ('luke twelve', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'DATE'): 2; ('23', 'DATE'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('xxii', 'GPE'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'DATE'): 2; ('Philipp', 'NORP'): 2; ('xxxvii', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('cxix', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John vi .', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thirteen .', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('xiv', 'ORG'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 2; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1 Sam ten .', 'QUANTITY'): 2; ('Shechem', 'ORG'): 2; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pilgrim', 'ORG'): 1; ('two .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Noah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Benhadad', 'GPE'): 1; ('1 king ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('20 , 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('early in the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('luke twenty-one', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('42.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xxvi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('thirty .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 Cor.', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Homer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Penelope', 'GPE'): 1; ('odyss', 'GPE'): 1; ('333', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('I. 414', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zeph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two . 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('thirty .', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('xxxiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16 ,', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty .', 'DATE'): 1; ('xvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 king ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Job ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('take heed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('luke v. 29', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John twelve', 'PERSON'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('luke xvi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two . 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deborah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John v. 41', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jezebel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Neh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('whatever quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sodom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ephron the Hittite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gideon', 'ORG'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel two', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter v. 17', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('James i .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirty . 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abimelech', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Sam xv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Sam xxii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'ORG'): 1"
B08803,1,Vera effigy IOHANNIS Collings S.T.P. man|be shadow picture shadow shadow,god: 0.5; sense: 0.5; reason: 0.5; man: 0.5; principle: 0.5; ladyship: 0.5; knowledge: 0.5; proposition: 0.4; evidence: 0.25; understanding: 0.2; providence: 0.15; year: 0.1; scripture: 0.1; madam: 0.05; help: 0.05; creature: 0.05; act: 0.05; thing: 0.05; divine: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1678', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('IOHANNIS Collings S.T.P.', 'ORG'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('R. White', 'PERSON'): 1; ('167•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Collings', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('John Collinges', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D.D. London', 'ORG'): 1; ('Edward Giles', 'ORG'): 1; ('Andrews', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Norwich', 'GPE'): 1; ('Frances Thompson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('your year', 'DATE'): 1; ('many day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the few year', 'DATE'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('19.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these latter day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Judg', 'PERSON'): 1"
B08803,4,mr. George Herbert providence providence end finger quill right creature,praise: 0.45; thing: 0.4; man: 0.4; wind: 0.4; hand: 0.4; creature: 0.4; way: 0.4; beast: 0.4; herb: 0.25; make: 0.15; sea: 0.15; art: 0.1; plenty: 0.1; plant: 0.1; prey: 0.1; power: 0.1; poison: 0.1; providence: 0.1; permission: 0.1; place: 0.1; rain: 0.1; bird: 0.1; meat: 0.05; world: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('George Herbert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('bee', 'ORG'): 1; ('sheep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('indian', 'NORP'): 1"
B08803,6 | 1790,lord Psal. soul commit lord well-doing Pet. lord way man,god: 0.5; providence: 0.5; world: 0.5; man: 0.5; motion: 0.5; thing: 0.5; action: 0.4; prayer: 0.35; body: 0.25; lord: 0.25; duty: 0.2; power: 0.2; divine: 0.2; event: 0.05; day: 0.05; reason: 0.05,"('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('daily', 'DATE'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20.22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('37.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Assyria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('76.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('25.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('a few day', 'DATE'): 1; ('evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('every night', 'TIME'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prop', 'LOC'): 1; ('Atlas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Atlas', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Neh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1"
B08803,6 | 1827,principal faculty life creature rest requie experience while power creature,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; power: 0.5; faculty: 0.5; creature: 0.5; body: 0.5; beast: 0.5; providence: 0.45; create: 0.3; lord: 0.3; virtue: 0.25; soul: 0.1; preserve: 0.05; uphold: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('the day', 'DATE'): 8; ('daily', 'DATE'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psalm 127', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('77.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the first day', 'DATE'): 1; ('104.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('three or fourscore year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psalm 113.9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psalm 127.3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('107.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('quam creatricis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Raymundus de', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ita omnes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mesua', 'GPE'): 1; ('arabian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sanat', 'ORG'): 1; ('gentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nova', 'LOC'): 1; ('terris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cummin', 'ORG'): 1; ('15.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nisi vegitaret deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cum ego dormio nisi', 'ORG'): 1; ('custodiret cum ego sim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Spatium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. second', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('God every hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('3. third', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('113.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('the ministry of inferior magistrate', 'ORG'): 1; ('membra culicis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('147', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('139', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('almost every hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ananias', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Saphira', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zechariah', 'GPE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeroboam', 'PERSON'): 1"
B08803,7,Prop. God providence creature care care proposition method providence i.e.,god: 0.5; church: 0.5; angel: 0.5; providence: 0.5; thing: 0.5; man: 0.5; world: 0.5; people: 0.5; creature: 0.35; care: 0.2; make: 0.2; promise: 0.1; salvation: 0.05; christ: 0.05; child: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('christian', 'NORP'): 8; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 7; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('thou', 'GPE'): 6; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Canaan', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 3; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 2; ('91', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('91.11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Josephs', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three hundred year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 2; ('Prop.', 'LAW'): 1; ('11.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abimelech', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('16.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Medes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Persians', 'NORP'): 1; ('1260 day', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 1; ('twenty one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('the asian church', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.1', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. third', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gibeon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ajalon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Joshuah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Corah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abiram', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jericho', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand put ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4thly', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pellam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Keilah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sisera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('classica venti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('91.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Parisian', 'NORP'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gallio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Darius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hamans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mordecai', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('outward providence', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7thly', 'DATE'): 1; ('grace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.4 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8thly', 'DATE'): 1; ('8.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cephas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dwell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.10', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('48.16', 'MONEY'): 1; ('18.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dingle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sodom', 'GPE'): 1; ('19.16', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Padan', 'GPE'): 1; ('28.12', 'MONEY'): 1; ('32.1', 'MONEY'): 1; ('34.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('a few year', 'DATE'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day of Elijah', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elija', 'NORP'): 1; ('seven thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Piedmont', 'GPE'): 1"
B08803,8 | 2702,affliction trouble saint fit kingdom God thing salvation heir salvation,god: 0.5; affliction: 0.5; man: 0.5; evil: 0.5; divine: 0.5; heart: 0.5; time: 0.5; reason: 0.4; way: 0.35; lord: 0.3; thing: 0.25; wisdom: 0.05; dust: 0.05; trouble: 0.05; providence: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 8; ('David', 'PERSON'): 6; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('the day', 'DATE'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Helena', 'ORG'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10.2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jonah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('polish', 'NORP'): 1; ('3.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('a night', 'TIME'): 1; ('the next night', 'TIME'): 1; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Phaenomenon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Shimei', 'ORG'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Troy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aeneas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Venus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Tyndaridis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lacenae culpatusve Pani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 1; ('Venus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Neptune', 'ORG'): 1; ('Juno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lextalionis', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nazianzene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('beneficiis afficis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plinius Secundus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('non aeris acervus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('auri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aegroto', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28.20', 'MONEY'): 1; ('132.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lord', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.9 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('76.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirty-nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Job', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Melancthon', 'GPE'): 1; ('next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('stulta•es', 'PRODUCT'): 1"
B08803,8 | 2951,soul fix assent god make people suit dispensation sort write,god: 0.5; faith: 0.5; life: 0.5; soul: 0.5; man: 0.5; promise: 0.45; heart: 0.4; word: 0.35; christian: 0.35; time: 0.3; world: 0.25; thing: 0.15; mean: 0.1; truth: 0.05; mercy: 0.05; evil: 0.05,"('christian', 'NORP'): 13; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('David', 'PERSON'): 6; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('thou', 'GPE'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('a evil day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('more than one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('125.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('46.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('94.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('their day', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sennacherib', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('passi graviora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 9', 'LAW'): 1; ('70 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaac', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('a good day', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David do Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('five 22.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Belial', 'GPE'): 1"
B08178,8,fault escape page line describe line re•de Lin page Pa.,man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; mr: 0.5; lin: 0.5; thesis: 0.5; soul: 0.45; fault: 0.45; author: 0.45; divine: 0.3; messia: 0.25; work: 0.25; world: 0.1; faculty: 0.05; thing: 0.05; press: 0.05; year: 0.05; book: 0.05,"('Lin', 'PERSON'): 7; ('li', 'PERSON'): 7; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Messiah', 'GPE'): 2; ('duae', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Genealogiae', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('fault escape', 'ORG'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. li', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pa. 40', 'GPE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('70', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('110', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('169', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('172', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('176', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('181', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('225', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('229', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('232', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cvius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('noxas perpurgan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tam paruo magna hbello', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sortitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('gaza', 'GPE'): 1; ('E. S.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theologica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Animae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Productio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Millenar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Criticus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Seria', 'GPE'): 1; ('nisi', 'GPE'): 1; ('VILVAIN', 'ORG'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('R.', 'NORP'): 1; ('1654', 'DATE'): 1; ('Theologis', 'ORG'): 1; ('medice crepidam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Parcite Theiologi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nil nisi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('velut echo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anglica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Preli', 'GPE'): 1; ('Carmina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('calamo', 'ORG'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Oxford Academia OXONIENSIS', 'ORG'): 1; ('THEOLOGICA', 'ORG'): 1; ('summa octo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('octo Theiologi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae tenue hoc liquido', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theiologis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ordine', 'NORP'): 1; ('certo', 'NORP'): 1; ('scripta sequente l•bro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Productio', 'GPE'): 1; ('Qûi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quarta Propheteias de Messia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stemma Genethliacum', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('maxima', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('sexta aperit mysteria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joanni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de regno mille', 'ORG'): 1; ('Messia', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johns', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Propbetiae de Messia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangeliis', 'ORG'): 1; ('terris cum martyribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('mille', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristocratic', 'ORG'): 1; ('one thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Epistola', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Mainard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('howbeit', 'GPE'): 1; ('•ho disnerve', 'ORG'): 1; ('Essais Rob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vilvain', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hunc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mihi vir multis titulis charissime', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tantum ego grati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pendo', 'GPE'): 1; ('mei', 'ORG'): 1; ('Devot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non adulatorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aut mendacia •ingo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inferiora tuis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Appello Evangelium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tailor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thorndike', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Smiths', 'PERSON'): 1; ('••fth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Cowper of Galoway', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('h•k•w•s', 'GPE'): 1; ('•ch', 'NORP'): 1; ('Theorem', 'ORG'): 1"
A95924,11,Lambethae article Lambeth appendix article praedestination agitate John archbishop Canterbury,man: 0.5; soul: 0.5; god: 0.5; article: 0.5; part: 0.5; life: 0.4; sin: 0.4; whole: 0.3; cause: 0.3; thing: 0.3; dr: 0.2; save: 0.2; faith: 0.2; spirit: 0.1; body: 0.1,"('it|be', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Wil', 'LOC'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lambethae cusi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lambeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John archbishop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('1595', 'DATE'): 1; ('dr.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('whitaker instance', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three proposition', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Frenchman', 'ORG'): 1; ('Margaret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cambridg', 'ORG'): 1; ('article 1', 'LAW'): 1; ('article 2', 'LAW'): 1; ('article 3', 'LAW'): 1; ('article 4', 'LAW'): 1; ('article 5', 'LAW'): 1; ('article 6', 'LAW'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('article 7', 'LAW'): 1; ('article 8', 'LAW'): 1; ('article 9', 'LAW'): 1; ('Animadversio apposita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Janus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('may fall', 'DATE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('frailty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('intentionaly', 'GPE'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Rainolds', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lambethian', 'NORP'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seventeenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Whitgift Archbishop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('whitaker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('soul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eve it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ S. luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gabriel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine solar month', 'DATE'): 1; ('39 week', 'DATE'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Animai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucretius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nata', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('dire•pta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erebi', 'NORP'): 1; ('vastasque lacunas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pliny', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arcane miracle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Archelaus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Democritus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epicurus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Hippocrates', 'GPE'): 1; ('Galens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pentagon', 'ORG'): 1; ('hatd', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A95924,13,manner substance God thing sort air divine angel limit place,soul: 0.5; god: 0.5; body: 0.5; man: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; sin: 0.5; adam: 0.5; seed: 0.4; create: 0.35; father: 0.25; parent: 0.25; creation: 0.15; part: 0.05; nature: 0.05,"('Adam', 'PERSON'): 16; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 13; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Traduction', 'ORG'): 2; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Aristotle', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Vegetativ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sensitiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('intellectiv liv eternal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sparta', 'GPE'): 1; ('Adam Rib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the seven day', 'DATE'): 1; ('divina particulam aurae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('massilians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apollinaris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Jerom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hunnius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Magirus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Goclenius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Brightman', 'ORG'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eucherius', 'GPE'): 1; ('de novo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('literary republic assert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('palliativ salvs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Priscillianists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tertullianists', 'ORG'): 1; ('the day thou eat', 'DATE'): 1; ('damnati S. Bernard .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('antequam nati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forlese', 'NORP'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three degree', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Comparat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Whitaker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter Lombard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam mar :', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 Joh', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cumel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('privativ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gehezais', 'GPE'): 1; ('•vae hinc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eccls', 'ORG'): 1; ('secondary', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Zechary', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('57 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('mov', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zedekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('ergo it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacobs', 'ORG'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('133', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('whi•h', 'GPE'): 1"
A95924,13 | 3761,Answ. infusion time conception traductist inference difficulty day hour distance,soul: 0.5; parent: 0.5; man: 0.5; body: 0.5; seed: 0.5; god: 0.5; part: 0.5; generation: 0.35; sol: 0.35; answ: 0.35; arg: 0.15; sin: 0.1; adam: 0.05; create: 0.05; whole: 0.05; spirit: 0.05,"('Sol', 'PERSON'): 13; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 12; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 11; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('Traduction', 'ORG'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Seth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Answ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Eve', 'PERSON'): 2; ('no particular three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a few hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Embryon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marsilius Ficinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('exerci•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristotle assert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('foris adve•it', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('w•l', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Varus', 'GPE'): 1; ('the first six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dominicans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Franciscans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Luciferians', 'NORP'): 1; ('circumstantialy', 'GPE'): 1; ('1. 28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the seven day', 'DATE'): 1; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caus', 'ORG'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('adesse jovi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jehov', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'MONEY'): 1; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ewe', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athaeneus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hippocrates', 'NORP'): 1; ('Males', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('casualy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Helides', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ethiope', 'LOC'): 1; ('multiloq•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mantuan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui viret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Natos', 'ORG'): 1; ('Traducal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Repl', 'ORG'): 1; ('ergo thosinnat', 'ORG'): 1; ('formativ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Postulatum', 'GPE'): 1; ('praeparando', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1"
A95924,13 | 3824,Repl. source principal subject faculty soul seed spirit blood seed,soul: 0.45; man: 0.45; god: 0.45; sin: 0.45; whole: 0.45; parent: 0.45; create: 0.45; flesh: 0.45; body: 0.4; sol: 0.2; seed: 0.1; humanity: 0.05; union: 0.05; nature: 0.05; conception: 0.05; pollute: 0.05; pollution: 0.05; phrase: 0.05; piece: 0.05; point: 0.05; peter: 0.05; prepare: 0.05; precipitat: 0.05; person: 0.05; posterity: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('Sol', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Eve', 'PERSON'): 2; ('S. Austin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Repl', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zanchius', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tene•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gordian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter Moulin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bridewell', 'ORG'): 1; ('Will', 'GPE'): 1; ('consent year', 'DATE'): 1; ('quot homines', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Traduction', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('11. 33', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the seven day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hippo', 'NORP'): 1; ('goodman', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gloucester', 'GPE'): 1; ('logico-philosophico - theology', 'ORG'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jugiter genitus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('genitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be inquire', 'PERSON'): 1"
A95924,14,Appendix appendix theory take mr. Henry woolnot treaty entitle original,soul: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; sin: 0.5; body: 0.5; adam: 0.5; nature: 0.5; whole: 0.5; propagation: 0.45; creation: 0.35; part: 0.2,"('Adam', 'PERSON'): 34; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 22; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 10; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Sol', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('mar', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thetis', 'GPE'): 1; ('realy', 'GPE'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hilary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eucherius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Traduction', 'ORG'): 1; ('18.', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scaliger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('angel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sensitiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('elementary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rachel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 1; ('ruth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scylla', 'ORG'): 1; ('Charybdis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sicil', 'GPE'): 1; ('Columbus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cuba', 'GPE'): 1; ('wherein sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Whale', 'ORG'): 1; ('Supralapsarians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Adam', 'GPE'): 1; ('18. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Adam quoad existentiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('unionem', 'ORG'): 1; ('circumstantialy', 'GPE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('goodman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first institute', 'ORG'): 1; ('six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('woolnot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nostram', 'ORG'): 1; ('Allter', 'GPE'): 1; ('nova', 'LOC'): 1; ('Eve', 'PERSON'): 1"
A95924,15 | 3993,Ob. object matter god prescience preordination future event found prevision,god: 0.45; man: 0.45; decree: 0.45; prescience: 0.45; evil: 0.45; vessel: 0.45; grace: 0.35; life: 0.35; mean: 0.25; potter: 0.25; thing: 0.15; act: 0.15; power: 0.15; mercy: 0.1; part: 0.05; parcel: 0.05; permissiv: 0.05; period: 0.05; perdition: 0.05; people: 0.05; paul: 0.05; persecutor: 0.05; ordain: 0.05; operation: 0.05; divine: 0.05,"('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sol', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('hereof Rabbi Isaac bar Sesac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hownbeit', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('h•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('god', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('t•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('•ay •h•n', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam nati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non quam noti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8. 15. 32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nazaret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('50. 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvinians', 'NORP'): 1; ('vocavit', 'GPE'): 1; ('justificavit', 'GPE'): 1; ('non decet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('nam cum vino', 'PERSON'): 1"
A95924,16,Reprobatio praevisis reprobation foreknow side predestination election be show black,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; decree: 0.5; sin: 0.5; action: 0.5; author: 0.5; evil: 0.5; reason: 0.4; thing: 0.35; chief: 0.3; reprobation: 0.3; end: 0.1; cause: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 7; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Pelagians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('21', 'DATE'): 2; ('Calvinists', 'NORP'): 2; ('Moulin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 2; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('54', 'DATE'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('god', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sec', 'ORG'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 §', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14 c', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('§', 'NORP'): 1; ('Supralapsarians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Reprobos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sermo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gen.', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui non vetat cum possit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jubet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Jerem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of Arles against', 'ORG'): 1; ('490', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arausican', 'NORP'): 1; ('grey assembly', 'ORG'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacobus Andreas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frederic earl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wirtenberg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('guil•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hague', 'GPE'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 1; ('dort synod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mahometans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alcoran', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Titus 3', 'LAW'): 1; ('Edwin Sandys', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hemingius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lutheran', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('manichee', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three opinion two', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('hose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3 33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('86', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jonah 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Marlorat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 3.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('outward suggestion', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wil', 'LOC'): 1; ('counsil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward earl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Warwick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tiberius', 'NORP'): 1; ('damn million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('irrespectiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dr.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ʋsh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Got••s•', 'ORG'): 1; ('138', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Seotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('operativ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('81. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('18 39 Rom', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('22. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('shun sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dagon house', 'ORG'): 1; ('Whitaker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pareus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sauls', 'ORG'): 1; ('Noe', 'ORG'): 1"
A95924,16 | 4047,tempt woe cast reject dialogue grace glory minister daunt afflict,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; decree: 0.5; save: 0.5; pleasure: 0.45; evil: 0.45; hell: 0.45; beast: 0.4; damn: 0.25; soul: 0.2; creature: 0.1; tempt: 0.1; grace: 0.05; torment: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 4; ('Sol', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 2; ('grace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('526', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Will', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('frailty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 2 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('liber•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('people many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sacrifi•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Twiss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jud•s', 'PERSON'): 1; ('b•tra••d', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mat 26', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('realy', 'GPE'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('107', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Jerom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('so many million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Diagoras', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('overald', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvinists', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be nihil', 'FAC'): 1; ('Calvinists', 'NORP'): 1; ('velle suo venit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Novit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Postea', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elohim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('libito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lie gravis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('certo', 'NORP'): 1; ('ant•', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam statuit Mundum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aut', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1"
A95924,17,Thetis Iii Ecclesiae church polity know verity paternity prime h•story,church: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; elder: 0.5; apostle: 0.5; presbyter: 0.5; priest: 0.5; paul: 0.5; saint: 0.5; deacon: 0.25; disciple: 0.2; father: 0.1; christ: 0.1; order: 0.1; word: 0.1; laic: 0.05; prelate: 0.05; chief: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 17; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 17; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 8; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 6; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 6; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 5; ('John', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Elders', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 4; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Clemens', 'PRODUCT'): 4; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('Sanedrim', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jerom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('S. Ambros', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Sol', 'PERSON'): 3; ('episcopat', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Nasi', 'ORG'): 2; ('Sagan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('twenty three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Evangelist', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 2; ('Deacon', 'ORG'): 2; ('Apostle', 'PERSON'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Philippi', 'GPE'): 2; ('S. John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Barnabas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Corinth', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('the seven asian church', 'ORG'): 2; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Gaius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 2; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Linus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Anacletus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 2; ('Marc', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Clerics', 'ORG'): 2; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Julius', 'ORG'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Thetis Iii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cain', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Moses', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zebadiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amariah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antiochus', 'NORP'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('the supreme Sanedrim', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abbethdin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('senate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Suffragan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('causeless', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Racha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 19', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ day', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('L. 14 Antiq', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Moses', 'NORP'): 1; ('Barabas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gallio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Distingue', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Josua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pour', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('only four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelical ministry', 'ORG'): 1; ('10 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('cho twelv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 21', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 1; ('Stephans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Episcopi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. John angel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Corinth', 'GPE'): 1; ('Galatia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Colossi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thessalonica', 'GPE'): 1; ('Indea', 'GPE'): 1; ('Titus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Timothy of Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S.', 'NORP'): 1; ('division multiply daily', 'ORG'): 1; ('Oeconomus', 'ORG'): 1; ('ordain', 'GPE'): 1; ('last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelv throne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('22 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('Andronicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epaphroditus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chrysostom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oecomenius', 'ORG'): 1; ('episcopat be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('weekly', 'DATE'): 1; ('every first day', 'DATE'): 1; ('twelv apostle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apostles', 'ORG'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cleopas', 'GPE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('James ▪ Act•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('gav diffinitiv sentence', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Simeon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•4', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ephesus to Miletum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('heed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thessal•nica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Macedonia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Achaia', 'GPE'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8. 6. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ep scopat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epirus and Illyricum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Macedon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tralleis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Thracia', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Paul trust Titus and Timothy', 'ORG'): 1; ('Titus 1', 'LAW'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrinus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Patmos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dorotheus , Demochares', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petrus de Natalibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Volateranus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Onesimus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Timothy at Ephesus : Apelles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Polycarpus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Smyrna', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sardis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Irenaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cletus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clemens Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Linus Paul Deacon', 'ORG'): 1; ('the apostle day', 'DATE'): 1; ('John die', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Areopagit S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Corinth', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heracla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dionysius', 'ORG'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Evag', 'ORG'): 1; ('year Corinth', 'DATE'): 1; ('Timothy at Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Denys', 'GPE'): 1; ('the first century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sardinia', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Synod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chalcedon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Phaesbytert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the Jew Sanedrim', 'FAC'): 1; ('Keis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rustica Ruricolae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fabri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Smiths', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eph.', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('gift', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.', 'DATE'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•ct•', 'GPE'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('presbyter ab', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('•n', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Paul 1 Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4 14', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('presbyteres•es', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 20. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jeronimo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Celestin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hilary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ambros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cartwright', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Knox', 'ORG'): 1; ('Milston', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jus Divinum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Keis', 'ORG'): 1; ('16 19', 'DATE'): 1; ('18 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('the black month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Acephalon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Marian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('almost a hundred 180', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aerius', 'ORG'): 1; ('1500 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bethleem Juda', 'FAC'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James Apostles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Onesimus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Apelles , Denys Areopagit', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('annually', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('noon', 'TIME'): 1"
A95924,18 | 4120,bishop brand breach charity contrary verity be martyr tyranny pope,church: 0.5; ordination: 0.5; christ: 0.5; minister: 0.5; power: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; people: 0.5; man: 0.5; right: 0.35; presbyter: 0.35; god: 0.3,"('Christians', 'NORP'): 9; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Keis', 'PERSON'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('episcopat antichristian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fucatio•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Papal Prelacy', 'ORG'): 1; ('1500 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('mar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'ORG'): 1; ('christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('episcopat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ignatius ◊ Ep', 'ORG'): 1; ('a• Ep•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ananias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saphira', 'PERSON'): 1; ('causaly', 'GPE'): 1; ('derivativ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Corah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Moses', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tyler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'NORP'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ʋzziah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sixteen century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Milan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ambros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vinyard', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Laity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clerus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clerus Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Barnabas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clerics', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Catabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Messiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'GPE'): 1; ('outward appearance', 'PERSON'): 1; ('verbū', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('28 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('John Evangelist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Baptists', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wolf come', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 40', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('the holy ministry', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('undu order', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ordain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Magus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bois', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gauden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('episcopat be institute', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('about 100 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Edward 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1547', 'DATE'): 1; ('scan', 'NORP'): 1; ('episcopat free', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Penry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Martin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ciconia', 'GPE'): 1; ('he|be', 'PERSON'): 1"
A95924,19,supply take adversary antagonist presbyterians accuser judge rail revile produce,church: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; god: 0.5; cartwright: 0.5; man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; elder: 0.5; priest: 0.35; beza: 0.3; name: 0.25; minister: 0.25; law: 0.1; prince: 0.1; apostle: 0.05; power: 0.05; matter: 0.05,"('Cartwright', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 19; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Genevan', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Cartwright', 'ORG'): 2; ('Cartwright', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sol', 'PERSON'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 2; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Chrysostom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Elders', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Marc', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 2; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ambros', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Clemens', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Anacletus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Cyril', 'ORG'): 2; ('Theodoret', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Episcopal', 'ORG'): 2; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 2; ('presbyterians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vicars', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Stats', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('15. 24', 'DATE'): 1; ('E•h', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Co••s 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('civil magistrate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('only two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Beza de Presb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('188', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Knox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('next lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('under 40.', 'DATE'): 1; ('the Jew Sanedrim', 'FAC'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('twenty four', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('heresy', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Officio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two or three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Portuis', 'GPE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Caus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Beza', 'ORG'): 1; ('Erastus', 'ORG'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Erastus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deacon', 'ORG'): 1; ('more than seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Viret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Justin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Prelat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('their day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sadeil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('S. Marc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anicetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Archdeacon Damasus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sixtus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Damasus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the catholic church and council', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cartwright', 'EVENT'): 1; ('Cyril', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nomine mutato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('narratur fabula de se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Thracia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pontus', 'ORG'): 1; ('thirteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicen Synod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Antioch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fifteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Newington', 'GPE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hitchin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Denys', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thebais', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mariota', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lybia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Miletus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cyprus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('eight hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Magisterialy', 'GPE'): 1; ('fox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the morning dawn', 'TIME'): 1; ('Nicen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Moses', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gallaesius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jethros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15. 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Beza', 'GPE'): 1; ('Danaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hilary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hyperbolicaly', 'GPE'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Thomas Mores Ʋtopia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Barow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greenwood', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('May', 'DATE'): 1; ('ordain', 'GPE'): 1; ('twelv apostle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Genevans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Quale', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cleri', 'NORP'): 1; ('antistes caput', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cleri', 'GPE'): 1; ('Presbyteratus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Corpus Episcopii : j•s', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Historia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Monarchae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Saera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Coetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('ʋsque ad apostolicos', 'PERSON'): 1; (""th'apostle"", 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Presbyteris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clero', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('erat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('schismatisi suncti', 'PERSON'): 1"
A95924,22,Messiae Prophetae Christum Messiah prophet Christ perform ali••r Messia retulere,christ: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; son: 0.5; adam: 0.5; david: 0.5; father: 0.5; abram: 0.5; seed: 0.35; sin: 0.2; sem: 0.15; covenant: 0.1; jew: 0.05; japhet: 0.05; noah: 0.05; bear: 0.05,"('David', 'PERSON'): 11; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('Abram', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Prophetae', 'ORG'): 2; ('Messiah', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Zerobabel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sem', 'ORG'): 2; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Obed', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jacobs', 'ORG'): 2; ('quae de Messiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae de Messia', 'ORG'): 1; ('quaeque', 'NORP'): 1; ('quae christus facta peregit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cuncta', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam bene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prophetica Christo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam bene complevit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('singula', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('christus item', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('duae Genealogiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('William Cowper', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Galloway', 'LOC'): 1; ('saint Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Josephs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('saint luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salathiel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rhesa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam Seth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Enos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mahalale•l', 'ORG'): 1; ('Methuselah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David ▪ son', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Messiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Notae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the virgin earth', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eve', 'PERSON'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abram', 'NORP'): 1; ('2 Sect', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Salah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peleg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Reu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Terah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('luke superad Cainan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 26', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Japhet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1600', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3 Sect', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Pharez', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezram', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aminadab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Naasson', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('japhet family', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thamar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canaanit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bathsheba', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sara', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rebecca', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nazianzen', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lion for institute', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('perogativ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rahab a Canaanit', 'ORG'): 1; ('ruth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1"
A95924,23,Zerobabel role father Sect. Matthew line Salomon Nathan whole brother,christ: 0.5; year: 0.5; david: 0.5; matthew: 0.5; line: 0.5; son: 0.5; generation: 0.4; king: 0.3; descent: 0.3; father: 0.25; man: 0.25; joseph: 0.2; adam: 0.15; god: 0.1; salathiel: 0.05,"('David', 'PERSON'): 22; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 11; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 6; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Salathiel', 'ORG'): 5; ('Zerobabel', 'GPE'): 4; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jeconiah', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Josephs', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Eli', 'ORG'): 3; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1656', 'DATE'): 3; ('Abram', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 3; ('Augustus', 'ORG'): 3; ('Jesse', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 2; ('Neri', 'ORG'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('luke', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Aminadab', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Eliakim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 2; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('70', 'DATE'): 2; ('77', 'DATE'): 2; ('Ozia', 'GPE'): 2; ('Josia', 'GPE'): 2; ('353', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('942', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4031', 'DATE'): 2; ('4030', 'DATE'): 2; ('Cherdic', 'NORP'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('520', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('120', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('942.', 'DATE'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Naasson', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ishai', 'GPE'): 2; ('4 Sect', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Nathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeconiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 17.', 'DATE'): 1; ('eighteenth', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matthew jeconiahs son', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Salomons', 'LOC'): 1; ('Rehoboam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('last fall', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pedaiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hananiah 1 Chr', 'ORG'): 1; ('3. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('number nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rhesa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Meshullam', 'NORP'): 1; ('Philo', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mary progenitor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zechary', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isai 7', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Job Goel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Shiloh', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Immanuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Goel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gaal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jess•s', 'GPE'): 1; ('saint luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Summary', 'ORG'): 1; ('77', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Seth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Methusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Salah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peleg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Terah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pharez', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Naasson', 'ORG'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('Salmon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nathan', 'ORG'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matatha', 'ORG'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mainan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jonan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'DATE'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('Simeon', 'ORG'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matthas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('jorim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eliezer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('48', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elmodam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('51', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cosam', 'ORG'): 1; ('52', 'DATE'): 1; ('53', 'DATE'): 1; ('54', 'DATE'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('56', 'DATE'): 1; ('Neri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('58', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rhesa', 'ORG'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joanna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('60', 'DATE'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('62', 'DATE'): 1; ('S•m•i', 'PERSON'): 1; ('63', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mattathia', 'ORG'): 1; ('64', 'DATE'): 1; ('65', 'DATE'): 1; ('Naggi', 'GPE'): 1; ('66', 'DATE'): 1; ('67', 'DATE'): 1; ('Naum', 'ORG'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('69', 'DATE'): 1; ('71', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joanna', 'GPE'): 1; ('72', 'DATE'): 1; ('73', 'DATE'): 1; ('74', 'DATE'): 1; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('76', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('salom•n', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jehosopha•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joram', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joatham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Achaz', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ezekiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Manasse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jehoichim', 'GPE'): 1; ('Azor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Achim', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eleazar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mattham', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joseph Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('J•coniah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salathiel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Azaria', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tesserad', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Shiloh', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cains', 'GPE'): 1; ('japhet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cham', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abrahams', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacobs', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chronology', 'ORG'): 1; ('Babylon 545', 'ORG'): 1; ('535', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the next 353', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('545. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('twenty three', 'DATE'): 1; ('535. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Diluvium A. m. 1656', 'PERSON'): 1; ('A. 1656', 'DATE'): 1; ('two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('pristin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ferdinand', 'GPE'): 1; ('146', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about 246', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('100', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antediluvian', 'NORP'): 1; ('almost twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('A. 494', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1066', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('571', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('582. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('all 61', 'DATE'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('117', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharamont', 'PERSON'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1134', 'DATE'): 1; ('Leo Isaurius', 'ORG'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Matthews', 'NORP'): 1; ('Salmah', 'ORG'): 1; ('1. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('437.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Salmath', 'NORP'): 1; ('Obed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('437. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('David', 'GPE'): 1; ('sixteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('casualy', 'GPE'): 1; ('hunc scrupulum solvas', 'ORG'): 1; ('eris mihi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phoebus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Candidus imperti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('scis verius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Panditur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Genethliac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucas', 'ORG'): 1; ('explicu•re', 'ORG'): 1; ('genealogiam christi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('d• stirpe Davidis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lo Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('stirpe Davidis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Secus', 'GPE'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Davide', 'GPE'): 1; ('Davidis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangelii Biblia', 'PERSON'): 1"
A95924,24,Thetis Apocalypsus revelation revel Apocalypse speculation preamble vision revel Christ,god: 0.5; rev: 0.5; church: 0.5; ibid: 0.5; angel: 0.5; call: 0.5; christ: 0.5; throne: 0.5; child: 0.35; son: 0.25; man: 0.1; whit: 0.1; part: 0.1; star: 0.05; lamb: 0.05,"('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 18; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('twenty four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ibid', 'ORG'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 2; ('Apocalypse', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Evangelist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Patmos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Domitian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vespasian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cambridg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1638', 'DATE'): 1; ('age 53', 'DATE'): 1; ('Clavis Appellativorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Smyrna', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pergamus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thyatira', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sardis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philadelphia ▪ Laodicea', 'ORG'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('name', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lapillis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Reubens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one hundred forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('twelv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelv time one thousand', 'ORG'): 1; ('14. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10 , 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Augustulus Rome', 'ORG'): 1; ('five 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 v. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arabia', 'GPE'): 1; ('hebrew Abaddon', 'FAC'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tures', 'ORG'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('1260', 'DATE'): 1; ('4 5. 1260', 'DATE'): 1; ('annal day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eliseus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zerobabel with Jesua', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sodom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelv star', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('god throne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('realy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('September 29. day', 'DATE'): 1"
A95924,28 | 4332,voice heaven water thunder v. voice Harpers harp song throne,angel: 0.5; beast: 0.5; god: 0.5; harvest: 0.5; saint: 0.5; lamb: 0.45; time: 0.45; christ: 0.4; city: 0.25; phial: 0.25; babylon: 0.2; king: 0.15; whore: 0.1; heaven: 0.1; earth: 0.05; judgement: 0.05; lord: 0.05,"('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Phial', 'ORG'): 4; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('one thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one hundred forty', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('earth', 'LOC'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Nicen', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 2; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19 11', 'DATE'): 2; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('one thousand six hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Armageddon', 'GPE'): 2; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('angel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Harpers', 'ORG'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('1. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Titus 1', 'LAW'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vigilantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('720', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Leo Isauricus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constantinus Iconomachus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leo Armenius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Michael Balbus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Francfort', 'GPE'): 1; ('almost three hundred A.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('825', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lewis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21 9', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Waldenses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('phil•ry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('no rest day', 'DATE'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Stats', 'GPE'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romish Catholics', 'NORP'): 1; ('myrrh', 'ORG'): 1; ('Frankincens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('abondon the beast communion', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vers', 'LOC'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('R.', 'NORP'): 1; ('11. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('haveng', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('51.', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tiglatpeleser', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jeremies', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('saviour parabol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euphrates', 'LOC'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('the east king', 'LOC'): 1; ('Ishmael', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('joel Joel 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nnd', 'NORP'): 1; ('19 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Palestin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight to a mile', 'TIME'): 1; ('dans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Palestine', 'GPE'): 1; ('viz saint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Po', 'LOC'): 1; ('Verona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about two hundred mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('one thousand six hundred', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last eight chapter', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pagan emperor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Johns', 'GPE'): 1; ('hundred year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('caesarcan', 'NORP'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('4 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Juvenal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Messalina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lycisca', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nuda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salomons', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Euphrates', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A95924,30,Catholicis warn Catholics caution conclusion Roman Catholics observation bliss bale,beast: 0.5; god: 0.5; image: 0.5; man: 0.5; saint: 0.45; devil: 0.4; idolatry: 0.35; roman: 0.35; horn: 0.3; babylon: 0.25; demons: 0.2; head: 0.2; soul: 0.15; angel: 0.15; name: 0.1; spirit: 0.05; rev: 0.05,"('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Roman Catholics', 'NORP'): 2; ('Roman catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('666', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Catholics', 'NORP'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Armageddon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leo 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('one hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Frankincens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14 9 10 , 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('no rest day', 'DATE'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Ʋtopia', 'GPE'): 1; ('18. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Supplement', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bell', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nimrod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caesar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julius', 'ORG'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lagus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Mars', 'LOC'): 1; ('nam deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hereof saint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('2 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apocalypse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nimrod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Belus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deastri', 'ORG'): 1; ('lie hypocrisy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Demon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sol', 'PERSON'): 1"
A95924,31 | 4432,add argument saint Austin proof gentile report saint Peter prophesy,year: 0.5; rev: 0.5; time: 0.5; god: 0.5; son: 0.5; thing: 0.5; end: 0.5; christ: 0.45; man: 0.35; book: 0.2; mystery: 0.2; church: 0.15; prophecy: 0.05; seal: 0.05; world: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('395', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Apocalypse', 'ORG'): 5; ('A. 1655', 'DATE'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 4; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 4; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1290', 'DATE'): 3; ('1260', 'DATE'): 3; ('1655', 'DATE'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('John', 'PERSON'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('quae', 'GPE'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19 v. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'DATE'): 2; ('year', 'DATE'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sol', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'DATE'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('mysteria magna', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Joanni', 'GPE'): 2; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('365.', 'DATE'): 1; ('30. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('minist•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('365', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6000.', 'DATE'): 1; ('the six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('every day 1000 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('next year 1655', 'DATE'): 1; ('6000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('year fall', 'DATE'): 1; ('about 315', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('A. C. 1655', 'PERSON'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aueis', 'ORG'): 1; ('last year 1653', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ibrihim', 'ORG'): 1; ('1617', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mustapha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Osman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1622', 'DATE'): 1; ('Morat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amurat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('A. 1640', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ibrihim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('age six', 'DATE'): 1; ('Julian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('no other than', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('A. 395', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('455', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('no year', 'DATE'): 1; ('12 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('10 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('proph•ts', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. 14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anthichrist', 'NORP'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seventy year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Relativs', 'NORP'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Relata', 'ORG'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('10. 2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Johns revelation', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('what year', 'DATE'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('ergo it|be presumption', 'ORG'): 1; ('19 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('7 14', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ibid', 'ORG'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34 35', 'DATE'): 1; ('the Dan 7', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('throne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 and 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('finito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Silesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('the three year and', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 16. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('16. 18. 21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one year', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•iv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('placuere semel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Medus vir celebris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nulli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('artibus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judicio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John declare', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mira brevi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Germanus', 'LOC'): 1; ('venturis', 'NORP'): 1; ('adhibenda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mira', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vix credenda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('next year', 'DATE'): 1"
A95924,32 | 4470,Sol. shadow semblance word text babylons captivity saint longing Zion,day: 0.5; judgement: 0.5; christ: 0.5; saint: 0.5; year: 0.5; kingdom: 0.5; earth: 0.5; heaven: 0.45; man: 0.35; lord: 0.3; god: 0.25; jerusalem: 0.15,"('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 15; ('Sol', 'PERSON'): 9; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 8; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 7; ('that day', 'DATE'): 6; ('Millenar', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 6; ('the day', 'DATE'): 5; ('David', 'PERSON'): 5; ('John', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('this day', 'DATE'): 4; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one thousand year', 'DATE'): 3; ('the judgement day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('one day', 'DATE'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Daniels', 'ORG'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('last day', 'DATE'): 2; ('those thousand year', 'DATE'): 2; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Zion', 'ORG'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('twenty four hour', 'TIME'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('22', 'DATE'): 2; ('the thousand year', 'DATE'): 2; ('six thousand year', 'DATE'): 2; ('seven thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('archer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('those one thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('•2', 'GPE'): 1; ('Burroughs', 'ORG'): 1; ('late day', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('Haggai 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('••b', 'ORG'): 1; ('2 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sinai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'LOC'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isai 2', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bibles', 'GPE'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Millenar', 'GPE'): 1; ('saint John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isai 63', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bozra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('12. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Babylonish', 'NORP'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('just one thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Methusalah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('so many million of million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Crabrones', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Burton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austin L. 20', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vives', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('A. 1650', 'DATE'): 1; ('1655', 'DATE'): 1; ('1695', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Graecas Calendas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('M•••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the next age', 'DATE'): 1; ('yea Irenaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apocalypse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Justin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trypho', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isai 65. 17.', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelv apostle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rabins', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Messiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('R. Ketina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isai 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('90. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('yesterday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the school of R. Elias', 'ORG'): 1; ('six thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judaism', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gehenna', 'GPE'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('92', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the great day', 'DATE'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Peter 2 Pet', 'LAW'): 1; ('3 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the very judgement day', 'DATE'): 1; ('wherein dwell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('65.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('66.', 'DATE'): 1; ('24 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('new kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('14 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('Johns', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('7. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 10 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('20.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Daniel imagine confusa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'GPE'): 1; ('Stats', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the Dan 7.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Synedrion', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jud•cii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('•6', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sanhedrim', 'ORG'): 1; ('five 6 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('thousand thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1"
