tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A51250,1,address living government people commonwealth England call royalist presbyterians independent,power: 0.5; god: 0.4; man: 0.4; governor: 0.4; christ: 0.4; king: 0.4; son: 0.4; government: 0.4; commonwealth: 0.25; subject: 0.2; lord: 0.1; pr: 0.1; pretence: 0.1; presbyterians: 0.1; prejudice: 0.1; prayer: 0.1; priesthood: 0.1; pet: 0.1; place: 0.1; prince: 0.1; peace: 0.1; apostle: 0.1; ordinance: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('presbyterians', 'NORP'): 1; ('fifth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('James Cottrel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1656', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gov•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wittlesey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('April 7. 1656', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.12,18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('14.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.19,20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.14,15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('75.3 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.15,16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('5.19,20,22,23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('66.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('103.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.25,35,37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.15,17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14,15,17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Melchizedec', 'ORG'): 1; ('7.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.25 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.1 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A55306,11,excellency privilege consideration adoption thing glory freegrace lustre believer glory,god: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; son: 0.5; adoption: 0.5; glory: 0.5; christ: 0.5; heart: 0.5; adopt: 0.45; thing: 0.4; heaven: 0.25; lord: 0.2; prayer: 0.1; man: 0.05; heir: 0.05,"('Psal', 'PERSON'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 4; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4.6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 2; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('1 Joh', 'DATE'): 1; ('Durandus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Medina', 'GPE'): 1; ('translationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Par', 'ORG'): 1; ('Achmet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('Caeli', 'GPE'): 1; ('12.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abba', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ʋrim', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('40.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cicero', 'LOC'): 1; ('Gal.', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Sinai', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ezek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('8.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Shechinah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kol', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('33.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Linons', 'ORG'): 1; ('34.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Musculus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('sixthly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Barak', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('89.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('89.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quirinus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A55306,16,believ bath sin pardon sin pardon word experience conclusion Fide.,conscience: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; grace: 0.5; god: 0.5; faith: 0.5; believer: 0.5; love: 0.5; assurance: 0.5; word: 0.3; self: 0.2; thing: 0.15; pardon: 0.15; heaven: 0.05; saint: 0.05; testimony: 0.05; man: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 11; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('thou', 'GPE'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 2; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8.16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('believ', 'GPE'): 1; ('two proposition', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.3', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eustathians', 'NORP'): 1; ('13.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 9.2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 7.18', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 5.13', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Hebrews', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Esther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Galat', 'GPE'): 1; ('6.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Corinth', 'DATE'): 1; ('13.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de Justif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('praecepta essent impossibilia', 'ORG'): 1; ('neminem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('27.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Agatha', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caspar Olevian', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bolton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hieron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Menander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sextius', 'ORG'): 1; ('every night', 'TIME'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('religionis', 'NORP'): 1; ('26.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('quidam modus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('conscientia', 'GPE'): 1; ('noveris fidem', 'NORP'): 1; ('St', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abimelech', 'ORG'): 1; ('20.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 4.51', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Salvo', 'ORG'): 1"
A56405,2 | 550,reverend clergy say paragraph sin saint honour dr. Drayton reverend,position: 0.5; sin: 0.45; saint: 0.45; christ: 0.45; word: 0.45; faith: 0.45; preface: 0.4; paragraph: 0.35; god: 0.3; life: 0.25; fight: 0.2; paul: 0.15; reference: 0.15; practice: 0.05; principle: 0.05; prevailer: 0.05; present: 0.05; promise: 0.05; prayer: 0.05; phrase: 0.05; prophet: 0.05; veterator: 0.05,"('Paul', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Levites', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 4; ('Drayton', 'GPE'): 3; ('Levite', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thi•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wiltshire', 'GPE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Coloss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('Belial', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 3.8 .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'LOC'): 1; ('John Tendring', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A56405,5 | 745,cause justification consider application righteousness Christ sense soul application act,sin: 0.5; god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; man: 0.5; faith: 0.45; lord: 0.45; thing: 0.45; vindicator: 0.35; grace: 0.3; doctrine: 0.3; saint: 0.3; position: 0.15; end: 0.15; justification: 0.05; word: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Agrippa', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('that day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Topick', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11.14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('22', 'DATE'): 2; ('1.21', 'DATE'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter Lombard lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Senten', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.29', 'DATE'): 1; ('nefanda', 'ORG'): 1; ('malo permista', 'PERSON'): 1; ('justificam nobis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zachary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.74', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('75', 'DATE'): 1; ('grace justifi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lachesi', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James 4.5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.14', 'MONEY'): 1; ('2.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('115.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gusmond', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the finis rei', 'ORG'): 1; ('Levites', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Jus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('no morning light', 'TIME'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('55.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('depart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeremiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tarry thou', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.20 , 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Coloss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('61.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('36.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amos 9.8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Canaanite', 'GPE'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zephan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zacha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 4.2', 'LAW'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.70', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('71', 'DATE'): 1; ('74', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('deliverer', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacob', 'ORG'): 1"
A56405,6,Abraham Heb. faith Abraham call place inheritance obey faith land,god: 0.5; law: 0.5; man: 0.5; righteousness: 0.5; lord: 0.5; christ: 0.45; grace: 0.45; thing: 0.45; justify: 0.4; sin: 0.3; faith: 0.2; justification: 0.1; sanctify: 0.1; spirit: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 5; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 5; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 4; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 3; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('6.11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Caleb', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 2; ('Joshuah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6', 'DATE'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 2; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Topick', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('August', 'DATE'): 2; ('4.3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26.18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isaac', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('25.27', 'MONEY'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioshuah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isaao', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jephunneh', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('106.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phineas', 'NORP'): 1; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 2.3', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 42.7', 'LAW'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Job', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deborah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Naomi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hannah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rebeccah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zacharie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephen', 'GPE'): 1; ('6.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Barnabas', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gideon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Barack', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jephtah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('herein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('first many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 14.4', 'LAW'): 1; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Brightman', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arrias Montanus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('i John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ierusasalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('37.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('128.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Justine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Resp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orthodoxos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zacharie', 'GPE'): 1; ('chapter 1.6', 'LAW'): 1; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Magnus', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 1; ('119.155', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hieron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Nat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Grat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('idem de tempor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('56', 'DATE'): 1; ('89', 'DATE'): 1; ('idem de verbis', 'ORG'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('idem lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Julian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Prosp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Senten', 'PERSON'): 1; ('idem ibidem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alippius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Possidius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('de Jesun', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the first Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Epiphanie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Andrews', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Overal', 'ORG'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('21.11', 'DATE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 5.23', 'LAW'): 1; ('Isaiah 45.24', 'ORG'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('sixthly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('22.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.4 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 3.3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1"
A56405,6 | 990,consideration voice unbeliever saint say beast sin sea head horn,say: 0.5; axiom: 0.5; scripture: 0.5; day: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; sense: 0.5; lord: 0.5; sin: 0.45; word: 0.25; doctrine: 0.2; christian: 0.1,"('christian', 'NORP'): 11; ('Querie', 'PERSON'): 11; ('thou', 'GPE'): 7; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 6; ('John', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 3; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 2; ('1.10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the lord day the first day of the week', 'DATE'): 2; ('the say day', 'DATE'): 2; ('the first day of the week', 'DATE'): 2; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 2; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6.36', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('more than ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arrias Montanus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canaanite', 'GPE'): 1; ('15.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.6 .', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sergius Paulus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('John Knox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('a hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'NORP'): 1; ('John tender', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('age in year', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 7.45', 'PERSON'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('48', 'DATE'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('Wilts', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James 1.14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Salisbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Festus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anabaptist', 'NORP'): 1; ('20.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('some year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lincoln', 'ORG'): 1; ('18.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Papa Romanus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romanus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('58.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James 1.13', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a week', 'DATE'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('16.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('22.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nihil point', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 Sam 12.25', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tenderden', 'GPE'): 1; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tenderden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1"
A56405,6 | 1102,translator translation word Paul righteousness law contradistinction another righteousness attain,god: 0.5; righteousness: 0.5; man: 0.5; life: 0.5; christ: 0.5; say: 0.5; sin: 0.5; law: 0.5; adam: 0.45; distemper: 0.25; thing: 0.15; lord: 0.05; reason: 0.05; querie: 0.05,"('Adam', 'PERSON'): 16; ('Querie', 'PERSON'): 9; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Cox', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('James', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3.18', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Drayton', 'GPE'): 2; ('ten pound', 'QUANTITY'): 2; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Vorstius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4', 'DATE'): 2; ('7', 'DATE'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.11 , 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezek', 'ORG'): 1; ('16.51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sodon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gomorrah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five 49', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sodom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('64.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Coloss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.19 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ditton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('New-Sarum', 'ORG'): 1; ('march 16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('1657', 'DATE'): 1; ('Windam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wilts', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('their own quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Wilts county', 'GPE'): 1; ('Wiltshire', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zacheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pilate', 'ORG'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Synodalia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Andrews', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirty year of age', 'DATE'): 1; ('Enoch', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('James 1.13', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('19.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('57.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'NORP'): 1; ('1.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('58.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('James 1.27', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('America', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James 2.16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ja', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.14 15 , 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A56405,7,paraphrase salutation preface lover sense God truth paraphrase preface self,say: 0.5; church: 0.5; book: 0.45; part: 0.45; reader: 0.45; self: 0.4; place: 0.4; scripture: 0.4; sense: 0.35; vindication: 0.35; right: 0.2; master: 0.15; person: 0.1; sin: 0.1; possibility: 0.1; life: 0.1,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Mitcham', 'GPE'): 4; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('146', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('200', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('l. ult .', 'PERSON'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('Winton', 'ORG'): 2; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Topick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('English', 'NORP'): 1; ('John 3.5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stevens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('64.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Wilts', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('6.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 18.23', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Crupsis', 'ORG'): 1; ('PAraph', 'ORG'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Wilton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 2.22', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sidkenu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('100 l. 37', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('117', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('127', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('136', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 2', 'DATE'): 1; ('139', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('144', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('188', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('210', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('prudentia', 'ORG'): 1; ('constantia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('217', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('228', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a. p. 229', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('230', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('233', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. 10', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('241', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bruti', 'GPE'): 1; ('243', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('245', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('254', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('256', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('14.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Surry', 'GPE'): 1; ('Robert Cranmer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anthony Sadler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1664', 'DATE'): 1; ('Surry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sadler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cranmer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Harris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward Bristock', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the 24th day of', 'DATE'): 1; ('November', 'DATE'): 1"
A52810,1,discourse discovery person period Antichrist enquiry make time ruin answer,god: 0.5; church: 0.5; christ: 0.5; prophecy: 0.5; lord: 0.5; day: 0.5; world: 0.5; bless: 0.45; seal: 0.4; time: 0.2; antichrist: 0.15; christian: 0.1; book: 0.05; nobility: 0.05; divine: 0.05; author: 0.05,"('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Christopher Ness', 'PERSON'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('the latter day', 'DATE'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Fleetstreet', 'GPE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('1679', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anthony earl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Shaftsbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('Etymologist', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aliis', 'ORG'): 1; ('tuum verò', 'PERSON'): 1; ('British', 'NORP'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Palladium', 'GPE'): 1; ('the Atlas of England', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Beelzebub', 'ORG'): 1; ('Neh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epphrata', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bethlehem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nulla infoelicitas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Corrumpit', 'FAC'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Esth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the former day', 'DATE'): 1; ('2d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.4,7', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.25.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hebr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jewel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a few hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('month', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aug. 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('79', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A52810,7,CHAP. Antichrist be controversy smoke bottomless-pit darken truth God world,antichrist: 0.5; christ: 0.5; tribe: 0.5; turk: 0.5; god: 0.5; time: 0.5; jerusalem: 0.5; city: 0.5; temple: 0.5; beast: 0.3; jew: 0.15; john: 0.05,"('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 33; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 16; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 13; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 9; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('John', 'PERSON'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 4; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 4; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('dan', 'PERSON'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 3; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Grotius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Simon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('49.18', 'MONEY'): 2; ('Judg', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Judaism', 'ORG'): 2; ('7.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Simeon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 2; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 2; ('Johns', 'GPE'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Mahomet', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('john-baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('our day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theudas', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon-Magus', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mille sequuntur', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.1,3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peter ministry', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Remandus de antichristo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three year and half', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pererius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Babylon', 'ORG'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 kin', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('12.28.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three year and a half', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dan be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tostatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49.17', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Jacobs', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simeon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Donne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about 94 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Titus Vespasians', 'LOC'): 1; ('Domitian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Titus', 'LAW'): 1; ('Pathmos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.9 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Propertius', 'ORG'): 1; ('toti quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('praesidet orbi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cyrus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Titus Vespasian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Galatinus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arcan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'TIME'): 1; ('21.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('6.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.10,12,13', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hebr', 'ORG'): 1; ('13.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pontius Pilate', 'ORG'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('2.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daemonum Stabulo', 'FAC'): 1; ('Sin', 'ORG'): 1; ('6th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rosse', 'ORG'): 1; ('165', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sibs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evang', 'GPE'): 1; ('2d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('247', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Century', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('perfidiâ', 'GPE'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Koran', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Relig', 'GPE'): 1; ('175', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Laity', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('177', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('179', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Musulmanni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Turks', 'NORP'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mensalia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Orientalis Antichristus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39 yea', 'TIME'): 1; ('Holmes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sergius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('666', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Cotton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A52810,10,Anselm Tim. wise spirit God time Antichrist faith apostle Thess.,pope: 0.5; christ: 0.5; church: 0.5; doctrine: 0.5; god: 0.5; devil: 0.5; sword: 0.5; time: 0.35; temple: 0.25; jesus: 0.25; saint: 0.25; satan: 0.2; foundation: 0.1; apostle: 0.05; antichrist: 0.05,"('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 5; ('2 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2d', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3d', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Benno Uspergensis', 'ORG'): 2; ('platina', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Boniface', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anselm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Espancaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('70', 'DATE'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('there|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1; ('71', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the apostle day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.18 .', 'DATE'): 1; ('72', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ Col', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.18,19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Laity', 'GPE'): 1; ('74', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('76', 'DATE'): 1; ('13.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.2 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55.12,13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2ly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('3ly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('79', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Presbyteri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('geriti qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('80', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vatican', 'FAC'): 1; ('Matthew Parisiensis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('81', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sixtus', 'ORG'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matthew Paris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Guil', 'LOC'): 1; ('1072', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satanas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Damianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nicolaus Gallicus Narbonensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arnolphus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Catologo Testium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petrarch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mantuan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wickliff', 'GPE'): 1; ('Husse', 'EVENT'): 1; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prague', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alsted , Pareus', 'ORG'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('90. 85', 'DATE'): 1; ('22.38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 10.8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('87', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Templum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 2.23', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mark 1.9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('88', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johns', 'GPE'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('urbe', 'GPE'): 1"
A52810,11,CHAP. v. clause God call God part induction Papa pope,pope: 0.5; devil: 0.5; god: 0.5; wonder: 0.5; man: 0.5; antichrist: 0.5; miracle: 0.45; church: 0.45; emperor: 0.4; time: 0.25; image: 0.2; beast: 0.2; power: 0.05,"('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 19; ('2d', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('6th', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 6; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('3d', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Ann', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Benedict', 'PERSON'): 3; ('9th', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Hildebrand', 'LOC'): 3; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 3; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('John', 'PERSON'): 3; ('5th', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Boniface', 'GPE'): 3; ('Sylvester', 'PERSON'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Papa', 'ORG'): 2; ('8th', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lateran', 'GPE'): 2; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 2; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('100', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 2; ('Nicholas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('120', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('115', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('117', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Cardin', 'NORP'): 2; ('Tom 10', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Benno', 'PERSON'): 2; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10th', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('god', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Boniface', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 2; ('89', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('90', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('396', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Remondus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prelacy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('platina write', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Steven', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephani', 'NORP'): 1; ('Frederick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Peter king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hungary', 'GPE'): 1; ('Petra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Henry', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Frederick Barbarossa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('91.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nich', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vignier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 1; ('94', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('10.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Parag', 'GPE'): 1; ('143', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antichristum', 'ORG'): 1; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('alter deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leo the 10th', 'ORG'): 1; ('supreme head', 'ORG'): 1; ('Episcopus Episcoporum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jacobus de voragine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bellarm', 'GPE'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Miranda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Miracula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('99', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('101', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('7.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('102', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('103', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dunstan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Patrick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gooderick', 'GPE'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wednesday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Friday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Morton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bene de i Scripsisti Thoma', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('105', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 1; ('Delphos', 'GPE'): 1; ('107', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Henry Stephanus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herodotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Polidore Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Westchester', 'ORG'): 1; ('108', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Origen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Celsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan kingdom', 'PERCENT'): 1; ('109', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('110', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Stella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('111', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Austin de civit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dei lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesuit Acosta', 'ORG'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('114', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('260', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('261', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 Cent', 'MONEY'): 1; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('236', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('332', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('333', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pareus medulla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod etiam ab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sumitur', 'GPE'): 1; ('etiam ab inimicis veritatis', 'ORG'): 1; ('probetur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vives de', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amici', 'NORP'): 1; ('Inimici', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gregorius Magnus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('614', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('118', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Stephanus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Stephen', 'GPE'): 1; ('897', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tiber', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baronius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erroris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui ista', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sulla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Catilinas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sylla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('985', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('diabolica dominandi', 'ORG'): 1; ('largitione', 'ORG'): 1; ('quidem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rhemensem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('adjuvante diabolo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Benno de vita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gest', 'GPE'): 1; ('Stella de vit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caranza', 'ORG'): 1; ('Summ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneas Silvius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sylvester Diabolicâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('121', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('William', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Malmesbury', 'ORG'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ursus', 'ORG'): 1; ('1304', 'DATE'): 1; ('122', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Boniface', 'ORG'): 1; ('the 8th', 'DATE'): 1; ('Celestine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Damasus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Brazutus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('124', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregor', 'GPE'): 1; ('Florentinus Vigern', 'PERSON'): 1; ('641', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Guil', 'LOC'): 1; ('1086', 'DATE'): 1; ('125', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Venus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luitprandus Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heylin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Geography of Italy', 'ORG'): 1; ('181', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('182', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('126', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the 9th Paragraph', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jerem', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('127', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('maris stella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Biel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Missae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('80', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('128', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paragraph 89', 'FAC'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('Piedmont', 'GPE'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sclater', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thessalon', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('130', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romish Babel', 'ORG'): 1; ('John ver .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('131', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1260 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Foemin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('some hundred of year', 'DATE'): 1; ('132', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nascens', 'GPE'): 1; ('3th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Decrescens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Expirans', 'NORP'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('133', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Crakanthorpe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vigilius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Antichrist be Nascent', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('our day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luther , Calvin , Perkins', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('134', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the follow century', 'DATE'): 1; ('135', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ecclesiastical', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sylvester', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bishop', 'ORG'): 1; ('Y. 404', 'DATE'): 1; ('Leo the first', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('2d', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phocas', 'GPE'): 1; ('the 6th century', 'DATE'): 1; ('136', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hildebrand', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ephah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luthers', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('137', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Wickliff', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.6,8,9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Waldenses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Illyric', 'PERSON'): 1"
A52810,12,CHAP. paragraph induction objection Romanists way remove Amasas body people,antichrist: 0.5; christ: 0.5; come: 0.5; world: 0.5; time: 0.5; peter: 0.45; objection: 0.4; apostle: 0.35; empire: 0.3; elias: 0.3; ly: 0.3; thing: 0.1; man: 0.1; person: 0.1; thess: 0.05; rom: 0.05,"('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 27; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 8; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2ly', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Enoch', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 2; ('3ly', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('4ly', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2d', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('2 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 2; ('6th', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('24.14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.6,7', 'DATE'): 2; ('138', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amasas', 'GPE'): 1; ('20.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('139', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('luke 4.4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.15.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1000 year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('140', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. year and half', 'DATE'): 1; ('141', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Terraefilius', 'ORG'): 1; ('13.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('grecian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('142', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.7.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('143', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romae Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romae', 'LOC'): 1; ('Parag', 'GPE'): 1; ('94', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('144', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.15,20', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Damasus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Telesphorus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day of Silvester', 'DATE'): 1; ('145', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('17.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('146', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('147', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('148', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('149', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Illyricum', 'GPE'): 1; ('15.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('frustrà', 'GPE'): 1; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('15.24,28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Stapleton', 'FAC'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('1.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.15,20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.6,23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('151', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Enoch', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('11.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('152', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'FAC'): 1; ('1.2,40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('153', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('11.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('154', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('155', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Augustulus', 'GPE'): 1"
A52810,14,ram horn instrument wall congruity mean wall Babylon breath Christ,god: 0.5; antichrist: 0.5; king: 0.5; babylon: 0.5; kingdom: 0.5; rev: 0.5; man: 0.45; beast: 0.45; angel: 0.35; power: 0.2; knowledge: 0.15; pope: 0.15; christ: 0.15; lord: 0.05; thing: 0.05,"('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 37; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 17; ('France', 'GPE'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Babylon', 'ORG'): 4; ('Waldus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 4; ('Jericho', 'GPE'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 3; ('angel', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 3; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Waldenses', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2d', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Pareus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11.4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14.14', 'DATE'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('18.9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('french', 'NORP'): 2; ('twenty thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 2; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 2; ('Denmark', 'GPE'): 2; ('Swedeland', 'ORG'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 2; ('4.6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Judg', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Dagon', 'GPE'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 2; ('Esa', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 2; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 2; ('170', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.27,28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('171', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2ly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('those two last century of year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mordecai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Haman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Esther 6.13', 'PERSON'): 1; ('172', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.6,8,9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('173', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Picardy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bohemia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Savoy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lombardy', 'GPE'): 1; ('about 1100', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('6.16 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('174', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Romanum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Episcopis parem', 'LOC'): 1; ('loco predicto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('175', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ecclesia Romana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylonica', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wickliff', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year of Christ 1371', 'DATE'): 1; ('this 2d', 'DATE'): 1; ('the ministry of Waldus', 'ORG'): 1; ('14.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('176', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Martin Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.9.10.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('177', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Papa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('178', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('last century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('179', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('evangelicos', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Melancton', 'ORG'): 1; ('Oecolampadius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zuinglius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bullinger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aretius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gualther , Musculus ,', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lauater', 'GPE'): 1; ('Polyander', 'ORG'): 1; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chemnitius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Marlorat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Reinolds', 'ORG'): 1; ('Whittaker', 'ORG'): 1; ('damnum antichristo vel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('180', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Illyricus in Catologo Testium', 'ORG'): 1; ('the antichristian idolatry', 'ORG'): 1; ('42.', 'DATE'): 1; ('181', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('their day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hebr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('182', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('183', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('12.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('184', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.16,17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('185', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sibbs', 'GPE'): 1; ('Evangel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Childerick', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Pepin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('186', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('187', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('188', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('189', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Benjamin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alps', 'LOC'): 1; ('190', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('191', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Armageddon', 'GPE'): 1; ('19.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.36,37,38,39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('192', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42 month', 'DATE'): 1; ('13.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('193', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luther', 'GPE'): 1; ('Saxony', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hassia', 'GPE'): 1; ('194', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gustavus Adolphus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('195', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hugonots', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('about 2150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60 year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('196', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('197', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('198', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('199', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lewis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('201', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('contraris curantur contrariis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 . 1•.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('202', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('14.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('61.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('203', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('204', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Sam 6.14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antichri•', 'ORG'): 1; ('205', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jud', 'PERSON'): 1; ('206', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('207', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last age of the', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('208', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('209', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniels', 'ORG'): 1; ('210', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Moguntiae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mentz', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Strasburg', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Gottenburgh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Mentelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('211', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('incredibilem', 'GPE'): 1; ('usum generi humano ha•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Typographica', 'GPE'): 1; ('Medul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('311', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('212', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sympson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the 14th', 'DATE'): 1; ('the 15th', 'DATE'): 1; ('213', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this 11th', 'DATE'): 1; ('2 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('214', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('goliath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10 17.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('more than one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('215', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Boannerges', 'GPE'): 1; ('Marc 3.17', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nazianzen', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tonitru', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vitaque fulgur erat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Urim', 'ORG'): 1; ('216', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phaeton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('217', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('6. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the seven .', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('218', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.5 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('219', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hazael', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jehu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.17 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('220', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.7.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('221', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('58.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lebanon', 'GPE'): 1; ('222', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('223', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('knox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('224', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4ly', 'DATE'): 1; ('Staggers', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Parag', 'GPE'): 1; ('52.55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('89', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('225', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some year', 'DATE'): 1"
A52810,20,CHAP. Xiv intimation point Antichrist wit sackcloth prophecy witness dominion,witness: 0.5; beast: 0.5; antichrist: 0.5; slaughter: 0.5; rev: 0.5; time: 0.45; slay: 0.45; church: 0.4; vial: 0.35; god: 0.2; year: 0.2; death: 0.15; ground: 0.1; christ: 0.1; prophet: 0.05; power: 0.05,"('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 24; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 24; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 21; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('3d', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('2d', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 6; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 6; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('trumpet', 'PERSON'): 3; ('12.7', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2ly', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 3; ('11.7', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('3.4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2 .', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 2; ('Elijah', 'GPE'): 2; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Zerubbabel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 2; ('4ly', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('5th', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('42.', 'DATE'): 2; ('11.13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6th', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Salvo', 'ORG'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('10th', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 2; ('that year', 'DATE'): 2; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Eli', 'ORG'): 2; ('Xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('393', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antichristianism', 'NORP'): 1; ('394', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Interpretum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('scripturas semel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zeph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('395', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('396', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Epocha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mortis morti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi morte', 'ORG'): 1; ('397', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('prophet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('398', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levite', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('399', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('only 7000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('400', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amos 8.9,10 . 2 kin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('401', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 11.15', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 16.8', 'LAW'): 1; ('402', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('403', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Oil', 'LOC'): 1; ('404', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johns', 'GPE'): 1; ('13.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('405', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('his hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('John 8.20', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('22.53', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('406', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('407', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('brightman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1547', 'DATE'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bohemia anno Dom', 'ORG'): 1; ('1618', 'DATE'): 1; ('1621', 'DATE'): 1; ('Piedmont', 'GPE'): 1; ('about 1655', 'DATE'): 1; ('408', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Twiss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many year ago', 'DATE'): 1; (""duke d' Alva"", 'ORG'): 1; ('Coligni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('some hundred-thousands', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('irish', 'NORP'): 1; ('the antichristian brood', 'ORG'): 1; ('409', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amos 6.3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('410', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('411', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the same hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Joshuah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('412', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. year and', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('100 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('413', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('120', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('praemiss', 'NORP'): 1; ('414', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•', 'ORG'): 1; ('415', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about 3. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('1260', 'DATE'): 1; ('416', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('417', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quod hacten•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Impleri', 'NORP'): 1; ('jam plenari•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. year and half', 'DATE'): 1; ('418', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('419', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antiochus', 'NORP'): 1; ('11.45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('420', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every century', 'DATE'): 1; ('421', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1666', 'DATE'): 1; ('3 year and', 'DATE'): 1; ('dutch', 'NORP'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('422', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year 66', 'DATE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('423.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Brightman', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cromwell', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cranmer', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('424', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('425', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cotton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('260', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('426', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('427', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('428', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Julian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Julian', 'GPE'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hebr', 'ORG'): 1; ('13.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3 day', 'DATE'): 1; ('so many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('3 Y. and', 'PERSON'): 1; ('430', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.1,2,3,4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('those 3 year and', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('431', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Florus', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('maximè mortiferi morientium bestiarum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('432', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about 3 day', 'DATE'): 1; ('433', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42 month', 'DATE'): 1; ('13.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('434', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dioclesian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sabachthani', 'ORG'): 1; ('435', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('D. G.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('49.7', 'MONEY'): 1; ('17.6 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('436', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3ly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1"
A50211,3,war undertake be prevalency prayer Moses mount army valley philistine,prayer: 0.5; god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; indians: 0.5; enemy: 0.5; day: 0.5; army: 0.4; heathen: 0.4; man: 0.35; people: 0.3; church: 0.2; time: 0.15; hear: 0.15; colony: 0.05,"('Indians', 'NORP'): 24; ('indian', 'NORP'): 12; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('New-England', 'LOC'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('english', 'NORP'): 4; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Licinius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('19 1675', 'DATE'): 2; ('1676', 'DATE'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('June', 'DATE'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hampton', 'ORG'): 2; ('Plymouth', 'GPE'): 2; ('Cobbet', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('z•rah the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ethiopian', 'NORP'): 1; ('a thousand thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaia•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sennacherib', 'GPE'): 1; ('one night', 'TIME'): 1; ('304', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marcus Aureliu•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vandal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('g•rmans', 'NORP'): 1; ('nine hundred seventy and five thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Imperialists', 'NORP'): 1; ('five day', 'DATE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('•eathen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constant••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Licinius', 'ORG'): 1; ('August de Civitat•', 'DATE'): 1; ('5 hundred 26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('claudian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('militat Aether', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Classica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nisibis', 'GPE'): 1; ('sapor•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 1; ('s•mpso•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Persiens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Morland Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Waldenses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two thousand and five hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sepulchre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oswald', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ethelfride', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cedwalla', 'GPE'): 1; ('P•nda', 'ORG'): 1; ('Oswal•', 'GPE'): 1; ('1•0', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cedwalla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Danes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Osvick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ashdon', 'ORG'): 1; ('danish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gustavus Adolphus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sweden', 'GPE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of the', 'ORG'): 1; ('Absolom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Achitophel', 'GPE'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('heark•ed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Decemb', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sudbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('April .', 'DATE'): 1; ('a month', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day of Mi•ian', 'DATE'): 1; ('egyp•ians', 'NORP'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Natick', 'ORG'): 1; ('punka••g Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ʋncas', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter indian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Indian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Peter Jethro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quanonchet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pomham', 'GPE'): 1; ('Monoco', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30 , 1676', 'DATE'): 1; ('two hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('July', 'DATE'): 1; ('three hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the same month', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about a hundred and eighty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Conn•cticut', 'GPE'): 1; ('Boston', 'GPE'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quaboag', 'ORG'): 1; ('Willard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a few hour or minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('march', 'DATE'): 1; ('wachus•t', 'ORG'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the spring of the year 1676', 'DATE'): 1; ('fifteen hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sachim', 'NORP'): 1; ('May 8. 1676', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bridgwater', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Taunton', 'GPE'): 1; ('July 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mahomet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('foster', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Charlstown', 'GPE'): 1; ('9th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('May , 1676', 'DATE'): 1; ('a few week', 'DATE'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rowlandson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('October 1676', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ipswich', 'GPE'): 1; ('about thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('cobbet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('December', 'DATE'): 1; ('no long than three week', 'DATE'): 1; ('July 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('1677', 'DATE'): 1; ('Salem', 'GPE'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sisera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jabin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kison', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oreb', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zeeb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zeba', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zalmunna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip the grand', 'ORG'): 1; ('prayer•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two and twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('may 18. 1676', 'DATE'): 1; ('no less than three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sachims', 'NORP'): 1; ('the Nipmuck Sachims', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pocasset', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fort', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Quanonchet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a few day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the latter end of June . 1676', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('that month', 'DATE'): 1; ('this very month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dublin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('some one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Londen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Suffolk', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dorset', 'ORG'): 1; ('Devon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Somerset', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lancashire', 'GPE'): 1"
A57315,3 | 15578,another prayer God heart night darkness sin mist error side,god: 0.5; scripture: 0.5; take: 0.5; thing: 0.5; prove: 0.5; day: 0.45; man: 0.45; prayer: 0.4; people: 0.35; spirit: 0.35; quakers: 0.3; life: 0.1; lord: 0.05; heart: 0.05,"('Quakers', 'ORG'): 9; ('this day', 'DATE'): 5; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 3; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 2; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6th', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the 19th', 'DATE'): 1; ('Quakers', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mordecai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Esther 5', 'ORG'): 1; ('500', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34.', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epaphany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Belial', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lent', 'EVENT'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('so much a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('1600 year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 16. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('grape', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('fig', 'ORG'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leonard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hurst Perpoint', 'ORG'): 1; ('George butler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Broadwater', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rottingden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Warbleton', 'GPE'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('George vinter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry Hollowel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sussex', 'GPE'): 1; ('this several year', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John •s', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('several year', 'DATE'): 1; ('as many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Babylon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Herod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day of Joh', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day and year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('24. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('four .', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year 1663', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1"
A59111,18,man Christianity spend day question school man body hide accident,god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; man: 0.5; love: 0.5; self: 0.5; word: 0.45; book: 0.4; scripture: 0.35; knowledge: 0.35; body: 0.2; saviour: 0.2; wisdom: 0.15; oracle: 0.15; christ: 0.1; sin: 0.1; christian: 0.05,"('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Collect', 'ORG'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Suarez', 'PERSON'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Neise', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hierar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Olearii', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alcoran', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abudac', 'ORG'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mahometan', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caesarius of Arles', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the 2d Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aug. de C. D. l. 15', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil aliud', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('amor', 'ORG'): 1; ('inhians', 'NORP'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1"
A59111,39,Monday easter Monday easter call Monday day paschal-week whole week,god: 0.5; day: 0.5; man: 0.5; week: 0.5; lord: 0.45; heaven: 0.45; world: 0.4; time: 0.4; saviour: 0.35; people: 0.35; another: 0.25; son: 0.2; nation: 0.1; church: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('this week', 'DATE'): 5; ('the day', 'DATE'): 5; ('Monday', 'DATE'): 4; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('Chrys', 'ORG'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 3; ('Saturday', 'DATE'): 2; ('the week', 'DATE'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Eden', 'GPE'): 2; ('persian', 'NORP'): 2; ('the second day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the whole week', 'DATE'): 1; ('541', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Palmar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Talm-Sunday', 'GPE'): 1; ('Maundy-Thursday', 'ORG'): 1; ('Good-Friday', 'DATE'): 1; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Constit', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Every day of this week', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sup', 'ORG'): 1; ('586', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ambr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('the seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('542', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('146', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Smyth', 'GPE'): 1; ('221', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Wednesday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('their season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Platonist', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'EVENT'): 1; ('Moses', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Aegypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Israelitish', 'NORP'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the ministry of king', 'ORG'): 1; ('Michaiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zechary', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jehciada', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezekiel be murder', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Reven', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Judea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('Mahometanism', 'NORP'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Collect', 'ORG'): 1; ('brethren meet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the prince of day', 'DATE'): 1; ('all the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1"
A59111,42,Thursday easter day bless master apprehend style day passion-week saviour,god: 0.5; day: 0.5; sacrament: 0.5; church: 0.5; bread: 0.5; sacrifice: 0.5; master: 0.4; saviour: 0.4; man: 0.4; world: 0.25; bless: 0.2; lord: 0.2; blood: 0.05; sin: 0.05; time: 0.05,"('this day', 'DATE'): 13; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Thursday', 'DATE'): 6; ('the day', 'DATE'): 6; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Chrys', 'ORG'): 3; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 3; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('the evening', 'TIME'): 2; ('118', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('evening', 'TIME'): 2; ('Friday', 'DATE'): 2; ('the year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Aug. Ep', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Maundy', 'ORG'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paschal', 'ORG'): 2; ('five day', 'DATE'): 1; ('P. Innoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fabiol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hte', 'ORG'): 1; ('twelve', 'DATE'): 1; ('fourteen', 'DATE'): 1; ('twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Smyth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('all night', 'TIME'): 1; ('midnight', 'TIME'): 1; ('Euseb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('livre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('547', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('african', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ludolph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('alii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aethiopick church', 'PERSON'): 1; ('202', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Castro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('holland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theolog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('557', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('807', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Grotius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('germans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thursaday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christians Lavipedium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maundy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 13.34', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antiphona', 'LOC'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'DATE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Oriental', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Conc', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anastas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('P.P.', 'ORG'): 1; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ambr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jonas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eden', 'GPE'): 1; ('Felicity', 'GPE'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('Melchisedech', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Misch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Beracoth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laity', 'ORG'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('august', 'DATE'): 1; ('the dawn of', 'TIME'): 1; ('Collect', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('only twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A59111,43 | 15998,examination lord prayer whole omit prayer be prayer perform cold,god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; sin: 0.5; soul: 0.5; mercy: 0.5; christ: 0.45; spirit: 0.45; world: 0.35; prayer: 0.3; life: 0.3; day: 0.3; mind: 0.1; jesus: 0.1; evil: 0.05; self: 0.05; love: 0.05,"('Satan', 'FAC'): 7; ('thou', 'GPE'): 7; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 7; ('the day', 'DATE'): 4; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Collect', 'ORG'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the Spectres of the', 'ORG'): 1; ('thy day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the terrible day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mahometans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Andrews', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Taylor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('meek person', 'FAC'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A59111,44,Easter-eve festival easter ancient bind observance fast devotion preparation Christian,day: 0.5; church: 0.5; jesus: 0.5; world: 0.5; time: 0.45; man: 0.35; lord: 0.35; christian: 0.3; heart: 0.25; night: 0.25; easter: 0.25; cross: 0.2; kingdom: 0.1; religion: 0.1; god: 0.1; saviour: 0.1; make: 0.05; soul: 0.05; apostle: 0.05; sorrow: 0.05,"('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 10; ('Saturday', 'DATE'): 4; ('Chrys', 'ORG'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('this day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Easter-eve', 'DATE'): 1; ('Easter-eve', 'LAW'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paschal', 'ORG'): 1; ('all night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Eus', 'GPE'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('536', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('541', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('156', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('676', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the joyful morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Palladium', 'ORG'): 1; ('85', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sepulchre', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a little after midnight', 'TIME'): 1; ('App', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('14 ,', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rupert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('585', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Palladium', 'GPE'): 1; ('86', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ambros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Millian', 'GPE'): 1; ('smith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('124', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('125', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thursday', 'DATE'): 1; ('the holy week', 'DATE'): 1; ('St Chrysostom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the other day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Conc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saturdays', 'DATE'): 1; ('Presanctificata', 'ORG'): 1; ('9.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'GPE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christ kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sanhedrim', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sear', 'DATE'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Zebedee', 'ORG'): 1; ('20.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Collect', 'ORG'): 1; ('Magdalen', 'ORG'): 1; ('I. Magd', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Magd', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('V. Magd', 'PERSON'): 1"
A59111,45 | 16186,Collect. almighty God beget son Jesus Christ haste overcome death,god: 0.5; jesus: 0.5; lord: 0.5; man: 0.5; priest: 0.45; saviour: 0.45; sin: 0.4; angel: 0.4; world: 0.3; church: 0.25; son: 0.25; soul: 0.2; sacrament: 0.15; time: 0.05; body: 0.05; heaven: 0.05,"('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 22; ('§', 'NORP'): 11; ('thou', 'GPE'): 9; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Saturday', 'DATE'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('§', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Corinth', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Collect', 'ORG'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('view yonder', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('easter-day', 'DATE'): 1; ('week', 'DATE'): 1; ('Good-Friday', 'DATE'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Easter', 'LOC'): 1; ('20.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of Gangra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ludov', 'ORG'): 1; ('101', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lothar', 'GPE'): 1; ('357', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Buxtorf', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jud', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Passiion', 'ORG'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elijah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Seraphim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Magdalene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('demeanour', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hosannah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baptist', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'GPE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Patin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Belshazzar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('111', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A53275,2,matter consideration pulpit press Christians repeat duty report reference generality,end: 0.5; word: 0.5; thing: 0.5; book: 0.5; god: 0.5; matter: 0.45; labour: 0.45; duty: 0.4; read: 0.4; self: 0.3; man: 0.15; prayer: 0.15; treatise: 0.1; mind: 0.05; time: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('thou', 'GPE'): 7; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 3; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 3; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Bibles', 'GPE'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('6. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fro•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('look|it', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alios', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scripturan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dulc•ùs', 'ORG'): 1; ('bibuntux', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nourish', 'NORP'): 1; ('lineâ', 'ORG'): 1; ('no day', 'DATE'): 1; ('nunquam satis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Comenii', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chyle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('48. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Manton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('spirit|be', 'LOC'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('noluit quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('fuisse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Brinsley', 'PERSON'): 1; ('farewell', 'PERSON'): 1"
