tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A85396,1,cash lump clay soul man• ne• shadow lump gift grace,people: 0.5; god: 0.45; hand: 0.45; man: 0.45; work: 0.45; enemy: 0.45; self: 0.4; world: 0.4; time: 0.3; nation: 0.25; arm: 0.2; king: 0.2; power: 0.05; opposer: 0.05; omnipotency: 0.05; pass: 0.05; parliament: 0.05; overcome: 0.05; outlive: 0.05; order: 0.05; oppress: 0.05; oppose: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('••', 'ORG'): 2; ('m•n', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('ne•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dt g g', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ὑβριστοδικαι', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jolm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tr•mell ▪ post q•••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athaliah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('fiat justitia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tyranni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry Cripps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lodowick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1649', 'DATE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Elihu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•4', 'ORG'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•aith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Messiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('1• .', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('•••••ada', 'ORG'): 1; ('Esa 31 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('the 2 Chr', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('th•i•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('tog•th•r', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ch•mosh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ashtaroth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('••donians', 'NORP'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•isse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Melita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('2•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philemon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pert•n••', 'GPE'): 1; ('al•', 'GPE'): 1; ('20. 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A85396,7 | 87,argument consequence proposition reason denial man individual person consider nature,power: 0.5; king: 0.5; life: 0.5; god: 0.5; people: 0.5; law: 0.5; case: 0.5; man: 0.5; subject: 0.45; superior: 0.35; state: 0.15; derivation: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 3; ('parem', 'GPE'): 3; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('noonday', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•ame', 'GPE'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alpha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Omega', 'PERSON'): 1; ('exerci•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('more than two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('midnight', 'TIME'): 1; ('between 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('40.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('miscrie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sect', 'LOC'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pol••ick', 'ORG'): 1; ('M•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rutherford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('inte••m', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Par', 'ORG'): 1; ('•ight', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('s•n', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five thousand pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('adulte•er', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('superio•r', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1"
A85396,9,reckon doctor Hamond author piece publish doctor Sect. trouble difference,doctor: 0.5; army: 0.5; man: 0.5; way: 0.5; word: 0.5; expression: 0.5; flattery: 0.45; christians: 0.35; conscience: 0.3; tertullian: 0.25; self: 0.25; action: 0.1; resistance: 0.1; time: 0.1; thing: 0.05; honour: 0.05,"('Christians', 'NORP'): 12; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 8; ('••', 'ORG'): 7; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('thi•', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Hamond', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 2; ('witho•t', 'ORG'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('desi•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('treati•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('anti-cavalerism•', 'NORP'): 1; ('besid•s •is', 'LAW'): 1; ('miscarry s•', 'ORG'): 1; ('beca•se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Areopagi', 'NORP'): 1; ('Areopagites', 'ORG'): 1; ('Montanas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Fortunas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•grees', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('q•d', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pri•iti••', 'NORP'): 1; ('m•••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('clau•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('arraig•eth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('more than half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Montanus', 'NORP'): 1; ('John • 44', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal 65', 'LAW'): 1; ('adjunct•m', 'ORG'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('th••', 'ORG'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ear••', 'ORG'): 1; ('const••ct••n', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('metapho•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('••de•s•ood', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tong•e', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('h••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•ccl', 'ORG'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('t•e', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gr••mar', 'GPE'): 1; ('•••', 'GPE'): 1; ('2 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('d•n', 'GPE'): 1; ('•d N.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tremellius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Syriac', 'LOC'): 1; ('Gualther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('English', 'NORP'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Areopagi', 'GPE'): 1; ('A•eopagites', 'GPE'): 1; ('go••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vit', 'LOC'): 1; ('numera•ur', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prynne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('139', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('140', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('j•m', 'ORG'): 1; ('fox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Monum', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian •••', 'ORG'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lyri••••', 'GPE'): 1; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('j•lian h•d', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sleid•n', 'GPE'): 1; ('8. 22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('L•• •••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('depend••g', 'FAC'): 1; ('First •hen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Father•', 'ORG'): 1; ('licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•ccidere', 'ORG'): 1; ('Martyrdo•', 'ORG'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('•lew', 'GPE'): 1; ('inva•it', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('incendi•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('••• •••', 'ORG'): 1; ('142', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1••', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('144', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•• ▪ ••', 'ORG'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('matte•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Barnabas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•ycophantrie', 'GPE'): 1; ('un - christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Flatteri', 'ORG'): 1; ('Herod', 'NORP'): 1; ('doubtles•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('hic lab•r', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Victori•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vic••rie', 'GPE'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•im •', 'PERSON'): 1; ('br••g', 'NORP'): 1; ('gre••', 'NORP'): 1; ('•aid', 'ORG'): 1; ('quaelibet', 'GPE'): 1; ('•pt', 'ORG'): 1; ('the memo•ie of', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('greate•t', 'ORG'): 1; ('call•d', 'ORG'): 1; ('•ind', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•n••ie•', 'ORG'): 1; ('••ch •••', 'ORG'): 1; ('• … plishm•nt •f', 'ORG'): 1; ('docto•r', 'FAC'): 1; ('•lattery', 'ORG'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fest••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul ▪ m•d', 'PERSON'): 1; ('prea•h', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('J•nkins', 'PERSON'): 1"
A86630,25,scene Thetis Peleus Prometheus choir deity free Prometheus Hercules Juno,peleus: 0.5; christ: 0.45; man: 0.45; christian: 0.45; religion: 0.45; church: 0.45; god: 0.4; thetis: 0.4; heart: 0.35; certainty: 0.25; christianity: 0.25; salvation: 0.1; communion: 0.05; papam: 0.05; pain: 0.05; peace: 0.05; passion: 0.05; part: 0.05; phil: 0.05; obless: 0.05; observe: 0.05; poet: 0.05,"('christian', 'NORP'): 8; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 5; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Hymen', 'PERSON'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('Prometheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hercules', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Juno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thetis and Peleus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peleus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prometheus Peleus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. Cyril', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ep', 'NORP'): 1; ('par', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hyde', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('Brightwell', 'ORG'): 1; ('Berks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('R. W. for Richard Davis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oxford', 'GPE'): 1; ('1658', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ajax', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tragedian', 'NORP'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('E. H.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou lover', 'PERSON'): 1"
A86946,7 | 2317,mercy God please apostle truth way salvation pillar church Gal.,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; son: 0.5; make: 0.5; joy: 0.5; law: 0.5; saint: 0.45; angel: 0.25; earth: 0.2; spirit: 0.2; heaven: 0.2; mercy: 0.1; song: 0.05; sense: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 11; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 7; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('latin', 'NORP'): 4; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('contra', 'NORP'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romano', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tiber', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aquila', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chrys', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat', 'GPE'): 1; ('Justine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trypho', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jam. 2', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the Hebrves , Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Vellosillo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Seth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('15.', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bibles', 'GPE'): 1; ('bell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the greek nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Belial', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('debtor essentiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet ▪', 'ORG'): 1; ('Belial', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet sinc jugo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('10. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 4 34', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('CAP', 'PERSON'): 1; ('labores sensuum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('motuum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ad delectationem dvo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cognitio huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('56', 'DATE'): 1; ('exultavit', 'GPE'): 1; ('gestivit', 'GPE'): 1; ('105', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calander', 'GPE'): 1; ('the 17 of December', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christmas', 'DATE'): 1; ('nos viam prudentiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesse', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clavis David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('oriens', 'GPE'): 1; ('lucis', 'GPE'): 1; ('mortis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('rex gentium', 'ORG'): 1; ('salva hominem quem de limo formasti :', 'ORG'): 1; ('7.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thoma Didyme', 'ORG'): 1; ('Virginum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hugo', 'EVENT'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('virgin blush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hecate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Judea', 'ORG'): 1; ('paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('6. 50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cantus', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A86946,17 | 2991,sect Xiii prayer dislike do deprecation man misery thanksgiving mercy,prayer: 0.5; god: 0.5; church: 0.5; man: 0.5; necessity: 0.5; heart: 0.5; gift: 0.45; faith: 0.4; eternals: 0.3; word: 0.25; thing: 0.25; form: 0.1; occasion: 0.05; make: 0.05; soul: 0.05; religion: 0.05; minister: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Xiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Occasionals', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui benè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Demetrius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Diotrephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Agamemnon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Achilles', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Occasional', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zacharie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hannah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tenent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chrysostom', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('chur•h', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arcula medica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bee', 'ORG'): 1; ('gather honey', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sharon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('unsettle', 'ORG'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('eorum', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Bemaraith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jarchi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cordis eorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Bechozek', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ezra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'MONEY'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A86946,17 | 3041,conscience point religion conscience man bind duty God name error,practice: 0.3; praelatus: 0.25; praise: 0.25; people: 0.25; performance: 0.25; piety: 0.25; point: 0.25; porch: 0.25; possession: 0.25; power: 0.25; god: 0.25; communion: 0.25; lord: 0.25; religion: 0.25; authority: 0.25; commandment: 0.25; word: 0.2; duty: 0.2; church: 0.15; house: 0.1; son: 0.1; example: 0.05; give: 0.05; self: 0.05; man: 0.05,"('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('no less than three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('no less than two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('praelati spiritualis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aedificationem s•t', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Praelatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('22ae', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('88', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('122', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sauls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('one minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('Solomon Jarchi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Vaani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aben Ezra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Davids', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hallelujah', 'GPE'): 1; ('medicina', 'GPE'): 1; ('jehovae cor patrium', 'PERSON'): 1"
A85746,1,method chapter add margin collect end London print T.W. Joshua,power: 0.5; person: 0.5; authority: 0.35; thing: 0.35; subject: 0.35; author: 0.35; god: 0.3; say: 0.25; right: 0.2; empire: 0.2; state: 0.2; people: 0.15; pen: 0.15; place: 0.15; piety: 0.15; presbyter: 0.15; pastor: 0.15; peace: 0.15; prince: 0.15; church: 0.1; name: 0.1; man: 0.05,"('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('T.W.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joshua Kirton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1651', 'DATE'): 1; ('Latium', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jew', 'GPE'): 1; ('Turk', 'GPE'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cassander', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arminius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('he|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Elders', 'PERSON'): 1; ('we|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('C. B. the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Xii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the last age', 'DATE'): 1; ('Grotius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Barksdale', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sudeley', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jan. 6. 1651', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hugo Grotius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('senate', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'EVENT'): 1; ('Chrysostom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernard follow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1"
A85746,7,CHAP. authority rule thing function ARistotle part architect architect hand,priest: 0.5; king: 0.5; office: 0.5; priesthood: 0.5; law: 0.5; function: 0.5; pastor: 0.45; right: 0.4; authority: 0.4; man: 0.3; god: 0.25; power: 0.15; divine: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the supreme authority', 'ORG'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Major', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lichfield', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.16', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Melchisedec', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Homer', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rome 1', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('about two thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Moses', 'NORP'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('54.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.6.5.10', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sedulius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangelicall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.81.83', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Chalcedon', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edgar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Martianus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theodoret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('synod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balsamo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1"
A85746,15,CHAP. election pastor part empire say function function presbyte•s deacon,people: 0.5; election: 0.5; apostle: 0.5; church: 0.5; pastor: 0.5; place: 0.45; man: 0.4; bishop: 0.35; thing: 0.35; deacon: 0.3; right: 0.25; presbyter: 0.15; word: 0.1; law: 0.1; ordination: 0.05,"('Paul', 'PERSON'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 5; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('greek', 'NORP'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 3; ('cyprian', 'NORP'): 3; ('deacon', 'ORG'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the apostle institute', 'ORG'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Barnabas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('x.', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('presbyte•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philo', 'NORP'): 1; ('Laodicea', 'GPE'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Plinius Secundus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('the Institutes of Christians', 'ORG'): 1; ('Levite', 'FAC'): 1; ('Judus Iscariot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('01', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('senate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Syndic', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pantanus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Demetrius', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Frumentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('India', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chalcedon', 'GPE'): 1; ('the London Synod', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Talmudists', 'NORP'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezechiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pliny', 'ORG'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hebrews', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('luke 10.1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the ministry of the apostle', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theodoret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysostomo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clemens of Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Barsabas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mathias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Syriac', 'LOC'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Titus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('1.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('plebeian', 'NORP'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pollu•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of Chalcedon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexander Severus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Severus', 'GPE'): 1; ('about a hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aurelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aurelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Celerinus', 'PERSON'): 1"
A86417,10 | 7921,virtue sin treason covenant subject tie other obedience define Chap.,right: 0.5; law: 0.4; sin: 0.4; god: 0.4; obedience: 0.4; treason: 0.4; nature: 0.4; subject: 0.35; man: 0.25; kingdom: 0.25; punishment: 0.25; punish: 0.15; sovereign: 0.15; remove: 0.1; reason: 0.1; rebel: 0.1; recite: 0.1; regicide: 0.1; religion: 0.1; proposition: 0.1,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 2; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('levy money', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•aith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twofold', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('integer vitae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pharetra', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('inhospital•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caucasum', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('x.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1"
A86417,12,lord king earth God say psalmist Psal. v. psalmist Psal.,god: 0.5; power: 0.5; man: 0.5; thing: 0.5; right: 0.5; honour: 0.5; word: 0.5; reason: 0.5; worship: 0.45; law: 0.4; nature: 0.15,"('three', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('99 v. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Rigbt', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 9 v. 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('honour', 'PERSON'): 1; ('x. a•l', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('xi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('creat•ur', 'GPE'): 1; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui fingi•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•uro', 'ORG'): 1; ('bene•it', 'PRODUCT'): 1"
A85683,7,reader advise passage author sckiekard Reg Hebr Jew christian east,room: 0.5; house: 0.5; part: 0.5; place: 0.5; jerusalem: 0.5; word: 0.45; chamber: 0.4; wall: 0.4; man: 0.4; god: 0.35; king: 0.2; say: 0.15; temple: 0.15,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 29; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 22; ('greek', 'NORP'): 12; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 11; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Caesarea', 'PERSON'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('arabic', 'NORP'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Alijah', 'GPE'): 5; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 5; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Syriacke', 'ORG'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Joppa', 'PERSON'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('14.', 'DATE'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Arab', 'NORP'): 3; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Gamaliel', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Kibla', 'ORG'): 3; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Vulcan', 'NORP'): 3; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jeremie', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Drusius', 'ORG'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Talmudists', 'NORP'): 2; ('Shecina', 'LOC'): 2; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tab', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Varro', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Vitruvius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Meade', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tabitha', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Alkibla', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Meccha', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Kibla', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('ark', 'GPE'): 2; ('Sennacherib', 'GPE'): 2; ('Sethon', 'GPE'): 2; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leon Modena Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dalla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oriente •posto', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('un', 'ORG'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Johan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('164', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomons', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('the arabic century', 'DATE'): 1; ('solomon temple', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alah', 'ORG'): 1; ('22. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('invidiam aliarum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eleazar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zohar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iliad', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eustathius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Moschopulus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Moschopul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('138', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hesychius', 'NORP'): 1; ('22.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Kimki', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 1', 'LAW'): 1; ('dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel in Babylon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Talm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Berac', 'GPE'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('Benjamin bar Jona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ju•hasan', 'ORG'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year 933', 'DATE'): 1; ('1173', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tobit', 'LOC'): 1; ('Sarah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Raguel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Echbatane', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bodleian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paulus Fagius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Munster', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Petronius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Summas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Va••ar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. C. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('coeli summa advocet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Proseuchae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the Code Beracoth', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet the', 'ORG'): 1; ('Talmud', 'ORG'): 1; ('Omedin ▪ Berac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('R.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hanina', 'GPE'): 1; ('ben Dosa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mishna Talm', 'ORG'): 1; ('ros ▪', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hassan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gemera Tal ▪', 'FAC'): 1; ('Avoda Zara', 'PERSON'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a. Gamaliel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sirach', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Modena', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de gli ▪ Riti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rosh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hashan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rabbans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cyriaci', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mahometans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Phasis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tarick', 'FAC'): 1; ('Alphraganus', 'DATE'): 1; ('Morocco', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alkas', 'NORP'): 1; ('Scaliger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scalig', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pollux', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Succah', 'GPE'): 1; ('R. Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('R. Simeon Talmud', 'ORG'): 1; ('Succa', 'GPE'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ben Iochai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nevoch', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aben tybbo•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maimon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sapientes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rabbinorum', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('nam plurima', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'ORG'): 1; ('L. Praet .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vlpian', 'NORP'): 1; ('inquili•i', 'LAW'): 1; ('Coenacula', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heins', 'ORG'): 1; ('Civium', 'ORG'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('contignationibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vitruvius', 'ORG'): 1; ('superiora domus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caenacula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('justifi', 'ORG'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('deci•it', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Coenaculariam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet ▪', 'ORG'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('saint mark', 'GPE'): 1; ('saint luke 22', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('24. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Josia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abaz', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Troas', 'ORG'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tabitha', 'GPE'): 1; ('9 37', 'DATE'): 1; ('39', 'DATE'): 1; ('Troas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ahaziah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mahumetans', 'NORP'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hali', 'PERSON'): 1; ('MSS', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laudin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sahan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laudin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ibn ▪ el Sahan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Joppa', 'GPE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aethiopicke', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christianorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 1; ('Geograph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('rex liberalitate ac sump tibus devictà', 'ORG'): 1; ('Joseph de bell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jud :', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caesarea Stratonis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jafo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tremelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vrishelem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Antioch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sheba', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iudg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Moab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('Coeuacul•', 'ORG'): 1; ('18. 33', 'DATE'): 1; ('Shunem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sarepta', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sam 18', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac Abraban ▪', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jonathan Targum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abrabaniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('west', 'LOC'): 1; ('west ▪', 'GPE'): 1; ('Italy Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Mizrach', 'ORG'): 1; ('Oriens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Schickard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Menasse', 'GPE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Herodotus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Assyria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aegypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('assyrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Homer', 'FAC'): 1; ('Hesiod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phavorinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iulius Pollux', 'ORG'): 1; ('Magalia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Suidas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Herodotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Euterp', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nidda', 'ORG'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Drus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ex•it sanguis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Buxtorfe', 'ORG'): 1; ('2676', 'DATE'): 1"
A85683,22,CHAP. Xviii Zach. man name east Zach. servant east place,east: 0.5; heaven: 0.5; man: 0.5; part: 0.5; god: 0.5; place: 0.5; time: 0.35; lord: 0.3; sun: 0.3; face: 0.25; word: 0.25; say: 0.25; call: 0.1; west: 0.1; world: 0.1,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 25; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 9; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Arab', 'NORP'): 7; ('greek', 'NORP'): 7; ('arabic', 'NORP'): 7; ('east', 'LOC'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Eden', 'GPE'): 6; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 6; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 4; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Ptolemy', 'GPE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Syriacke', 'ORG'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Ephrem', 'PERSON'): 3; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Zachary', 'GPE'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('6. 12', 'DATE'): 2; ('3. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Plin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 2; ('Geography', 'ORG'): 2; ('35', 'DATE'): 2; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Zoroaster', 'GPE'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Esdras', 'GPE'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('Ezra', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Aethiopicke', 'ORG'): 2; ('Relig', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Bethraman', 'FAC'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the month', 'DATE'): 2; ('Gen', 'PERSON'): 2; ('kedem', 'ORG'): 2; ('persian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Joma', 'GPE'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cyrus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cyrill', 'ORG'): 2; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the day spring', 'DATE'): 2; ('Maimon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('§', 'NORP'): 2; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Bethlem', 'NORP'): 2; ('Liber', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Xviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ecce vir', 'PERSON'): 1; ('west point', 'GPE'): 1; ('porphyry de nympharum an•ro', 'ORG'): 1; ('Varro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Festus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cincius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cinnius Capito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aequinoxes', 'ORG'): 1; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('proxima autem fa•c•bu• utrinque', 'ORG'): 1; ('Europ• Calpe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam •b', 'PERSON'): 1; ('causam indig', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Columnas e •s', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('creduntq••p rf•ssas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pro•m', 'GPE'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('averro•s', 'FAC'): 1; ('Arist', 'ORG'): 1; ('west .', 'GPE'): 1; ('Calpe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abyla', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hercules', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Beton', 'ORG'): 1; ('Diognetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ptolemy', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bipasis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexandri', 'GPE'): 1; ('exuperato', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amne', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexander Responsum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peutingerian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Biblioth', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('arabic meridian', 'NORP'): 1; ('ten degree', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Hyphasis Ptolemy', 'ORG'): 1; ('131', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about 120 degree', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('70 degree', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Geog.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Asia Tab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ʋmbilicus Terrae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pletho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Irenaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apostolorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D• Sp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sanct', 'GPE'): 1; ('6. 27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregory Nyssen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Orat', 'GPE'): 1; ('ecclesiast', 'PERSON'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anastas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hexaëmeron', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hieronymus Magius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Henoch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leviathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezech', 'ORG'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Primasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('68 32', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('Selah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'MONEY'): 1; ('plantaverat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maronites', 'NORP'): 1; ('Oriente', 'ORG'): 1; ('Selden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judea', 'ORG'): 1; ('orientali consitum', 'ORG'): 1; ('fuisse', 'ORG'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Betoch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apocalypse', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Tremelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cain', 'ORG'): 1; ('4. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lxx', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mizrach', 'ORG'): 1; ('the west Achor', 'GPE'): 1; ('the north Smol', 'LOC'): 1; ('Kibla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('South', 'LOC'): 1; ('Shecina', 'LOC'): 1; ('Maimon', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Catena', 'ORG'): 1; ('hundred 35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Genes', 'GPE'): 1; ('3328 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Leviticus C. 16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tawos', 'ORG'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Saadiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mishn .', 'ORG'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Talmud', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mishna Talmud', 'ORG'): 1; ('maimonid', 'DATE'): 1; ('jom .', 'GPE'): 1; ('h•ccippurim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Levit', 'GPE'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('the Jerusalem Isychius', 'ORG'): 1; ('•aith Baruch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('justitiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Procopius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Michah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bethlehem Ephrata', 'ORG'): 1; ('Micha', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('the day of old', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phara', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phara', 'GPE'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the golden candlestick', 'FAC'): 1; ('Beth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oeconomy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zacharie', 'GPE'): 1; ('6. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('horoscope', 'GPE'): 1; ('105', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the Jew Tryphon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Justin', 'ORG'): 1; ('James the Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Billioth', 'LOC'): 1; ('••o•ensi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Justus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zacharie ehe Prophet', 'ORG'): 1; ('saint luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zacharie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scaliger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jeremie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet tsemach Tsaddick', 'ORG'): 1; ('Severus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Taeitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orientalis', 'NORP'): 1; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('58', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nubian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bethlem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eccl', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bede', 'NORP'): 1; ('resurrectionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Syriack', 'ORG'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Archiv', 'ORG'): 1; ('James the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iustin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tryphon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arab d•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Biblioth', 'GPE'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cicestrensi•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('Conciliorum Arab', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bodloi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the latter day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul de palatio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oriente', 'LOC'): 1; ('loco veniet ubi nunc est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('aethiopian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hippolytus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the mount Olivet', 'FAC'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the mount Olivet', 'LOC'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Clemens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('that hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('the Jerusalem Talmud', 'ORG'): 1; ('the three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Galilaei', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Galilee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pentateuch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Archi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bod•eianis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nisan', 'PERSON'): 1"
A85683,40,nonlatinalphabet Augustus monarch empire prelate rite nonlatinalphabet Caesar Octavian Augustus,god: 0.45; clause: 0.45; book: 0.45; prayer: 0.45; thing: 0.45; heart: 0.45; man: 0.45; day: 0.45; copy: 0.35; gospel: 0.2; word: 0.2; octavian: 0.05; occasion: 0.05; passage: 0.05; part: 0.05; orison: 0.05; opinion: 0.05; place: 0.05; nazarite: 0.05; note: 0.05; point: 0.05; find: 0.05; self: 0.05; time: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 10; ('greek', 'NORP'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Augustus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('arabic', 'NORP'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Syriacke', 'ORG'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Octavian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexandrinum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lego', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rader', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xxxvii', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('this long day', 'DATE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('xxxviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('vetustissimis', 'GPE'): 1; ('codicibus graecis desit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Armagh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Worcester', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Erpenius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Medicean', 'NORP'): 1; ('Kirstenius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Non h•c', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aegyptiaco', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romano', 'ORG'): 1; ('Syriaco', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Alrumi', 'ORG'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Specimen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athanesius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mahumedans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eutychius', 'GPE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mahumedan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Matthai Authenticum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salmasius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trapezitic•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('panem crastini da nobis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('B.', 'NORP'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1"
A85783,12 | 9606,Satan power appoint God service benefit saint say heart Isa.,sin: 0.5; devil: 0.5; darkness: 0.5; god: 0.5; satan: 0.5; time: 0.5; world: 0.45; christ: 0.45; sinner: 0.4; saint: 0.3; state: 0.2; man: 0.15; soul: 0.05,"('Satan', 'FAC'): 13; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 12; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 6; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Balak', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 2; ('the night', 'TIME'): 2; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noremburg', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leviathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jonah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cephas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.24.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('he|will', 'NORP'): 1; ('Balaam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('caveat emptor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae edi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quaeque', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('vile wretch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('anni', 'NORP'): 1; ('the year end', 'DATE'): 1; ('last a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('one hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('a few day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('outward cross', 'ORG'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Doct', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 3.19', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; (""uncomfortab'enesse"", 'GPE'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mansion-house', 'FAC'): 1; ('12.44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James 3.15', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('all the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('six and seven', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('7.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A85549,1,reformation restitvtion argue Silvanus Hymeneus church Christ discover life estate,church: 0.4; christ: 0.4; hym: 0.4; god: 0.4; silv: 0.4; truth: 0.4; scripture: 0.4; apostle: 0.4; member: 0.3; people: 0.25; religion: 0.15; power: 0.1; place: 0.1; presume: 0.1; prayer: 0.1; praise: 0.1; print: 0.1; pleasure: 0.1; person: 0.1; peter: 0.1; prophet: 0.1; friend: 0.05; time: 0.05,"('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Silvanus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Hymeneus', 'GPE'): 2; ('J. G.', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Corinth', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Mathias', 'PERSON'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('T. B.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cornhill', 'GPE'): 1; ('1643', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hymeneus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('i hear seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('twice seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('120', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Barsabas', 'ORG'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Barnabas', 'PERSON'): 1"
A87878,3,manuduction consequence time year flood confusion tongue build Babel happen,year: 0.5; time: 0.5; god: 0.5; part: 0.4; king: 0.4; america: 0.4; noah: 0.35; jew: 0.35; oil: 0.35; confusion: 0.3; flood: 0.25; people: 0.25; man: 0.15; tongue: 0.1; gen: 0.1; phaleg: 0.05; world: 0.05,"('America', 'GPE'): 13; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 12; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 12; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 7; ('american', 'NORP'): 6; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Nimrod', 'PERSON'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Phaleg', 'GPE'): 4; ('239', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Tartar', 'ORG'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jo', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('1656', 'DATE'): 2; ('his day', 'DATE'): 2; ('1996', 'DATE'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Phaleg', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 2; ('66 year', 'DATE'): 2; ('about 140 year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Babel', 'ORG'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Brerewood', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ierome', 'ORG'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Acosta', 'ORG'): 2; ('Americans', 'NORP'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('46', 'DATE'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('Babel', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('98 year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('239 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('209', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('176', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('118', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('340 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abram', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('1757', 'DATE'): 1; ('Diluvium 101', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('all 239 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('100 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aust', 'LOC'): 1; ('dei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ult .', 'GPE'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('120 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the ark sufficient', 'ORG'): 1; ('a mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('9 v. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Horace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Circa', 'ORG'): 1; ('erat qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fragilem•truci', 'ORG'): 1; ('Primus', 'GPE'): 1; ('140 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('about the forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('1797', 'DATE'): 1; ('about 1800', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nebuchadnezar', 'ORG'): 1; ('about forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heber', 'PERSON'): 1; ('India', 'GPE'): 1; ('about forty or fifty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('about 180 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('about 240', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('250 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Diodorus Siculus lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the persian court', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nimrod', 'ORG'): 1; ('52 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('17 hundred thousand footman', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('two hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zoroaster', 'GPE'): 1; ('four hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('250', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('283', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('two hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a little above two hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iaphe•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sem', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('cham approach', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 19', 'TIME'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mediam regionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de laët de orig', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salmanasser king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Assyria', 'GPE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Esdras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arsareth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about 1500 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('heb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antiq', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Senaar', 'ORG'): 1; ('indian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Anian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Purchas Amer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magis inclino', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae cohaerere credit', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('quam', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('72', 'DATE'): 1; ('116', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Grotius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arias Montanus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magi', 'NORP'): 1; ('500 or 1000 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('er•e', 'GPE'): 1; ('57 year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('Functius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jason', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2740', 'DATE'): 1; ('500 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 1; ('Colchis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mengrelia', 'GPE'): 1; ('about 20 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the tuscan sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('grecian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ophir', 'GPE'): 1; ('2970', 'DATE'): 1; ('hundred of year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Brerewood', 'ORG'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the west Indies', 'ORG'): 1; ('Benjamin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('Maffeius', 'ORG'): 1; ('about 13 or', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Acosta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diodorus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Herodotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('irish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('as v. 30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hannah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ely', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•yle', 'GPE'): 1; ('Davids', 'ORG'): 1; ('elishah', 'GPE'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('all night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Bethel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zarephath 1', 'LAW'): 1; ('17. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('myrrh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Holophernes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mary Magdalen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14. 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('Galen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apronius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A87878,3 | 10795,another oil comfort David Ps. oil countenance grief death son,people: 0.5; woman: 0.45; swine: 0.45; oil: 0.45; jew: 0.45; cap: 0.45; hebrew: 0.4; use: 0.4; foot: 0.4; god: 0.35; american: 0.3; lib: 0.25; cust: 0.15,"('Jew', 'NORP'): 12; ('american', 'NORP'): 11; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 6; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 5; ('America', 'GPE'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('night', 'TIME'): 4; ('Brasile', 'GPE'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Io', 'LOC'): 3; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Odyssey', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 2; ('India', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ind.', 'GPE'): 2; ('vescuntur', 'GPE'): 2; ('scythian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Peru', 'GPE'): 2; ('jovinian', 'NORP'): 2; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('french', 'NORP'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('virginitas quae', 'ORG'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 2; ('David Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Athaeneus lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Democritus', 'ORG'): 1; ('exteriora oleo', 'ORG'): 1; ('interiora melle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('109', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mich. 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Athenaens lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thucydides', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Lacedaemonii corpora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nundati', 'GPE'): 1; ('Oleum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athletae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Robur', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ceroma', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ja', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aust', 'LOC'): 1; ('Iudaei', 'ORG'): 1; ('Florida', 'GPE'): 1; ('jewel hang', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('auribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sa•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•evit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 v. 27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•ll', 'GPE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mar.', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cana', 'GPE'): 1; ('west-indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Purchas America', 'LOC'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nova', 'LOC'): 1; ('Lerius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cambians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Goans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Peguans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bengalans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lev.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tartar', 'ORG'): 1; ('ab equis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('animalibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('demptis porcis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arabian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Samoëdes', 'NORP'): 1; ('plenilunio suilla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('carnibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('piscibus indiscriminatim vescuntur', 'ORG'): 1; ('animantibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Virginia', 'GPE'): 1; ('porcos', 'NORP'): 1; ('413', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sichi', 'GPE'): 1; ('porcos', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peruvianorum', 'GPE'): 1; ('the Jesuit Ni', 'ORG'): 1; ('Duran', 'GPE'): 1; ('1636', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paraquaire', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dec. 2', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 and 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chineses', 'NORP'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Maffeius', 'ORG'): 1; ('caro suilla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phasides', 'NORP'): 1; ('quam eructavit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Manasseh', 'ORG'): 1; ('2000', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Delasser', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Telemachus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('nisi aliqua vetula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plavus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Persa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aquam pedibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Grotius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('german', 'NORP'): 1; ('their day', 'DATE'): 1; ('galli•se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gaul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pluto', 'ORG'): 1; ('seven-night', 'TIME'): 1; ('month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cuba', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dec.', 'DATE'): 1; ('11. 37', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Acosta', 'ORG'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('apud hos barbaros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('indecora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•fficitur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 v. 29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrys', 'ORG'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Commistio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tanto postea facta', 'ORG'): 1; ('detestabili•r', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salmanasser', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non erat', 'NORP'): 1; ('simul cum patre balneari', 'FAC'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Persae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Indi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ethiope', 'LOC'): 1; ('filiabus', 'ORG'): 1; ('neptibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('indian', 'NORP'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Exod', 'GPE'): 1; ('1. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tremellius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pagnine', 'ORG'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('robustas', 'ORG'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Benjamin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ichabod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('mille', 'ORG'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('amplyfie', 'ORG'): 1; ('irish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Strabo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tibareni', 'GPE'): 1; ('Asia Minor', 'LOC'): 1; ('Purchas', 'ORG'): 1"
A87878,3 | 10993,conjecture language word speech Acosta proem book Iudaeorum american Innumer•b•les,jew: 0.5; american: 0.5; custom: 0.5; part: 0.5; america: 0.5; world: 0.5; author: 0.5; man: 0.5; observ: 0.4; word: 0.35; people: 0.15; use: 0.1,"('american', 'NORP'): 22; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 19; ('America', 'GPE'): 14; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 6; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 5; ('Observ', 'ORG'): 5; ('Acosta', 'PERSON'): 4; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Io', 'LOC'): 4; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Observ', 'GPE'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ind.', 'GPE'): 2; ('Papa', 'ORG'): 2; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('Messiah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Regius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('proem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Innumer•b•les', 'ORG'): 1; ('loco', 'PERSON'): 1; ('stitu', 'GPE'): 1; ('ita ingenio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('moribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('72', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('700', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Brasile', 'GPE'): 1; ('76', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('D•', 'GPE'): 1; ('548', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quot populi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('92', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvins', 'GPE'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('suo •buti', 'GPE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Brasilian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Amazon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Orenoque Papa', 'ORG'): 1; ('182', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Purchas de ▪ America', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cusco', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nanna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Sagardus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('king v. 25', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Titus •lay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Acosta', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iarricus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Scythia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sumatra', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bornea', 'GPE'): 1; ('the east indian island', 'LOC'): 1; ('jovinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Scots', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scythians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Massagetes', 'GPE'): 1; ('•umanis', 'ORG'): 1; ('licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some century of year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Acosta de Proc', 'ORG'): 1; ('ut tempora etiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('implenda', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('west-indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('6 year 18000', 'DATE'): 1; ('Netherlands', 'GPE'): 1; ('100 million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('400000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('raleigh', 'ORG'): 1; ('Barth .', 'GPE'): 1; ('Casas', 'GPE'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Salmanasser', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judaea', 'ORG'): 1; ('junctim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('west Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Observ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Purchas', 'ORG'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Inania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Americans', 'NORP'): 1; ('above 400 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fifteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('the 12th', 'DATE'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Judaea', 'NORP'): 1; ('the 25th', 'DATE'): 1; ('26th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('P. Maffeius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•d insaniam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7 Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('iguanaes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Descr', 'ORG'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('Attig', 'GPE'): 1; ('50', 'DATE'): 1; ('Florida', 'GPE'): 1; ('Israelites', 'LOC'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levit', 'GPE'): 1; ('17. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israelites', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('10 v. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Passover', 'GPE'): 1; ('Daniel', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi mores', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Horace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('plura', 'GPE'): 1; ('non ego paucis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bodine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('the supreme power', 'ORG'): 1; ('3d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('i•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bodine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Opinionists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Inconformists', 'ORG'): 1; ('B•zaes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zanchius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Edicta', 'ORG'): 1; ('f•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('▪ Winslow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leriu•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Villagagnon', 'ORG'): 1; ('proselyte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dyer monstrous child', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cotten', 'PERSON'): 1"
A89326,4,CHAP. immortality soul be teach philosopher time people nation be,man: 0.5; soul: 0.5; god: 0.5; body: 0.5; thing: 0.5; life: 0.5; another: 0.5; mind: 0.45; book: 0.35; time: 0.3; plato: 0.15; immortality: 0.15; self: 0.05; world: 0.05,"('Plato', 'PERSON'): 13; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Hermes', 'GPE'): 3; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Timaeus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 3; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Zoroastres', 'ORG'): 2; ('Platonists', 'NORP'): 2; ('Anaxagoras', 'GPE'): 2; ('Diogenes', 'ORG'): 2; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Epicurus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Phoedon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abeaham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Poemander , Hermes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Poemander', 'GPE'): 1; ('Poemander', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Esculapius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Chaldeans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Chalcidius', 'ORG'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chaldye', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'LOC'): 1; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('syrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Amonium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Assyria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Phocylides', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sibil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orpheus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iliad', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theognis , Homer', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hesiodus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pindar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pherecides', 'ORG'): 1; ('Timaeus of Locres', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Jamblichus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arckitas', 'ORG'): 1; ('pythagor•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philolaus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heraclitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Epicharmus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heraclides', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thales', 'GPE'): 1; ('Democritus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epicurus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Lucretius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucrece', 'GPE'): 1; ('Xenophon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Xenophon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Malapart', 'ORG'): 1; ('our day', 'DATE'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alcibiades', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simplicius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theophrastus', 'ORG'): 1"
A89326,4 | 11149,Latines say philosophy Greeks opinion writer opinion exercise superstition manner,soul: 0.5; thing: 0.5; body: 0.5; man: 0.5; book: 0.5; god: 0.5; self: 0.5; time: 0.35; mind: 0.25; place: 0.2; world: 0.2; word: 0.15; part: 0.15; opinion: 0.15; another: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 5; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thou mount', 'GPE'): 2; ('Getes', 'LOC'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hippocrates', 'GPE'): 2; ('Latines', 'ORG'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tusculane', 'GPE'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Cicero', 'FAC'): 1; ('Scipio', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('japet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Senecaes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gallio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucillus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucillus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phavorinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('elysian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pindarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sophocles Euripides', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Niger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Senega', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aristotle and Callisthenes', 'ORG'): 1; ('thracian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Herodotus', 'NORP'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('gebeleizie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zamolxis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marsilles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hetruscians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Scythians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hegesias', 'GPE'): 1; ('cyrenian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cleombrotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ambraciot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierocle', 'ORG'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Corax of Naxus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Polites', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epictetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Simplicius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Platonists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Plotinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Plotin', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Numenius , Jamblichus , Porphirius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Proclus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Themistius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Galen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1"
A88639,21,remedy ʋnreasonableness substance speech intend conference London Feb. head mr.,opinion: 0.5; man: 0.35; god: 0.35; grace: 0.35; mean: 0.35; word: 0.35; occasion: 0.3; opposition: 0.25; thing: 0.25; freedom: 0.2; say: 0.2; judgement: 0.2; obligation: 0.15; nonnulli: 0.15; opponent: 0.15; oblige: 0.15; number: 0.15; ministry: 0.15; mr: 0.15; self: 0.1; sense: 0.05; question: 0.05; account: 0.05; world: 0.05,"('London', 'GPE'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Feb. 11. 1649', 'DATE'): 1; ('John goodwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nonnulli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. London', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John macock', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lodowick Lloyd', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry Cripps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1650', 'DATE'): 1; ('Simson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jehojakim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36. 32', 'DATE'): 1; ('farewell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('John GOODVVIN', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11. 1649', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God .', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A86981,3,material proof brevity sake text doctor tenet search state question,christ: 0.45; dr: 0.45; kingdom: 0.45; isay: 0.45; year: 0.45; proof: 0.4; text: 0.4; saint: 0.4; earth: 0.4; church: 0.35; time: 0.1; psal: 0.05; psalm: 0.05; prophecy: 0.05; prophet: 0.05; prove: 0.05; pryn: 0.05; privilege: 0.05; quality: 0.05; put: 0.05; prideaux: 0.05; jew: 0.05; thing: 0.05; world: 0.05; call: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 22; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 19; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 13; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 10; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('37', 'DATE'): 5; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('32', 'DATE'): 4; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('14', 'DATE'): 4; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 4; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 3; ('21', 'DATE'): 3; ('Mahumetans', 'NORP'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Alsteed', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Babylonish', 'NORP'): 2; ('27', 'DATE'): 2; ('28', 'DATE'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2. 31', 'DATE'): 2; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Drs', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8', 'DATE'): 2; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 2; ('15. 24', 'DATE'): 2; ('the end of the thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two day', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('Millen', 'ORG'): 1; ('79', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('those thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('heathens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alcoran', 'PERSON'): 1; ('William Burton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tieho Brahe', 'ORG'): 1; ('Miranda', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39 40', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phaenomena', 'ORG'): 1; ('ipsi sibi', 'ORG'): 1; ('somnia fingunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Troja', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Testimonio Humano', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('340', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Paget', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ainsworth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Talmudick', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thalmudists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Scriptum', 'GPE'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. to', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 78', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'MONEY'): 1; ('48. 19 and 49.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Balaam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('110', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 6. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sterry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24. 23. 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('54. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('59 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('65. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('66.', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('50.', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'DATE'): 1; ('34. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 10. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('17. 43', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('8. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('they|will', 'PERSON'): 1; ('V. Paraeum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pryn', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('1000 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('nine mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Willets Synops', 'ORG'): 1; ('1296', 'DATE'): 1; ('folio shadow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cephas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quakers', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D. H.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('154', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ser', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('this thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('nova', 'LOC'): 1; ('rex ▪', 'ORG'): 1; ('nova Sacramenta', 'LOC'): 1; ('gratiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 10 , 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the l•st day', 'DATE'): 1; ('M•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baylys', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Disswas', 'ORG'): 1; ('246', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hebrews', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('134', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('8. 33', 'DATE'): 1; ('ad finem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylonish', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Daniel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Colos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('70. 71', 'DATE'): 1; ('248', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('249', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('238', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lactantius Instit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('13. 43', 'DATE'): 1; ('p•r Ca•ach•esin', 'GPE'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('abundance', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('22.', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 19 and', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('94', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Arians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('24. 3', 'DATE'): 1"
A85400,4 | 11818,Sect. p. parliament man vote person deputy p. degree people,church: 0.5; apostle: 0.5; independent: 0.5; member: 0.5; congregation: 0.5; god: 0.45; man: 0.45; pastor: 0.4; scripture: 0.4; synod: 0.25; assembly: 0.2; jerusalem: 0.15; mr: 0.1; lawfulness: 0.05; government: 0.05,"('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 11; ('synod', 'PERSON'): 9; ('christian', 'NORP'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Prynne', 'PERSON'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('prynne', 'PERSON'): 5; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Levite', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the apostle day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('Ephesus', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 2; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10. 12', 'DATE'): 2; ('13', 'DATE'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'DATE'): 2; ('14.', 'DATE'): 2; ('24', 'DATE'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('32', 'DATE'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('si nullus erit pulvis ,', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quaelibet officio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('apta', 'NORP'): 1; ('18. 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('arrian', 'GPE'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Novatians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Josephs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas Iscariot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Libera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Smyrna', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Presbyterall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22.', 'DATE'): 1; ('presbyterians', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apostles', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Benjamin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Manasseh', 'ORG'): 1; ('Simeon', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joih', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24. 16 ,', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 and', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Croesus erat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the late day', 'DATE'): 1; ('14. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sadducee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 22', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Deu', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 8 , 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('11. 16', 'DATE'): 1"
A85400,4 | 11846,assertion action interrogatory God God issue contradiction form plea doctrine,way: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; government: 0.5; doctrine: 0.5; church: 0.5; mr: 0.5; state: 0.5; place: 0.4; christ: 0.3; contrariety: 0.25; thing: 0.05,"('Prynne', 'PERSON'): 8; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('prynne', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 3; ('30', 'DATE'): 3; ('31', 'DATE'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('a hour', 'TIME'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('prynn', 'PERSON'): 2; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('injuriam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('galatian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('scis simulare', 'PERSON'): 1; ('navibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('obsta•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('venienti', 'ORG'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('pryns', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('8. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('holland', 'GPE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('A. S.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucas Osiander', 'ORG'): 1; ('the 6th century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('40.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'DATE'): 1; ('39th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Cameron', 'ORG'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('1500 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('about 200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Burton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('300.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ulysses', 'ORG'): 1; ('twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Penelope', 'GPE'): 1; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1"
A85386,4 | 12254,part reason inference word mention contrary word page sense way,mr: 0.5; power: 0.5; man: 0.5; prynne: 0.5; passage: 0.5; word: 0.5; parliament: 0.5; meaning: 0.45; magistrate: 0.4; author: 0.4; cause: 0.1; law: 0.05; discourse: 0.05; interpretation: 0.05,"('Prynne', 'PERSON'): 18; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('prynne', 'PERSON'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 3; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Dedic', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('111', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Adam Steuart', 'PERSON'): 2; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Edwards', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('107', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('163', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('169', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Katherine Chidley', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Katherine Chidleys', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some year', 'DATE'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('A. S.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('A. Steuart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('180', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S.', 'ORG'): 1; ('presbyterians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('England Actapol', 'NORP'): 1; ('191', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quod defertur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('apricum', 'GPE'): 1; ('fox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacobus Acontius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('72.', 'DATE'): 1; ('73.', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac Mat 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 27', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('supreme temporal magistrate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antapol', 'ORG'): 1; ('159', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('160', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('166', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('170', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('108', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('109', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('110', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('diminuentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('versus finem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Neptune', 'ORG'): 1"
A89158,5,TETRACHORDON Matt be say wife writing divorcement wife Matt pharise,law: 0.5; man: 0.5; divorce: 0.5; cause: 0.5; saviour: 0.5; god: 0.5; reason: 0.5; word: 0.4; christ: 0.35; pharise: 0.35; marriage: 0.2; join: 0.1; consent: 0.05; wife: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('christian', 'NORP'): 6; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 5; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 4; ('greek', 'NORP'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 2; ('that day', 'DATE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 2; ('herodian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Cameron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marinaro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Law', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Horace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quintius', 'ORG'): 1; ('senate', 'ORG'): 1; ('freeman', 'GPE'): 1; ('Austine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marcion', 'FAC'): 1; ('Aretas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petra', 'ORG'): 1; ('fillip house', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baptist', 'NORP'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herod', 'NORP'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Hilary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Moses', 'NORP'): 1; ('Philo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Syriac', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one quarter', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paraeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ill accident', 'GPE'): 1"
A89280,18,entrance self view Moses spirit Plato governor commonwealth epistle Dion,moses: 0.5; god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; man: 0.5; sense: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; world: 0.45; earth: 0.35; place: 0.25; scripture: 0.25; truth: 0.2; creation: 0.2; moon: 0.1; appearance: 0.1; sun: 0.05; nature: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Cabbala', 'GPE'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Moses', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 2; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gibeon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Plato', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dion', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philo', 'NORP'): 1; ('yesterday', 'DATE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Osiris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isis', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vulcan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diodorus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diodorus Siculus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bacchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ceres', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hebrews', 'PERSON'): 1; ('juxta linguam humanam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five cubit', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('thirty cubit', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psalm 19', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joshua 10', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sunn•', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou moon', 'LOC'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ajalon', 'ORG'): 1; ('many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernard , Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('Phaenomena', 'ORG'): 1; ('vail', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'LOC'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psalm 25', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Galat', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ishmael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaak', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sara', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rebecca', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jacobs', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rachel steal Laban T••raphim ▪', 'ORG'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heber', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jabin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sisera', 'PERSON'): 1"
A89280,20,Vers. be say verse nearness water spur devotion bring earth,god: 0.45; ver: 0.45; man: 0.45; sun: 0.45; earth: 0.45; sense: 0.4; day: 0.4; shape: 0.4; thing: 0.4; moses: 0.25; name: 0.25; sight: 0.1; plant: 0.05; place: 0.05; principle: 0.05; power: 0.05; policy: 0.05; poem: 0.05; plato: 0.05; production: 0.05; person: 0.05; permit: 0.05; light: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('Jao', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Cabbala', 'GPE'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('spring', 'DATE'): 2; ('Zeus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('summer', 'DATE'): 2; ('Helios', 'GPE'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 2; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Psalm 104', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nahum 1. 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the second day', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philo the Jew', 'ORG'): 1; ('a plentiful year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('clarian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Macrobius', 'GPE'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eloah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jehovan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cornelius Labeo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bacchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the four quarter of the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bacchus and Ceres', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('no less than', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anthropomorphites', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato his Symposion', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Aristophanes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('strawberry', 'ORG'): 1"
A89280,26,CHAP. Iii encage serpent nonlatinalphabet Pherecydes Syrus nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet name,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; soul: 0.5; cabbala: 0.5; adam: 0.4; philosophy: 0.4; life: 0.35; pythagoras: 0.35; ver: 0.35; place: 0.35; divine: 0.25; spirit: 0.2; moses: 0.2; part: 0.1; sense: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 33; ('Cabbala', 'GPE'): 23; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 17; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Plotinus', 'GPE'): 6; ('Pythagoras', 'LOC'): 6; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Abaris', 'PRODUCT'): 3; ('Grotius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Phaenomena', 'ORG'): 3; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 3; ('Pherecydes Syrus', 'GPE'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Plato', 'ORG'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Bezaliel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Aholiab', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Lucretius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 2; ('cabbala', 'GPE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Xenocrates', 'GPE'): 2; ('Pythagoras', 'NORP'): 2; ('Selden', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Metapontium', 'ORG'): 2; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Olympius', 'ORG'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('frait', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cartesius', 'ORG'): 1; ('princeps mali', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Castellis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Onocentauri', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hesychius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Castellio Satyri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Castellio render Fauni', 'ORG'): 1; ('Strepitus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Satyros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vulgo taciturna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('silentia rumpi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lamia', 'ORG'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Luoretius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12. 43', 'DATE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Ager ▪', 'ORG'): 1; ('Shedhim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'GPE'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Praestantiorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ficinus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thorn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('— nil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magno vita', 'FAC'): 1; ('Pythagorean', 'ORG'): 1; ('prophec•es', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adami', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rupertus', 'ORG'): 1; ('fuisse', 'ORG'): 1; ('huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Aeneid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('donec long diê perfecto temporis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Concretam', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet .', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aether', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hierocles', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heros', 'GPE'): 1; ('Maimonides', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vehicles', 'ORG'): 1; ('Proteus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rabbi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philo Judaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('234', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('398', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Iamblichus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Parthenis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Eudoxus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Homer', 'FAC'): 1; ('Aristobulus', 'NORP'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrinus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Josephus against Appion', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Justine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Clemens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Sidon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Moses', 'NORP'): 1; ('Porphyrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pythagora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abaris', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sicily', 'GPE'): 1; ('Empedocles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epimenides', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexanemus , Epimenides', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aethrobates', 'GPE'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Speusippus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anaxilides', 'ORG'): 1; ('Perictione', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristocles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrinus ▪', 'LOC'): 1; ('Hermippus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Numenius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cartesian', 'NORP'): 1; ('perplex melancholy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('no less than three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jordan', 'GPE'): 1"
A89280,28,Ver. field interpretation Origens Ver. difference light difference verse Ver.,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; ver: 0.5; adam: 0.5; divine: 0.5; christ: 0.45; life: 0.4; light: 0.35; day: 0.25; righteousness: 0.25; water: 0.15; image: 0.15; soul: 0.1; mind: 0.1; passion: 0.1; whole: 0.05; nature: 0.05; body: 0.05; word: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 12; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 3; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Plato', 'ORG'): 2; ('the sixth day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Origens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the sixteenth and', 'DATE'): 1; ('eighteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dionysius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thersites', 'GPE'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Venus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heraclitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Porphyrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('anima', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Homer', 'GPE'): 1; ('Adam Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Plotinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plotinus', 'LOC'): 1; ('un', 'ORG'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cabbala', 'GPE'): 1; ('Minorem Mundum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam be nonlatinalphabet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Origen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('ista', 'NORP'): 1; ('dominetur', 'GPE'): 1; ('a clear day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the first day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Philo', 'NORP'): 1; ('the second day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the four day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the five day', 'DATE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1"
A89280,30,CHAP. Iii story dispute prelate blacksmith Adam apple mean subtlety,man: 0.5; adam: 0.5; life: 0.5; divine: 0.5; light: 0.5; ver: 0.45; god: 0.45; pleasure: 0.35; thing: 0.3; mind: 0.3; sense: 0.25; body: 0.15; power: 0.1; conscience: 0.05; serpent: 0.05; self: 0.05,"('Adam', 'PERSON'): 25; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Philo', 'GPE'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Philo', 'NORP'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('Bodinus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Guyon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Adam', 'GPE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cabbala', 'GPE'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eve', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('rixas', 'GPE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('many hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Spencer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Americans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 1; ('Countreymans', 'NORP'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('Belial', 'GPE'): 1; ('skill', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Religionists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pilgrim', 'ORG'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hominem sum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('humani nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fifteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('332', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Brutus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
B29252,14,explication text clear analysis power give heaven earth will God,spirit: 0.5; christ: 0.5; power: 0.5; ministry: 0.5; father: 0.5; man: 0.45; god: 0.45; word: 0.45; promise: 0.4; apostle: 0.35; gospel: 0.3; lord: 0.05; mouth: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 14; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('thou', 'GPE'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 4; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1.4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 3; ('John', 'PERSON'): 3; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('John 15.16', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('16', 'DATE'): 2; ('14.1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4', 'DATE'): 2; ('5', 'DATE'): 2; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('John 13.3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Exousia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dunamis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 8.29', 'PERSON'): 1; ('110.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 17.8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chapt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.2', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('59.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 15.1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timothy', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Keep', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.9 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the end of age :', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('68.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.16', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('the ministry of reconciliation', 'ORG'): 1; ('15.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the ministry of the', 'ORG'): 1; ('the ministry of Moses', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.3', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ ministry be constitute', 'ORG'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.17.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('133.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.3 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('61.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('59.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('44.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1"
