tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A73382,10,sense place head touch spread whole body head rest body,heart: 0.5; man: 0.5; sense: 0.5; eye: 0.5; body: 0.5; hand: 0.5; object: 0.45; fall: 0.45; ear: 0.4; thing: 0.25; tongue: 0.15; god: 0.15; right: 0.1; liver: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 24; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 19; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 18; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 16; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('the fall', 'DATE'): 9; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 8; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('thou', 'GPE'): 6; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Pericardia', 'ORG'): 3; ('Abner', 'ORG'): 3; ('Joab', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Philomenes', 'ORG'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Iam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8.13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10.2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Reticulum', 'ORG'): 2; ('Hazael', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('2.23', 'MONEY'): 1; ('12.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('icteriacis', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cornea', 'GPE'): 1; ('17.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('heeallude', 'TIME'): 1; ('fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('causam imputans', 'PERSON'): 1; ('occasionem oculo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'MONEY'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.17', 'DATE'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('revelat aurem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('perforate', 'GPE'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('Exo', 'LOC'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('obedientiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ianua', 'NORP'): 1; ('9.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('58', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leviathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('49.6', 'MONEY'): 1; ('1.19 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('45.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iam. 3.6', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tertia commovit multos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chalde', 'LOC'): 1; ('Doeg', 'GPE'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 1; ('Neptune', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cupid', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('31.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hosea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Michael the Archangell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Salomons', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ambidexter', 'ORG'): 1; ('subiecto', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ʋeritas', 'ORG'): 1; ('logica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amaza', 'GPE'): 1; ('Amaza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 19.34', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Syriacke', 'ORG'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('the greek nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.78', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Greeke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('139', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Easie 59.7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Antiochus Epiphanes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antiochus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam deform', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hippocrates', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hippocrates', 'GPE'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('Differuntsensus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.23 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein reason', 'PERSON'): 1"
A73382,28,CHAP. Iii passion cure virtue philosopher passion virtue virtue passion,virtue: 0.5; middle: 0.5; vice: 0.5; work: 0.5; passion: 0.5; man: 0.5; diogenes: 0.5; call: 0.5; god: 0.45; justice: 0.4; aristippus: 0.05; circumstance: 0.05; extreme: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Diogenes', 'ORG'): 4; ('Aristippus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('quantitatis absolutae', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Plato', 'ORG'): 2; ('3.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Morologia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nabal', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet est', 'ORG'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 kin', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('18.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amonius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seu medium rei', 'ORG'): 1; ('twofold', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vel rationis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('5.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mark', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel proportionis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quando', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('17.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ultimum finem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Helena', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristippus and Diogenes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Platonis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Fastu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luerecia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cleopatra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gulf', 'LOC'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('10.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1"
A73382,35,CHAP. sadness grief sadness passion soul discontentment receive object contrary,sadness: 0.4; christ: 0.4; soul: 0.4; passion: 0.4; god: 0.4; man: 0.4; grief: 0.4; object: 0.35; death: 0.35; thing: 0.25; reason: 0.15; superior: 0.1; pain: 0.1; remit: 0.1; regenerate: 0.1; repentance: 0.1; repent: 0.1; renew: 0.1; reserve: 0.1; remedy: 0.1; quest: 0.1; resurrection: 0.1,"('second', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26.38', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('x.', 'ORG'): 1; ('duplex tristitia', 'ORG'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('duplex tristitia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tristitia', 'ORG'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('vel secundum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Seneca', 'GPE'): 1; ('tristitia perturban', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('duplex facult', 'ORG'): 1; ('facultates superiores', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('55 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('duplex objectum', 'ORG'): 1; ('vel excessu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eli', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amos 5.16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Coelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tibia', 'ORG'): 1; ('maesta', 'ORG'): 1; ('phrygian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Iairus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the joy reserve', 'ORG'): 1; ('1 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Esai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('53.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Math', 'ORG'): 1; ('26.38', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('Easie 50.4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Corinthian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A79208,23,argument conclusion discourse Iris love night day soul inspire flame,god: 0.5; sin: 0.5; man: 0.5; power: 0.5; argument: 0.5; ability: 0.5; evil: 0.5; lady: 0.45; lover: 0.25; tempt: 0.25; woman: 0.2; draw: 0.2; dilemma: 0.05; devil: 0.05; author: 0.05,"('Iris', 'PERSON'): 3; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Celadon', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sin', 'LOC'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sterrey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('PROV', 'ORG'): 1; ('26.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Giles Calvert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1652', 'DATE'): 1; ('brown', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 8.44', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18 32', 'DATE'): 1; ('1 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 1.7 ,', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A70747,78,day vengeance God people face whole world nation Jew banish,god: 0.35; word: 0.35; saviour: 0.35; jew: 0.35; world: 0.35; bless: 0.35; jesus: 0.3; john: 0.3; temple: 0.25; nature: 0.15; native: 0.15; objection: 0.15; notion: 0.15; nazareth: 0.15; passage: 0.15; mute: 0.15; name: 0.15; people: 0.15; nation: 0.15; father: 0.15; son: 0.15; thing: 0.1; prophet: 0.1; lord: 0.05,"('Jew', 'NORP'): 9; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 7; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Celsus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Nazareth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('x. the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('V. 27', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pythian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Herod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the John xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xi', 'ORG'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xviii V. 20', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Beelzebub', 'ORG'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Xii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat twenty-five V. 6', 'ORG'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'FAC'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('more than twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A70493,9 | 2941,P. instance man Berea son religion father door whole matter,emperor: 0.5; julian: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; author: 0.5; father: 0.4; christians: 0.35; psalm: 0.3; king: 0.3; time: 0.3; saint: 0.1; prayer: 0.1; church: 0.05; instance: 0.05; word: 0.05,"('Julian', 'NORP'): 12; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 10; ('Julian', 'PERSON'): 7; ('christian', 'NORP'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Julian', 'GPE'): 5; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Gregory Nazianzen', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Constantius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Valentinian', 'NORP'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 3; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Maris', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Juventinus', 'LOC'): 2; ('Maximus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Dioclesian', 'NORP'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('CHAP', 'ORG'): 2; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('James', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Babilas', 'GPE'): 2; ('Berea', 'GPE'): 1; ('Berea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chalcedon', 'GPE'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Julians', 'NORP'): 1; ('spoliantibus non resistit', 'ORG'): 1; ('caedentibus non repugnat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maximian', 'NORP'): 1; ('cum tam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nefanda', 'NORP'): 1; ('verbo quidem reluctamur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('remittimus ultionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Instit.', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Theodoret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ninety year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('thirty two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 26.9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Longinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Billius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregory Nazianzen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Elias Cretensis', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Mandamus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lexicon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Billius and Cretensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nazianzen or Basil', 'ORG'): 1; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('presbyterians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Scotish', 'NORP'): 1; ('above forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Knox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Buchanan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Charles Stuart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bracton', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quicunque', 'NORP'): 1; ('Stephens', 'GPE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James 3.9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sheba', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Publia', 'GPE'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('swan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('anon', 'LOC'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('late year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pasquil', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Arians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Caesaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('imperatorem Constantius', 'PERSON'): 1"
A70493,14 | 3210,plorate Pertaesi Conservator Legum protector Secundus Deperditae instaurator Judex Regiae,law: 0.5; god: 0.5; power: 0.5; king: 0.5; thing: 0.5; authority: 0.5; prince: 0.45; subject: 0.45; mean: 0.3; church: 0.25; man: 0.2; case: 0.15; baxter: 0.05; mr: 0.05; people: 0.05; gospel: 0.05,"('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Baxter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Suprema', 'ORG'): 2; ('quotquot', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pertaesi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Legum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('religionis', 'NORP'): 1; ('nulli Secundus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Regiae Stirpis Extirpator Perfidus', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui consentientibus dissentit ab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Modernis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Anabaptistis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Regicidis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('majestatis oppressus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gloria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Inglorius', 'NORP'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('89', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('80', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('85', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caesar authority', 'ORG'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 1; ('61', 'DATE'): 1; ('Grotius de imperio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('210', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mutato regis animo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deo', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sanderson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('noonday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cicero de legibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('judicando', 'ORG'): 1; ('Praetores', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ollis', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the supreme authority', 'ORG'): 1; ('supreme authority', 'ORG'): 1"
A79898,2 | 3597,faith deliverance evil assistance time trouble resurrection body glory Christ,god: 0.5; sermon: 0.5; comfort: 0.5; play: 0.5; lord: 0.5; entitle: 0.5; day: 0.4; man: 0.3; book: 0.3; love: 0.2; christ: 0.2; master: 0.15; child: 0.1; faith: 0.1; saint: 0.1; time: 0.1; grace: 0.05,"('oct', 'DATE'): 19; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('York', 'GPE'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('comfort', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Katherine Bretterg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Katherine Pura : Christoqua•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Coelis', 'GPE'): 1; ('31.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Overton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('verton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 1•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•ll', 'ORG'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('rutling', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('72', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('William miller', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('the Jew Juvenal', 'FAC'): 1; ('Robert Stapylton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Churchil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Britanici', 'GPE'): 1; ('knowledge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gunter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('J. B. sermon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Job 14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'TIME'): 1; ('medice cura', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christopher Meret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('William', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Glucester', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Norwich', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dr.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('entitle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('justice triumph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Novem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pilgrim', 'ORG'): 1; ('anne Dudson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the 30.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jan. 1661', 'DATE'): 1; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('the royal commonwealth', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thomas Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam Drake', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1669', 'DATE'): 1; ('— entit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15 , march', 'DATE'): 1; ('Horatius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spanish Gipsy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fertiplace', 'ORG'): 1; ('English', 'NORP'): 1; ('S.C.', 'GPE'): 1; ('Templum Musicum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Synop', 'LOC'): 1; ('Tillotson', 'ORG'): 1; ('god , oct', 'DATE'): 1; ('Clavis Homerica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Warren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Janua Janua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Commenii Vestibulum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Owen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('buttler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erasmiana', 'GPE'): 1; ('Johanne Betto m. D.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas Elborow Entit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Ignatius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apostle S. John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Barnabas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Busby', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theoph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clark', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•ong', 'GPE'): 1; ('master h', 'PERSON'): 1; ('B.', 'NORP'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('November', 'DATE'): 1"
A73324,5 | 3719,enemy town gate port Civitas man strength shut gate heart,world: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; flesh: 0.5; pleasure: 0.5; life: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; sin: 0.45; enemy: 0.4; rom: 0.25; thing: 0.25; conscience: 0.05; death: 0.05; heart: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 14; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 4; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 4; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 2; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Philip', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Civitas', 'ORG'): 1; ('6. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 3. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Easie 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jam.', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rachel Math', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sarah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Micol', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Vashtay', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ahashuerus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abigail', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nabal', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tomorrow', 'DATE'): 1; ('12. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('18. 36', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('sincera v•lupt as', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amos 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Templum', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('more than 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('non mortalia pectora cogit', 'ORG'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Indos', 'ORG'): 1; ('Math', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('16.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chureh', 'NORP'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('21. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov 10', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Achan', 'ORG'): 1; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ahab 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gehezi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('••rba', 'GPE'): 1; ('Fronti', 'ORG'): 1; ('Belial', 'GPE'): 1; ('1 Pet', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('quidem qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('avaritiam coercet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cohibet', 'GPE'): 1; ('8. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('serp•nt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1"
A73451,2 | 4017,cauponante belligerante challenge make point Josephus doctrine pope Martins dispensation,man: 0.5; book: 0.5; mr: 0.5; church: 0.5; council: 0.45; word: 0.45; christ: 0.45; untruth: 0.45; roger: 0.45; pag: 0.45; thing: 0.15; heretic: 0.1; manner: 0.05,"('Roger', 'PERSON'): 11; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 10; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 7; ('England', 'GPE'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 3; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Rogers', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Postellus', 'GPE'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Franciscans', 'NORP'): 2; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Stapleton', 'ORG'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Augustin', 'ORG'): 2; ('Siricius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Toby', 'ORG'): 2; ('S. John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('non cauponante bellum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('of million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Charing', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chester', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Derby', 'ORG'): 1; ('Darington', 'GPE'): 1; ('mount Minekin', 'LOC'): 1; ('R.', 'NORP'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Plessi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Marlie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas Rogers', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Roger untruth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jane', 'PERSON'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('187', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('§', 'NORP'): 1; ('Limbus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sutcliffe', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Willet', 'ORG'): 1; ('1600', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('353', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Roger blush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phariseis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('evang', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luc', 'DATE'): 1; ('528', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Stapleton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Ses', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('inn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('447', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simplicianum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calixtus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paschalis', 'ORG'): 1; ('holy council of Carthage', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('102', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Busgradus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Busgradus', 'GPE'): 1; ('115', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chalcedon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Honorius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chronico', 'GPE'): 1; ('422', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('116', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Machabee', 'LOC'): 1; ('the three council of Carthage', 'ORG'): 1; ('twelve hundred year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apocalypse', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nine and thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judith', 'NORP'): 1; ('disciplinarian', 'NORP'): 1; ('121', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eckius', 'PERSON'): 1"
A78506,2,man forlese give •elf prime man hedge dispute general •ome,man: 0.45; king: 0.45; people: 0.45; god: 0.45; power: 0.45; authority: 0.4; sin: 0.4; parliament: 0.35; prayer: 0.35; reason: 0.35; time: 0.25; nation: 0.2; pestilence: 0.05; peril: 0.05; policy: 0.05; point: 0.05; plea: 0.05; plague: 0.05; place: 0.05; piece: 0.05; peter: 0.05,"('•hey', 'ORG'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('forlese', 'NORP'): 1; ('•ome', 'ORG'): 1; ('•heir brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paragraph', 'NORP'): 1; ('coelestibus ira', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sepulchre make Collector', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the supreme authority', 'ORG'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('balak errant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bocardo', 'GPE'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Hartfordshire', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('my quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Worcester house', 'ORG'): 1; ('Wednesday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Robert Barker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John bill', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1636', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.5 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezechias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hester', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1"
A72754,3,form prayer prescribe time visitation other necessity pastors curate parishioner,psal: 0.5; lord: 0.4; mercy: 0.4; god: 0.4; sin: 0.4; father: 0.4; prayer: 0.35; voice: 0.3; heart: 0.3; sake: 0.25; glory: 0.15; people: 0.15; power: 0.1; promise: 0.1; priest: 0.1; prescribe: 0.1; provoke: 0.1; praise: 0.1; pit: 0.1; place: 0.1; name: 0.1; minister: 0.1,"('thou', 'GPE'): 14; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Wednesdayes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Friday', 'DATE'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('9 to thou', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('kneel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Osee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jonas 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal 51', 'LAW'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('64', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ose', 'ORG'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baruc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jonas 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('79', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every night', 'TIME'): 1; ('beati quorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1"
A72754,5,almighty father err stray way lose sheep follow device desire,lord: 0.5; god: 0.5; father: 0.5; mercy: 0.5; people: 0.5; christ: 0.5; sin: 0.4; priest: 0.35; glory: 0.35; prayer: 0.25; jesus: 0.25; spirit: 0.25; answer: 0.15,"('thou', 'GPE'): 13; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('morning', 'TIME'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 3; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 3; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('meek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Osee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jonas 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('51', 'DATE'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('64', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judith 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jonas 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('79', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fifteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ponce Pilate', 'ORG'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Collect', 'ORG'): 1; ('this night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1"
A74793,2,London air whole gale sigh street tear sense acknowledgement sin,god: 0.5; land: 0.5; lord: 0.5; king: 0.5; time: 0.5; jesus: 0.5; christ: 0.4; london: 0.3; adversary: 0.25; way: 0.2; life: 0.2; isa: 0.2; people: 0.2; kingdom: 0.15; day: 0.05; whole: 0.05,"('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 5; ('London', 'GPE'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Robert', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Warwick', 'GPE'): 2; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('74.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Machiavelli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leth•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('docto•rs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.2 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.2 preach', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('remorseles•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Samuel Clark', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bennet Fink', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isa. 49. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa.', 'DATE'): 1; ('praecepta', 'NORP'): 1; ('William Wilson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1650', 'DATE'): 1; ('aetatis', 'ORG'): 1; ('50o', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seese', 'NORP'): 1; ('earl of', 'PERSON'): 1; ('above twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'DATE'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the great day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 17', 'DATE'): 1"
A79904,36,C. BRETTERG portrait Katherine Bretterg life mrs. Katherine Bretterg KAtherine,god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; time: 0.5; joy: 0.5; husband: 0.5; self: 0.5; mercy: 0.45; bless: 0.45; soul: 0.4; life: 0.25; heart: 0.2; day: 0.15; sin: 0.1,"('thou', 'GPE'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Katherine Bretterg', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1601', 'DATE'): 2; ('John Bruen', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('KAtherine Bretterg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cheshire', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bruen-Stapleford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hanah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about twenty year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('William Bretterg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bretterghold', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lancashire', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leverpool', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('eight chapter', 'TIME'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('about two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abba', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'LOC'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('a little season', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('136', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('William Harrison', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('anno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('her age 22', 'DATE'): 1"
A78514,14,CHAP. assyrian idolatry nation worship sun assyrian idolatry Egypt Israelite,sun: 0.5; god: 0.5; day: 0.5; saint: 0.5; worship: 0.5; planet: 0.5; call: 0.35; time: 0.35; priest: 0.3; name: 0.3; temple: 0.2; idol: 0.15; man: 0.15; idolatry: 0.1; belus: 0.05; heathen: 0.05,"('assyrian', 'NORP'): 12; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 9; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('the day', 'DATE'): 9; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 7; ('Nimrod', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 5; ('Belus', 'PRODUCT'): 5; ('Assyria', 'GPE'): 5; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Boëmus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Pantheon', 'ORG'): 4; ('Nic', 'PERSON'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Macrob', 'ORG'): 4; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 3; ('Shinar', 'GPE'): 3; ('Saturnus Babylonicus', 'FAC'): 3; ('Saturn', 'PRODUCT'): 3; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jo', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Chaldea', 'GPE'): 3; ('Berecynthia', 'PERSON'): 3; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 3; ('43.13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 2; ('11', 'DATE'): 2; ('Ashur', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Niniveh', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Semiramis', 'ORG'): 2; ('Ninus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Caelius phoenix Ogyges', 'ORG'): 2; ('Clav', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 2; ('sphaer', 'GPE'): 2; ('his day', 'DATE'): 2; ('the day of their week', 'DATE'): 2; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 2; ('Boniface', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Diana', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Juno', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Vesta', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 2; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Phoebus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Dux', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ezech', 'ORG'): 2; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Macrobius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 2; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Bassianus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Pantheus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Nimrod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Juno Guevar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aethiopia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Saturnus Aegyptius', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Jupiter Mizraim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erech', 'NORP'): 1; ('Calneh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.9', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jupiter Belus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rehoboth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rezen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Niniveh', 'ORG'): 1; ('mihi pater', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Proavus', 'LOC'): 1; ('ab avo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Patre', 'ORG'): 1; ('columnam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Templum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Belo Socero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rheae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Olympo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Guevara ep .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('don Fra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Guevara', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Saturnus Aegyptiacus', 'ORG'): 1; ('a hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('six and fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two and sixty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rhea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Olympia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Fascicul', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bell', 'ORG'): 1; ('Baal', 'GPE'): 1; ('Beelphegor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Beelzebub', 'ORG'): 1; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antiq', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('de Sphae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hammond', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Maimonides', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Henoch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Methusalah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heber', 'DATE'): 1; ('Maimon Maimor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('primo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Moses day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nabuchadnezzar', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('magi', 'NORP'): 1; ('Josephus de Antiq', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rudolph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('P. Rami', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Geom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('prooemio', 'GPE'): 1; ('about six hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anaximander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Melisius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thales Milisius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eudoxus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chaldee Clavius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Shinar', 'LOC'): 1; ('Assyrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 1; ('203', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day of the month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peter day', 'DATE'): 1; ('James day', 'PERSON'): 1; ('what day of the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day of the moon', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day of', 'DATE'): 1; ('the first hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('the first hour of the day', 'TIME'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('next Saturn', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven day', 'DATE'): 1; ('venerem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mercurium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoniam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sortiti futura', 'PERSON'): 1; ('adeò persuasum habuerunt', 'ORG'): 1; ('ista astrauno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ubi de Assyria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Venus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Venus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Verstegan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Verstegan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sunday , Monday', 'DATE'): 1; ('tuescoes day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Woodensday', 'GPE'): 1; ('Frigaesday', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saturday', 'DATE'): 1; ('this hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('weekday , Monday , Tuesday , Wednesday , Thursday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Norse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Woden', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('all-saint day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Beatae Mariae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. de Civit', 'DATE'): 1; ('dei l. 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bonifacius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christiani', 'NORP'): 1; ('fiat', 'ORG'): 1; ('ʋbienim impii', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christiani', 'ORG'): 1; ('Festum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bonifacio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Samos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thebes', 'ORG'): 1; ('St James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dionysius', 'GPE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Andrew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bellona', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cunina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Segetia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Forculus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rumbal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anthony', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('George', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vesta', 'ORG'): 1; ('Atys Tho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vallois', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Galli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trivethiccis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Atys', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1155', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Andr', 'ORG'): 1; ('Controv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lyranus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ezechiel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezec', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day of the week be first', 'DATE'): 1; ('Je. de Sacr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day of the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Praepa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phoebe', 'GPE'): 1; ('Delia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cynthius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cynthia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Titan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Titania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Janus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Iana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nigidius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('decoris cansâ apponitur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Macrobius Macro', 'ORG'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter , Iames ,', 'ORG'): 1; ('Magdalene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('their day', 'DATE'): 1; ('8.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.13 .', 'DATE'): 1; ('65.757', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zeph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.13.32', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Diversae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('solis nomina', 'ORG'): 1; ('9.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('mar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('errantibus', 'GPE'): 1; ('ipsarum vero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Macrob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 1•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sol ipse de quo vitam omnia mutuantur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timaeo', 'GPE'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cor coeli', 'ORG'): 1; ('Priscas', 'GPE'): 1; ('quod mortalium mente', 'PERSON'): 1; ('venerationem alliceret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pertraherétque magìs', 'ORG'): 1; ('Glos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('g•n', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sicul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ant.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sozoman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simeon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Seleucia s•z•m', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ʋsthazar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saboris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Simeon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Saboris', 'NORP'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 1; ('Irshemesh', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacob be Potipherah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Asenath', 'ORG'): 1; ('41.45', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Potipherah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heliogabalus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aurelius Antonius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Severus Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexianus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Imper', 'ORG'): 1; ('Helingabalus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heliogabalus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ʋrania', 'GPE'): 1; ('herodian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Heliogabalus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pallas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Otreus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hecuba', 'GPE'): 1; ('Augnstine', 'ORG'): 1; ('dei l. 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Otriades', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aencid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Hom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iliad', 'GPE'): 1; ('de legih', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Boniface', 'GPE'): 1; ('chapter 9', 'LAW'): 1; ('Romani', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dydimaei Apollinis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sacarn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Massagethites', 'GPE'): 1; ('scythian', 'NORP'): 1; ('pecoribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('ubi de Scythia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ethiopian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tartar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ely', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theophilus Brabourne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('197', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A78514,19,CHAP. Xiv objection antiquity week answer government planet feign publish,planet: 0.5; day: 0.5; name: 0.5; week: 0.5; government: 0.5; time: 0.5; weekday: 0.5; rule: 0.5; hour: 0.45; god: 0.45; knowledge: 0.1,"('hourly', 'TIME'): 25; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 8; ('the first hour', 'TIME'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Eudoxus', 'ORG'): 8; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 8; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Saturday', 'DATE'): 7; ('christian', 'NORP'): 6; ('week', 'DATE'): 5; ('no week', 'DATE'): 5; ('that day', 'DATE'): 5; ('the first hour of the day', 'TIME'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('the day', 'DATE'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 4; ('the day of the week', 'DATE'): 4; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Friday', 'DATE'): 4; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 4; ('sabbathday', 'DATE'): 3; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 3; ('weekday', 'DATE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 3; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Sylvester', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the seven day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 2; ('persian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Egyptians', 'NORP'): 2; ('the week day', 'DATE'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Assyria', 'GPE'): 2; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Heylin', 'ORG'): 2; ('Heyl', 'ORG'): 2; ('Saturn', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Henricus Hassianus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 2; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 2; ('America', 'GPE'): 2; ('grecian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Tuisco', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Chaldea', 'GPE'): 2; ('Feria', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Cynthia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mercurius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Venus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mars', 'LOC'): 1; ('Jove', 'GPE'): 1; ('Satur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ordine', 'NORP'): 1; ('sibi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Heylin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('each day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Heyl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('assyrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('persian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'LOC'): 1; ('the week before', 'DATE'): 1; ('the week and the day of the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dionysius Exiguus', 'ORG'): 1; ('about the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Plato', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Macrob', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scip', 'GPE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plut.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('brev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Decr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aristarcus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Copernicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('sequitur ultima luna subest', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Macrob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clav', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de sphaera page', 'PERSON'): 1; ('his hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('the frst hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('seven day', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven day to the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joseph Anti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thousand of year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Friday , Saturday and', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Turks', 'NORP'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the selfsame day', 'DATE'): 1; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('48', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('have week', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vienna', 'GPE'): 1; ('four hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('dutch', 'NORP'): 1; ('Theodore Bibliander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Verstegan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tuisco', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aschenaz', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sarmatia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dutchman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Teutshen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Terra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arezia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bibliander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Shinar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antiq', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Verstegan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the first day of the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('the second day of the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nomina gentes', 'ORG'): 1; ('diebus', 'ORG'): 1; ('every day of the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Feriae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heylin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Polydore Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sylvester Romanus Pontifex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('memoriam', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Inv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Feriae Heyl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dr heylin', 'ORG'): 1"
A76805,4 | 5931,remainder light world sun moon star thing sun fire default,fire: 0.5; heaven: 0.5; sun: 0.5; day: 0.5; thing: 0.5; man: 0.5; light: 0.5; earth: 0.5; god: 0.3; star: 0.3; self: 0.3; water: 0.1,"('four', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('thou', 'GPE'): 4; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Leviticus', 'GPE'): 3; ('the three day', 'DATE'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('four day', 'DATE'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Timaeus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('six day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Zohar', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'DATE'): 2; ('Evangelist', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jeremie', 'PERSON'): 2; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 2; ('aqua', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the first day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the four day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the second day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'LOC'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eliezer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Merchavah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chomah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scemesch', 'NORP'): 1; ('Maor', 'NORP'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jareha', 'GPE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('a month', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a perpetual day', 'DATE'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('shine sun', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orpheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aurora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the four season', 'DATE'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Homil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the 43', 'DATE'): 1; ('Easie 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 3', 'LAW'): 1; ('Leviticus 2', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nadab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abihu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the 32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Deut', 'GPE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simeon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('the quintess•nces of Raimund Lullius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rupescissa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ʋlstadius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pica de mirandula', 'ORG'): 1; ('Astrolog•', 'ORG'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('147', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gen.', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cratylus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('115', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heron', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gerfalcon', 'GPE'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('pour thereon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paracelsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salt-Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Beuvois', 'GPE'): 1; ('Estiomenes', 'NORP'): 1; ('Raimund Lullius', 'ORG'): 1; ('one minute of a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('harden', 'GPE'): 1"
A63269,10,unfold mystery covenant grace make cordial soul promise life comfort,god: 0.5; scripture: 0.5; lord: 0.5; soul: 0.5; word: 0.5; christ: 0.45; bless: 0.35; read: 0.35; heart: 0.3; book: 0.25; heaven: 0.2; spirit: 0.2; death: 0.15; joy: 0.1; world: 0.05; comfort: 0.05; thing: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 14; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Alipius', 'ORG'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('this hour', 'TIME'): 2; ('tolle', 'GPE'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Goliath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('allis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aurea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('119.50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('51', 'DATE'): 1; ('92', 'DATE'): 1; ('Thessalonica', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ Estrangements', 'ORG'): 1; ('flagon', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tom 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antonius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bilney', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alice Benden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine week', 'DATE'): 1; ('a night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Midgeley', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Yorkshire', 'GPE'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Katherine Brettergh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('at least eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('will', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('i than thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 17', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('John holland', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Leigh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Selah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('about five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('summer|be - evening', 'FAC'): 1; ('sunshine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('from night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Eliah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('139.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 4.11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('25.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty , thirty', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('a hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('16.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('no few than five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a season', 'DATE'): 1; ('six and', 'TIME'): 1; ('14.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('89.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('13.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Absalon', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('84.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A61807,8 | 6431,thing deliver define declare canon council council Trent salvation article,council: 0.5; faith: 0.5; church: 0.5; trent: 0.5; article: 0.5; decree: 0.5; man: 0.3; define: 0.3; believe: 0.25; proposition: 0.2; pope: 0.2; canon: 0.2; contrary: 0.15; sess: 0.1; canus: 0.05; rule: 0.05; mention: 0.05; definition: 0.05; anathema: 0.05; make: 0.05,"('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 14; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('R. H.', 'PERSON'): 6; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Trent', 'LOC'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('Pius IV.', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the Trent council', 'ORG'): 3; ('Canus', 'LOC'): 3; ('Canus', 'FAC'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('194', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('§', 'NORP'): 2; ('192', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Concilii', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('quam Nemo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('general council', 'ORG'): 1; ('the 12th', 'DATE'): 1; ('1200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('186', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ibid', 'ORG'): 1; ('ea quidem manifesta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anathematismos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sin', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam aliquando Apostolus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Synodus', 'NORP'): 1; ('appellari', 'ORG'): 1; ('siquis autem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sess', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eos', 'ORG'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('Quarta', 'ORG'): 1; ('proprie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('firmiter credendum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catholicam de justification', 'ORG'): 1; ('Doctrinam', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam nisi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('justificari non poterit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pontificum', 'LOC'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romanist', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sess', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('quae de poenitentiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sacramentis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oecumenica Synodus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('credenda', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('nihil horum dicunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. a. c', 'PERSON'): 1; ('R. H. Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cassander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wicelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('cajetan', 'GPE'): 1; ('R. H. S. 192', 'PERSON'): 1; ('british', 'NORP'): 1; ('Asaph', 'ORG'): 1; ('R. H. S. 193.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Laity', 'ORG'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gelasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 c .', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet , council', 'ORG'): 1; ('Episcop', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pius IV.', 'ORG'): 1; ('R.', 'NORP'): 1; ('quam Nemo Salvus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. 194', 'ORG'): 1; ('Super Pet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calicis Sess', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johannes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Moronus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ludovicus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Simoneta', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tridentini', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Julio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the holy council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Oecumenicis Conciliis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tridentina', 'NORP'): 1; ('contraria', 'GPE'): 1; ('haerese', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('ego pariter damno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rejicio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hanc veram catholicam fidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('195', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Constance Sess', 'ORG'): 1; ('Basil Sess', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of Florence Sess', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lateran V. Sess', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('72', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('198', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1; ('no more than three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mass.', 'GPE'): 1; ('the council of Florence', 'ORG'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Caranza', 'ORG'): 1; ('Armenians', 'NORP'): 1; ('873', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('874', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1633', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lateran', 'GPE'): 1; ('a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('about half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Pius V.', 'PERSON'): 1"
A69617,3,argvment premvnire mr. speaker order house day penalty clergy cannon,law: 0.5; king: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; cannon: 0.5; praemunire: 0.5; court: 0.5; england: 0.45; edw: 0.45; commission: 0.4; clergy: 0.2; church: 0.15; cap: 0.15; case: 0.15; hen: 0.05,"('England', 'GPE'): 28; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 23; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 18; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 12; ('Stat', 'ORG'): 12; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Norwich', 'PERSON'): 7; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('James', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('William Sawtree', 'PERSON'): 4; ('speaker', 'PERSON'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('York', 'GPE'): 3; ('Eliz', 'PERSON'): 3; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 3; ('Martyrum', 'GPE'): 3; ('the king commission', 'ORG'): 3; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1o', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('finis', 'NORP'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('152', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Fineux', 'ORG'): 2; ('Romanas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ed', 'PERSON'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Fitz', 'ORG'): 2; ('Exeter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('those day', 'DATE'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('D.', 'NORP'): 2; ('32', 'DATE'): 2; ('Thetford', 'GPE'): 2; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 2; ('Oxford', 'GPE'): 2; ('Woolsey', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Mich.', 'GPE'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 2; ('Doct', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Avignion', 'ORG'): 2; ('Bonony', 'ORG'): 2; ('Stephen Gardiner', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Winchester', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Anthony Mildmay', 'PERSON'): 2; ('march 2. 1640', 'DATE'): 1; ('their late convention', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Deanes', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('omnis rei', 'ORG'): 1; ('J. D. and', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sint', 'ORG'): 1; ('nobis de contemptu', 'ORG'): 1; ('Coronae', 'ORG'): 1; ('premoniti', 'ORG'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Richard 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Statutes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1607', 'DATE'): 1; ('priset', 'ORG'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ley denglitre', 'FAC'): 1; ('est foundu sur le ley de dieu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('ley de tre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ley de dieu sont', 'ORG'): 1; ('H. 8.191 Kell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('un', 'ORG'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('about 169', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Elutherius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Habetis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lambert', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hagar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1150', 'DATE'): 1; ('Steph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gratian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ember-day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the rogation week', 'DATE'): 1; ('Stephen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Roger bacon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rex Stephanus', 'GPE'): 1; ('legibus Italiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('the three and sixth year', 'DATE'): 1; ('N. B. 40', 'PERSON'): 1; ('agatis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lawneston', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cornwall', 'GPE'): 1; ('Roger Loveday', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Walter de Wyburne', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non sunt de Testamento', 'ORG'): 1; ('Matrimonio', 'GPE'): 1; ('lasionem Coronae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('depauperationem manifestam quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ulterius', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Par', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Durhams', 'GPE'): 1; ('William Willicon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Rowman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Durham', 'GPE'): 1; ('agatis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('4000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marks', 'ORG'): 1; ('the end of the 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('Westm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Shimei', 'ORG'): 1; ('2 kin', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('5o', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('N. Br', 'PERSON'): 1; ('152.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6 . 11o', 'DATE'): 1; ('12 .', 'DATE'): 1; ('44o', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('foe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36o .', 'DATE'): 1; ('15o', 'DATE'): 1; ('Edw. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('saint lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1609', 'DATE'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trespass•', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('magna charta be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('rege Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Richard Cockerall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trin', 'GPE'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anthony Buckley', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bangor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Whorewood', 'ORG'): 1; ('John ap Hugh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hoell', 'ORG'): 1; ('William Bateman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Edmundsbury', 'ORG'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de Heretico', 'GPE'): 1; ('N. B. foe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('170', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Margaret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas Arundel archbishop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pembroke - Hall', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ridley', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Bradford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pembroke', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Kell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('181', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Standish', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Roy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ang', 'ORG'): 1; ('legibus civilibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('100000', 'DATE'): 1; ('18840', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hampton', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 Car', 'TIME'): 1; ('a year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('20.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Edw', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. third', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jaco', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Contrariorum', 'GPE'): 1; ('excommunicantur', 'NORP'): 1; ('illi qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('de paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sheriff•', 'ORG'): 1; ('sva duritia', 'FAC'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('silva caedua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('B. Prem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('romana aut alibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('N. B.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('romana', 'GPE'): 1; ('christianitatis', 'GPE'): 1; ('430', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('I. R. machinans', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cognitionem quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('curiam domini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('153', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 1; ('Audley', 'ORG'): 1; ('1637', 'DATE'): 1; ('12o', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('maij last', 'PERSON'): 1; ('simulata sanctitas duplex iniquitas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tiptofts', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anthony', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14o', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23o', 'DATE'): 1; ('Carliel', 'GPE'): 1; ('25o', 'DATE'): 1; ('3 . 25o', 'DATE'): 1; ('8.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.37 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 1o', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cawdry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('potestas ordinis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Canonnico', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lettany', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arminians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paulinae Synodus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('integer aeger', 'PERSON'): 1"
A63318,30,salutation breathe life life spirit measure sufferer seed sake glory,life: 0.5; lord: 0.5; god: 0.5; dear: 0.5; heart: 0.5; glory: 0.5; power: 0.35; truth: 0.35; father: 0.25; bless: 0.25; love: 0.2; lamb: 0.15; name: 0.1; peace: 0.1; spirit: 0.1; wisdom: 0.05; light: 0.05; seed: 0.05,"('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('C. l', 'ORG'): 1; ('Daniel baker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sarah Cheevers', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this 11th', 'DATE'): 1; ('month of the year , 1661', 'DATE'): 1; ('this the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Immanuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('livi•g', 'ORG'): 1; ('D. B. Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Benjamin', 'ORG'): 1; ('this 5th day of the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('the 30th', 'DATE'): 1; ('11th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('1661', 'DATE'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('truth|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('the mighty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the ancient day', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A67626,13,matter concernment right guide conversation self nature dream concernment self,god: 0.5; dream: 0.5; thing: 0.5; evil: 0.5; man: 0.5; lessius: 0.5; spirit: 0.45; mind: 0.45; self: 0.35; angel: 0.35; gen: 0.35; matter: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Lessius', 'PERSON'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Lessius', 'ORG'): 5; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Sanderson', 'PERSON'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lessius de justitiâ l. 2', 'ORG'): 2; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('40', 'DATE'): 2; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('31.10', 'MONEY'): 2; ('16.9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('circa divinationem', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Quakers', 'GPE'): 2; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13.1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Casaub', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Enthus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Casaub', 'ORG'): 2; ('1.8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8.19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jackson', 'PERSON'): 2; ('34.1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('impart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('immittit', 'NORP'): 1; ('nisi ad aliquid significandum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mat 1.20 Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'DATE'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('41', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Judg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.24', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Balaam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abimelech', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laban', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacob', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharaoh , Nabuchadnezzar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharaohs Baker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil agere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('aliter enim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Filliucus Quaest', 'ORG'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('124', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baldwinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Baldwin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('quando', 'PERSON'): 1; ('certo', 'NORP'): 1; ('Coelius Rhodig', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Virgil', 'GPE'): 1; ('Galen de praesagio', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('libidinem', 'GPE'): 1; ('putrid', 'GPE'): 1; ('Galen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Latines', 'ORG'): 1; ('Galen l. 3. de lco', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('twofold', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Job 33.15', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('17 16.17', 'DATE'): 1; ('nam vel omnibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baldw', 'GPE'): 1; ('vel nullis fidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baldwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Filliucius Quaest', 'ORG'): 1; ('121', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dvo necessaria', 'ORG'): 1; ('Enthusias', 'NORP'): 1; ('18.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('non licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seu', 'ORG'): 1; ('cognitionem desiderare per somnia', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi urgen', 'ORG'): 1; ('ratio occurrat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel nisi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('29.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Casaubon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lessius de justitiâ', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('20.6', 'MONEY'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Joel 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de eventis', 'GPE'): 1; ('sixthly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 Gal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gespel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.1', 'DATE'): 1; ('nineth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1"
A67626,16,blessing matter world guide providence God misery mischief seed occurrence,god: 0.5; book: 0.5; word: 0.5; people: 0.5; providence: 0.5; place: 0.5; matter: 0.3; psalm: 0.25; day: 0.25; soul: 0.25; time: 0.2; verse: 0.2; open: 0.2; read: 0.15; saint: 0.15; origen: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('l. 8', 'PERSON'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19.21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13.13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 2; ('Pencerus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Adrian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Sulpitius Severus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sulpit', 'GPE'): 1; ('Martini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Turonica', 'GPE'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('laudem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antonius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tolle', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euseb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Planctus Origen', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('ego vero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('infaelix ante', 'PERSON'): 1; ('diluculum de strato', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('quidem', 'GPE'): 1; ('cognitionem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Diaboli', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('that morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Blackmore', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Ps', 'ORG'): 1; ('50.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Planctus seu', 'ORG'): 1; ('Origenis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Maceriam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('coactus', 'ORG'): 1; ('dixit deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Franciscus Junius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tremelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Enthus', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pencerus de divination', 'ORG'): 1; ('Virgilianae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Helius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Helius Spartianus', 'ORG'): 1; ('procul ille autem', 'ORG'): 1; ('ramis', 'ORG'): 1; ('olivae sacra ferens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nosco crines incana', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romani', 'NORP'): 1; ('legibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Missus', 'PERSON'): 1"
A68951,47,saint Stephen calf idol purpose S. HIEROM idol image deadman,image: 0.5; god: 0.5; church: 0.5; place: 0.5; picture: 0.5; man: 0.5; idol: 0.45; make: 0.35; cherub: 0.3; wall: 0.3; temple: 0.3; nature: 0.1; form: 0.1; thing: 0.1,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('IESVS', 'ORG'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Salomons', 'NORP'): 2; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 2; ('Stephen', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. HIEROM', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deadman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ELIBERIS', 'ORG'): 1; ('EPIPHANIVS', 'ORG'): 1; ('LACTANTIVS Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cont', 'GPE'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Abraham Genes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Segnius', 'ORG'): 1; ('animos demissa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('TERTVLLIAN', 'GPE'): 1; ('SOZOMENVS', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Gregory NAZ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('Diocesaraea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orat', 'GPE'): 1; ('Barlaam', 'GPE'): 1; ('DAMASVS', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. John LATERAN', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. CHRYSOSTOME', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Aug', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('the council of ELIBERIS cap', 'ORG'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty five', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A63066,15,CHAP. Vii verse thing Zerubbabel altar temple Ezra notation name,god: 0.45; verse: 0.45; king: 0.45; man: 0.45; ezra: 0.45; lord: 0.45; law: 0.45; son: 0.35; priest: 0.3; people: 0.3; thing: 0.15; service: 0.1; hand: 0.1; emperor: 0.05; practice: 0.05; preferment: 0.05; polit: 0.05; polity: 0.05; pomegranate: 0.05; place: 0.05; precept: 0.05; prevent: 0.05; prepare: 0.05; pinchpenny: 0.05,"('Ezra', 'PERSON'): 13; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 5; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 3; ('Nehem', 'GPE'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Seraiah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('9', 'DATE'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tiberius', 'ORG'): 2; ('chapter 5.11', 'LAW'): 2; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ho', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 2; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Zerubbabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Artaxerxes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Esters', 'ORG'): 1; ('thirteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('8.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Meraioth ]', 'ORG'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zeraiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paterc', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 1; ('Chaldea', 'GPE'): 1; ('straminea candelam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Varro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Albertus', 'NORP'): 1; ('quem nihil', 'ORG'): 1; ('penitùs fugit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bonosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abulensis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('persian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Magi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Druides', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Brachmanni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sapientes sapientèr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.20 , Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('45.12', 'MONEY'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Moses , Gal', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('medicina', 'GPE'): 1; ('jehovae cor patrium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylon ,', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 2.43', 'LAW'): 1; ('the five month', 'DATE'): 1; ('four month', 'DATE'): 1; ('popish pilgrim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('holy Ezra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eliezer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'MONEY'): 1; ('1 Sam 7.3', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('11.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amos 4.12', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nucem frangat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diogenes', 'ORG'): 1; ('benè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lilmod lelam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Esth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scriba', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Valentinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Kings', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Easie 10.8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Maximilian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joban', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Manl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('loc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('586', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jaddus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Albion', 'GPE'): 1; ('110.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Easie 56.6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ambros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xerxes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Val', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Max', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 c . 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Esther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexander Severus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mammaea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hanani', 'NORP'): 1; ('7.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tully', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Morocco', 'GPE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quod ego volo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paulinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('16.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arist', 'ORG'): 1; ('polit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('magna charta', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter 14', 'LAW'): 1; ('47.22', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Jezabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Levite', 'FAC'): 1; ('tempora mutantur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou Ezra ] qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('17.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Obediemus Atridis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mandan•ibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('non alitèr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iphigenia', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('leo Modena', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A63066,16,CHAP. Viii verse chief father chieftain Ezra Zerubbabel verse son,verse: 0.5; god: 0.5; son: 0.5; man: 0.5; king: 0.5; prayer: 0.5; heb: 0.4; name: 0.35; day: 0.35; psal: 0.2; work: 0.2; word: 0.2; sin: 0.1; hand: 0.1; chap: 0.05; servant: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Ezra', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Zerubbabel', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Neh', 'PERSON'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Sherebiah', 'PERSON'): 3; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('24.20', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Adonikam', 'ORG'): 2; ('2.13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Levites', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'DATE'): 2; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 2; ('38', 'DATE'): 2; ('15.2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Phineas', 'NORP'): 1; ('Eleazar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred and fifty', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pahath-Moab', 'ORG'): 1; ('Moab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jahaziel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lucet pagina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesbaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Emmanuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jehiel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zechariah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nehem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Josiphiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bebai', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eposteris', 'NORP'): 1; ('posterioribus Tremel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('rari quip', 'ORG'): 1; ('numero vix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quot Thebarum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel divitis ostia Nili', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sat. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('137.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Casiphia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iddo', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sherebiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('8.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hashabiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joshuah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three-fold', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('58.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('119.46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Basil , Latimer', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lambert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Colet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pauls', 'GPE'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tournay', 'FAC'): 1; ('Clark', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deane', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('holy Ezra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('73.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('viribus ira', 'ORG'): 1; ('90.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jam. 4 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.3', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('20.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('55.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('73.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rachel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sauls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hoshabiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trustees', 'ORG'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six hundred and fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('243750 pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37500 pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('312 pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('auro contrâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Esa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mecha', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mahomet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aug. Adversus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tu non crede malis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('clark live', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Q. Mary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oxford', 'GPE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('paer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gideons', 'LAW'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.74.75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119.91', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('56.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.5', 'DATE'): 1"
A63066,17,CHAP. verse thing gaudia heaven joy mixture life overspread sin,god: 0.5; sin: 0.5; verse: 0.5; psal: 0.5; mercy: 0.5; heaven: 0.5; lord: 0.5; hand: 0.45; people: 0.3; iniquity: 0.25; self: 0.2; ezra: 0.15; see: 0.05; day: 0.05; man: 0.05,"('Psal', 'PERSON'): 12; ('Ezra', 'PERSON'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 5; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('evening', 'TIME'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('winter', 'DATE'): 2; ('136', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Q. Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 2; ('maxima', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('infelix', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.18.23', 'DATE'): 1; ('59.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nehem', 'GPE'): 1; ('13.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Malachi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 2.11', 'LAW'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lycophron', 'ORG'): 1; ('quartan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simonides', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.6 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pluck •ff', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scodra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('143.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bradford', 'GPE'): 1; ('6.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('73.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peters', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ult', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter 30.16', 'LAW'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Illum', 'ORG'): 1; ('dico', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter 9.5', 'LAW'): 1; ('124.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('99', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.10', 'MONEY'): 1; ('18.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 1.9 .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('totius substantiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sisera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pliny', 'ORG'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('34.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('104.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('indian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('26.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('23.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('119.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.8 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sparta', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quintilian', 'NORP'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('sit simplex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('humilis confessio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('verecunda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Integra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lachrymabilis , accelerata', 'ORG'): 1; ('accusans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mar. 7.23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ascham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('nine year', 'DATE'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.21', 'DATE'): 1; ('jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mich. 1.5', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canaanite', 'GPE'): 1; ('conteratur', 'GPE'): 1; ('thrice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Buxtorf', 'ORG'): 1; ('Polony', 'GPE'): 1; ('13.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('103.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('112.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cautional', 'ORG'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui fidem amisit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hominem agnoscit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('40.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('shun', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('senacherib', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pharaohs', 'LOC'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('32.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A63066,18,CHAP. verse Ezra pray present suppliant cause God judge appeal,god: 0.5; verse: 0.5; heart: 0.5; man: 0.5; sin: 0.5; son: 0.5; day: 0.45; ezra: 0.45; house: 0.45; child: 0.2; wife: 0.15; head: 0.1; work: 0.1; father: 0.05; repentance: 0.05,"('Ezra', 'PERSON'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Shechaniah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Eli', 'ORG'): 2; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 2; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Bavaria', 'GPE'): 2; ('x. verse 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anashim', 'ORG'): 1; ('Venashim', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bechi•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jehiel ]', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Easie ◊ Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehiel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 26', 'DATE'): 1; ('Theodoret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui nil sperare potest', 'PERSON'): 1; ('desperet nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('50.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('perad', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hannah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vicenza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Signor Conte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('earl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('chapter 9.2', 'LAW'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mantuan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 7.10', 'LAW'): 1; ('Bucer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Diazius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alphonsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ego verò illius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('arise Ezra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Shecaniah', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Galeacius Caracciolus', 'ORG'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Staupicius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erford', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clark', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Levite', 'FAC'): 1; ('7.35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('28.20', 'MONEY'): 1; ('31.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119.106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johanan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Turks', 'NORP'): 1; ('Zant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nequitiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('crimina', 'GPE'): 1; ('jura', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sanhedrin', 'NORP'): 1; ('chapter 23.12', 'LAW'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a whole day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Stellae', 'GPE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Draco', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cainites', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.16', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Beelzebub', 'ORG'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('from day to day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the nine month', 'DATE'): 1; ('the month of may', 'DATE'): 1; ('Diodate', 'PERSON'): 1; ('September', 'DATE'): 1; ('Esth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the accustom season', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('December', 'DATE'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('latin Hiems', 'NORP'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('conscientia svi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter 9.6', 'LAW'): 1; ('11.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('62.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vomitus sordiū', 'ORG'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('28.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a few year', 'DATE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Laelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('jussa sequi tàm velle mihi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nulli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Easie 55.7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sanedrim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abimelech', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gideons 70', 'LAW'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jonathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Asahel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('honorabiles fecit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Clerus Britannicus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cleri', 'GPE'): 1; ('Campian', 'NORP'): 1; ('ministris eorum nihil', 'LOC'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the first day of the first month', 'DATE'): 1; ('full three month', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caligula', 'GPE'): 1; ('Germanici', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Belial', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cesar Borgia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Valence', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Petro Alingi Farnesis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cosmus Chaerius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fanum', 'GPE'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('George Carpenters', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Munchen', 'GPE'): 1; ('806', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bonner', 'PERSON'): 1"
A63066,21,grieve aliud trudit sorrow another Christians faith patience exercise multitude,king: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; verse: 0.5; word: 0.5; time: 0.5; nehemiah: 0.45; place: 0.4; another: 0.3; thing: 0.25; house: 0.15; gate: 0.1; church: 0.1; call: 0.1; jew: 0.05; heart: 0.05; prayer: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Nehemiah', 'PERSON'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 5; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 5; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 3; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 3; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('chapter 5.14', 'LAW'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 2; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the night', 'TIME'): 2; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('94.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('55.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Squier', 'ORG'): 1; ('1597', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesuite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 1; ('527', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bourbon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Angelo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wolsey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1027', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('137', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leo Moden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zecher Lechorban', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nebridius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Terence', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Valens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Arian', 'NORP'): 1; ('l. c', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('crebras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hannah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Darius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.5', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ipse aspectus viri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve year', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('epit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('114', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('keeper', 'PERSON'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezra 7.6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Saddeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Phoenicia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Naaman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('48.3', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22.3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amorites', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tobiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Asperius', 'ORG'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jewesses', 'ORG'): 1; ('Visier', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('bassa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Voy• P. 114', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Avicen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Porphyrius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Aetna', 'ORG'): 1; ('Siculi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27.4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Actius Sincerus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frederike', 'ORG'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezra 8.32', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Homer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui sapit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehoshaphat', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Portam Galilae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Golgotha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Siloe', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isa', 'GPE'): 1; ('8.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cedron', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Siloah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rogel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('136.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scaligers', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scaligeri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scaligers', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'GPE'): 1; ('eâdem', 'GPE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('poenitenda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui proferenda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry', 'GPE'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('manibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('paucis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tully', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Brutus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('B. Pilkington', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pyrites', 'ORG'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Horonite', 'NORP'): 1; ('Geshem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arabia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lewis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hungary', 'GPE'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erasmi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qualem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Capito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('h•b', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11 36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nibil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lipsius , Ʋnicum', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui crimine vacabant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tacit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Virtus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pietas', 'NORP'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('163', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alps', 'LOC'): 1"
