tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A42450,7,sect V. sum end gospel end mark deep quality gospel,god: 0.5; gospel: 0.5; christ: 0.5; faith: 0.5; oath: 0.5; law: 0.5; righteousness: 0.5; man: 0.5; magistrate: 0.5; saviour: 0.25; nature: 0.05; name: 0.05; power: 0.05; lord: 0.05; way: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('••', 'ORG'): 4; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Belial', 'GPE'): 2; ('3. • .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Messiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor 14', 'ORG'): 1; ('Belial', 'ORG'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'ORG'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jonathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('49', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacobs', 'ORG'): 1; ('dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Esa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('59.5', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.11.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('72.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('138.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat •', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.13.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.3 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('das caelestia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1"
A41510,2 | 89,whit touch tincture Christ be head body word head material,sense: 0.5; god: 0.5; word: 0.5; man: 0.5; adversary: 0.5; doctor: 0.5; kendal: 0.5; master: 0.4; say: 0.35; cause: 0.3; perseverance: 0.2; book: 0.1; write: 0.1; doctrine: 0.05,"('Kendal', 'PERSON'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('John Owen', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Owen', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('moon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('17.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('terris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 1; ('Almam matrem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oxoniensem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Campania', 'GPE'): 1; ('a quarter of a hour', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hocus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the noon day', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luther , Calvin , Zuinglius , •elancthon', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Bucer , Pareus , Gualther', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calvin , Musculus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Kendal', 'NORP'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('m•ster Kendal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maledicta glossa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('textum quae vitiat bonum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Irenaeus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nazienzen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('370', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('371', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('372', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('373', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('374', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Gerardus Vossius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Doctot', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pry', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam judicare', 'PERSON'): 1; ('George Kendal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('uncouth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 3.16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'FAC'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('Almam matrem Acad', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oxon', 'PERSON'): 1"
A41510,2 | 98,man genius nonlatinalphabet manage warfare discovery master art way beset,man: 0.5; book: 0.5; truth: 0.5; kendal: 0.5; argument: 0.45; god: 0.4; part: 0.25; mr: 0.25; cause: 0.25; place: 0.2; text: 0.2; hand: 0.2; doctor: 0.2; doctrine: 0.2; scripture: 0.1; thing: 0.1; redemption: 0.1; perseverance: 0.05; sense: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('Kendal', 'PERSON'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Owen', 'PERSON'): 3; ('John Owen', 'PERSON'): 2; ('un', 'ORG'): 2; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul to Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('uncouth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some year', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'DATE'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Messiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('George Kendal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 1; ('Acheron', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dordracene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thrive many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Witchcote', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the university of Cambridge', 'ORG'): 1; ('specie', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('frothy jest', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Crimine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tunies', 'ORG'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('demittitur', 'NORP'): 1; ('notorious pervert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forlese', 'NORP'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('290', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('grace-church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Blissland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bodmin', 'GPE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Justus', 'ORG'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pareus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prophetae', 'ORG'): 1; ('vitam aeternam', 'PERSON'): 1"
A41510,2 | 155,doctor translation mistranslation say gloss another supposition ill ghost viz.,person: 0.5; man: 0.5; word: 0.5; doctor: 0.5; sort: 0.5; god: 0.5; faith: 0.5; apostle: 0.5; apostate: 0.4; soul: 0.15; promise: 0.15; sense: 0.1; place: 0.1; prove: 0.1,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 11; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hebrews', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Styx', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('un', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hebrews', 'ORG'): 1; ('as much brevity', 'MONEY'): 1; ('their month', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('erat', 'NORP'): 1; ('viribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pareus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pareus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apostolus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Prophetae', 'ORG'): 1; ('justitiam fidei stabiliendam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('— sed satis habet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Promissiones', 'NORP'): 1; ('Loc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('361', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('209', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('218', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('221', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('225', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('231', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('258', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('307', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('minuenda', 'GPE'): 1; ('verbatìm', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hebrves', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('438', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'NORP'): 1; ('nomina', 'GPE'): 1; ('numina vana :', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Styga', 'ORG'): 1; ('nomina vana timetis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erebus', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A41510,2 | 181,say error mistake sense text hand see set foot neck,man: 0.5; doctor: 0.5; believer: 0.5; mr: 0.5; word: 0.5; apostle: 0.5; god: 0.5; faith: 0.45; soul: 0.4; save: 0.35; thing: 0.1; covenant: 0.1; cause: 0.05; viz: 0.05,"('lamb', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Owen', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Henry Jeanes', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('debet negligi', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 1; ('a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('digna probatio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Georgius Trapezuntius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aliâ aggrediundum est viâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iphicli', 'NORP'): 1; ('Doctoris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mensâ deturbatam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fig', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paean', 'NORP'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('Norton Fallgate', 'ORG'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('scribimus indocti', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bethleem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bethel Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('proselyte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Henry Jeans', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jeans', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Twiss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1"
A41510,8,blasphemy argument truth God revile blasphemy lightless-starre p. argument deep,doctrine: 0.5; gospel: 0.5; mr: 0.5; man: 0.5; parable: 0.45; resbury: 0.4; error: 0.4; christ: 0.35; say: 0.35; servant: 0.3; talent: 0.25; god: 0.25; pelagius: 0.1; mat: 0.05; pelagianisme: 0.05; minister: 0.05,"('Resbury', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 6; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Pelagianisme', 'ORG'): 4; ('resburies', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jo', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('25.14', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Re•bury', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jacobus Grynaeus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Loc', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anti-Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('Socinianisme , Pelagianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('their day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tenent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pelagian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Socinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pelagio-Socinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Arminius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jericho', 'GPE'): 1; ('Austin', 'GPE'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pelag•us', 'GPE'): 1; ('the council of Palestine', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1631', 'DATE'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elizabeth day', 'DATE'): 1; ('three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ad articulos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pelagianisme', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Faustus Rhegiensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('humanam carnem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sumpsisse', 'GPE'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Orthodoxograph•ae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1503', 'DATE'): 1; ('Faustus', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eli•ah 1', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('18.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Resbury', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten degree low', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('bypast', 'ORG'): 1; ('168', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('169', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('etiam omnes qui sunt', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marloratus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ecclesiasticâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dicuntur negotiari', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calvin Harmon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ita etiam intelligit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('64', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Zaccheus', 'GPE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('uncouth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nempe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('natural•bus', 'ORG'): 1; ('ita etiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marlorat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('marlorat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Talentum', 'ORG'): 1; ('nemini eripitur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('suo vitio illud sepelivit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deodate', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Musculus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Gualther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('illis', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui non sunt vulgaria', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('seqq', 'ORG'): 1; ('quòd rationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('imaginem', 'ORG'): 1; ('similitudinem', 'NORP'): 1; ('Luc', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A41510,9,CHAP. cry clamour mr. resburies pamphlet falsifieation misreport opinion adversary,man: 0.5; conversion: 0.5; god: 0.5; grace: 0.5; self: 0.5; mr: 0.5; birth: 0.5; adversary: 0.45; convert: 0.45; power: 0.35; truth: 0.1; sense: 0.05; say: 0.05; thing: 0.05,"('resburies', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Resburie', 'PERSON'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('175', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Re•burie', 'PERSON'): 2; ('174', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Socinianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pelagianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('176', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('173', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Balak', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 1; ('beor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Moab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('midian depart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Divination•', 'ORG'): 1; ('22.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('178', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('179', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('157', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('182', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('183', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('184', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('transcription', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('adversa•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('que••ion', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam ipsi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. Homil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidem ille ( diabolus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('consil•um', 'GPE'): 1; ('elige•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('omnem hominem', 'ORG'): 1; ('idem d• G•nesi contra Man•chaeos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pelag', 'GPE'): 1; ('proem', 'GPE'): 1; ('frustra blasphemas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ingeris', 'GPE'): 1; ('damnetur ille qui damnat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pelag', 'FAC'): 1; ('163', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1"
A41510,11,CHAP. v. mr. pawsons title sermon vindication grace mr. Pawson,mr: 0.45; pawson: 0.45; grace: 0.45; man: 0.45; kendal: 0.45; truth: 0.4; title: 0.35; part: 0.3; ground: 0.25; thing: 0.2; world: 0.2; sermon: 0.2; god: 0.1; arminius: 0.1; way: 0.1; place: 0.05; piecemeal: 0.05; preferment: 0.05; preach: 0.05; pollution: 0.05; policy: 0.05; poison: 0.05; plead: 0.05; printer: 0.05; piety: 0.05; hand: 0.05,"('Pawson', 'PERSON'): 11; ('Resburie', 'PERSON'): 5; ('pawsons', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Arminius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Arminius', 'ORG'): 3; ('Arminianisme', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('Kendalls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Pawson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maior', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('lizabeths day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('28.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('55.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eleven degree', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Contradictio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('m. Pawson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ad•uncto', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.1', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Resbury', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Oris Cerberei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Echidnae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arminianum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•hat', 'LOC'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Lebanon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rutuli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nilum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heu Regni', 'ORG'): 1; ('Obliti', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bresland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bodmin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cornwall', 'GPE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eph', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pawson', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 4.6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('462', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A41510,13,CHAP. Vii mr. Pawson man justify Christ intention God express,christ: 0.5; mr: 0.5; man: 0.5; pawson: 0.5; word: 0.5; scripture: 0.5; self: 0.5; god: 0.35; elect: 0.35; save: 0.3; gospel: 0.2; text: 0.15; act: 0.1; faith: 0.05,"('Pawson', 'PERSON'): 16; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 11; ('1.4', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 4; ('pawsons', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'DATE'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('462', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Red', 'GPE'): 1; ('Castellio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Malachi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Malachiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aeterno', 'ORG'): 1; ('enim verbum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('loco nihil', 'ORG'): 1; ('odisse decrevi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('neque desunt manifesta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('expositionem confirmemus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('elegit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam certè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'ORG'): 1; ('omne', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('tempora aeterna', 'ORG'): 1; ('gratiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christo Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tempora aeterna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam tamen', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam efficaciter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Praedestin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Contra Seb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('castellionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bezas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('463', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 Joh', 'DATE'): 1; ('192', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('203', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kendalls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('paws•ns', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred to one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Electra', 'ORG'): 1"
A41510,16,CHAP. title mr. Kendalls book error foundation earth Sand. mr.,man: 0.5; book: 0.5; god: 0.5; mr: 0.5; kendal: 0.5; truth: 0.5; doctrine: 0.5; thing: 0.4; kendalls: 0.35; time: 0.3; judgement: 0.25; church: 0.15; say: 0.05,"('Kendalls', 'PERSON'): 13; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 7; ('greek', 'NORP'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('nineteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('x. concern', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sand', 'GPE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Kendall•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Praxiteles', 'NORP'): 1; ('Venus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Agrippa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laban', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacobs', 'ORG'): 1; ('Babel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many day', 'DATE'): 1; ('27.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sand', 'LOC'): 1; ('Lucina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui etiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the reform church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('operari de novo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Respublica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kendalls christian', 'ORG'): 1; ('socinians', 'NORP'): 1; ('arminians', 'NORP'): 1; ('pelagians', 'NORP'): 1; ('inter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aemilius', 'ORG'): 1; ('nobiles quosdam dicebat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae ab', 'ORG'): 1; ('illis', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui legitimo toro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nobiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('haberi nolebant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zuinglius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Scultetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('1526', 'DATE'): 1; ('Caligula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Suetonius', 'ORG'): 1; ('vel quod nunquam per genium suum dejerassent', 'PERSON'): 1; ('debet abesse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezek', 'ORG'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomons', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Metam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fab', 'ORG'): 1; ('aspiciunt oculis superi mortalia justis', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sibi dixerat ipse', 'FAC'): 1; ('bona comparat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('scottish', 'NORP'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hourly', 'TIME'): 1; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('unchristian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Woodden', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A41510,17,CHAP. taste mr. Kendalls forge charge mr. Kendal forge opinion,man: 0.45; god: 0.45; mr: 0.45; adversary: 0.45; kendal: 0.45; thing: 0.45; love: 0.45; prerogative: 0.4; opinion: 0.35; truth: 0.15; person: 0.1; grace: 0.1; sense: 0.05; reader: 0.05; counsel: 0.05; kendalls: 0.05; charge: 0.05; untruth: 0.05; piscator: 0.05; point: 0.05; perpetration: 0.05; phrase: 0.05; pile: 0.05; passage: 0.05; place: 0.05; prejudice: 0.05; praeter: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Kendalls', 'PERSON'): 5; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 4; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Prideaux', 'ORG'): 2; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 2; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Kendalls', 'ORG'): 2; ('xi', 'ORG'): 1; ('volant hyberno grandine plura', 'PERSON'): 1; ('number|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil difficilius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('plurima bona fieri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non nisi', 'NORP'): 1; ('j•ta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('polliceri videntur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam supremum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('moderatorem , de solio suo', 'ORG'): 1; ('aliquando tandem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('faeliciter deturbandum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Semideos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui oculato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet brevi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('121.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('four or five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('274', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Diana Mendacina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('m. Kendalls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('majestatis praerogativae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('artibus plausibilius', 'ORG'): 1; ('august', 'DATE'): 1; ('Battus', 'ORG'): 1; ('illis montibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('yonder mountain', 'PERSON'): 1; ('benigene impertienda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cantabrigiensem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Westmonasteriense', 'GPE'): 1; ('summos totius angliae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Europae Theologos', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bibliorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('nomina', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('venerabum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Calvinum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rezam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paraeum', 'ORG'): 1; ('uspiam extiterint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the university of Cambridge', 'ORG'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paraeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nestor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Menelaus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sun , moon ,', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laverna', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Pulchra Laverna', 'ORG'): 1; ('mihi fallere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('videri', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laverna', 'ORG'): 1; ('cozen', 'GPE'): 1; ('knavish', 'NORP'): 1; ('resburies', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tenent', 'ORG'): 1; ('finxerat esse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('beget hereon', 'PERSON'): 1"
A41510,18,CHAP. Xii interview mr. Kendal principle logic ghost contrary nature,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; mr: 0.5; principle: 0.5; kendal: 0.5; gospel: 0.45; thing: 0.4; world: 0.4; lord: 0.35; ghost: 0.15; death: 0.1; reason: 0.1; logic: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('25', 'DATE'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Agrippa', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('Xii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('God|be', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('forlese', 'NORP'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 1.9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('judam proditorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('adeò quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quantum', 'ORG'): 1; ('generi humano christi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judaeis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Prateol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('uncouth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('seu', 'ORG'): 1; ('potius furfuris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('monstrosae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel eum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quicquam agere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('maximâ eum gloriae svae parte', 'ORG'): 1; ('justitiam sepelit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Opusc', 'GPE'): 1; ('de aeternâ praed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('843', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quenquam vero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nulli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 12.37', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 7.5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 8.46', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 4.48', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fig', 'PERSON'): 1; ('heathens', 'GPE'): 1; ('26.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('7.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1"
A41510,18 | 412,capacity man God wisdom goodness power justice capacity gospel preach,god: 0.5; mr: 0.5; thing: 0.5; foreknowledge: 0.5; kendal: 0.5; man: 0.5; creature: 0.5; knowledge: 0.45; day: 0.35; principle: 0.3; say: 0.3; part: 0.1,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Kendalls', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('seven day', 'DATE'): 4; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the six day', 'DATE'): 2; ('six day', 'DATE'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('no few than five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Kendalls', 'ORG'): 1; ('498', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('499', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('500', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('several year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pawson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('152', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('deplorata colono vota jacent', 'ORG'): 1; ('longi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('anni', 'NORP'): 1; ('the long year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anselm , Aquinas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('know•th', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('92', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('at least forty year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('sundry year', 'DATE'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Deans', 'NORP'): 1; ('93', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('march 10. 1656', 'DATE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('this hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kendal be Ingeniolum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zerviah', 'GPE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ingeniolum', 'ORG'): 1"
A41510,19 | 433,savour demand fellow God faith heart act element faith plant,god: 0.5; kendal: 0.5; state: 0.5; mr: 0.5; man: 0.5; faith: 0.45; religion: 0.45; christian: 0.4; doctrine: 0.35; case: 0.3; providence: 0.3; thing: 0.1; foundation: 0.1; world: 0.05,"('christian', 'NORP'): 15; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the beginning and period', 'DATE'): 2; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 2; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('amici', 'NORP'): 1; ('inimici', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gradus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Fr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixthly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Systeme', 'EVENT'): 1; ('154', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ingeniolum', 'ORG'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('synodians', 'NORP'): 1; ('lie athwart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('generalibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bathsheba', 'GPE'): 1; ('non-suiteth', 'NORP'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 3.16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'FAC'): 1; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 1"
A41510,19 | 456,thing consider clerk mr. Kendal undertake faith reform church matter,mr: 0.5; kendal: 0.5; man: 0.5; self: 0.5; absurdity: 0.5; book: 0.5; exception: 0.45; text: 0.35; observation: 0.35; god: 0.3; scripture: 0.15; necessitate: 0.1; passage: 0.1; discourse: 0.1; part: 0.05; kind: 0.05,"('seventeenth', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Thursday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Friday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aquilino', 'ORG'): 1; ('91', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 3.16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('nick-naming', 'ORG'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thucydides', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nero', 'ORG'): 1; ('neminem hominem pudicum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aut ullâ corporis parte', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zacheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('behold', 'GPE'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nabal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A41510,20,place deny god beginning period man life shake doctrine God,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; mr: 0.5; kendal: 0.5; christ: 0.5; sense: 0.5; word: 0.5; say: 0.5; scripture: 0.45; intention: 0.2; meaning: 0.15; sort: 0.1; place: 0.05; book: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 7; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('king', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 2; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Esai', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the beginning and period', 'DATE'): 1; ('215', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cambridg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('160', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phaenomena', 'ORG'): 1; ('467', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('468', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Reprobis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Piscator contra Schaffman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam si mera vina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Socinus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Arminius', 'ORG'): 1; ('•atissimo godvino', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epist', 'LOC'): 1; ('Acad', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oxon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('49', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50', 'DATE'): 1; ('51', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 1; ('120', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nazianzen', 'LOC'): 1; ('5.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('58.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('45.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('si nullus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quaelibet officio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('apta tuo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('127', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('448', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jezabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thyatira', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Grotius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('divina decreta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam alia vult deus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('alia', 'GPE'): 1; ('vero nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christianorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('quidam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luc', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('546', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('547', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('218', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A41510,21,CHAP. Xiv instance mr. Ks. contradiction death Christ possibility salvation,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; mr: 0.5; word: 0.5; thing: 0.5; part: 0.5; king: 0.5; freedom: 0.4; adversary: 0.35; book: 0.25; ks: 0.2; epistle: 0.1; way: 0.05; say: 0.05; world: 0.05; reader: 0.05,"('king', 'PERSON'): 20; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 5; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 4; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Ingeniolum', 'ORG'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jamjam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('George be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixthly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fourteen', 'DATE'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('verum etiam ostendamus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('potestati omnia aequaliter subjacent', 'ORG'): 1; ('miseriae', 'ORG'): 1; ('convenientiorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. lib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nisi susciperet hominem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nasceretur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aug. de ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cyrill', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leo , Bernard', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi aliter nostrâ causâ visum esset', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('synodians', 'NORP'): 1; ('nisi qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hanc viam invenit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('85', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. a. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Guliel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Kendalls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Meritum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Frigida', 'PERSON'): 1; ('humentia siccis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mollia', 'NORP'): 1; ('propertie•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Belial', 'GPE'): 1; ('every hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('as thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Socinianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scabiosa Theologia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arminianisme', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pelagianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('paria •quaedam', 'ORG'): 1; ('viscera amorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('miserecordiam astute comminiscuntur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aliquibus ex illi•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paulò', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Requ', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Davenant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hereof', 'PERSON'): 1; ('215', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('no less than', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('79', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('152', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cambridg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('convert grace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('91', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('senate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Pareus', 'ORG'): 1; ('half-god', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arminius', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Goliath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bombardiloquus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Braggadocchio', 'GPE'): 1; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Virgil', 'GPE'): 1; ('partibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('humero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Achilles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hector', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Achilles', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ajax', 'PERSON'): 1; ('honorem Aemulus Ajaci .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Maximus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Magnus', 'GPE'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('perce••e', 'ORG'): 1; ('nunc huc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Estius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Estius', 'ORG'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('Principiorum', 'GPE'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('punis•ments', 'LOC'): 1; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('un', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.8', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A41510,22,CHAP. mr. king passage say adversary abortion miscarriage God intention,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; word: 0.5; say: 0.5; mr: 0.5; thing: 0.5; save: 0.45; truth: 0.4; sense: 0.4; king: 0.4; salvation: 0.25; mean: 0.05; page: 0.05,"('king', 'PERSON'): 21; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Arminianisme', 'PERSON'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 5; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Prideaux', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('215', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('seventeenth', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Pelagianisme', 'ORG'): 2; ('Arminius', 'ORG'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('God .', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dort', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('447', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('448', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('26.61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pontius Pilate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thetis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ingeniolum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scythia Anglicana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cornwall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('187', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('235', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('239', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('240', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arminius , Arminianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('kendaels', 'PERSON'): 1; ('king acknowledge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('25.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('doct•ines', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mat 11.21', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chorazin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bethsaida', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Capernaum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mat 15.22', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a thousand pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('two thousand pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('151', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('contra-remonstrancie', 'ORG'): 1; ('reader', 'PERSON'): 1; ('149', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Agens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Patiens', 'ORG'): 1; ('squilla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('133', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Autolycus', 'GPE'): 1; ('de candentibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('130', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('274', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1"
A41510,23,CHAP. Xvi Specimina mr. Kendalls insultation god intention place act,god: 0.5; mr: 0.5; time: 0.5; king: 0.5; man: 0.5; word: 0.5; parent: 0.5; thing: 0.5; cause: 0.35; child: 0.35; world: 0.1; generation: 0.05; place: 0.05; creature: 0.05; truth: 0.05,"('king', 'PERSON'): 30; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 12; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('Devon', 'PERSON'): 5; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Evangelist', 'FAC'): 2; ('Xvi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Specimina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kendalls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dort', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etiam de nihilo', 'ORG'): 1; ('232', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('undu', 'GPE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tus', 'ORG'): 1; ('prohibet alienum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('king queri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('209', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('210', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('pagan superstition', 'FAC'): 1; ('one minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Eccl', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('principal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Transgressor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vero', 'ORG'): 1; ('nihil verius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three degree', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('about noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bathsheba', 'GPE'): 1; ('Calendas Graecas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('inscio quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi bonum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aug. de praedestin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fulgentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('188', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Scythia Anglicana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christmas', 'DATE'): 1"
A41510,23 | 543,slip comfort death Christ signify ox fatling slay think Christ,mr: 0.5; king: 0.5; man: 0.5; hand: 0.5; god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; kendal: 0.35; ks: 0.3; part: 0.3; antecedent: 0.25; fatling: 0.2; ox: 0.2; way: 0.1; mistake: 0.1; preparation: 0.1; guest: 0.05; book: 0.05,"('king', 'PERSON'): 17; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Dover', 'GPE'): 3; ('morning', 'TIME'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Thomas Edward', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 2; ('91', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('saepe de uno diversis', 'ORG'): 1; ('tanquam de dvobus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('12.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Duckenfield Chappel', 'LOC'): 1; ('Cheshire', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('G. Kendal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('502', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('manner', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Balaam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('un-risen', 'ORG'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Barbary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jocularibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edwards', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solent', 'ORG'): 1; ('jactantiis etiam de nihilo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mar. 9.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('T. Blake', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baxter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Botley', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fisher', 'PERSON'): 1; ('labra lactucas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('134', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('reader', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('61', 'DATE'): 1; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('John Owen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Obadiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chaldeans', 'NORP'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1"
A41510,24,CHAP. Xvii taste mr. Kendal jearing frolic language term adversary,ransom: 0.5; man: 0.5; mr: 0.5; god: 0.5; application: 0.5; king: 0.4; pay: 0.4; another: 0.4; woodcock: 0.3; answer: 0.2; part: 0.15; give: 0.15; simile: 0.15; kendal: 0.15; master: 0.1; reason: 0.05; christ: 0.05,"('king', 'PERSON'): 14; ('London', 'GPE'): 9; ('Kendal', 'PERSON'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Devon', 'PERSON'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Evangelist', 'FAC'): 3; ('horn', 'PERSON'): 3; ('half a dozen', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Bodmin', 'GPE'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('lana caprina', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Bindo', 'GPE'): 2; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Braggadocchio', 'GPE'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Arminius', 'ORG'): 2; ('John 3.16', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Bodmin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Bodmin', 'ORG'): 2; ('Xvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kendal ʋn-christian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Braggadocchio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Richardo', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hannibal Cretensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bombardiloquus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 1; ('erit aliquantulum barbar contundi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Synodal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cathedrae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Synodales', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bombardiloquo Pyrgopolinice', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('70', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('domini incipit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('uncouth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvin , Musculus', 'ORG'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Muse', 'ORG'): 1; ('odorem Testa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Richardo', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nilus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('163', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ibidem', 'ORG'): 1; ('161', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('16.51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52', 'DATE'): 1; ('164', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ingeniolum', 'ORG'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Kendal', 'NORP'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A41510,27,CHAP. Specimina master Kendal gobye give strength stress argument mr.,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; providence: 0.5; thing: 0.5; creature: 0.5; word: 0.45; master: 0.4; species: 0.4; hand: 0.35; understanding: 0.25; mr: 0.2; king: 0.15; say: 0.15; book: 0.1; answer: 0.05,"('king', 'PERSON'): 7; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('Kendal', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Baxter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Specimina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 3.16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sosia', 'LOC'): 1; ('nam quom illi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forty foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('120', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('56', 'DATE'): 1; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Richardo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bindo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nilus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('endite', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('with•ut', 'ORG'): 1; ('one half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Kendal', 'NORP'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bodmin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('139.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('aeterno', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Musculus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('tuo omnes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.12.2.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abimelech', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sarah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.6', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Abigail', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nabal', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('25.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1"
A41510,27 | 695,way master Kendal confidence soul grant man name member write,god: 0.5; kendal: 0.5; master: 0.5; providence: 0.5; determine: 0.5; sense: 0.45; man: 0.45; fear: 0.3; decree: 0.3; salvation: 0.25; action: 0.2; parent: 0.15; respect: 0.1; bastard: 0.1; thing: 0.05; work: 0.05; person: 0.05; meaning: 0.05,"('Kendal', 'PERSON'): 25; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 2; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('139.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Scythia Anglicana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aut etiam non coagente', 'PERSON'): 1; ('their quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('terris', 'GPE'): 1; ('eris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fallacia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi bonum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aug. de Praedestin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fulgentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zanchius', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('188', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Kendal', 'ORG'): 1; ('quicunque', 'NORP'): 1; ('335', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('336', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('74', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('salmacida spolia sine sanguine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Kendal', 'NORP'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40 or 50 mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1"
A41510,27 | 717,part p. thing intention king allow God Master Kendal man,god: 0.45; decree: 0.45; christ: 0.45; man: 0.45; sense: 0.45; word: 0.45; world: 0.45; consideration: 0.4; master: 0.3; intention: 0.3; death: 0.25; kendal: 0.1; obtain: 0.05; objection: 0.05; order: 0.05; orator: 0.05; opportunity: 0.05; opinion: 0.05; offend: 0.05; offence: 0.05; occasion: 0.05; page: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('king', 'PERSON'): 5; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('Kendal', 'PERSON'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Evangelist', 'FAC'): 3; ('127', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('John 3.16', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Evangelist', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('God', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Kendal heterodox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('448', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('449', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('205', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('206', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hugo Grotius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('nam alia vult deus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('alia', 'GPE'): 1; ('verò nonlatinalphabet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Grotius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luc', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dordracene', 'GPE'): 1; ('caeterum quando', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('pro amicis suis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hostibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('negativè accepto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('99', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('John 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('destinari praesertim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('primo loco', 'PERSON'): 1; ('208', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('51.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quod scripsi scripsi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kendal', 'NORP'): 1; ('more than ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('156', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('157', 'DATE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'NORP'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('qui cum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('herein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten ounce', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Electra', 'ORG'): 1; ('decr•e', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A41510,28,CHAP. Xxi master Kendal approach blasphemy undertake God power son,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; master: 0.5; thing: 0.5; king: 0.5; act: 0.5; unworthiness: 0.5; mr: 0.45; kendal: 0.45; cause: 0.35; creature: 0.2; intention: 0.05,"('Kendal', 'PERSON'): 19; ('king', 'PERSON'): 12; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Xxi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('viribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('pieta tua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('ille', 'NORP'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Phaethon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phaethon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Re•burie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('149', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('efficere de novo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kendal', 'NORP'): 1; ('west', 'LOC'): 1; ('Mar. 12.24', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('principal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('70', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('veritatis evidentia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tenent', 'ORG'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forlese', 'NORP'): 1; ('127', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ingeniolum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharaohs', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('218', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('219', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('220', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Deans', 'NORP'): 1; ('principalis', 'GPE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Davids', 'ORG'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Devon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paean', 'NORP'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1"
A40800,2,argument scripture ground divine faith offend protestant part religion ground,church: 0.5; thing: 0.5; opinion: 0.5; way: 0.5; council: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; reason: 0.5; tradition: 0.35; part: 0.2; faith: 0.15; contrary: 0.1; truth: 0.1; scripture: 0.1,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 16; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 13; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 4; ('greek', 'NORP'): 3; ('§', 'NORP'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Synesius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Dominicans', 'NORP'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('Papias', 'PERSON'): 2; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Irenaeus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Isidorus Pelusiota', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Successiion', 'ORG'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ariminum', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of Florence', 'ORG'): 1; ('Canus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Nicephorus Callistus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ariminum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('172', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 22', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dionysius Alexandrinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('at least two hundred and fifty year', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dial', 'PERSON'): 1; ('307', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Justin', 'ORG'): 1; ('propugnacula defendunt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Feuardentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arrius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salvian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Niceph', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tom 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('555', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('206', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('caesariut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Greeke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evagrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('god grace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nilus', 'GPE'): 1; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thucydides', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Massa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fast day', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iustin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrinus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ludovicus Vives', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet .', 'ORG'): 1; ('49', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 1"
A45169,1,John Humphreys London print author humble reader nature art self,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; lord: 0.5; christ: 0.5; herod: 0.5; david: 0.5; prince: 0.45; saul: 0.4; king: 0.35; sam: 0.35; kingdom: 0.2; rev: 0.15; sin: 0.05; heart: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('thou', 'GPE'): 8; ('David', 'PERSON'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 6; ('Herod', 'PERSON'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('18', 'DATE'): 3; ('Saul', 'ORG'): 3; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('17', 'DATE'): 2; ('Bethlehem', 'GPE'): 2; ('two year old', 'DATE'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Augustus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Pharaoh', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11.7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jezabel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 2; ('John Humphreys', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('1682', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rama', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rachel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the very morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'DATE'): 1; ('the 13th', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('8.5 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jeremiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phimbria', 'NORP'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('Achitophel', 'GPE'): 1; ('17.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.4 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 19.2', 'LAW'): 1; ('12.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.11', 'DATE'): 1; ('22.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Doeg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('20.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('79', 'DATE'): 1; ('Amon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('36.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ashur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balaam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Naboth', 'ORG'): 1; ('24.35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tertullus', 'GPE'): 1; ('24.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Meroz', 'GPE'): 1; ('Obadiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('106.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jonathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 20.2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1"
A45169,3,Christ bear trouble commotion war Christ cause wickedness perverseness Herod,christ: 0.5; king: 0.5; god: 0.5; church: 0.5; child: 0.5; man: 0.5; herod: 0.5; righteousness: 0.3; gospel: 0.25; bear: 0.15; self: 0.15; spirit: 0.15; life: 0.15; lord: 0.1; truth: 0.1; peace: 0.05; earth: 0.05; kingdom: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 9; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 5; ('30', 'DATE'): 3; ('Herod', 'NORP'): 2; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('finis', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14.28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('29', 'DATE'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heroa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dagon', 'ORG'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dagon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sam 5.3 .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elizabeth day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jezabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('Zach', 'GPE'): 1; ('13.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('erit', 'GPE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rachel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Benjamin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gadarens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('10.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('tuo novissimo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet pro rege', 'ORG'): 1; ('judicia tua regi da', 'PERSON'): 1; ('justitiam tuam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tuum adjudicandum justè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('temporibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('etiam amplitudo donec non', 'ORG'): 1; ('dòminabitur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jehova', 'GPE'): 1; ('ac omnes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deus gratiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('illustre faciem tuam', 'ORG'): 1; ('maximé', 'ORG'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cappadocia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Horace', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cappadocum rex', 'ORG'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Modes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year 1664', 'DATE'): 1; ('100', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('false brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prelacy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Titus', 'PRODUCT'): 1"
A49813,7,Augustin Marlorat place Christ apostle exception other invention disciple pool,christ: 0.5; minister: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; apostle: 0.5; church: 0.5; perfection: 0.45; word: 0.35; life: 0.3; light: 0.25; king: 0.2; call: 0.1; thummim: 0.1; doctrine: 0.1; john: 0.05; clergy: 0.05; gospel: 0.05,"('Thummim', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Urim', 'ORG'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Urim', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the apostle day', 'DATE'): 3; ('James', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('John', 'PERSON'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('latin', 'NORP'): 3; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 3; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cain', 'ORG'): 2; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 2; ('1.1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('18', 'DATE'): 2; ('english', 'NORP'): 2; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Pius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 2; ('Augustin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marlorat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hebrves', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hebrews', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thummius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apostles', 'ORG'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('babylonian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ezra 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nehem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 23.8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James 3.1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wilson', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('John 1.1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James 1.21', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 1.9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 8.12', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hundred of year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Golgotha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.15.10 Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.1 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Babel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hebrews', 'ORG'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('world|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alpha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Omega', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephen be stone', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('7.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('55.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Stephen', 'GPE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8.2 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 1.7 .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James 5.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul be Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abaddon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apolyon', 'GPE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gilboa', 'GPE'): 1; ('2 Sam 1.21', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paepal', 'ORG'): 1; ('one hundred thousand pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Bakers Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this edwara day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Devonshire', 'GPE'): 1; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Magdiburg', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year 1559', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('supreme', 'ORG'): 1; ('nine thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Prebends', 'ORG'): 1; ('one hundred and twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mary day', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fonts', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tippets', 'ORG'): 1; ('the year 1644', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year 1653', 'DATE'): 1; ('Oliver Cromwell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year 1658', 'DATE'): 1; ('Richard Cromwell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aencas Silvius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneas damnavit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aencas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Turkey Turks', 'GPE'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rhine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1"
A49813,8 | 3382,institution practice day|be voluntary collection necessity use service church year,church: 0.5; year: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; tithe: 0.5; priest: 0.5; day: 0.45; pope: 0.45; christian: 0.4; use: 0.35; man: 0.2; thing: 0.2; alban: 0.15; constantine: 0.15; minister: 0.1; doctrine: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('christian', 'NORP'): 10; ('Alban', 'ORG'): 7; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 5; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 4; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 4; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 4; ('monthly', 'DATE'): 3; ('Selden', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Amphibalus', 'ORG'): 3; ('Alban', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 3; ('Ethelbert', 'PERSON'): 3; ('about two hundred year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Apologet', 'ORG'): 2; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 2; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('about the year 250', 'DATE'): 2; ('these day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Mantuan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 2; ('Napier', 'ORG'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sylvester', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Wickliff', 'PERSON'): 2; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('about the year 800', 'DATE'): 2; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Saxons', 'NORP'): 2; ('Augustin', 'ORG'): 2; ('weekly', 'DATE'): 1; ('turtudian', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('vel cum velit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed sponte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stipes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Turtullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ʋrsin', 'GPE'): 1; ('227', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Polydor de invent', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Maximinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('304', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ʋrban', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Homil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orig', 'GPE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levit', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cypr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prosp', 'ORG'): 1; ('contemplat', 'ORG'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sportulae', 'ORG'): 1; ('the apostle day', 'DATE'): 1; ('about the year 310', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lucina', 'ORG'): 1; ('Polydor', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about the year 314', 'DATE'): 1; ('Constantius and Helen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Malchi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hospinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('gestaus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('vasa aurea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sacerdotes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hermannus Gigas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lateran', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. Marl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Religio', 'NORP'): 1; ('filia devoravit matrem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('outward lustre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Babylon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Byzantium', 'GPE'): 1; ('the council of Constance', 'ORG'): 1; ('Helvetia', 'GPE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty four', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pontif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this sylvester day', 'DATE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry', 'GPE'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixthly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Jubile', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam Merrymouth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Carmelite Fryar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caesarea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 1; ('the year 340', 'DATE'): 1; ('Conc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('about the year 384', 'DATE'): 1; ('about the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('398', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Milan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hippo', 'GPE'): 1; ('about the year 400', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ambr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year 440', 'DATE'): 1; ('about the year 470', 'DATE'): 1; ('leo de jejun', 'ORG'): 1; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangel', 'GPE'): 1; ('1000', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bernard abbot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Claravallis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year 1127', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hugo de Sacro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the 17th', 'DATE'): 1; ('pope and council', 'ORG'): 1; ('about the year 1200', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zacheus', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui decimas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non mortalia', 'ORG'): 1; ('auri sacra fame', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Golds', 'ORG'): 1; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year 1274', 'DATE'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year 1560', 'DATE'): 1; ('Philip the apostle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Joseph of Arimathea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the british day', 'DATE'): 1; ('about the year 290', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dioclesian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Verulamium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Verulam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Albanum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('faecunda brittannia profert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('british', 'NORP'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bede', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year 600', 'DATE'): 1; ('Northumbrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Angli', 'GPE'): 1; ('Deira', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alla', 'ORG'): 1; ('Northumberland', 'ORG'): 1; ('Angli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dei ira', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hallelujah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Benedict', 'PERSON'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('Milton', 'PERSON'): 1"
A49813,11,Henry enact monastery abbey priory other house monk canon nun,tithe: 0.5; order: 0.5; person: 0.5; pope: 0.5; land: 0.5; man: 0.45; maintenance: 0.45; call: 0.45; thing: 0.35; people: 0.3; knight: 0.25; day: 0.2; exemption: 0.05,"('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Rhodes', 'ORG'): 2; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('sec', 'ORG'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Chappel', 'LOC'): 1; ('CAP', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saxons', 'NORP'): 1; ('priest canonical institute', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about the year 1200', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cistercians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Adrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cistertians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thomas Ridley', 'PERSON'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gelasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year 1117', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Saracen', 'NORP'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about the year 1120', 'DATE'): 1; ('Solyman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Malta', 'GPE'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Confreres', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Burgundy', 'ORG'): 1; ('C•steaux', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('frank almoigne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('133', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Littletou', 'GPE'): 1; ('136', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('former day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pontif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexander Cruces', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Altaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mantuan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('altar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1"
A41490,3,backside opinion foreside face backside opinion general lax expression discourse,christ: 0.5; man: 0.5; mr: 0.5; righteousness: 0.5; way: 0.45; opinion: 0.45; answer: 0.4; god: 0.4; time: 0.25; truth: 0.25; self: 0.25; word: 0.15; impute: 0.15; minister: 0.1; discourse: 0.1; hand: 0.05,"('W.', 'PERSON'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Socinian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2o', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wonderful s .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phillida', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phillis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cato — contra', 'ORG'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Cato', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Jjm and Oijm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Machiavelli', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellzebub', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'LOC'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Michael the Archangell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Archangel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('belzeebub', 'ORG'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Achitophel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Archangell', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('qui tonitru', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Olympi', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jove', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Messenger•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Rabsecah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hour', 'TIME'): 1"
A41490,5,reform church mind judgement sense meaning scripture reform church divine,opinion: 0.5; mr: 0.5; faith: 0.5; christ: 0.5; arminian: 0.5; man: 0.5; righteousness: 0.5; god: 0.5; word: 0.3; imputation: 0.25; arminius: 0.2; justification: 0.1; socinian: 0.05; thing: 0.05; satisfaction: 0.05,"('Arminian', 'NORP'): 22; ('W.', 'PERSON'): 18; ('Socinian', 'NORP'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Arminius', 'ORG'): 7; ('Arminianisme', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Arminius', 'PERSON'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Socinus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 3; ('arminians', 'NORP'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Venus', 'ORG'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Wal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ajax', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('us', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Prideaux', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod non habet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vlyssean', 'NORP'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hyperbaton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the end of this 2', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('virgulam censoriam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('W. p. 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Socinus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Mezentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mortua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('corpora vivis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('oribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('blasphemer', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mar. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('swenkfeldian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Antitrinitarian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arrian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eutychian', 'NORP'): 1; ('nestorian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Valentinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Novatian', 'GPE'): 1; ('pelagian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Maniche', 'ORG'): 1; ('G.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jovinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nestorius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Daniel be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Socinianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('justitiam christi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('imputari', 'GPE'): 1; ('arbitrari se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contineri', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apostoli', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('ingentia magni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lepus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gracchi', 'ORG'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60. 61', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anti-Arminian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Symbolum', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about the year 1626', 'DATE'): 1; ('Censura', 'ORG'): 1; ('confessionem seu', 'ORG'): 1; ('declarationem sententiae eorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('harrow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('protota', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inter justificationis causas', 'ORG'): 1; ('fidem hanc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('obedientiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fidem ipsam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('se', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christiani', 'LOC'): 1; ('VValker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lect', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianismi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('tandem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arminio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('instrumentalis iustificationis nostrae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bertius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lubbertus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('hanc sententiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Vorstius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('every hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Socinus', 'FAC'): 1; ('the Arminian party', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten degree', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 1"
A41490,5 | 3949,Lycori Blanditus Pictor Minervae contrary man mr. Ws. intent portraiture,righteousness: 0.5; christ: 0.5; thing: 0.5; faith: 0.5; man: 0.5; law: 0.5; mr: 0.5; god: 0.45; satisfaction: 0.3; impute: 0.25; ws: 0.15; word: 0.15; scripture: 0.1; act: 0.1,"('W.', 'PERSON'): 15; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Socinian', 'NORP'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Shimei', 'ORG'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Euangelicall', 'ORG'): 2; ('qui venerem tuam pinxit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lycori', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Blanditus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arrius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ignoramus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Troy after Homer', 'ORG'): 1; ('misshape conceit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('that spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Utica', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ilerda', 'NORP'): 1; ('1. 21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bathsheba', 'GPE'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('13.', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 19', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•o be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('natu•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gualther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('docet imputandi verbum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('gratiae verò eius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nos me•uimus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Euangelicall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ipse dixit', 'PERSON'): 1"
A41490,5 | 3972,divine clever obedience Christ consideration respect performance law oversight pity,righteousness: 0.5; faith: 0.5; man: 0.5; law: 0.5; christ: 0.5; scripture: 0.5; god: 0.45; mr: 0.45; thing: 0.4; interpretation: 0.4; way: 0.1; page: 0.1; believer: 0.05; reward: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 6; ('W.', 'PERSON'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Evangelicall', 'PERSON'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('us', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('7 day', 'DATE'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('near|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mulgeat hircos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dalila', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Obtorto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40 foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('heu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('oblitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Portea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Porteus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Xanthus', 'NORP'): 1; ('obelisque', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fallacia divisionis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ioh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome 5. 1', 'FAC'): 1"
A41490,6,mr. Ws. argument stage face man complexion thing word start,mr: 0.35; man: 0.35; righteousness: 0.35; exposition: 0.35; testimony: 0.35; god: 0.3; wotton: 0.3; goodwin: 0.25; opinion: 0.25; word: 0.2; prince: 0.15; profession: 0.15; pen: 0.15; person: 0.15; phine: 0.15; phineas: 0.15; pity: 0.15; place: 0.15; pope: 0.15; priesthood: 0.15; law: 0.15; page: 0.1; argument: 0.05; heretic: 0.05; justify: 0.05; thing: 0.05,"('W.', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Wotton', 'GPE'): 4; ('Socinus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Phine', 'ORG'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Socinian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phineas', 'NORP'): 1; ('omnis aristippum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristippus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Musculus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Autolycus', 'GPE'): 1; ('candida de ingris', 'ORG'): 1; ('White Cowes', 'ORG'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('old day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Wotton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lebanon', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Socinianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('as much brevity', 'MONEY'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1"
A41490,7,mr. W. righteousness impute Abraham conformity law page God lie,mr: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; condition: 0.5; righteousness: 0.5; christ: 0.5; faith: 0.5; scripture: 0.35; page: 0.35; vv: 0.3; reason: 0.1; thing: 0.1; word: 0.05; satisfaction: 0.05; justice: 0.05; law: 0.05; contradiction: 0.05; sin: 0.05,"('W.', 'PERSON'): 24; ('Socinian', 'NORP'): 7; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 6; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 5; ('us', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('G.', 'PERSON'): 4; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('VVotton', 'GPE'): 3; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('ibidem', 'PERSON'): 2; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apocrypho', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rome 5. 19 and 8. 4', 'ORG'): 1; ('10. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the pelagian heresy', 'ORG'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('Korah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Downeham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('B. Downham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('John 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a summer day', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('laudibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dothan', 'GPE'): 1; ('a•l', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'NORP'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mar. 14', 'DATE'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A41490,8 | 4078,mr. W. time fault gratification offence door season mix contradiction,righteousness: 0.4; christ: 0.4; faith: 0.4; god: 0.4; mr: 0.4; believer: 0.4; impute: 0.4; expression: 0.4; man: 0.3; abraham: 0.25; argument: 0.2; paper: 0.1; palate: 0.1; philip: 0.1; person: 0.1; pen: 0.1; passion: 0.1; passage: 0.1; part: 0.1; place: 0.1; order: 0.1; justify: 0.05,"('W.', 'PERSON'): 15; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 14; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('three day', 'DATE'): 2; ('three night', 'TIME'): 2; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 2; ('secunda ferat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Oedipus', 'ORG'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apostle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('uncouth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('us', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35 mr', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cardo', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 1; ('William', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Io Paean', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quoniam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 20', 'DATE'): 1"
A41490,9,way confirmation act tragedy m. W. p. testimony mind God,sin: 0.45; christ: 0.45; mr: 0.45; omission: 0.45; author: 0.45; testimony: 0.4; faith: 0.35; commission: 0.3; way: 0.25; blood: 0.2; righteousness: 0.2; scripture: 0.2; satisfaction: 0.15; sense: 0.1; interpretation: 0.05; produce: 0.05; prerogative: 0.05; proverb: 0.05; promissor: 0.05; promise: 0.05; purge: 0.05; pretend: 0.05; piece: 0.05; point: 0.05; purpose: 0.05; time: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('W.', 'PERSON'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pharises', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('John 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Socinus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Arminius', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('more than one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('190', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bolton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ad finem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('birth|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('before', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solomons day', 'DATE'): 1; ('this last quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A41490,10,obedience righteousness Christ life consideration death obedience viz. be punishment,christ: 0.5; righteousness: 0.5; faith: 0.5; impute: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; abraham: 0.5; mr: 0.45; testimony: 0.4; sense: 0.3; author: 0.2; word: 0.15,"('W.', 'PERSON'): 10; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('21', 'DATE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('21. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 12', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nunc illue', 'ORG'): 1; ('Credat Iudaus Apella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bucer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bullinger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham Deo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Priscian', 'NORP'): 1; ('ipsi ad justitiam imputatum est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Illyricus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('justitiam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Socinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Luther , Calvin', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Apuleius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Poema', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chimaeram', 'ORG'): 1; ('Harpyas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gigantes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Centimanum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sphynx', 'PERSON'): 1; ('raven harpy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gyges', 'ORG'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; (""Cerb'rus"", 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the mean season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nesci••i', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1"
A46060,3,speech child tooth speech self thing man tooth eloquence abate,body: 0.45; soul: 0.45; man: 0.45; god: 0.45; spirit: 0.45; another: 0.35; heaven: 0.35; life: 0.3; nature: 0.3; resurrection: 0.25; creation: 0.25; book: 0.2; earth: 0.15; truth: 0.05; piadar: 0.05; phocylides: 0.05; player: 0.05; plato: 0.05; plant: 0.05; place: 0.05; pindarus: 0.05; plotinus: 0.05; phadon: 0.05; pet: 0.05; death: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Demosthenes', 'NORP'): 1; ('R.', 'NORP'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein dwell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('65.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sibylla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hitherto come', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orpheus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theognis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Iliad Herm', 'FAC'): 1; ('Paenander', 'ORG'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hesiod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pindarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chalcidins', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zoroastres', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hermes', 'GPE'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chaldea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'LOC'): 1; ('Lil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Legum 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hordelitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philolaus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Epicharmus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thales', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anaxagoras', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucretius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phadon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scipio', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gallio', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucillius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Epictetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Simplicius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Plotinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 1', 'LAW'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 18', 'LAW'): 1; ('14. 20. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 11', 'LAW'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A49958,6,CHAP. Iii person valley death valley kidron David jonathans lad,death: 0.5; sin: 0.5; christ: 0.5; saint: 0.5; god: 0.5; life: 0.5; lord: 0.45; day: 0.45; glory: 0.4; man: 0.35; head: 0.15; grave: 0.1; heaven: 0.05; ps: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 4; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 3; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Ps', 'ORG'): 3; ('daily', 'DATE'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 2; ('he|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('Lebanon', 'GPE'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ro', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('that day', 'DATE'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hovell', 'ORG'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Diodor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Camden', 'GPE'): 1; ('Glamorganshire', 'GPE'): 1; ('elysian', 'NORP'): 1; ('22.29', 'DATE'): 1; ('13.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sueton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Coleg', 'GPE'): 1; ('Caligula', 'GPE'): 1; ('Medes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Persiens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('he|will', 'NORP'): 1; ('Phocas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leviathan Job 41.29', 'ORG'): 1; ('Barr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jailor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hippocrates', 'NORP'): 1; ('Coan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Galen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Skelitons', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 1; ('10 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Irel', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Eden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arabia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gilead', 'ORG'): 1; ('India', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a last hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('milkwhite', 'NORP'): 1; ('9.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Machpeloh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Job', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zorah', 'GPE'): 1; ('32.50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Behemoth', 'GPE'): 1; ('146.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Patmos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six-foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lond', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1639', 'DATE'): 1; ('noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('51.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lev 14.6', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('32.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Evangelicall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•v••', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32.1 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('7.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.19.20.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul 2 Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Capernaum', 'ORG'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Joh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('holy John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Melchizedek', 'GPE'): 1; ('110.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Kidron', 'ORG'): 1; ('Olivet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Levites', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Mat 20.22', 'ORG'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('saint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('12 24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28.11', 'MONEY'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.2 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bern', 'ORG'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a. Ed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('517', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('quouiam cum peccavit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('concupisentiam genite', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('V. 14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('89.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Enoch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('102.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
