tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A57659,56,CHAP. V. Elysium field place pleasure soul man afie• life,moon: 0.5; minerva: 0.5; man: 0.5; vulcan: 0.5; endymeon: 0.5; love: 0.5; erych: 0.4; honius: 0.3; delight: 0.3; god: 0.3; world: 0.25; life: 0.1; body: 0.1; virgin: 0.05; sin: 0.05; heaven: 0.05; sun: 0.05; soul: 0.05,"('Vulcan', 'NORP'): 11; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 11; ('Endymeon', 'GPE'): 5; ('Erych•honius', 'ORG'): 5; ('Juno', 'PERSON'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('elysian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('V. e Elysium', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('drunk•rd•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Acheron', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phlegeton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•eers', 'ORG'): 1; ('••sse', 'NORP'): 1; ('Elis', 'ORG'): 1; ('•eep', 'NORP'): 1; ('I. Endymeon', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Endymeon Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the moon', 'LOC'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('inconstanci•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('saint Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the moon fall', 'LOC'): 1; ('Primus Erychthonius', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•inerva', 'GPE'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('increas•d', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•ury', 'ORG'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de spectaculis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pliny and Empedocles be .', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A56533,43,observe side proceed time Iesuit• interim advantage modesty distribution libel,curez: 0.5; church: 0.5; doctrine: 0.5; archbishop: 0.5; letter: 0.45; assembly: 0.45; divine: 0.4; thing: 0.35; time: 0.35; god: 0.3; say: 0.15; truth: 0.15; proposition: 0.1; word: 0.05; lord: 0.05; jesuit: 0.05; name: 0.05; book: 0.05; author: 0.05,"('Curez', 'PERSON'): 11; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 5; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 3; ('Sorbonne', 'GPE'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('the Curez of Rouen', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Monsieur de four', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Maclou', 'ORG'): 1; ('Brisacier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Maclou', 'DATE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a whole month', 'DATE'): 1; ('•ideli•y', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty or', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty and eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Monsieur', 'LOC'): 1; ('wer•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Assembly•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sagittae', 'ORG'): 1; ('plagae', 'ORG'): 1; ('63', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lesbian', 'NORP'): 1; ('casu•sts', 'ORG'): 1; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('those hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vrban Viii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('138th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('these hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('S•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Wiclef', 'ORG'): 1; ('Divine', 'ORG'): 1; ('de S. cyrian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('93', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('secul•r', 'ORG'): 1; ('Wiclif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Libertinisme', 'PERSON'): 1; ('o• God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('employme•t', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jansenisme•', 'GPE'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('caelestibus ira', 'PERSON'): 1; ('loquela tua manif•stum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bese•ch', 'GPE'): 1; ('wher•of', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calvinists', 'ORG'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calumnies•', 'ORG'): 1; ('power•ul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deliverer', 'ORG'): 1"
A57655,5,A. R. ROSSEUM ALcides Lernaeum Leviathan supera amphytrioniadem D. C.,motion: 0.45; sense: 0.45; thing: 0.45; fancy: 0.45; part: 0.45; imagination: 0.45; life: 0.4; organ: 0.35; nature: 0.35; appetite: 0.25; memory: 0.15; god: 0.1; colour: 0.05; art: 0.05; leviathan: 0.05; fiction: 0.05; mind: 0.05; people: 0.05; passage: 0.05; position: 0.05; phrase: 0.05; philosopher: 0.05; pottage: 0.05; patriarch: 0.05; outside: 0.05; power: 0.05,"('Leviathan', 'GPE'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Hobbs', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('belluae domitorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ros calamo', 'ORG'): 1; ('monstra marina d•mas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quantum', 'ORG'): 1; ('superavit viribus hydram', 'ORG'): 1; ('D. C.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eurydice', 'ORG'): 1; ('Republica', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leviathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hobb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander Ross', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epidemis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Euripides', 'NORP'): 1; ('Orestes', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Oedipus', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1"
A57655,7 | 2638,phrase part cap God personate Moses Christ son man personality,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; reason: 0.5; law: 0.5; faith: 0.5; conscience: 0.45; word: 0.45; subject: 0.45; power: 0.4; prince: 0.25; christ: 0.2; cap: 0.1; injury: 0.1; thing: 0.05; right: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('David', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Uriah', 'PERSON'): 8; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Hobbs', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 4; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('Pompey', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judaea', 'ORG'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty one chapter', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Muscovit', 'ORG'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antoninus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aurelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('numquam libertas', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam sub rege pio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the supreme senate', 'ORG'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty eight chapter', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Atraeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('equalis astris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lebanus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Daniel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('caesárve priorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pompeiúsve parem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hobbs', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leviathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('twenty nine chapter', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Th••', 'ORG'): 1; ('the christian school', 'ORG'): 1; ('13.', 'DATE'): 1; ('tha•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orestes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Juvenal', 'GPE'): 1; ('ta••en', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mens habet attonilos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quátient•', 'ORG'): 1; ('paena autem', 'ORG'): 1; ('vehemens', 'GPE'): 1; ('ac multo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ceditius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rhadamanthus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Persius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sat.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Siculi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aera juvenci', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aut magis', 'NORP'): 1; ('pendens', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('laquearibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Purpureas', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam si', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sibi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Palleat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14. 14', 'DATE'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('chapter 29', 'LAW'): 1; ('Mat 16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Agrippa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vincit maenia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Latius', 'NORP'): 1; ('quam si lybiam remotis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gadibus jungas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Polit', 'NORP'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Aurelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('humanos• edicta', 'ORG'): 1; ('ac vita regentis', 'ORG'): 1; ('par•to legi quisquis legem sanxerit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('singuli dominio', 'GPE'): 1; ('thirty one chapter Cap', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('the 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Leviathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Holy•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('•aith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('24. 26', 'DATE'): 1"
A57655,7 | 2672,cap Urim give priest give sovereign God priest commonwealth Israel,man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; soul: 0.5; god: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; body: 0.5; kingdom: 0.5; immortality: 0.45; life: 0.4; torment: 0.15; hobbs: 0.1; faith: 0.1; world: 0.1; call: 0.1; cap: 0.1,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Hobbs', 'PERSON'): 6; ('44', 'DATE'): 6; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Hobbs', 'ORG'): 4; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 4; ('42.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Arius', 'ORG'): 3; ('Aen', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Urim', 'ORG'): 2; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 2; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('Christ', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Virgil', 'ORG'): 2; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('•ay', 'GPE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 4. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fro•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('heresy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('whil•t', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mahometans', 'NORP'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('three and forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty four chapter Cap', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 34', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mat 14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Suidas', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('44•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•be', 'ORG'): 1; ('•aith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Umbrae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hobbs', 'FAC'): 1; ('10. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('a hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vrigil', 'LOC'): 1; ('Polidorus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deiph•bus', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('locis adero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dido', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magna mei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Creusa', 'ORG'): 1; ('infelix', 'NORP'): 1; ('Creusae', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lucretius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ennius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Acberusia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ennius aeternis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mar. 9 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('luke 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin Geneva', 'LOC'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('Solomon , Eccles', 'ORG'): 1; ('3. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'MONEY'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomons', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('20.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Originists', 'NORP'): 1; ('errat perversius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quanto videtur de', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the platonic year', 'DATE'): 1; ('elysian', 'NORP'): 1"
A57655,7 | 2687,Armor•• tellure Virg. AEn doctrine admit wickedness profaneness life condition,man: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; christ: 0.5; devil: 0.5; god: 0.5; soul: 0.5; scripture: 0.4; word: 0.3; thing: 0.2; satan: 0.2; vision: 0.2; body: 0.15; obedience: 0.15; cause: 0.1; possess: 0.05; mr: 0.05; hobbs: 0.05; disease: 0.05; use: 0.05; part: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Hobbs', 'ORG'): 5; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Hobbs', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('•aith', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John 13', 'PERSON'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 2; ('46', 'DATE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('— quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('AEn', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas Iscariot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hol•', 'ORG'): 1; ('luke 9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vapou•s', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6500', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Macedonia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mat 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scaeva', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mat 16.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('these latter day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet •', 'ORG'): 1; ('Wierus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bodin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zacuta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('t•rquentur', 'GPE'): 1; ('coguntu•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hobbs', 'GPE'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seduce eve', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forty six chapter', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zenn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('imperito nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam injustius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui nisi quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam sit tibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hercules', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('miraris bonos viros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi', 'NORP'): 1; ('quam frequens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the university of the world have receive', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leviathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Solon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Joel 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Austin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A51177,3,relation protestant profession substance religion hold error consent time Waldenses,church: 0.3; time: 0.3; visibility: 0.3; faith: 0.3; succession: 0.3; self: 0.3; way: 0.3; man: 0.3; obscurity: 0.25; pharisies: 0.2; person: 0.2; point: 0.2; plebeian: 0.2; plantation: 0.2; place: 0.2; philosopher: 0.2; possession: 0.2; peruse: 0.2; pedigree: 0.2; splendour: 0.2; salvation: 0.05; orthodox: 0.05; scripture: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Arianisme', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Walter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Waldenses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('400 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Renerus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Silvestri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apostolorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('arena maris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('plebeian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Arragon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tholouse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Whitaker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam quando videntur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('extruitur duritia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisies', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichristianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('successio', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Stapleton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Andrew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the very first day', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('welter soul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Manchester', 'PERSON'): 1"
A54224,8 | 5073,current version allow nonlatinalphabet light enlighten part other loss express,light: 0.3; man: 0.3; god: 0.3; enlighten: 0.3; world: 0.3; life: 0.3; john: 0.3; thing: 0.25; part: 0.25; participle: 0.2; parallele: 0.2; pnre: 0.2; please: 0.2; place: 0.2; phrase: 0.2; persuade: 0.2; people: 0.2; peace: 0.2; passage: 0.2; way: 0.15; salvation: 0.1; make: 0.1; soul: 0.05,"('Joan', 'PERSON'): 7; ('John', 'PERSON'): 6; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('quae', 'GPE'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('G. F.', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('Johanni', 'PERSON'): 2; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('omnem hominem', 'ORG'): 2; ('erat', 'NORP'): 2; ('vera quae', 'FAC'): 1; ('Jeremiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Quakers', 'ORG'): 1; ('G. F. be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('G. F. be own', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa. 3. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 Jo', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('our day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this very day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erasm', 'ORG'): 1; ('erat Fons', 'ORG'): 1; ('ipsi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bez', 'PERSON'): 1; ('agatur', 'GPE'): 1; ('quidem hominibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lucet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Maldonatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maldon', 'ORG'): 1; ('411', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('412', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonnulli hoc de naturali', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vita erat lux', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cypri', 'GPE'): 1; ('vera quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cyprian lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Johannes', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam condita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('verbum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('imo quae deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fons', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae omnibus impertit naturalis luminis', 'ORG'): 1; ('nostrarum lucet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quas animas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cameron', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lucem esse ab illo sole', 'ORG'): 1; ('mortis liberemur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('all day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 1; ('less than two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A50248,2 | 7904,distinction admit question Vrsin Catech. Explic. •uast page Parem faith,supper: 0.5; lord: 0.5; church: 0.5; child: 0.5; baptism: 0.5; fitness: 0.5; parent: 0.5; state: 0.5; faith: 0.45; thing: 0.35; believer: 0.05; time: 0.05; baptize: 0.05; membership: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 3; ('Hanmer', 'ORG'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Propos', 'GPE'): 2; ('Assumption', 'ORG'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Vrsin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Catech', 'ORG'): 1; ('•uast', 'GPE'): 1; ('81', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('426', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Parem', 'GPE'): 1; ('brethren acknowledge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('• Jew inwar•ly ••at', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('profe•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('•as', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mag•stra•e', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('Passeover', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.6 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israelitish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ames Medul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'DATE'): 1; ('ecclesiastical•y', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'GPE'): 1; ('12.48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Catechumeni', 'NORP'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('132', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anabaptist', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ca•echumeni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('t•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('Canonists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gerhard', 'ORG'): 1; ('184', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ebrius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Domin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('genera••y', 'ORG'): 1; ('Disciplina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52', 'DATE'): 1; ('53', 'DATE'): 1"
A55005,4,deportment discourse expression heart burden sickness God reply preach other,god: 0.5; religion: 0.5; self: 0.5; heart: 0.5; thing: 0.5; time: 0.5; christ: 0.4; business: 0.4; soul: 0.4; strength: 0.25; world: 0.25; life: 0.2; creature: 0.1,"('thou', 'GPE'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('anno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1647', 'DATE'): 1; ('the 46 year of his age', 'DATE'): 1; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 1; ('he|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Clark', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('many minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('7.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('each hour and minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('subj•ct', 'GPE'): 1"
A59834,39 | 13202,fault reflecter answerers way reduce head point answerer doctrine represent,church: 0.45; worship: 0.45; answerer: 0.45; image: 0.45; council: 0.45; divine: 0.45; action: 0.45; doctrine: 0.4; god: 0.35; part: 0.35; sense: 0.15; sin: 0.1; reflecter: 0.05; paul: 0.05; pian: 0.05; peter: 0.05; person: 0.05; perplex: 0.05; people: 0.05; penitent: 0.05; penance: 0.05; pay: 0.05,"('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 st .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('62', 'DATE'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('91', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('nostra pian scelera', 'ORG'): 1; ('Matris', 'GPE'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Balinghem a Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tournay', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amiens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Roman catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('ten year', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('kneel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paragraph', 'NORP'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Turks', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bellarmin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Irenaeus , Epiphanius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the Trent council', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abigail', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Wicelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vives', 'ORG'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Historical', 'ORG'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Greg. de Valent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bellarmin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A56163,8,CHAP. Iii Classis president supplication prayer intercession thanksgiving king gospel,king: 0.5; supplication: 0.5; prayer: 0.5; thanksgiving: 0.5; intercession: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.45; gospel: 0.45; duty: 0.4; kingdom: 0.3; christians: 0.2; lord: 0.1; apostle: 0.1,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 32; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 23; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 12; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Lu', 'PERSON'): 9; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('David', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 6; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 6; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 5; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 4; ('14', 'DATE'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('17', 'DATE'): 3; ('45', 'DATE'): 3; ('Chrysostom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('28', 'DATE'): 3; ('3 .', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('21', 'DATE'): 3; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('33', 'DATE'): 2; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('24', 'DATE'): 2; ('2. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('38', 'DATE'): 2; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('42', 'DATE'): 2; ('1. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'DATE'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('19', 'DATE'): 2; ('20', 'DATE'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4 .', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sedulius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Claudius', 'NORP'): 2; ('44', 'DATE'): 2; ('29', 'DATE'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('myrrh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('many hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('72. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sheba', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zechariah', 'GPE'): 1; ('9 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 13', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('68', 'DATE'): 1; ('69', 'DATE'): 1; ('70', 'DATE'): 1; ('39 37', 'DATE'): 1; ('21. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mar. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('20. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 36', 'DATE'): 1; ('41.', 'DATE'): 1; ('22. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('kingship', 'GPE'): 1; ('L•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('app•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('smith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quakers', 'ORG'): 1; ('August 1659', 'DATE'): 1; ('the university of Cambridge', 'ORG'): 1; ('Quaker', 'ORG'): 1; ('George Whitehead', 'PERSON'): 1; ('George fox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('a whole hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('9 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('13. 46', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('18.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('11. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('Fellow•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 32', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judas 3.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4ly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Hymeneus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ps. 72. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ps. 72', 'DATE'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Remigius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('crown', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theodoret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter encage Pet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theodo•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rhemigius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Oecume•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('above 500 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Socrates Scholasticus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caligula', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('for•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hymno ◊ de ◊ Christi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Herodes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pugna•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Claudius •', 'ORG'): 1; ('irish', 'NORP'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('J•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pagan king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('G•', 'ORG'): 1; ('12. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian Liberties', 'ORG'): 1; ('Stephens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ja•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Agrippa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arrian', 'GPE'): 1"
A56163,17 | 15312,archbishop prayer D• Christe participibu• line line line line lord,king: 0.5; god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; christ: 0.5; archbishop: 0.5; kingdom: 0.45; sword: 0.4; prayer: 0.4; life: 0.25; servant: 0.2; th: 0.2; jesus: 0.2; line: 0.15; thing: 0.1; end: 0.05; blessing: 0.05; man: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 13; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('•', 'ORG'): 9; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 7; ('James', 'PERSON'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('D•', 'PERSON'): 2; ('d•', 'PERSON'): 2; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 2; ('•', 'GPE'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('benedictionibus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('contra', 'NORP'): 2; ('tuum', 'NORP'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Ghos•', 'ORG'): 1; ('pecoator•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nguine su•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tuum J•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('des•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('victorem de invict•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ecclesiam defend•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sublime•', 'GPE'): 1; ('n•', 'ORG'): 1; ('ins•', 'ORG'): 1; ('iantibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('domine cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cens post ◊ à ◊ ◊', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christum •', 'ORG'): 1; ('lie p•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kin•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Q•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('M•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Regalia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arc•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Accipe s•', 'ORG'): 1; ('icet', 'ORG'): 1; ('virtu•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pulumque vid•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('licet Christianum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('def•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Archb•', 'ORG'): 1; ('domine', 'NORP'): 1; ('bonorum', 'GPE'): 1; ('adeptam benè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sibi', 'GPE'): 1; ('praestitum', 'GPE'): 1; ('honorem dign•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Honorifica', 'GPE'): 1; ('uberi', 'ORG'): 1; ('diebus', 'ORG'): 1; ('regno', 'GPE'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('qua intelligas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('iam doce', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lapsis', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui de se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('introierit s• … lvabitur .', 'ORG'): 1; ('ipse qui est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui aperit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemo aperit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('umbra mortis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('merearis eum de quo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tua deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('benedicat tibi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lor•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rtaker o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ete•', 'ORG'): 1; ('g•', 'NORP'): 1; ('rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Maj•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sanctis', 'NORP'): 1; ('propinquiorem ◊', 'ORG'): 1; ('tanto', 'GPE'): 1; ('locis congruis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cleri', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'ORG'): 1; ('rex r•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hom•', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('A•', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui tua miseration•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Regni guberna•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('virtutum etiam omnium', 'ORG'): 1; ('voraginem devitare', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•', 'LOC'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('the Nicene Creed', 'ORG'): 1; ('ntiam srumenti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('benedictionibus repleatur', 'ORG'): 1; ('montibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('benedictionibus', 'GPE'): 1; ('jacentibus deorsum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Natio•', 'ORG'): 1; ('ado•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bl• …', 'ORG'): 1; ('sse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('te•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pora alieni vitam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Domin•', 'ORG'): 1; ('se circumcingi desiderat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('majestatis', 'ORG'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('licet indignas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('auth•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Apostolorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Psalmista', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tuo super', 'ORG'): 1; ('eundem vim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('exerceas molem', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam Christiani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('viduas', 'ORG'): 1; ('pupillos clementer', 'ORG'): 1; ('defendas', 'ORG'): 1; ('desolata', 'GPE'): 1; ('ulciscaris injusta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('justitiaeque cultor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Armill', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quibus intelligas omnes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Armill', 'ORG'): 1; ('the Abbor of Westminster', 'ORG'): 1; ('Divinae potestati esse subjecta•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('quenquam', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('terris', 'GPE'): 1; ('nisi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('collocata de coelis', 'ORG'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the four quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('han•', 'GPE'): 1; ('tuum jacobum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('domine divitia•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('misericordia tua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jugiter famuletur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gal•', 'ORG'): 1; ('multiplici', 'GPE'): 1; ('coronam', 'ORG'): 1; ('ipse largiente', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ou• … ministry', 'ORG'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('populi', 'GPE'): 1; ('ita perseveres auctor', 'ORG'): 1; ('cum rege regum glorieris cui est', 'ORG'): 1; ('gloria per aeterna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1"
A56163,17 | 15530,prayer end archbishop breast shoulder point shoulder bough arm crown,king: 0.45; lord: 0.45; god: 0.45; archbishop: 0.45; crown: 0.45; hand: 0.45; people: 0.45; prayer: 0.45; majesty: 0.3; word: 0.25; sword: 0.25; head: 0.1; servant: 0.05; plurim: 0.05; pio: 0.05; prelate: 0.05; precept: 0.05; praesens: 0.05; power: 0.05; popul: 0.05; point: 0.05; poet: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 11; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('England', 'GPE'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('God', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 2; ('J. A. B.', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the king goerh', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chamb', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hea•', 'ORG'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Infid•', 'ORG'): 1; ('un', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marshals', 'ORG'): 1; ('earl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ju•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('T. D•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('70', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Diodorus Siculus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('lotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('insignibus splendidâque', 'ORG'): 1; ('mos erat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aegyptiorum •', 'ORG'): 1; ('cum bonis', 'ORG'): 1; ('caeteris', 'GPE'): 1; ('regi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('TUENTI', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod videlicet piam ergâ Deo•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magnanimus', 'ORG'): 1; ('mend• … cio', 'ORG'): 1; ('tandem omnis concupiscentiae victor', 'ORG'): 1; ('gratiam repend•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('peroravit antistes', 'GPE'): 1; ('regem quidem culpa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eximens', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vitam diis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('regem exhortaretur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ille cebris', 'ORG'): 1; ('modestiam', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('•', 'ORG'): 1; ('libellis sacerdos consulta quaedam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vitam conducentia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sacris praelegebat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('animo consideratas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('praescriptam', 'ORG'): 1; ('administrationem simili', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etiam de ambulandi', 'ORG'): 1; ('definitum', 'ORG'): 1; ('erat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('certam', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('repletionem immodicam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hâc ergà subdito', 'ORG'): 1; ('collegia', 'GPE'): 1; ('non tàm de uxoribus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('MEMORATIS INTEGRUM', 'ORG'): 1; ('STA•', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ad h• … plurim• …', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maxima', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Claudian', 'NORP'): 1; ('vitam qui debet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quantum', 'ORG'): 1; ('secreti numi•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Imperii', 'GPE'): 1; ('rependi•', 'ORG'): 1; ('alterna vicem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cum Reg•', 'ORG'): 1; ('gradibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Unaque', 'GPE'): 1; ('Augustus •', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('196', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('197', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quisquis sub', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nunquam libertas gratior', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam sub', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seu', 'ORG'): 1; ('p• … seu', 'ORG'): 1; ('de s• … judicium non indignatur haberi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Si•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('do•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('moribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Verior Augusti', 'FAC'): 1; ('fiducia belli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pristina Romuleis', 'ORG'): 1; ('artibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('larem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Auspiciis', 'ORG'): 1; ('nom de', 'ORG'): 1; ('vostre majesty', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam •', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1"
A54202,26,truth postscript complaint Unfair enemy God alarm a•d almighty power,christian: 0.5; word: 0.5; principle: 0.45; dialogue: 0.45; religion: 0.45; whitehead: 0.4; world: 0.35; way: 0.35; write: 0.3; defence: 0.25; penn: 0.25; enemy: 0.25; practice: 0.2; book: 0.15; forgery: 0.1; name: 0.05,"('G. Whitehead', 'PERSON'): 5; ('W. Penn', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('J. Owen', 'PERSON'): 2; ('T. Danson', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Francis Howgil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Thomas Hicks', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Quaker', 'ORG'): 2; ('Unfair', 'ORG'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('G. fox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rusticus', 'GPE'): 1; ('R. Baxter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gauden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Edward Burroughs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('T. Vincent', 'GPE'): 1; ('W. Maddox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('A. Smalwood', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Geo', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Keith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('T. Taylor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('T. Jenner', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('R. Gorden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('J. Newman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('W. Burnet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vindicated', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('socinians', 'NORP'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nick-name', 'PERSON'): 1; ('J. Faldo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('the Christian-Quaker', 'ORG'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('W.P.', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tho', 'GPE'): 1; ('Baptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('George Whitehead', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year , 1673', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dsiegn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('68', 'DATE'): 1; ('69', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('88', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('n••', 'PERSON'): 1"
A56381,4,rule principle justice reference God man instance god relation creature,god: 0.5; creature: 0.5; power: 0.5; man: 0.5; right: 0.5; condition: 0.45; thing: 0.45; dominion: 0.4; goodness: 0.4; sovereignty: 0.25; innocent: 0.2; adam: 0.15; misery: 0.1; person: 0.05; justice: 0.05,"('Adam', 'PERSON'): 8; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('mosaic', 'PRODUCT'): 3; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('forlese', 'NORP'): 2; ('duo cum idem faciunt saepe', 'ORG'): 1; ('illi non licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seventy thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Davids', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sauls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heraclitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('tragedian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Initium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ethic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gassendus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Episcopius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcopeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Curcellaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hobs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1"
A51289,19,CHAP. v. form invocation bless virgin use church Rome devotion,prayer: 0.5; paragraph: 0.5; virgin: 0.45; god: 0.45; invocation: 0.45; christ: 0.45; church: 0.4; bless: 0.4; thing: 0.3; son: 0.25; answer: 0.25; rosary: 0.1; soul: 0.1; power: 0.05; paradise: 0.05; part: 0.05; patronage: 0.05; peccata: 0.05; peril: 0.05; poenae: 0.05; pontificals: 0.05,"('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('cordis mei', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Paragraph', 'NORP'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('maris', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Chemnitius', 'NORP'): 2; ('veni', 'ORG'): 2; ('Signa', 'ORG'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dulia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hyperdulia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gratiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod suspiro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mea sana vulnera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gratiarum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dulcis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eruditus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constans', 'NORP'): 1; ('•orde', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•odie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('custodiam tuam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('malis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Diaboli', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('•ora', 'ORG'): 1; ('mihi assistas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('Devotionist', 'ORG'): 1; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cor meum illumina', 'ORG'): 1; ('gloriosa virgo maria', 'ORG'): 1; ('Libera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mater illuminationis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('salut••meae m•ntis', 'NORP'): 1; ('exaudi ▪ domina', 'ORG'): 1; ('adesto propitia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mundentur sorde', 'ORG'): 1; ('illuminent•r', 'ORG'): 1; ('gloriosa domina', 'ORG'): 1; ('porta', 'GPE'): 1; ('salutis', 'NORP'): 1; ('finem', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vitae munera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sorde aufer piaculi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Poenae', 'ORG'): 1; ('SheChrist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paragraph .', 'GPE'): 1; ('the Hortulus Animae', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canticum', 'GPE'): 1; ('dignare dulcis maria nunc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Oratio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mariam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dulcedo', 'GPE'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hortulus Animae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chemnitius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('135', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paragraph', 'LOC'): 1; ('Paragraph', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hortulus Animae', 'FAC'): 1; ('Thyatira', 'PERSON'): 1"
A51289,20,Paragraph invocation daughter God sense argument title boon creature general,god: 0.3; daughter: 0.3; virgin: 0.3; christ: 0.3; psalm: 0.3; church: 0.3; son: 0.3; form: 0.25; say: 0.2; piece: 0.2; phrase: 0.2; power: 0.2; point: 0.2; plenary: 0.2; prayer: 0.2; passage: 0.2; patronage: 0.2; prerogative: 0.2; pergamus: 0.2; title: 0.1; call: 0.1; invocation: 0.1; psalter: 0.05; sense: 0.05; salvation: 0.05,"('Pergamus', 'GPE'): 3; ('Thyatira', 'PERSON'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Fons', 'ORG'): 2; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paragraph', 'NORP'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('quae publicè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•oatibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chemnitius', 'NORP'): 1; ('the council of Constance', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hortulus Animae', 'FAC'): 1; ('Laudamus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Gratiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('maris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('blaspemo•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ingratiam tuam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inclina ad', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aurem tuam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('commendo spiritum meum', 'ORG'): 1; ('totam vit•m', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('71', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Resperge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cor meum dulcedine tua .', 'ORG'): 1; ('huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paradisi', 'NORP'): 1; ('Psalm 104', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clementia', 'GPE'): 1; ('seculis aeternis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('generationem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psalm 117', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tua mundus perseverat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quem tu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('domina', 'GPE'): 1; ('quoniam desiderabiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tribulati estis', 'ORG'): 1; ('animabus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Psalm 81', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psalm 46', 'PERSON'): 1; ('manibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('virgini gloriosae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoniam ipsa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vianostrae reconciliationis', 'ORG'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('amor•m tuum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('anima mea', 'FAC'): 1; ('virgo sancta', 'ORG'): 1; ('meae', 'ORG'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('totius salutis meae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('God .', 'DATE'): 1; ('Illuminatrix', 'GPE'): 1; ('Flumen', 'GPE'): 1; ('mater d•i', 'PERSON'): 1; ('coeli', 'GPE'): 1; ('domina mundi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the Litaniae Mariae', 'FAC'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pergamus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicanor', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thyatira', 'GPE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sixtus', 'ORG'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1470', 'DATE'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mortis', 'PERSON'): 1"
A51289,28,CHAP. answer Paragraph image Christ worship •orship contrary doctrine council,image: 0.5; christ: 0.5; worship: 0.5; council: 0.5; god: 0.5; saint: 0.5; prototype: 0.45; man: 0.4; paragraph: 0.3; sense: 0.25; cross: 0.25; church: 0.1; term: 0.05; virgin: 0.05; latria: 0.05; thing: 0.05; honour: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 10; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('Latria', 'GPE'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Paragraph', 'NORP'): 5; ('Photius', 'ORG'): 5; ('Bonaventure', 'PERSON'): 5; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 5; ('Azorius', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Adrian', 'NORP'): 4; ('Analogum', 'PERSON'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Paragraph', 'LOC'): 4; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Dulia', 'GPE'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Nicene', 'ORG'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('John', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Rumwald', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 2; ('Irene', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 2; ('Bonaventure', 'GPE'): 2; ('Relativè', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paragraph', 'GPE'): 2; ('Photius', 'GPE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hyperdulia', 'GPE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Thomas Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sinon', 'FAC'): 2; ('Durandus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Veronica', 'ORG'): 2; ('Cranmer', 'ORG'): 2; ('ark', 'GPE'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('morning', 'TIME'): 2; ('expres•y', 'GPE'): 1; ('about 400 year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('the Nicene council', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Terminativè', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christ Terminativè', 'ORG'): 1; ('Transitivè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of nice speak', 'ORG'): 1; ('purpose•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paragraph', 'ORG'): 1; ('Instit', 'GPE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Theologorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cultu honorari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Latriae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hyperdulia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('6 to 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 to 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ have Latria', 'ORG'): 1; ('this council of nice', 'ORG'): 1; ('87.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of nice and of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gabriel Biel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('integr•ty', 'ORG'): 1; ('vanum etiam mendacemque', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chemnitius a Sinon', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('the next Paragraph', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('corpora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('procul pellantur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•nimici', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Aereae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Agnus', 'FAC'): 1; ('79', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chemnitius', 'NORP'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nicene council', 'ORG'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nominando', 'NORP'): 1; ('honorem ac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('altar ad honorem tuum', 'ORG'): 1; ('N.', 'NORP'): 1; ('digneris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pantheon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'GPE'): 1; ('ezeki•l', 'GPE'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Boxley', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hortulus Animae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Veronica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Johannes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Metonymis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Electa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Beata', 'ORG'): 1"
A51289,30,CHAP. answer antagonist chapter reply distinction paragraph reduce antagonist answer,church: 0.5; dr: 0.5; thorndike: 0.5; man: 0.5; idolatry: 0.5; god: 0.5; england: 0.4; truth: 0.3; error: 0.3; self: 0.3; chapter: 0.25; salvation: 0.15; doctor: 0.1; time: 0.05; exhortation: 0.05; name: 0.05; taylor: 0.05,"('England', 'GPE'): 12; ('Taylor', 'PERSON'): 9; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 6; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Apocalypse', 'ORG'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('potter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hammond', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Luciferians', 'NORP'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('x. the', 'ORG'): 1; ('this 10th', 'DATE'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be •ell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('n•r', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Schoolman', 'ORG'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('mores sweet harangue', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apocalypse', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Repl', 'ORG'): 1; ('whenas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Synopsis Prophetica', 'ORG'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Meroz', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Meroz', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antichristianism', 'NORP'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Synopsis', 'ORG'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('meek expectance', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romanism', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paragraph', 'LOC'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hooker', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('lucif•rians', 'NORP'): 1; ('2. dr', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•r', 'GPE'): 1; ('Topick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joseph Mede', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thorndike', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Downham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Armagh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('archbishop abbot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thorndikes', 'ORG'): 1; ('the 13th', 'DATE'): 1"
A53737,7,patience use self discourse reason animadversion satisfaction contrary end design,self: 0.5; man: 0.5; thing: 0.5; design: 0.5; religion: 0.5; peace: 0.5; discourse: 0.5; church: 0.45; reason: 0.45; advantage: 0.2; end: 0.15; animadversion: 0.1; part: 0.05; mistake: 0.05; person: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('cum victore', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Roman catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hesiod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicom', 'ORG'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thereon', 'GPE'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('audiam facta cum video', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('judicio miser', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wit•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cain', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('miht', 'ORG'): 1; ('quoniam superis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aversa voluntas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Samaritane', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Crescens', 'ORG'): 1; ('Justin', 'ORG'): 1; ('senate', 'ORG'): 1; ('arian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('irish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Crassus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Carbo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Plautus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Suspicio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('si surripnisse suspicer', 'ORG'): 1; ('jovi coronam de', 'ORG'): 1; ('astat summo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui tu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lett', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sedis', 'LOC'): 1; ('assiduis circumvolet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('another day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alcoran', 'PERSON'): 1; ('graculos de sedition querente', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tandem porcas insane minori', 'PERSON'): 1"
A53737,8,CHAP. vindication chapter animadversion method fiat Lux. Romanists doctrine merit,work: 0.45; merit: 0.45; god: 0.45; protestant: 0.45; doctrine: 0.45; grace: 0.45; word: 0.45; mercy: 0.3; faith: 0.3; christian: 0.2; man: 0.2; sin: 0.15; method: 0.1; mind: 0.05; plea: 0.05; philip: 0.05; pretend: 0.05; pour: 0.05; posture: 0.05; portion: 0.05; point: 0.05; poet: 0.05; pleasure: 0.05; principle: 0.05; righteousness: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('christian', 'NORP'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 3; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one day', 'DATE'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('so many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('vanum etiam mendacem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arena', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rhem', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Suarez', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thom', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bagus de merit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. d .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('uncouth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thuanus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('se quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('obtineret ;', 'PERSON'): 1; ('passionis merito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sibi merito vindicet', 'FAC'): 1; ('fiducia fretus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('innitentis domino suo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deleri non posse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi ab eo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the kingdom nf', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hadrian Animula', 'LOC'): 1; ('Hospes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('nudula nec', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jocos', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bellarmin', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('incertitudinem propriae justitiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inanis', 'NORP'): 1; ('fiduciam totam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sola', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vit', 'ORG'): 1; ('bell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('San.', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antuerpiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1631', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1"
A53737,9,CHAP. Iii defence chapter animadversion Principles receive gospel room Oure,gospel: 0.5; church: 0.5; religion: 0.5; principle: 0.5; christ: 0.45; pope: 0.4; thing: 0.35; receive: 0.25; man: 0.25; brittans: 0.25; whole: 0.25; inhabitant: 0.2; truth: 0.2; year: 0.15; britain: 0.15; sense: 0.05; self: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 25; ('Brittans', 'NORP'): 7; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 3; ('Saxons', 'NORP'): 3; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Claudius', 'NORP'): 3; ('english', 'NORP'): 2; ('Joseph of Arimathea', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Englishmen', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Palestine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Totilas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Belisarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('ipse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui Senatorii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('alia', 'GPE'): 1; ('multitudine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romae Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vasta ibi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Procopius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Goth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sigonius de Imper', 'ORG'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vrbs Roma', 'ORG'): 1; ('ac spectaculum', 'ORG'): 1; ('etiam hostibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greeks', 'GPE'): 1; ('tbracians', 'NORP'): 1; ('christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Austin', 'GPE'): 1; ('british', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Circumagi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pope Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John of Constantinople', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thes•i', 'ORG'): 1; ('amo', 'ORG'): 1; ('quondam puer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('hei mihi qualis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quantum mutatur', 'FAC'): 1; ('thirteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Capernaum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 1; ('about the fourteenth year', 'DATE'): 1; ('fifty three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the six year', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sundry year', 'DATE'): 1; ('that year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Simon Zelotes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('summo tempore Tiberii caesaris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tiberius Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('the thirty nine year', 'DATE'): 1; ('five or six year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the Roman - Church', 'ORG'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'DATE'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('41', 'DATE'): 1; ('Protea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Menelaus', 'ORG'): 1"
A53737,10,CHAP. IV. vindication chapter animadversion church Rome fall apostasy difference,church: 0.5; heresy: 0.5; idolatry: 0.5; god: 0.5; apostasy: 0.5; way: 0.45; worship: 0.45; faith: 0.4; fall: 0.4; man: 0.35; enquiry: 0.15; word: 0.1; self: 0.1; truth: 0.05; thing: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 5; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 5; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lateran', 'GPE'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('heresy', 'GPE'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day of old', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Laodicea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Totilas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dagon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('apostasy heresy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zerubbabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucilius', 'GPE'): 1; ('credunt signis', 'ORG'): 1; ('cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Creaturum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory de Valentia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('St Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dulcia mella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Geor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22ae quoth', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Enchirid', 'ORG'): 1; ('materis imaginem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gentiles deos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('venerabantur', 'GPE'): 1; ('hastam elevatum', 'GPE'): 1; ('quod narratur de lappis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quondam Aegyptii', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam eorum qui', 'ORG'): 1; ('paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('quoniam nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod homo de semetipso', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ad gloriosam ipsam virginem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('matrem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deiparae', 'NORP'): 1; ('10th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Stephen Arch•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Patras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gratiarum', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'ORG'): 1; ('heresy interemit', 'GPE'): 1; ('Concordia Principum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fieri', 'GPE'): 1; ('Omnium', 'GPE'): 1; ('Virginum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gloria humani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maria unica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dominaris astris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Inclyta', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ingredi', 'ORG'): 1; ('celsae', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou virgin', 'GPE'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Phoebe', 'GPE'): 1; ('Diana lucidum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('nihil urbe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maturo', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Lenis Itithia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucina', 'ORG'): 1; ('vocari seu Genitalis Diva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paragraph Hero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vives', 'ORG'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('de Civit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ult', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christiani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Divas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('multis', 'NORP'): 1; ('inter eorum opinionem de sanctis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; (""de n'est Diss"", 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Polidore Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tu nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('verte', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Homer', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thucydides', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apostasia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Moses', 'NORP'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrinus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Strom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Latines', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cato', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('heresi quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('florem sequitur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('heresy', 'PERSON'): 1"
A53737,12,CHAP. vindication chapter th• animadversion Scripture man truth instance remove,man: 0.5; scripture: 0.5; principle: 0.5; god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; church: 0.5; moderation: 0.5; way: 0.45; christ: 0.4; truth: 0.35; religion: 0.2; protestant: 0.1,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 8; ('christian', 'NORP'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('Puritan', 'GPE'): 4; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 4; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hereunto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('§', 'NORP'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('199', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the apostle day', 'DATE'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dominicans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tales Casus Cassandra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa 8. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('outward splendour', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hareticidium', 'ORG'): 1; ('christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('salvation hereafter', 'ORG'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romano', 'ORG'): 1; ('frailty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constance', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Huss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bellarmine de Laic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Priscillianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Basilius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alexius Comnenus', 'ORG'): 1; ('1100 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Merindol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Waldenses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Piedmont', 'GPE'): 1; ('Philip king', 'ORG'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('243', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nequicquam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Volle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Succidimus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cogendus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Creon', 'PERSON'): 1"
A53737,14 | 23315,V. Peter episcopacy apostleship Paul successor Peter John church proof,church: 0.5; christ: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; peter: 0.5; world: 0.45; authority: 0.4; truth: 0.4; word: 0.35; scripture: 0.3; faith: 0.25; thing: 0.2; pope: 0.05; self: 0.05; place: 0.05,"('Peter', 'PERSON'): 18; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 6; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('the day', 'DATE'): 5; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('st Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Benno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Systeme', 'GPE'): 1; ('Quintiliane', 'PERSON'): 1; ('colorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('St Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a few day', 'DATE'): 1; ('antio•h', 'ORG'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'ORG'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('bull', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Medusa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('terris', 'GPE'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Judaism', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jebovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aftaroth', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jeroboam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bethel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Damascus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jehoiaki•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zedekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeremiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Messiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('constantinopolitan', 'GPE'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('dutch', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the catholic Church', 'ORG'): 1; ('•nquiry', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1"
A53737,14 | 23321,Iii self pope matter religion subjection church assent teach determination,church: 0.5; christ: 0.5; catholic: 0.5; thing: 0.5; man: 0.5; world: 0.5; faith: 0.5; day: 0.4; roman: 0.4; god: 0.3; truth: 0.25; make: 0.05; self: 0.05; christians: 0.05,"('catholic', 'NORP'): 10; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 6; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('the catholic Church', 'ORG'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('their day', 'DATE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one day', 'DATE'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 1; ('the first three hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Clemens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Corinth', 'GPE'): 1; ('Corinth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('the next three century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Diocesaen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chalc•don', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phocas unto', 'FAC'): 1; ('Boniface', 'PERSON'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Timothy by', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hippocrates', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hippocrates', 'NORP'): 1; ('Julius Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Julio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Casare', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caesare', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nani Bibulo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vandal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hun', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Longobards', 'GPE'): 1; ('Totilas', 'GPE'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Fredrick', 'GPE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('catholic Church', 'ORG'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Robert duke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Normandy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saracens', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Mens', 'PERSON'): 1"
A53737,15,CHAP. proposal protestant principle moderation unity be speak principle disenable,man: 0.5; church: 0.5; world: 0.5; thing: 0.5; christ: 0.5; god: 0.5; way: 0.45; unity: 0.45; christians: 0.35; mind: 0.25; principle: 0.15; party: 0.15; religion: 0.1; moderation: 0.1,"('Christians', 'NORP'): 14; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 2; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Archimedes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Candidus', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nova', 'LOC'): 1; ('demittitur', 'NORP'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Idaea of christian', 'ORG'): 1; ('nati natorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('illis', 'GPE'): 1; ('christan', 'NORP'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Systemes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Procrustes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anathemas', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Lupis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('agnis quanta sortito', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iii', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Agricola', 'ORG'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vives', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jansenius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Evangelium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cuitristia', 'ORG'): 1; ('crimina noxia cordi', 'ORG'): 1; ('ipse pater pl•ton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tartareae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('oram', 'GPE'): 1; ('Colubris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('panem', 'ORG'): 1; ('ipsi fibe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('outward advantage', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vox ultima christi', 'ORG'): 1; ('nubes•', 'GPE'): 1"
A53737,18 | 23352,discourse purpose word set page thing deliver news Christianity reject,thing: 0.5; man: 0.5; truth: 0.5; christ: 0.5; gospel: 0.5; faith: 0.5; religion: 0.45; part: 0.35; god: 0.3; reject: 0.3; love: 0.3; authority: 0.15; reveal: 0.1; commission: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 25; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 7; ('christian', 'NORP'): 6; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('Systeme', 'GPE'): 4; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nequaquam coit', 'PERSON'): 2; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arianisme', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('Suffenus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('h•c', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('poema cum scribit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gaud•t', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sophist•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lucian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1; ('sarta gratia', 'ORG'): 1"
A53737,18 | 23356,way mean branch other error mistake man branch root gospel,church: 0.5; man: 0.5; thing: 0.5; truth: 0.5; god: 0.5; reason: 0.5; scripture: 0.5; argument: 0.4; christ: 0.4; error: 0.3; way: 0.2; knowledge: 0.15; ground: 0.05,"('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('presbyterians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 2; ('Roman catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Armenians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pagina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dicis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orestes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Quakers', 'ORG'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tempora mutantur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ulysses', 'ORG'): 1; ('Socinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('the church of old', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mortua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('corpora vivis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Apella', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Caesar Borgia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('to many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1"
A53737,19,CHAP. faith charity Roman catholic discourse page spend commendation abstract,scripture: 0.5; church: 0.5; respect: 0.5; book: 0.5; catholic: 0.45; authority: 0.4; man: 0.4; christ: 0.4; part: 0.35; write: 0.3; read: 0.25; faith: 0.15; discourse: 0.1; thing: 0.1; contempt: 0.05; account: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 5; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 5; ('quae', 'GPE'): 5; ('Roman catholic', 'NORP'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 3; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Andradius', 'ORG'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('Possis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('half a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('a hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Epistola', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Antiochus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Epiphanes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Damascus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dec. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('libris tradi voluit', 'ORG'): 1; ('traditionibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('frailty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('canonem seu', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epistola', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Doctrinae', 'ORG'): 1; ('haeretico scilicet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed dum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luthero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('theologiam atramentariam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bononia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Julius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('deni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod inter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oculi', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam', 'NORP'): 1; ('Evangelii', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('missa legi solet', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec eo amplius cuiquam mortalium', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam diu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•aedemq', 'PERSON'): 1; ('legi vulgo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac turbine conciliavit quibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nostris', 'GPE'): 1; ('fieri', 'GPE'): 1; ('hanc doctrinam nostram', 'ORG'): 1; ('diversam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('contrariam etiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('docto', 'GPE'): 1; ('clamandi finem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hermannus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aesop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Brentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hosius de authoritat', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Revera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'NORP'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('libris quibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mysteria conscripta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ad credendum', 'GPE'): 1; ('illis continentur', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gravissimâ impietatis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cr•cifie', 'ORG'): 1; ('prey sir', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jusus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1"
A53737,22,CHAP. power assign papist protestant king matter principle discuss compare,king: 0.5; power: 0.5; church: 0.5; pope: 0.5; authority: 0.5; subject: 0.5; thing: 0.45; head: 0.35; man: 0.35; matter: 0.3; protestant: 0.3; law: 0.1; person: 0.1; principle: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 5; ('presbyterians', 'NORP'): 4; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 3; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 3; ('Roman', 'PERSON'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('58', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Justinian', 'NORP'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 2; ('Augustinus', 'GPE'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ambigucus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epistola', 'GPE'): 1; ('No•', 'ORG'): 1; ('supreme power', 'ORG'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('68', 'DATE'): 1; ('quemvis licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Brachia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('a very few year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Britannorum Romanis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inaccessa loca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('jactu concussa quiescunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abiathar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Theodoret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernard , Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('Archiepisc', 'GPE'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('regno suo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vmpirage', 'FAC'): 1; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('one half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lotharius', 'ORG'): 1; ('supreme authority', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Socrat', 'GPE'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euseb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('162', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('166', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Crescon', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 6', 'LAW'): 1; ('Jona 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('one degree high', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('magno conatu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pontificum', 'LOC'): 1; ('•Siqua tegunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ligebus ullis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•ority', 'ORG'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('Roman catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three and four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Parry', 'GPE'): 1; ('Raviliac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mariana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Allen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Garnet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gerard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joshuah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('64', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmine Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Pont', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hostiensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Henry', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Nicholas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mediolanens ▪ assert', 'ORG'): 1; ('Carerius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Canonists', 'NORP'): 1; ('de Major', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Obed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Barclay', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bozius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Schioppius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Marta', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dominicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('de Cleric', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('100000', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('Marsilius of', 'ORG'): 1; ('Padua', 'GPE'): 1"
A53737,27,pseudo-synod Greeks call council Frankford send father instruct due worship,image: 0.5; worship: 0.5; god: 0.5; church: 0.5; thing: 0.5; christ: 0.45; council: 0.45; day: 0.4; use: 0.35; self: 0.2; man: 0.2; matter: 0.1; practice: 0.1; doctrine: 0.1; christians: 0.05; hadrian: 0.05; word: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('Hadrian', 'NORP'): 8; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 7; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 7; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Nicene', 'ORG'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 3; ('those day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('their day', 'DATE'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the council of Frankford', 'ORG'): 2; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 2; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Celsus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('Irene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('490', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Frankford', 'ORG'): 1; ('Saracen', 'ORG'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Credenus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tarasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anastasius Bibliothecarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ammoria', 'GPE'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theodosius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oriental', 'NORP'): 1; ('Palestine', 'GPE'): 1; ('the council of Frankfurt', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theodorus', 'GPE'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Job 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('Constiteram', 'ORG'): 1; ('cum subito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Roscius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ver', 'GPE'): 1; ('Herculis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non solum venerari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etiam osculari soliti fuerunt', 'ORG'): 1; ('Minutius Felix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Indies', 'ORG'): 1; ('Spaniards', 'NORP'): 1; ('Zemes', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Esaiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tharasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Talmud', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alcoran', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nicholas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cosma', 'GPE'): 1; ('Damiana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abgarus king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Justin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vienna', 'GPE'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Smyrna', 'GPE'): 1; ('Polycarpus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trajan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucian Philopatris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Theodoret haeret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Selene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iraeneus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pontius Pilate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tom 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexand', 'ORG'): 1; ('Strom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adhortat', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Idololatria', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('persian', 'NORP'): 1; ('scythian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Seres', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Minutius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hilarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ambrose , Cyrillus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nycene', 'ORG'): 1; ('600.', 'DATE'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('some hundred of year', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A53737,28,apprehension custom church matter nature tendency blame information reason change,god: 0.5; church: 0.5; scripture: 0.5; word: 0.5; thing: 0.5; people: 0.5; tongue: 0.5; man: 0.45; use: 0.4; write: 0.35; practice: 0.15; part: 0.05; mean: 0.05; language: 0.05,"('greek', 'NORP'): 11; ('latin', 'NORP'): 9; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 6; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John 6', 'PERSON'): 2; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('some thousand year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Babylonish', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Carbones', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Pedo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Librat', 'NORP'): 1; ('Antithetis', 'LOC'): 1; ('figuras lundatur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Compendius', 'FAC'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('n•y', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bibles', 'GPE'): 1; ('terris animae', 'ORG'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Corinth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quakers', 'ORG'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eighteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('59 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('4. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Galen', 'GPE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pentateuch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gothish', 'GPE'): 1; ('Armenian', 'NORP'): 1; ('aethiopian', 'GPE'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Synagogne', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ptolemy Philadelphus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Onias', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hebrews', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Palestina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Latins', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('this year 1663', 'DATE'): 1; ('latin empire', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('five hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chrysostom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('syrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('indian', 'NORP'): 1; ('persian', 'NORP'): 1; ('ethiopian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('the hebrew Church', 'ORG'): 1; ('the greek church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Syrians', 'NORP'): 1; ('many thousand year ago', 'DATE'): 1"
A59234,24,change name use way cause put effect effect put cause,put: 0.5; example: 0.5; name: 0.5; man: 0.5; thing: 0.5; gen: 0.5; metonymy: 0.5; effect: 0.35; subject: 0.25; cause: 0.2; god: 0.15; war: 0.15; exod: 0.15; see: 0.1; adjunct: 0.05; day: 0.05; met: 0.05,"('english', 'NORP'): 21; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 4; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.19', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Lyaeo', 'GPE'): 2; ('Curii', 'GPE'): 2; ('Germania', 'GPE'): 2; ('Vcalegon', 'ORG'): 2; ('Amaryllis', 'NORP'): 2; ('mar', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 2; ('20', 'DATE'): 2; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('22.20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 2; ('Gomorrah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19.9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('23.10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 2; ('Exod', 'GPE'): 2; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hannibal', 'ORG'): 2; ('Scipio', 'ORG'): 2; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nova nomina', 'LOC'): 1; ('1. Efficientis', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Inventoris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marte', 'GPE'): 1; ('Autoris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Juvenalis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Materiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aeris acervus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arundo', 'ORG'): 1; ('aut instrumenti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gladius', 'GPE'): 1; ('lingua', 'GPE'): 1; ('Clades Libyae', 'ORG'): 1; ('paterae', 'ORG'): 1; ('cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('aeta nulla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Libelli', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bacchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Juvenal', 'GPE'): 1; ('Livius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vulcan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sebastian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sebastian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tully', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.29 , 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('35.18', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('128', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('meet materiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aes', 'ORG'): 1; ('pro nummo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('invasit italiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('domibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('grape', 'ORG'): 1; ('115.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('105.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.25', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('gladius pro caede .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arma', 'NORP'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clades Lybiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lybiae intulerunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cause•h', 'ORG'): 1; ('9.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Crumena', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('civibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anglia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anglis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 1; ('13.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39.4', 'MONEY'): 1; ('10.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Troy', 'GPE'): 1; ('hominem d•v•rari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('domi meae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jewry', 'GPE'): 1; ('15.3', 'MONEY'): 1; ('18.3', 'MONEY'): 1; ('depart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae sedem habet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cordati', 'NORP'): 1; ('aut aliquando', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cor fortitudinem', 'ORG'): 1; ('oris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aestas', 'ORG'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('the evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('the morning and evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('32.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Issachar', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('man day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Esth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Messis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Messis', 'ORG'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('six year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('17.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Apollo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aencas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('17.10', 'MONEY'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('righteou•nesse', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paschal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Passeover', 'GPE'): 1; ('26.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Titus 3.5', 'LAW'): 1; ('31.53', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hannabal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 18.7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('85.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pro magistratu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('victoriam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('49.10', 'MONEY'): 1; ('13.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('aspera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seculis vixerunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('temeritas', 'GPE'): 1; ('prudentia', 'NORP'): 1; ('Juvenum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('juventus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Senectus', 'ORG'): 1; ('— oculisve aut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.16', 'DATE'): 1; ('viros bonos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pro Justo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Libelli', 'GPE'): 1; ('libraria', 'GPE'): 1; ('pro circo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('libellis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bibliothecis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.12 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.15', 'MONEY'): 1; ('11.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('erit ipsissima benedictio', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.2', 'MONEY'): 1; ('quam ipsa benedicto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vixit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('evigilabit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Met.', 'GPE'): 1; ('Juxta Terentium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hannibal ibi moratur', 'ORG'): 1; ('pro exercitu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Annibalis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hannibal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.21.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canaanite', 'GPE'): 1; ('18.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aris imponit honorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scenas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('57.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Crudeli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rapinis', 'GPE'): 1; ('contumeli•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('crudeli', 'ORG'): 1; ('mendicando quaerit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('honesta cibum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('12.5', 'MONEY'): 1; ('46.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A59234,26,nonlatinalphabet derive nonlatinalphabet dissimulation nonlatinalphabet eiro nonlatinalphabet simulator take dissimulation,word: 0.5; another: 0.5; thing: 0.5; speech: 0.5; trope: 0.5; god: 0.45; lord: 0.45; form: 0.45; catachresis: 0.35; contrary: 0.25; say: 0.15; voice: 0.1; name: 0.1; man: 0.1; hand: 0.05; example: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 8; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Catachresis', 'NORP'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('egregiam laudem', 'PERSON'): 2; ('english', 'NORP'): 2; ('Gnatho', 'PERSON'): 2; ('vir gregis', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 2; ('ironia', 'GPE'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('quam sentit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jocari', 'NORP'): 1; ('potius dedecus', 'ORG'): 1; ('infamiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('foediffimè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('foedè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('alter erit maculis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arden', 'GPE'): 1; ('hunc ego si potui tantum 1 sperare dolorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sperare', 'PERSON'): 1; ('squalentibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('splendentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the persian army', 'ORG'): 1; ('Macedon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thraso', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thraso', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.22', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('14.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26.45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Micaiah', 'ORG'): 1; ('2• .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ramoth-Gilead', 'ORG'): 1; ('18.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jo•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•o•bt', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('Amos 4.4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('CAtachresis', 'NORP'): 1; ('contra•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('spee•h', 'ORG'): 1; ('ultorem promisi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vir gregis ipse caper', 'PERSON'): 1; ('capitis nive', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cani capilli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('spera•e dolo•em', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lauro', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('horseleech', 'ORG'): 1; ('137.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('46.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('metalepsi', 'GPE'): 1; ('quidam gradus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil ipse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quem tropum magis affectamus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1"
