tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A09135,21,sacerdote moor Ignatius Christum Ribadiner Ignace sermon Barcelona lib ca.,ignace: 0.5; lib: 0.5; miracle: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.45; day: 0.45; ribadiner: 0.45; xauier: 0.4; jesuit: 0.4; matter: 0.35; ca: 0.35; christ: 0.15,"('Ignace', 'PERSON'): 30; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 15; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Xauier', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 6; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 5; ('tur', 'GPE'): 5; ('Rib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 4; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Maffee', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Indies', 'ORG'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('seven hour', 'TIME'): 2; ('Maff', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('forty day', 'DATE'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 2; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Justinian', 'NORP'): 2; ('french', 'NORP'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('maflee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('eundem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Barcelona', 'GPE'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isabel Rousset', 'ORG'): 1; ('7. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Saturday', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven whole hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('the next Saturday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vesper', 'GPE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mount Cassin', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rib.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ozius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Padua', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam reliqui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gloria { que', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simon Roderic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter Faur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Silas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Morpheus', 'GPE'): 1; ('the apostle day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Salomen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Maffee', 'GPE'): 1; ('his young year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lewes', 'NORP'): 1; ('Loyola', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hozius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Benet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dominic', 'GPE'): 1; ('eight year', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven month', 'DATE'): 1; ('the university of Paris', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iames Laniez', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ʋersoris', 'NORP'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('pveri nasum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frances Xauier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Portugal', 'GPE'): 1; ('Horace Tursellin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. turs', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the ministry of other', 'ORG'): 1; ('Xauier', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Neophylum', 'ORG'): 1; ('the virgin marie', 'FAC'): 1; ('non opitulaberis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six month', 'DATE'): 1; ('two and twenty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('as many night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Sarra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tursellin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Xauier', 'GPE'): 1; ('Justinian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('late year', 'DATE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theodore Beza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('solutam et impexā', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maffee , Ribadiner', 'ORG'): 1; ('Piers', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lancelot Dulac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tristan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romant', 'ORG'): 1"
A02430,12,devil net bait partiality officer speech buyer seller evil excuse,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; heart: 0.5; fornication: 0.5; eye: 0.5; lust: 0.5; starch: 0.5; christ: 0.5; lord: 0.45; heaven: 0.3; fornicator: 0.15; evil: 0.05; woman: 0.05,"('Satan', 'GPE'): 3; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 3; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('eschew', 'ORG'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deceit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iam. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('sempiternam', 'GPE'): 1; ('memoriam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one day three', 'DATE'): 1; ('19.13', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Sodom', 'GPE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39.8', 'MONEY'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nicholaitan', 'ORG'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Asotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Asmodeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sam 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vriah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sara', 'GPE'): 1; ('Salax', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tobias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sara', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('101', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these last lustful day', 'DATE'): 1; ('7.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A02430,18,pride combine fashion man monster ruff ruffian boy head cut,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; body: 0.5; word: 0.5; christ: 0.45; self: 0.45; pride: 0.4; excess: 0.4; apparel: 0.3; skin: 0.3; soul: 0.2; time: 0.15; flesh: 0.15; shame: 0.1; heart: 0.05; household: 0.05,"('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nitimur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Spaniards', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ecclus', 'GPE'): 1; ('19.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('incessu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('verecundiam :', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.14', 'MONEY'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eve', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sara', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cynicus', 'GPE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Monta', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sophocles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aurelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lacedaemon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dionysius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gehesa', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jehovae .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('last 3. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Acrothorax', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Acolastus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A02430,25,Sodom sister consume world drown find God fire word world,hell: 0.45; fire: 0.45; god: 0.45; devil: 0.45; soul: 0.45; man: 0.45; pang: 0.4; pleasure: 0.4; world: 0.4; pain: 0.35; people: 0.2; prophesy: 0.05; propassion: 0.05; punish: 0.05; psalm: 0.05; ps: 0.05; prosperity: 0.05; prophet: 0.05; quench: 0.05; preserve: 0.05; prepare: 0.05; body: 0.05,"('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('18.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mark', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ʋer', 'ORG'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dulce diabolo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('brutish bawd', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cozener', 'ORG'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('no rest day', 'DATE'): 1; ('quoniam nec', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.24', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('torment one minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('deuteron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ʋirgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('aeneyde', 'ORG'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iulians', 'NORP'): 1"
A02430,28,job misery redeemer day earth skin worm body flesh God,god: 0.5; virtue: 0.5; body: 0.5; honour: 0.45; praise: 0.45; self: 0.45; lord: 0.4; heart: 0.4; eye: 0.4; soul: 0.35; heaven: 0.25; jesus: 0.2; world: 0.1; sin: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 7; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('19.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the latter day', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gloria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deo', 'LOC'): 1; ('66.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('PROV', 'ORG'): 1; ('23.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pray hearty', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('moon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('all the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('W.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Oxford', 'GPE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('H.L.', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Crosley', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1612', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Derby', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vilius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('auro', 'ORG'): 1; ('virtutibus aurum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('oculo eligunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non animo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('peccat qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('neminem timendo ad summū', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abnuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mela', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sigismond', 'PERSON'): 1"
A20158,2,patronage pardon acceptance token mind worship commandment Christ Jesus D.,world: 0.45; man: 0.45; vanity: 0.45; heaven: 0.45; life: 0.45; god: 0.45; hell: 0.45; sea: 0.4; day: 0.3; judgement: 0.25; torment: 0.2; christian: 0.15; operation: 0.05; occident: 0.05; part: 0.05; pardon: 0.05; pain: 0.05; ornament: 0.05; orient: 0.05; peace: 0.05; neglect: 0.05; navigation: 0.05; felicity: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('the day', 'DATE'): 4; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('comfort', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jehova', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vide praefa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jonas 1 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('a few year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de leg l. 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gratianus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caligula , Nero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heliogabalus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cypr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iohan', 'GPE'): 1; ('6.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A20158,8,CHAP. view vanity call good body youth oracle Esa. censure,man: 0.5; life: 0.5; beauty: 0.5; youth: 0.5; day: 0.5; death: 0.5; time: 0.45; age: 0.4; god: 0.35; sickness: 0.25; lord: 0.15; vanity: 0.1; body: 0.1; world: 0.1; psal: 0.05; health: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('David', 'PERSON'): 10; ('the day', 'DATE'): 6; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 5; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Cic', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Naomi', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('our day', 'DATE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('their day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Hieron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rosamund', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('sec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Esa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezekiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('1 kin', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('18.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nehushtan', 'GPE'): 1; ('39.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Selah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('71', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fabian', 'NORP'): 1; ('225', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('William Rufus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Basilius Macedo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ignatius Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('princip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('libris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sucton', 'GPE'): 1; ('Drusus Pompey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Claudius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gaguin', 'GPE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Navarre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pliny', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('natu li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7 7 cap', 'DATE'): 1; ('Marius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Munster', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 awl Gel', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('A• Seneca Ep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('71', 'DATE'): 1; ('104.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Terentius Varro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fabius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plutarc', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fab', 'ORG'): 1; ('64000', 'DATE'): 1; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nepot', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chrysostom', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Serm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.11.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eccl•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('119.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quantum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.3', 'MONEY'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bethlehem', 'ORG'): 1; ('ruth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Naomi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thersites', 'GPE'): 1; ('Narcissus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bathsheba', 'GPE'): 1; ('9.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('phoenician', 'NORP'): 1; ('Herod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucretia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Virginia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Liu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Absalon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sam 18', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Palestina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peneius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daphne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('votoque tuo tua forma', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ovid Met', 'ORG'): 1; ('119.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deck', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.10.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abishai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Benaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 23.18.20', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('9.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Menander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.2', 'MONEY'): 1; ('14.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 1; ('many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israelite', 'NORP'): 1; ('Baltasar', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Shunamites', 'LAW'): 1; ('2. kin', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Passim in Psalmis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Q. Curt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dang•r', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Moab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('48.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('78.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abimelech', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sara', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Reu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('94.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.30 32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aug. Confes.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aegypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chanaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sodom', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('section 4', 'LAW'): 1; ('g•d', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.2 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gen 47.9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('man year', 'DATE'): 1; ('90.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'MONEY'): 1; ('1.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hereof Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tirpsi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ierome', 'ORG'): 1; ('heliador', 'GPE'): 1; ('ten year', 'DATE'): 1; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A26371,21,CHAP. Xiv examination ground contempt clergy condition world extraction another,man: 0.5; clergy: 0.5; person: 0.5; god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; respect: 0.45; office: 0.45; priest: 0.45; religion: 0.4; world: 0.3; people: 0.3; christ: 0.1; whole: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('A. Gellius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('meek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('noblesse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fronto Cornelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scimpodium Graeciense', 'ORG'): 1; ('Doctrina', 'GPE'): 1; ('viris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucius Murena', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Murena', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ridley', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Felicity', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nobles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Teraphim', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clergy', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam 8.7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epictetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('factis procul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Poule', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Novis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chaucer', 'GPE'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('5.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Syriack', 'ORG'): 1; ('D. L.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Levit', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.3 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('quotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui sit ita moratus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gloriam', 'PERSON'): 1"
A29696,5 | 15194,soul hell god another atheist atheist wall London turn ash,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; atheist: 0.5; london: 0.5; time: 0.5; wall: 0.45; city: 0.4; world: 0.35; luxury: 0.25; lord: 0.25; glory: 0.2; hell: 0.2; heaven: 0.2; sin: 0.15; atheism: 0.05,"('London', 'GPE'): 19; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Psal', 'LOC'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lucian', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Chaldeans', 'NORP'): 2; ('last six year', 'DATE'): 2; ('10. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 1; ('Isa. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezek', 'GPE'): 1; ('9 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('73.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Titus 1', 'LAW'): 1; ('Machiavelli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spira', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cain', 'ORG'): 1; ('18. 6. 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Boristenesa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epicurius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Deicidium', 'ORG'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('James 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('16. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mat 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mentiuntur qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('noctu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Du Bart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the world|be a school', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Francis Taylor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sennacherib tomb', 'GPE'): 1; ('Herodot', 'GPE'): 1; ('assyrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Diagoras', 'GPE'): 1; ('half a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('a million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these last year', 'DATE'): 1; ('mark', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kingdom•', 'GPE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Caldees', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zion', 'GPE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'ORG'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gomorrah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Apicius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cyrus the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Astyages', 'PERSON'): 1; ('yesterday', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marcus Antonius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Darius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('malle se vitam quàm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theotimus', 'ORG'): 1; ('prodiga•ly', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('sepulchre', 'GPE'): 1; ('6. 19 second', 'TIME'): 1; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 1; ('one hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa. 49', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1"
A29696,6 | 15368,extensiveness fire self wind wall city parish consume hour fire,fire: 0.5; man: 0.5; hand: 0.5; city: 0.5; london: 0.5; lord: 0.5; flame: 0.5; house: 0.5; citizen: 0.45; heart: 0.25; god: 0.1; day: 0.1; king: 0.05; spirit: 0.05,"('London', 'GPE'): 28; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 8; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('14', 'DATE'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('four day', 'DATE'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 2; ('52.', 'DATE'): 2; ('13', 'DATE'): 2; ('15', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 2; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 2; ('76', 'DATE'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eighty one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Aegypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year before', 'DATE'): 1; ('more than 13000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('20. 47', 'DATE'): 1; ('Parma', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('21. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Libanon', 'GPE'): 1; ('the king house', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lebanon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 1; ('125', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chaldeans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nebuzaradan', 'ORG'): 1; ('the twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('William', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Richard Bakers', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aldgate', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('255', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('king royal palace', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jeremiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('741', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4034', 'DATE'): 1; ('745', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 41', 'DATE'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tacit', 'ORG'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('some year before', 'DATE'): 1; ('fourteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('64', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('80', 'DATE'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Commodius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1275', 'DATE'): 1; ('November', 'DATE'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('almost five hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'GPE'): 1; ('465', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('September', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28. 65', 'DATE'): 1; ('frigh•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('flam•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Benjamin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'LOC'): 1; ('Senacheribs', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('19 36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Belshazzar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('151', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('152', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cher•b', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Manasseh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tu•liw Hostilius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'NORP'): 1; ('tw•', 'NORP'): 1; ('pavorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('five pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('ten pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('twenty pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('thirty pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('forty pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('fifty pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1"
A29696,6 | 15452,God overturn London inhabitant moment earthquake Isa. 1• Psal• •8,fire: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; curse: 0.5; earthquake: 0.5; house: 0.45; world: 0.45; city: 0.45; earth: 0.4; hell: 0.25,"('London', 'GPE'): 8; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 2; ('thirteen', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Antiq', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Korah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Dathan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Abiram', 'ORG'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('fox', 'ORG'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('38', 'DATE'): 2; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tiberius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Trajan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Campania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ferraria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('1569', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('forty hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year 1171', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tripoli', 'GPE'): 1; ('Damascus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antiochia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Loradin', 'GPE'): 1; ('per•sh•d', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('defac•d', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year 1509', 'DATE'): 1; ('September', 'DATE'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('M•lm•sbu••', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ho•eden', 'GPE'): 1; ('the elev•n•• year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Henry the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('January', 'DATE'): 1; ('richa•d Ba••rs chron•cle', 'ORG'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ely', 'GPE'): 1; ('N•rfolk', 'GPE'): 1; ('Suffolk', 'GPE'): 1; ('steepl•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('the four and twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Derlington', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Durham', 'GPE'): 1; ('from morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Leyland', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year 1666', 'DATE'): 1; ('c•ty', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a few hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1584', 'DATE'): 1; ('Polan', 'GPE'): 1; ('one half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rhetia', 'GPE'): 1; ('1618', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aug. 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chronol', 'ORG'): 1; ('fif•een hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ʋzziah king Amos 1. 1. of Judah', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ʋzziah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 c . 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anthony', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Actian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Herod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judaea', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirty thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('ov•r', 'NORP'): 1; ('16. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Korah', 'GPE'): 1; ('a•l', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten thousand thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('19', 'MONEY'): 1; ('rich•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('h•s', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('8. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pat•imo•iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 13', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 24', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('jewel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('107', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('4. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('this present hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('heb 11', 'LAW'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('desar•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('satin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nebuchadn•zzar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Betty', 'ORG'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gen 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('5 23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('posteri•y', 'GPE'): 1; ('Belshazzar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nabuchadnezzar', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('4. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sphynx', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nov•', 'ORG'): 1; ('A•solom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hagar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ishmael', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cain', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('12. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('depart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arcadia', 'GPE'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cyril', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dionys', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('301', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A29696,6 | 15482,fire body soul fire body soul soul pain pain soul,fire: 0.5; hell: 0.5; sinner: 0.5; torment: 0.5; soul: 0.5; sin: 0.45; punishment: 0.45; man: 0.4; body: 0.35; god: 0.35; damn: 0.3; end: 0.15; year: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('London', 'GPE'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'DATE'): 2; ('9', 'DATE'): 2; ('35', 'DATE'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('August', 'DATE'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('21', 'DATE'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('dest•oy', 'NORP'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('one half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('the 2', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the great day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Simeon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('44 , 46', 'DATE'): 1; ('48', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('27. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nunqu•m', 'ORG'): 1; ('alway•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two hundred and fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('consume', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tha•', 'GPE'): 1; ('nisi conscie•tiae horror•m', 'ORG'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('no rest day', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('•ell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trajan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Falconella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mor•e', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lia millia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Myriades of year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trismegistus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alcoran', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('160', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('198', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Olympius', 'ORG'): 1; ('jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('so many million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Drexel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jackson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('as many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('how many million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('w•ep', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('John 15', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a thousand thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('million of year', 'DATE'): 1; ('socinians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. l. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Origen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('John 3. 17. 18 , 36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('69', 'DATE'): 1; ('70', 'DATE'): 1; ('71', 'DATE'): 1; ('74', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 54', 'DATE'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('56', 'DATE'): 1; ('57', 'DATE'): 1; ('58', 'DATE'): 1; ('20. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('b•ood', 'ORG'): 1; ('leo de Pas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Polium', 'GPE'): 1; ('four or five day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a few year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('aeter••m', 'GPE'): 1; ('sinner sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nunquam voluit', 'ORG'): 1; ('3. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('aeter•o', 'ORG'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('quam diu vivit', 'PERSON'): 1"
A29696,6 | 15535,peace sin Satan world divine withdrawing peace interrupt lose storm,god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; peace: 0.5; man: 0.5; world: 0.5; judgement: 0.5; fire: 0.35; people: 0.35; house: 0.25; crown: 0.2; way: 0.15; sin: 0.15; christ: 0.15; righteousness: 0.1; providence: 0.1; day: 0.05; son: 0.05; word: 0.05; hand: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 9; ('christian', 'NORP'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('London', 'GPE'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Achans', 'NORP'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 3; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('h•s', 'ORG'): 2; ('32', 'DATE'): 2; ('9 25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('28', 'DATE'): 2; ('29', 'DATE'): 2; ('9 6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('8. 12', 'DATE'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('42', 'DATE'): 2; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 2; ('5', 'DATE'): 2; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Shalom', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Naomi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Marah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Job 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Salvian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•reatest', 'LOC'): 1; ('hi•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('l•t', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Midas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('gold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Evagrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cedrenus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sinesius the bishop', 'ORG'): 1; ('three hundred pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the very next night', 'TIME'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41 ,', 'DATE'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the great day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('c•n', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('18 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Davids', 'GPE'): 1; ('three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('9 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('commoda prophanis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Incommoda', 'ORG'): 1; ('Psalm 77', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11. 33', 'DATE'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vives', 'ORG'): 1; ('a dark night', 'TIME'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Marcia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'DATE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Edom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ammon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Moab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day of God', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezek', 'ORG'): 1; ('18. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Babylonish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Chron', 'ORG'): 1; ('j•ws', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 24', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'MONEY'): 1; ('12 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('d•egs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Egyptians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Epigramm', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('18. 25. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Damam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Joshuah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gibeon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joshua 12', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('aa•on h•ld', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the very first day', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Angeronia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Volupia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('10. 34', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('39 9', 'TIME'): 1"
A29696,6 | 15588,burn citizen time time Pythagoras time Coel• soul heaven pearl,world: 0.5; man: 0.5; thing: 0.5; christ: 0.5; god: 0.5; time: 0.5; riches: 0.5; soul: 0.5; heart: 0.45; heaven: 0.45; love: 0.05; burn: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('thou', 'GPE'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 4; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('21', 'DATE'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15.', 'DATE'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Pythagoras', 'LOC'): 1; ('many hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Pharaohs', 'ORG'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('8. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Piggs', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('befor•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('ed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ezek', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('33. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('couns•l', 'ORG'): 1; ('Z•cheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('arabic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Basilius', 'ORG'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. 14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('citiz•ns', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jonahs', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ult', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jonah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eden', 'GPE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Heraclitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('37. 35', 'DATE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cruise', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('r•memb•r', 'ORG'): 1; ('m•y', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pecuniam da quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('spiri•', 'LOC'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('th•se', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a few hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('fig', 'ORG'): 1; ('6. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('g•d', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 33', 'DATE'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Seneca', 'GPE'): 1; ('4 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mordicai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Josiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('22', 'MONEY'): 1; ('3. 33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniels', 'ORG'): 1; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 1; ('o• •', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Glaucus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Diomedes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Menot', 'ORG'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('so many penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hamah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hamon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mammon', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('8. 32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('3. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cephas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('char•er', 'ORG'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Josephs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hamar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sechem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34.', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A29696,6 | 15635,man riches mite Job Psal. lord saint want lion hunger,world: 0.5; thing: 0.5; god: 0.5; sin: 0.5; man: 0.5; life: 0.5; job: 0.5; lord: 0.5; heart: 0.3; day: 0.3; riches: 0.25; iniquity: 0.1; rest: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 3; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('17', 'DATE'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('21', 'DATE'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('34', 'DATE'): 2; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('resp•ct', 'GPE'): 2; ('God', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('44', 'DATE'): 2; ('the great day', 'DATE'): 2; ('16', 'DATE'): 2; ('mark', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Spaniards', 'NORP'): 2; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'DATE'): 2; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('34. 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('13 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten pound', 'TIME'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('17. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('20. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuels', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Job 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('childr•n', 'ORG'): 1; ('d•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('b•r', 'ORG'): 1; ('this great day', 'DATE'): 1; ('themselv•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('6. 15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nobles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tully', 'PERSON'): 1; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('poss•sseth', 'NORP'): 1; ('17.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Naboth', 'ORG'): 1; ('pluta•ch', 'ORG'): 1; ('Syllae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Quintus Aurelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sylla', 'NORP'): 1; ('Zeli•u•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Americans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Melancthon', 'GPE'): 1; ('the •orld afford', 'EVENT'): 1; ('twenty four hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Latimer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Achans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lysimachus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('aust•n', 'ORG'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('inn', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('30. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 1 Tim', 'TIME'): 1; ('6. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('crown', 'ORG'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('30. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa. 49. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos 14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa. 30. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Job', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('79. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('51.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('8. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('36. 33', 'DATE'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1"
A26828,2,majesty subject wellwisher crown dignity lord commons court parliament Timothy,christ: 0.5; death: 0.5; love: 0.5; make: 0.5; jesus: 0.45; grace: 0.4; glory: 0.35; father: 0.3; god: 0.3; faith: 0.3; dear: 0.25; lord: 0.2; hope: 0.15; day: 0.1; sun: 0.1; sin: 0.05; star: 0.05,"('the day', 'DATE'): 8; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 8; ('morning', 'TIME'): 7; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 3; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('8.1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Timothy Batt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•yes', 'ORG'): 1; ('T. B.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('the eternal day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('moon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 15.5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('56', 'DATE'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pontious Pilate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rheuben', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('6.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jonathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A28620,6,outside nonlatinalphabet fear sin Dan. glory mortal ray sin grace,sin: 0.3; god: 0.3; evil: 0.3; judgement: 0.3; david: 0.3; word: 0.3; iniquity: 0.3; servant: 0.3; people: 0.3; prophet: 0.2; ray: 0.2; plague: 0.2; prayer: 0.2; preservation: 0.2; pressure: 0.2; prevail: 0.2; pride: 0.2; proof: 0.2; phrase: 0.2; world: 0.15; joab: 0.1; man: 0.05,"('David', 'PERSON'): 10; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Joab', 'PERSON'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Davids', 'ORG'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sin', 'ORG'): 2; ('it|be Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('archer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred fold', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('three month', 'DATE'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('mark David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('34.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1"
A28620,65,royalty faith heart-chearing-grace royalty faith grace faith grace soul consolation,god: 0.45; joy: 0.45; faith: 0.45; soul: 0.45; grace: 0.45; comfort: 0.4; condition: 0.4; heart: 0.35; promise: 0.35; people: 0.3; christ: 0.3; ground: 0.15; peace: 0.05; patience: 0.05; possession: 0.05; persecution: 0.05; perplexity: 0.05; power: 0.05; paul: 0.05; olive: 0.05; pardon: 0.05; thing: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('the year', 'DATE'): 2; ('sixteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Fruit', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.1.2', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fiducia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laetitia', 'ORG'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('such spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Heman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.3 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('77.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day of old', 'DATE'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('10.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A28620,108,god disappoint counsel god discover plot god remove evil god,god: 0.5; people: 0.5; lord: 0.5; church: 0.5; man: 0.5; thing: 0.5; promise: 0.5; experience: 0.4; engagement: 0.35; deliverance: 0.25; make: 0.1; water: 0.1; psal: 0.1; name: 0.1; rock: 0.05; egypt: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 18; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 8; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Deut', 'GPE'): 2; ('11', 'DATE'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ethiopia', 'GPE'): 2; ('32.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Exod', 'GPE'): 1; ('32.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jos', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('79.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('48.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('111.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Haman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Achitophel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balak', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Saul', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ahimelech', 'ORG'): 1; ('Goliath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 Sam', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('21.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Corin', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('22.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('51.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the ancient day', 'DATE'): 1; ('9.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Fidelis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•ecit', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('debitorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('god', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6 yea', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('91.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('54.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Seba', 'GPE'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('God .', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A28620,124,place Isa. enemy flood spirit lord standard violence phrase spirit,prayer: 0.5; god: 0.35; faith: 0.35; wonder: 0.35; sin: 0.35; church: 0.35; way: 0.3; mercy: 0.3; lord: 0.2; day: 0.2; power: 0.2; spirit: 0.15; pray: 0.15; profaneness: 0.15; prison: 0.15; pride: 0.15; preservation: 0.15; prophet: 0.15; place: 0.15; psal: 0.15; misery: 0.1; night: 0.1,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('54.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('147.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God .', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('— lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('9.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Acris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fervida', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('11.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('all night', 'TIME'): 1; ('David day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jonah', 'GPE'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('three night', 'TIME'): 1; ('21 day', 'DATE'): 1; ('21 night', 'TIME'): 1; ('forty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty night', 'TIME'): 1; ('four year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peter be .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.10 , 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Achan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A28903,8,Alas nymph thing consequence charm throne king arm spirit state,faith: 0.5; assurance: 0.5; god: 0.5; time: 0.5; answer: 0.5; reason: 0.45; mr: 0.4; definition: 0.35; dear: 0.3; friend: 0.2; sermon: 0.15; affiance: 0.1; nature: 0.1; day: 0.1; argument: 0.1; love: 0.1; city: 0.05; baxter: 0.05; cambridge: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('think|it', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the|common', 'PERSON'): 1; ('N. Baxter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('AVGVST', 'ORG'): 1; ('despir', 'ORG'): 1; ('CAP', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoniam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dilectio justitiae dicit', 'ORG'): 1; ('tua domine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Lichfield', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1635', 'DATE'): 1; ('two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bristol', 'ORG'): 1; ('the university of Cambridge', 'ORG'): 1; ('32.24.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32.28', 'MONEY'): 1; ('5.41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('3.12.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baxter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one month', 'DATE'): 1; ('the second day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the next morning', 'TIME'): 1"
A20770,3,treatise natvre definition faith Tertullian matter regard have truth mystery,faith: 0.5; god: 0.5; knowledge: 0.5; affiance: 0.5; justification: 0.5; christ: 0.5; truth: 0.5; assurance: 0.4; salvation: 0.25; nature: 0.25; word: 0.2; justify: 0.1; act: 0.1; promise: 0.05; fiducia: 0.05; ioh: 0.05; rest: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 10; ('Fiducia', 'PERSON'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Apol', 'ORG'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paphnutius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Socrat', 'GPE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elihu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nisus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Virgil', 'GPE'): 1; ('nostris spectentur ab annis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aeneid', 'GPE'): 1; ('leonem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fides', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Offic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mat 7.22.23', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fides Historiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('St Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('2. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Magus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Fides Promissionum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('count brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('V. G.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.8.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Electra', 'ORG'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Io', 'LOC'): 1; ('3.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('53.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 second', 'TIME'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('7.13', 'DATE'): 1; ('3 third', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eleventh', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ruth nonlatinalphabet : ruth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.12 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Foxe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fides', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('14.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('m. Foxe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Credere', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bonaventure', 'PERSON'): 1; ('scut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('citante kemnit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('loco de iustif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balaam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.20.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paynims', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magi', 'NORP'): 1; ('as much brevity', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Ep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hier', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hortano l. 1. ep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('numie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Candidus imperti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1"
A27177,382,song honour love faith due friendship endline right king scripture,king: 0.5; scripture: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; right: 0.5; self: 0.5; reader: 0.4; parliament: 0.35; conscience: 0.35; law: 0.2; another: 0.1; sir: 0.1; fellow: 0.05; suppose: 0.05; father: 0.05; bentham: 0.05; divine: 0.05; speaker: 0.05; place: 0.05; loyalty: 0.05; due: 0.05; preacher: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Joseph Bentham', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Broughton', 'GPE'): 2; ('Northamptonshire', 'GPE'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('William Tompson', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Leicestershire', 'GPE'): 2; ('1661', 'DATE'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('reader', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seventeen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('arrear', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('un-accused', 'ORG'): 1; ('almost three quarter of a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('24. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Grege', 'GPE'): 1; ('bello expulsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('July 14. 1643', 'DATE'): 1; ('rege', 'ORG'): 1; ('Septemb', 'ORG'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1660', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('N. W. 1647', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1"
A27413,10,hurt prejudice Chron. touch anoint sir look place urge royalist,king: 0.5; god: 0.5; sam: 0.5; lord: 0.5; anoint: 0.45; duty: 0.45; call: 0.4; man: 0.35; chron: 0.35; scripture: 0.3; david: 0.2; place: 0.2; people: 0.15; sir: 0.05; thing: 0.05; saul: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 29; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 16; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('David', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 7; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 5; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 5; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('14.', 'DATE'): 3; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('14', 'DATE'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Abimelech', 'PERSON'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gerar', 'ORG'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('24.', 'DATE'): 2; ('16', 'DATE'): 2; ('23', 'DATE'): 2; ('11.', 'DATE'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ki', 'GPE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Kings', 'ORG'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 2; ('226', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1 Chron', 'PERCENT'): 1; ('16. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal 105', 'LAW'): 1; ('Gerar for Abrahams', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'MONEY'): 1; ('heathen king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the supreme magistrate', 'ORG'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abimelech', 'ORG'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('48.', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('16. 42', 'DATE'): 1; ('42.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('22.', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 Chro', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('I•lians', 'NORP'): 1; ('149', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Belial', 'GPE'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('Bersheba', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Solomons day', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10 , 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 26', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('1 Ki', 'PERCENT'): 1; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. third', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('16. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abishai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('isra•l', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('18.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matthew 17', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('prey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezra 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('30. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ierem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Saul', 'ORG'): 1; ('Wilkinson of Wadesden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Buckinghamshire', 'GPE'): 1; ('some year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('George wither', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('196', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amasai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Davids', 'ORG'): 1; ('12. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Regnum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1"
A26829,39,faith suit pursuit place thought place repose God Christ rest,christ: 0.4; jesus: 0.4; duty: 0.4; faith: 0.4; lord: 0.4; god: 0.4; gospel: 0.35; glory: 0.25; soul: 0.2; mystery: 0.2; work: 0.2; honour: 0.15; providence: 0.1; progress: 0.1; reaching: 0.1; ray: 0.1; rashness: 0.1; race: 0.1; pursuit: 0.1; purpose: 0.1; reflection: 0.1; print: 0.1; time: 0.1; love: 0.05; truth: 0.05; book: 0.05,"('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 11; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isaac Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sibbs', 'GPE'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('T. Batt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('45.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Benj', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thomas Sawbridge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1680', 'DATE'): 1; ('William earl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bedford', 'GPE'): 1; ('Russel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ultima', 'GPE'): 1; ('so year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Media', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('the spring 1653', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the ministry of Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('428', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tome', 'ORG'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernad', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rutherford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('noonday', 'DATE'): 1"
A25241,11 | 28670,God Christ love nature love ocean lord saint cause be,christ: 0.45; god: 0.45; grace: 0.45; love: 0.45; man: 0.45; jesus: 0.45; covenant: 0.45; abraham: 0.45; salvation: 0.4; heart: 0.3; time: 0.15; adam: 0.05; order: 0.05; opinion: 0.05; patriarch: 0.05; particular: 0.05; parent: 0.05; ox: 0.05; people: 0.05; object: 0.05; ocean: 0.05; person: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 14; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 9; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 8; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119 112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Davids', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Colos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('45 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luk 4.22', 'PERSON'): 1; ('grace sigh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sharon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 1.16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Electra', 'ORG'): 1; ('the very same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this sad hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('26.2', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Jacob', 'ORG'): 1; ('32.24', 'MONEY'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('20.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A25241,38 | 30609,Christ reasoning hear say answer replication answer say side minister,heaven: 0.5; earth: 0.5; christ: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; saint: 0.5; world: 0.5; glory: 0.4; fire: 0.4; hell: 0.3; word: 0.15; time: 0.1; soul: 0.05; end: 0.05; day: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('John', 'PERSON'): 3; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('34.4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8.21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sydon', 'GPE'): 1; ('26.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seraphim', 'FAC'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('humour primordium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharsalia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hos Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('die ira', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sibylla', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mundus', 'ORG'): 1; ('hominibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('de civit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Polan', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('70', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hilary', 'GPE'): 1; ('14.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('102.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('2.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isay', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('10.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('wherein dwell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('the supreme court', 'ORG'): 1; ('21.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('51.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand acre', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Preston', 'ORG'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('23.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A38637,3,prevent affectation singularity fame discovery light man credulity dexterity whimsy,man: 0.5; truth: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; word: 0.5; god: 0.5; heart: 0.5; soul: 0.45; self: 0.35; mind: 0.3; faith: 0.3; light: 0.25; wisdom: 0.2; way: 0.15,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 5; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('french', 'NORP'): 3; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('meek', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Luc', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('yesterday', 'DATE'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('10.12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14.15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17.11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Novelist', 'NORP'): 2; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 2; ('2.1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('21.25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10.5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('fond', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('6 . 1y', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.17 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Achaz', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('adulterousnesse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Commissioned', 'ORG'): 1; ('Elihu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Opiniastretè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12 3 day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Charibdis', 'NORP'): 1; ('8.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet rhabim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('James 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('needy soul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•y', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('34.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('h•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Haman', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Mordecai', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Carnifex', 'ORG'): 1; ('im•artiall', 'ORG'): 1"
A38637,3 | 31365,key sun soul faith forehead control mind method measure Cor.,man: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; self: 0.5; lord: 0.5; truth: 0.5; heart: 0.5; way: 0.3; mind: 0.3; cor: 0.25; christ: 0.1; judgement: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 7; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 4; ('13.9', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('14', 'DATE'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('20.27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'DATE'): 2; ('10.15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('a• clean', 'ORG'): 1; ('consequenc•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('d•rknesse', 'GPE'): 1; ('jann•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 7.24', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('kiss Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Esai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 2.26', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 2.26', 'DATE'): 1; ('105.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal 105.12', 'LAW'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phaeton', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('viribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('tua corrige nota', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Laitie', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.12 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lo k', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•n', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tyatira', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jezabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gal. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('so many hundred and thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christmas', 'DATE'): 1; ('Easter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('16 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('meek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('6 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.17.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thess', 'LOC'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. to 17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('97.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('97 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.2 .', 'DATE'): 1"
