tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A35345,10 | 545,thing confess acknowledge Faustus conceit Christians Jew paganize opinion monarchy,god: 0.5; pagan: 0.5; thing: 0.5; world: 0.5; generate: 0.5; plato: 0.5; earth: 0.45; sense: 0.4; deity: 0.4; generation: 0.35; another: 0.15; man: 0.1; opinion: 0.05; word: 0.05; whole: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 38; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 23; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 9; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('Theogonia', 'GPE'): 6; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('Onatus', 'ORG'): 4; ('Cosmogonia', 'LOC'): 4; ('Proclus', 'PRODUCT'): 4; ('Faustus', 'ORG'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 3; ('Timaeus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('Schisma', 'GPE'): 2; ('Aliis', 'ORG'): 2; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('god', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Plato be Timaeus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 2; ('Plato', 'ORG'): 2; ('Juno', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hesiod', 'ORG'): 2; ('Pontus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Faust', 'GPE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('gentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('M•narchiae', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Monarchiae', 'NORP'): 1; ('jude•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sectas', 'ORG'): 1; ('duae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gentilism', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'GPE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pagani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Manichaei', 'NORP'): 1; ('Judaeis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Una Substantia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pagani', 'NORP'): 1; ('Una', 'LOC'): 1; ('Officia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Opera', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mundum', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Religionists', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. Ang.', 'ORG'): 1; ('contra', 'ORG'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Faustus Monarchiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian Boethius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Beatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('natura quidem vnus', 'ORG'): 1; ('prohibet esse quamplurimos', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thales', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laertius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pythagorean', 'NORP'): 1; ('Stobaeus', 'FAC'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anaxagoras', 'GPE'): 1; ('the moon earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('206', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Maximus Tyrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herodotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('certain•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Proclus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theophrastus', 'ORG'): 1; ('annual', 'DATE'): 1; ('Plotinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Orpheus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Proclus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Selene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('System', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Ma•rob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cosmogonia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tethys and Phorcys', 'ORG'): 1; ('Saturn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rhea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('28•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('P. 286', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cosmogonia', 'ORG'): 1; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cantilenam', 'GPE'): 1; ('flumina', 'GPE'): 1; ('aestu ferven', 'ORG'): 1; ('Astra', 'NORP'): 1; ('nati', 'PERSON'): 1"
A35345,10 | 561,Ovid instance pagan theogonist manner unmake deity world other god,god: 0.5; world: 0.5; make: 0.5; sense: 0.5; eternity: 0.5; cause: 0.5; thing: 0.45; deity: 0.4; pagan: 0.3; chaos: 0.3; inferior: 0.3; aristotle: 0.2; unmake: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 55; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('Platonists', 'NORP'): 9; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 8; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Hesiod', 'ORG'): 5; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 4; ('Epicharmus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Cosmogonia', 'LOC'): 3; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Theogonia', 'GPE'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Numenius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Porphyrius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cosmogonia', 'GPE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Proclus', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Arist', 'ORG'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Strabo', 'GPE'): 1; ('809', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Fundamenta', 'GPE'): 1; ('quicquam novit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Them', 'ORG'): 1; ('Orpheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Genetricem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theogonists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Orpheus and Linus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thales', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anaxagoras', 'GPE'): 1; ('non hic meus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Figura', 'ORG'): 1; ('Una', 'NORP'): 1; ('coeli', 'GPE'): 1; ('secreta quae mox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Statum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cuncta', 'ORG'): 1; ('Feras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arbores', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plutarch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vehicula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Orpheus', 'GPE'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Aut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('266', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simmias Rhodius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Orpheus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Steph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('849', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mosaic cabal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('moon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Placitis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Stobaeus', 'FAC'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ocellus Lucanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Grotius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Excerp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('478', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nempe Dî', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('iisdem', 'GPE'): 1; ('extitisse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam de', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nîl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ergo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('profecto', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nunc sic appellantur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('alia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Diodorus Siculus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plotinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('9 c', 'DATE'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Timaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('116', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simplicius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Orium', 'ORG'): 1; ('265', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Crantor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Proclus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Timae', 'GPE'): 1; ('85', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Salustius', 'ORG'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jamblychus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Proclus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato be Principles', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1"
A35345,10 | 634,christian theologer make God sense whole world God unfold creature,egyptian: 0.5; thing: 0.5; god: 0.5; wisdom: 0.5; man: 0.5; world: 0.5; egypt: 0.45; theology: 0.4; word: 0.35; make: 0.25; greeks: 0.25; deity: 0.25; doctrine: 0.05,"('egyptian', 'NORP'): 61; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 50; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 22; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 12; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('greek', 'NORP'): 8; ('Herodotus', 'NORP'): 6; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 5; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 4; ('syrian', 'NORP'): 4; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Celsus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 3; ('Nephthus', 'GPE'): 3; ('persian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Diodorus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 2; ('Neptune', 'ORG'): 2; ('Venus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Egyptians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Lucian', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Herodotus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Egyptian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Solon', 'ORG'): 2; ('Isocrates', 'GPE'): 2; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 2; ('Porphyrius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Pythagoras', 'LOC'): 2; ('Strabo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cosmogonia', 'LOC'): 2; ('indian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Berosus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Grammaticus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('Plutarch', 'GPE'): 2; ('Harpocrates', 'LOC'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jerom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greekish', 'NORP'): 1; ('european', 'NORP'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aether', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Juno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeolus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ceres', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bacchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Orpheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zoroaster', 'GPE'): 1; ('Orpheus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chaldeans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 1; ('1059', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('assyrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Europeans', 'NORP'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cratylus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Homer', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alpha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Etymon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thien', 'GPE'): 1; ('the beginning and end', 'DATE'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Varro', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nuptunus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scaliger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Osiris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nephthus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Venus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Busiris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euseb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 c', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Brutus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Volusi Bithynice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aegyptus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ibin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('121', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Climax', 'NORP'): 1; ('magi', 'NORP'): 1; ('Philo', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lycurgus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thales', 'ORG'): 1; ('Xenophon', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Literature', 'GPE'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('Persians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sancuniathon', 'ORG'): 1; ('15.715', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the Version of Alexander Polyhistor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Porphyry', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('P. l. 9 c .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Kircher', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Horus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Anaximander', 'ORG'): 1; ('Democritus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epicurus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Simplicius', 'ORG'): 1; ('mosaic', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Arist', 'ORG'): 1; ('l. 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('268', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('the light day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Euterp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Stobaeus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chalcidius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hermes Trismegist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Strabo L. 15', 'PERSON'): 1; ('715', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Domicilia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Diversoria', 'ORG'): 1; ('Diod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chaeremon', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Diodorus S.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle be Exotericks', 'ORG'): 1; ('horo-genitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clemens of Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Strom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('508', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('354', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrinus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Clemens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Harpocrates', 'GPE'): 1; ('digitóque silentia suadent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Osir', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Harpocrates', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thoth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hermes', 'GPE'): 1; ('fig', 'ORG'): 1"
A35345,10 | 664,Plutarch passage Hecataeus egyptian nonlatinalphabet God universe thing meaning God,thing: 0.5; god: 0.5; deity: 0.5; world: 0.5; pan: 0.5; whole: 0.5; name: 0.5; book: 0.4; egyptian: 0.3; universe: 0.25; isis: 0.2; word: 0.2; worship: 0.05; plutarch: 0.05; osiris: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 45; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 20; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('thou', 'GPE'): 9; ('Isis', 'ORG'): 9; ('Osiris', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Sarapis', 'PERSON'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Apuleius', 'ORG'): 5; ('Hammon', 'PERSON'): 4; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 4; ('nec', 'ORG'): 4; ('Tiberius', 'ORG'): 3; ('quae', 'GPE'): 3; ('Plutarch', 'GPE'): 2; ('Diodorus Siculus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Pan', 'ORG'): 2; ('nuncupari', 'ORG'): 2; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hecataeus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Orpheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Parmenides', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Metaph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arcadick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Macrobius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arcades', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('appellante nonlatinalphabet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed universae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Materialis dominatorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hyle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greeks', 'EVENT'): 1; ('Desaert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('Echinades', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Phaenomenon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('European', 'NORP'): 1; ('huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel ipse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tota', 'GPE'): 1; ('idcirco', 'NORP'): 1; ('totius majestatis effectorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('multis composito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hunc', 'ORG'): 1; ('potius', 'GPE'): 1; ('siquidem', 'ORG'): 1; ('hic ergo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('612', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('circum se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('isque sva firma stabilitas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec loco', 'PERSON'): 1; ('moveri potest', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sensibilis Mundus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('P. 617', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec fuit aliquid', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ficinus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cyril', 'ORG'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('fifteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the sixteenth', 'DATE'): 1; ('neith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Capua', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Metam', 'GPE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('commota', 'GPE'): 1; ('Luci', 'PERSON'): 1; ('luminosa culmina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maris salubria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nutibus meis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('moon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vnicum', 'ORG'): 1; ('tu sancta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('humani generis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sospitatrix perpetua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('miseris tribuis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fatorum inextricabiliter contorta retractas litia', 'ORG'): 1; ('meatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Inferi', 'GPE'): 1; ('numina', 'GPE'): 1; ('tuo nutu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('summorum maximus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vero unica', 'ORG'): 1; ('ratio numinis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Osiris', 'GPE'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('257', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('last', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ptolemy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nicocrion', 'GPE'): 1; ('Philarchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Euseb', 'GPE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A35345,10 | 763,argumentation take Topick prescience divination stoic existence God maker governor,god: 0.4; world: 0.4; whole: 0.4; thing: 0.4; stoic: 0.4; jupiter: 0.4; reason: 0.4; make: 0.4; man: 0.35; call: 0.15; obstinacy: 0.1; obedience: 0.1; original: 0.1; orderer: 0.1; order: 0.1; oracle: 0.1; opinion: 0.1; oneliness: 0.1; oeconomy: 0.1; overcome: 0.1; deity: 0.05; principle: 0.05; universe: 0.05; epictetus: 0.05; nature: 0.05; providence: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 59; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 26; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 21; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('thou', 'GPE'): 8; ('Epictetus', 'ORG'): 7; ('Zeus', 'PERSON'): 6; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 6; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Anton', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jove', 'PERSON'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 2; ('Epictetus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Topick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Incorporalis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrinus', 'LOC'): 1; ('D. Des', 'PERSON'): 1; ('425', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('420', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1075', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chrysippus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cleanthes', 'ORG'): 1; ('System', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('qualis futura', 'PERSON'): 1; ('amicis relinquatur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qualis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Resoluto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('natura', 'ORG'): 1; ('cogitationibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Juno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('kinsman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Enumeration', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ant.', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ant', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ant.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ant l. 7.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('•p', 'GPE'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antoninus', 'GPE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('125', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ant', 'ORG'): 1; ('257', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('251', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cicero be Lucilius Balbus', 'ORG'): 1; ('de N. D. l. 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('225', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mundum', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laertius', 'ORG'): 1; ('vocamus hominem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('praeclara quadam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('SVMMO', 'ORG'): 1; ('Platonists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Galileans', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the season of the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A35345,10 | 778,L. Annaeus Seneca philosopher saviour Christ apostle plurality god way,god: 0.45; thing: 0.45; world: 0.45; man: 0.45; another: 0.45; pagan: 0.45; whole: 0.4; jupiter: 0.35; poet: 0.35; king: 0.25; opinion: 0.2; heaven: 0.1; religion: 0.05; place: 0.05; pliny: 0.05; philosopher: 0.05; piety: 0.05; pilot: 0.05; petavius: 0.05; platonists: 0.05; plutarch: 0.05; plurality: 0.05; perstringe: 0.05; power: 0.05; book: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 30; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 28; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 12; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('greek', 'NORP'): 6; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 5; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Apuleius', 'ORG'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Maximus Tyrius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('partibus', 'ORG'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Seneca', 'GPE'): 2; ('Prudentius', 'ORG'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('201', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Plotinus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('syrian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Orat', 'GPE'): 2; ('L. Annaeus Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('formatorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Q. L. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rectorem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mundani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('operis dominum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Divinum', 'NORP'): 1; ('minima', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('442', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('omnibus praesto est', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('coeli', 'GPE'): 1; ('ista', 'NORP'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('singula adoramus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Varro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fabius Quintilianus', 'ORG'): 1; ('L. 7.6.3', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epicurus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pervicaciam certè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('supreme iversal numen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trajan', 'GPE'): 1; ('coelum ac sydera', 'ORG'): 1; ('bonorum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Causae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('L. Apuleius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apollonius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Summus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('de Philos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('278', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('prima', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('last Symmachus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('306', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eadem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Astra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mundus', 'NORP'): 1; ('prudentia', 'NORP'): 1; ('vno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('P. 285', 'ORG'): 1; ('Communis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Quaerimus', 'ORG'): 1; ('opertae quaeri aliter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nescia flecti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heraclitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('latin Version', 'LOC'): 1; ('perseverantiam earum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Coryphaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('the Pythian Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Harmonist', 'NORP'): 1; ('Musician', 'NORP'): 1; ('Plutarch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chrysostomus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('199', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('210', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('203', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('446', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prolepsis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Galen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Halys', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hellespont', 'GPE'): 1; ('proem', 'GPE'): 1; ('405', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('406', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Crete', 'ORG'): 1; ('Saturn', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Platonists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Numenius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Porphyrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Proclus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Damascius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Themistius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Empedocles', 'GPE'): 1; ('Orat', 'ORG'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cyril', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Julian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Xxvii', 'GPE'): 1; ('latin pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tragedian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Statius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Silius Italicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Persius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dio Chrysostomus', 'ORG'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('447', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Diss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('scythian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the barbarian alike affirm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dio Chrysostomus', 'PERSON'): 1"
A35345,10 | 849,give account Apuleius sense book Deo Socratis pagan god multitude,god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; world: 0.5; pagan: 0.5; part: 0.5; name: 0.5; nature: 0.5; whole: 0.45; theology: 0.4; call: 0.4; make: 0.25,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 31; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 8; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 4; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Seneca', 'PRODUCT'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Heraclitus', 'ORG'): 3; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 3; ('Ceres', 'ORG'): 3; ('Consentes', 'ORG'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('Anaxagoras', 'GPE'): 2; ('Cratylus', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Juno', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 2; ('Vulcan', 'NORP'): 2; ('Dionysus', 'NORP'): 2; ('Menander', 'PERSON'): 2; ('222', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Apuleius', 'ORG'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('evanid one', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Consentes', 'LOC'): 1; ('Selecti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Varro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dea mena', 'ORG'): 1; ('Levana', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cunina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Diva Rumina', 'ORG'): 1; ('Diva Potina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diva Educa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diva Paventina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Venilia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Agenoria', 'ORG'): 1; ('Strenua', 'GPE'): 1; ('Numeria', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Sentia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Virginensis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Dea Deverra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Domitius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dea manturna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Prema', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pertunda', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rusina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Collatina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vallonia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Seia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Segetia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tutilina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nodotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Volutina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Patelena', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hostilina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Flora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lacturtia', 'ORG'): 1; ('matura', 'ORG'): 1; ('Runcina', 'GPE'): 1; ('platonic pagan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 1; ('nomina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laertius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('121', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epictetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('85', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zephyrus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeolus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aeolus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Horus Apollo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laertius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pythagoras , Adv', 'ORG'): 1; ('331', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Italick', 'ORG'): 1; ('Brutus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('730', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('indian', 'NORP'): 1; ('greekish', 'NORP'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('extrinsecus operi suo circumfusus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maxima', 'GPE'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('minima', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Quintilian', 'NORP'): 1; ('partibus Immistus', 'ORG'): 1; ('viribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('dei praesentiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('oculi', 'GPE'): 1; ('sensibilis Substantia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Servius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('413', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cappa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deus Pertinens', 'ORG'): 1; ('terras Ceres', 'ORG'): 1; ('Neptunus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paulus Orosius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidam dum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('multis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Timore', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jamblichus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Orpheus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Timotheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Grot', 'GPE'): 1; ('Exc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aether', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arx', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cuncta', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sublimius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ib', 'NORP'): 1; ('53', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('aquae', 'ORG'): 1; ('simulat interdum Feram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tonitrua', 'GPE'): 1; ('Fulmina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucan', 'NORP'): 1; ('9 v. 580', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('Monad', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xenophanes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Melissus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nasci', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phaenomenon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('229', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Moschopulus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hephaestus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Demeter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ceres', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bacchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Venus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Muse', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arnobius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pro aqua Neptunum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cererem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pro obscoenis libidinis venerem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('379', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Terence', 'GPE'): 1; ('Venus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Plato', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fruges Cererem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nominetur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Liber', 'PERSON'): 1; ('751', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('752', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Proserpina , Pluto and Ceres', 'ORG'): 1; ('nymph', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dioscuri', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ammianus Marcellinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Elementorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('788', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sophocles his Electra', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Plato be Symposium', 'FAC'): 1; ('Philebus', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Venus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cicero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('N. D. L. 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Beneficiis eorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Graeciae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('majoribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('generi afferret humano', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Divina', 'GPE'): 1; ('fieri arbitrabantur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Capita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Subita', 'ORG'): 1; ('ex abdito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aras', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Fontes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Stagna', 'FAC'): 1"
A35345,10 | 856,call theology pagan personate sense thing nature substance affection substance,god: 0.4; thing: 0.4; nature: 0.4; pagan: 0.4; world: 0.4; name: 0.4; man: 0.3; whole: 0.25; fable: 0.25; theology: 0.25; sense: 0.25; worship: 0.2; heaven: 0.1; observe: 0.1; number: 0.1; origin: 0.1; origen: 0.1; oration: 0.1; orat: 0.1; opinion: 0.1; offspring: 0.1; occasion: 0.1; os: 0.1,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 24; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 6; ('Chrysippus', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 4; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Cleanthes', 'ORG'): 3; ('Juno', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Ev', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 2; ('Samos', 'GPE'): 2; ('Varro', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Latria', 'GPE'): 2; ('Cotta', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cicero', 'FAC'): 2; ('Bacchus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Aether', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Astra', 'NORP'): 2; ('nuncupari', 'ORG'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Julian', 'NORP'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('821', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Strabo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Porphyrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Porphyry', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cotta', 'ORG'): 1; ('molestiam suscepit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('minimè necessariam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rationem', 'ORG'): 1; ('vocabulorum cur quidque ita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod cum facitis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('profecto', 'GPE'): 1; ('eos qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('appellantur', 'GPE'): 1; ('naturas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non figuras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('L. 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('196', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hesiod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theogonia', 'GPE'): 1; ('378', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dionysius Halicarnass', 'ORG'): 1; ('L. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('223', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alia', 'GPE'): 1; ('quidem', 'GPE'): 1; ('magna fluxit multitudo deorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui induti specie humana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epicurus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Democritus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Strato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Manilius', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec Flamma', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec aer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidquam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scaevola', 'ORG'): 1; ('supreme iversal numen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('49', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('neque', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sacrilega', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simulachra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quaeque', 'NORP'): 1; ('Servitus religionis', 'NORP'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('D. L. 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Naturalium Rationum Interpretationes', 'ORG'): 1; ('physiologiam quaeramus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theologiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rationem naturae', 'ORG'): 1; ('345', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fruges Cererem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ecquem tam amentem esse putas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Animant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('general', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucretius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ceres', 'ORG'): 1; ('165', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Neptunum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cererem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constituit', 'NORP'): 1; ('abuti mavolt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam laticis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('matrem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidem vero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('N.D.L.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('220', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Balbus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Animans', 'NORP'): 1; ('god quoniam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('intelligentiam', 'GPE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('D.N.D.', 'ORG'): 1; ('241', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Animantes quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('377', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pagan god', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Commentitii and Fictitii', 'ORG'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('multis composito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('potius', 'GPE'): 1; ('nomine vocandus est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('siquidem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ipsius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('voles illi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nomina', 'GPE'): 1; ('quot munera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julian Orat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('P. 286', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pan', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('L. 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('761', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Strabo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Herodotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Juno', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vulcan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Neptune', 'ORG'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'GPE'): 1; ('moon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 ▪', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirty thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xenoph', 'ORG'): 1; ('Euthydemus', 'GPE'): 1; ('hims•lf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ammianus Marcellinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('236', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('237', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A35345,10 | 868,Lactantius Firmianus eal Rel. notice profession pagan God Ministers generate,god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; pagan: 0.5; world: 0.5; power: 0.5; nature: 0.5; name: 0.5; divine: 0.4; worship: 0.3; mind: 0.25; call: 0.25; theology: 0.2; idea: 0.05; deify: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 18; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 16; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 7; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Celsus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Vossius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Varro', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 2; ('Julian', 'PERSON'): 2; ('C. Cels', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Saturn', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Fulmina', 'GPE'): 2; ('Summanus', 'GPE'): 2; ('pagan god', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Lactantius Firmianus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'FAC'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('illi sunt qui vulgo coluntur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three hundred and sixty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zenocrate Gor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1246', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vossius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dispar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theologorum Naturalium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('numina', 'GPE'): 1; ('ita numina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aliquam majorem viderent', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ita Divinum', 'ORG'): 1; ('etiam devenere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('immanem', 'NORP'): 1; ('quae licet una foret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vario etiam afficeretur cultu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scaevola', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Falsas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mundum', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Epicurus and Strato', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Prudentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('inn vno Constituit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apuleius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Brutus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orig', 'GPE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('120', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Egyptians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Plotinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Julian', 'NORP'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('347', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('102', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Septimius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Limina', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hermaick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hammon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jamblichus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athena', 'ORG'): 1; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aphrodite Urania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Venus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Phanes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Proclus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athanasius Kircherus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Proclus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Plato be Timaeus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pherecydes Syrus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('C.D.L. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romani', 'NORP'): 1; ('nescio quem summanum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam jupiter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Templum', 'ORG'): 1; ('multitudo confluxit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Summani', 'ORG'): 1; ('audiri jam non potest', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Divina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Evan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'GPE'): 1; ('moon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athanasius Bp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Juno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('xxxiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Diana', 'GPE'): 1; ('Virgil concern Allecto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nomina mille', 'ORG'): 1; ('mille nocendi', 'ORG'): 1"
A35345,10 | 877,principle God thing thing chief ground polytheism pagan improve carry,god: 0.45; world: 0.45; thing: 0.45; whole: 0.45; soul: 0.45; part: 0.45; pagan: 0.45; body: 0.4; nature: 0.35; animal: 0.2; temple: 0.15; mind: 0.15; member: 0.05; pile: 0.05; pietati: 0.05; plutarch: 0.05; please: 0.05; platonists: 0.05; plato: 0.05; plant: 0.05; place: 0.05; polytheism: 0.05; piety: 0.05; worship: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 20; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 15; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 7; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 7; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Celsus', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 4; ('greek', 'NORP'): 4; ('Platonists', 'NORP'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('persian', 'NORP'): 3; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Manilius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('Mundum', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Simplicius', 'ORG'): 2; ('234', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Varro', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Pagani', 'NORP'): 2; ('magi', 'NORP'): 2; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 2; ('Mundus', 'NORP'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('C. Cels', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Quintilian', 'GPE'): 1; ('partibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('sacroque meatu', 'NORP'): 1; ('Divina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Communis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Balbus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cicero', 'LOC'): 1; ('natura', 'GPE'): 1; ('ea quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Strabo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heraclitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hippasus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Diogenes Apolloniates', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hippo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('omnia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epictet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Strato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Laertius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zeno', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aether', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cleanthes', 'ORG'): 1; ('one divine', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('P. Ev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('235', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Didymus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Celsus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('C.D.L. 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Varro', 'ORG'): 1; ('adhuc de naturali', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theologia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Graeci', 'ORG'): 1; ('animo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('animo dici', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the Greeks call Cosmos', 'FAC'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Socii', 'ORG'): 1; ('Faustus', 'ORG'): 1; ('verò coelum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aer', 'ORG'): 1; ('sensibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae cum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('colunt quae sunt .', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui corpora colunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quidam volunt omnia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ista', 'NORP'): 1; ('quae sententia velut magnorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('inquam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Compendio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Praetermissae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Animantis', 'NORP'): 1; ('tota vita est', 'FAC'): 1; ('vel membra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quaeque', 'NORP'): 1; ('caeteris separatam', 'FAC'): 1; ('placari', 'ORG'): 1; ('concitari', 'ORG'): 1; ('stultè dicitur', 'ORG'): 1; ('nulla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cont', 'GPE'): 1; ('260', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('335', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Magos Persarum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xerxes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Xerxes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diogenes Laertius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dinon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Macrobius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scipio', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('benè', 'ORG'): 1; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi coelum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ista quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('summi omnipotentiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('posse vix intelligi', 'ORG'): 1; ('nunquam posse', 'ORG'): 1; ('videri', 'ORG'): 1; ('aspectui Templum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui haec veneratur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sciatque', 'NORP'): 1; ('huius inducitur', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mysta', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cosmolatrae', 'ORG'): 1; ('universal acknowledge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('at least a three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Origen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egyptians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Psyche', 'ORG'): 1; ('329', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('330', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('331', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Orig', 'GPE'): 1; ('308', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('208', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A35345,10 | 922,catholic doctrine school henade Noes opinion doctor sort henade footstep,thing: 0.5; mind: 0.5; plato: 0.5; god: 0.5; world: 0.5; trinity: 0.5; make: 0.5; soul: 0.45; cause: 0.35; word: 0.25; hypostasis: 0.2; beginning: 0.15; plotinus: 0.1,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 44; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 36; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 24; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 24; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 24; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 12; ('Plotinus', 'GPE'): 8; ('Platonists', 'NORP'): 6; ('Plato', 'ORG'): 5; ('Psyche', 'ORG'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Timaeus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Zeus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Noes', 'ORG'): 3; ('Enn', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Porphyrius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Arius', 'ORG'): 3; ('Plotinus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cabbala', 'GPE'): 2; ('Mundum', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('S. Cyril', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet coessential', 'ORG'): 2; ('Demiurgus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Amelius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Agathotetes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henades', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Synesius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henad of Henades', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Noes', 'GPE'): 1; ('847', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Entia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Noes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinity of hypostase', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Boetius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Consol', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Initium', 'ORG'): 1; ('aliud', 'PERSON'): 1; ('interminabilis vitæ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('totam pariter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Divinae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('neque deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('videri', 'NORP'): 1; ('Simplicis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('dignarebus nomina velimus', 'ORG'): 1; ('platonem sequente', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deum quidem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ortum', 'GPE'): 1; ('mosaic', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dionysius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this first', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plato be Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tagathon', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Anaxagoras', 'GPE'): 1; ('Archelaus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caldee', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philebus', 'ORG'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tagathon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('the Nicene council', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cratylus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Chronos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plotinus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Atticus', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Proclus', 'GPE'): 1; ('three divine', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Nicene', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sabellius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Modes', 'PERSON'): 1"
A35345,11 | 1089,scripture paganism oracle divination contain prediction event time impute foreknowledge,thing: 0.5; understanding: 0.5; truth: 0.5; god: 0.5; self: 0.5; perception: 0.5; existence: 0.45; mind: 0.4; faculty: 0.3; make: 0.3; knowledge: 0.25; sense: 0.15; power: 0.05; time: 0.05; prophecy: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 11; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Phaenomena', 'ORG'): 2; ('Perceptibility', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaias', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'GPE'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('daniel week', 'ORG'): 1; ('four hundred and ninety year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Artaxerxes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Xerxes', 'GPE'): 1; ('the seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Levite', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('persian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lagidae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Porphyrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Eichon', 'ORG'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniels', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Apocalypse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phaenomenon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander Aphrodisius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Strom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('388', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrinus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two and two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Something', 'NORP'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('154', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Protagoras', 'GPE'): 1; ('Protagorean', 'NORP'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1"
A35345,11 | 1247,Vehicles soul Brutus whimsy figment allow act other body mean,thing: 0.5; soul: 0.5; self: 0.5; mind: 0.5; god: 0.5; life: 0.5; matter: 0.5; death: 0.4; understanding: 0.35; body: 0.3; knowledge: 0.25; sense: 0.15; man: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 6; ('Brutus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Phaenomenon', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 2; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('the mother|be Womb', 'FAC'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('Brutus', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pythagorean', 'NORP'): 1; ('Brutus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Porphyrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Virgil', 'ORG'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ind', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pontus', 'ORG'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Armenta', 'GPE'): 1; ('scilicet huc reddi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Resoluta Referri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('omnia', 'GPE'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Organization', 'ORG'): 1; ('Topick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('System', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Sovereignt•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rapid', 'GPE'): 1; ('the supreme king of heaven', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dementia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Celsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('P. 240', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('247', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plotinus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('265', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('743', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A30137,6 | 4186,heart spirit mind principle covenant bondage ismaels curse heart law,christ: 0.45; holiness: 0.45; god: 0.45; man: 0.45; law: 0.45; thing: 0.45; adam: 0.45; principle: 0.45; nature: 0.35; page: 0.25; heart: 0.15; spirit: 0.1; pag: 0.05; perfection: 0.05; people: 0.05; passage: 0.05; part: 0.05; paradox: 0.05; paradise: 0.05; pet: 0.05; ordinance: 0.05; lord: 0.05; righteousness: 0.05,"('Adam', 'PERSON'): 22; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 13; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 7; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('18', 'DATE'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 2; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 c•r', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('300', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('less than 300', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fowler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'MONEY'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('101', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('outward application', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quakers', 'GPE'): 1; ('9 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Answ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•he', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('necess•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Musculus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('84', 'DATE'): 1; ('136', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A30137,13,reader desire erratae pen happen reason author absence press page,god: 0.5; mr: 0.5; edition: 0.5; twelves: 0.5; soul: 0.5; saint: 0.35; time: 0.35; church: 0.3; child: 0.3; christ: 0.25; leave: 0.25; gospel: 0.2; man: 0.2; body: 0.05; faith: 0.05; christian: 0.05; order: 0.05; use: 0.05; manner: 0.05,"('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Quaker', 'ORG'): 2; ('Kenelm Digby', 'PERSON'): 2; ('reader', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('soul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. a. leave', 'PERSON'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('74', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('78', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('87', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('91', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('100', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('107', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Temple-bar', 'LOC'): 1; ('Baxter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('marshal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Blake', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cook', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cotton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hoole', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Twelves', 'GPE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gerizzim', 'ORG'): 1; ('the Nicene council', 'ORG'): 1; ('Socinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('wherein it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eighty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pius 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('W. Ramsay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Franciscans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Robert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Panton', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lincolnshire', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ralph •ames', 'PERSON'): 1; ('marry brown', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Charles Baily', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bunyans', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames Arminius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Simon Spiscopius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the university of Leyden', 'ORG'): 1; ('holland', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet animae naturam', 'ORG'): 1; ('absque totius natura', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phoedr', 'GPE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('G.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('B. G.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Williams', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Buttolph - church', 'ORG'): 1; ('lxix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('wean', 'PERSON'): 1"
A34110,2,observation dream thing say principle philosophy Campanella interpreter Toby Adam,thing: 0.5; god: 0.5; reason: 0.5; sense: 0.5; man: 0.5; truth: 0.5; philosophy: 0.5; scripture: 0.45; wisdom: 0.4; aristotle: 0.3; divine: 0.15; light: 0.1; nature: 0.05; way: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Campanella', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hercules', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 2; ('Verulamius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 2; ('heresy', 'GPE'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Toby Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saturn', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sirach', 'GPE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('John Henry Alsted', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Biblicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cassiodorus', 'ORG'): 1; ('T. Lydiat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Franc', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lambert Danaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lemnius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas Lydiat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Conradus As•acus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Otto Casmannus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'FAC'): 1; ('Nic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'GPE'): 1; ('Julius Scaliger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Goclenius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('al•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 2. v.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ekron', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gal. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antichristianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thomas Scotus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hagar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Memphis', 'GPE'): 1; ('N. W.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pythagorean', 'NORP'): 1; ('Verulam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('105', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Galen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Campanella', 'GPE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sulfur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christiana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A31089,10,supposition Iii saint Peter bishop assertion reason deny assure consideration,bishop: 0.5; saint: 0.5; peter: 0.5; church: 0.5; paul: 0.5; apostle: 0.45; place: 0.4; charge: 0.4; man: 0.35; time: 0.2; office: 0.2; practice: 0.15; city: 0.15; pope: 0.1; synod: 0.1,"('Peter', 'PERSON'): 31; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 17; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 10; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 4; ('contra', 'NORP'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Euseb', 'GPE'): 3; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 3; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 3; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Nic', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Athan', 'GPE'): 3; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 3; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4.11', 'DATE'): 2; ('Chrys', 'ORG'): 2; ('Chrysostome', 'EVENT'): 2; ('58', 'DATE'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('2.25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('haer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 2; ('Ant', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Apol', 'PERSON'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Athanasius', 'GPE'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Damasus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cypr', 'PERSON'): 2; ('46', 'DATE'): 2; ('12.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tom 8.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('115', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('non erat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Officii', 'ORG'): 1; ('quantum homini', 'ORG'): 1; ('penitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('baron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('§', 'NORP'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pancras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Claudius', 'NORP'): 1; ('saint luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sueton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tib 36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tiberius', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet ▪ Petr', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('189', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('apud bell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vales', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.2.15.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.18.2.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Corinth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pontus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bithynia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Galatians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Coloss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aristarchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marcus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Justus', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Conc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. Conc', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('80', 'DATE'): 1; ('episcop•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('secularibus expedito', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('P. Paschal ii Ep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('ministris Ecclesiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesiasticum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('debuerit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quaeratur', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexandro Iii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('86', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('diverse synod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Berytus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicomedia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athanas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('726', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('727', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sardican', 'NORP'): 1; ('765', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chalcedon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sardica', 'GPE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chalc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sin Sard', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Grat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arles', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anthimus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Menn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('I.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('744', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('administrationem loci celebrioris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cathedra quidem pellatur aliena', 'PERSON'): 1; ('P. Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('84', 'DATE'): 1; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euseb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Vit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregory Nazianzene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sasima', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Synod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('commoneo dilectionem vestram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de civitate alia', 'ORG'): 1; ('ad aliam transduci', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sibi commissam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('P. Damasi Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('apud Holsten', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('R. Marc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pelagius ii', 'LAW'): 1; ('benè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quando mutavit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sedem de Antiochia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pelag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ii Ep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('52', 'DATE'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('saint cyprian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('Soz', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cornelius apud Euseb', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('6.43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('P. Innocentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sozom', 'GPE'): 1; ('8.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cathedra una .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apostolis Petro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paulo Romae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.3.3.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dionysius', 'ORG'): 1; ('P. Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Donys', 'GPE'): 1; ('Corinth', 'DATE'): 1; ('apud Euseb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eus', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('faint luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two whole year', 'DATE'): 1; ('28.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1"
A35340,4,idolatry Jew other god describe notion Isa. mountain bed Casaub.,sacrifice: 0.4; feast: 0.4; god: 0.4; thing: 0.4; offer: 0.4; heathens: 0.3; time: 0.3; rite: 0.25; jew: 0.2; meat: 0.2; christian: 0.2; mountain: 0.15; idol: 0.15; man: 0.15; odyssee: 0.1; observation: 0.1; paganism: 0.1; pagan: 0.1; ox: 0.1; original: 0.1; offering: 0.1; part: 0.1; note: 0.1; worship: 0.1; tabernacle: 0.05; call: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 15; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 4; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Prometheus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Salmasius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 2; ('Iaphet', 'GPE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 2; ('Plautus', 'ORG'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('56', 'DATE'): 1; ('Casaub', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sabean', 'NORP'): 1; ('Arabia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Saba', 'GPE'): 1; ('Plinianis', 'NORP'): 1; ('497', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('500', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amos 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezek', 'GPE'): 1; ('18. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Targum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levit', 'GPE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('whatsoever', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mantissa', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isaak Abravanel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hattorah', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Idolis', 'ORG'): 1; ('instruebat de sacrificiis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a. hunc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sacrificii morem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('prometheo originem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ignem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('3028', 'DATE'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Julian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('europaeans', 'NORP'): 1; ('10. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chronology', 'ORG'): 1; ('Censorinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Varro', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vossius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Homer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iliad', 'GPE'): 1; ('Agamemnon', 'FAC'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chryse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Agamemnon', 'ORG'): 1; ('grecian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nestor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Neptune', 'ORG'): 1; ('eighty two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alcinous', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lycus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Poenulus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Convivas', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Interibi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gelasimus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Stichus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iamne', 'GPE'): 1; ('quot agnis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cum faciam vitula pro frugibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ipse venito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('uncouth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cataline', 'GPE'): 1; ('Strabo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('persian', 'NORP'): 1; ('fifteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nullâ parte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('relatâ', 'GPE'): 1; ('nihil velle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hostiae', 'GPE'): 1; ('quidam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herodotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cleobus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bithene', 'GPE'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Syriack', 'ORG'): 1; ('arabic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aristophanes', 'NORP'): 1; ('Plutus', 'EVENT'): 1; ('majorem mihi quam sibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the greek nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Umbrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Festus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Strobula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theophrastus', 'ORG'): 1; ('epula concelebrante accedit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('portionem auferat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hesychius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Vespae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Austine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('1 Corin', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anacreon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('EPULUM SACRIFICIALE', 'ORG'): 1; ('EPULUM', 'ORG'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A35340,9,instance etymon hebrew word nonlatinalphabet covenant Federall communion party nonlatinalphabet,god: 0.5; sacrifice: 0.5; covenant: 0.5; salt: 0.5; manner: 0.5; devil: 0.5; feast: 0.45; notion: 0.4; meat: 0.25; place: 0.25; friendship: 0.25; federall: 0.1; word: 0.1; blood: 0.1; table: 0.1,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 18; ('Federall', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('this day', 'DATE'): 3; ('R.', 'NORP'): 3; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 3; ('nec', 'ORG'): 3; ('Symbolum', 'ORG'): 3; ('Maymonides', 'PRODUCT'): 3; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Nachmanides', 'ORG'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 2; ('sibi', 'GPE'): 2; ('sanguinem', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Salis', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Zabii', 'GPE'): 2; ('Federall communion betwixt party', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Comedere', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('scythian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Herodotus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nasamones', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lybia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexander ab Alexand', 'ORG'): 1; ('thracian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Egyptians', 'NORP'): 1; ('ecornibus boum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('veteribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('loco erant', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('invicem propinante', 'PERSON'): 1; ('foederis', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Roxana', 'ORG'): 1; ('Friden', 'ORG'): 1; ('Russia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sigismond', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ferdinand', 'NORP'): 1; ('Muscovian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Shechinah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('SHECHINAH', 'ORG'): 1; ('Silius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Incolis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('qui habet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zion', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cozri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haber', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cozar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mincah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Benedictus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rhodii', 'LOC'): 1; ('Arden', 'GPE'): 1; ('verum dum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('instruunt sacrificiis', 'ORG'): 1; ('carentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('illis quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nebulam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Solinus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sicily', 'GPE'): 1; ('Collis Vulcanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sarmenta', 'GPE'): 1; ('licet viridia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sponte concipiunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vagabunda', 'GPE'): 1; ('quem contigerit', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam imago', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ritè voti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('illo', 'ORG'): 1; ('altari', 'GPE'): 1; ('Maximus Tyrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Comede', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Berachoth', 'ORG'): 1; ('salitum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Archilochus', 'GPE'): 1; ('habita legatione', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etenim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('communem mensam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ezra 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 1; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Palatii', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tully', 'GPE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pliny', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sacris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nulla sacra sine molâ', 'ORG'): 1; ('Il. a. nonlatinalphabet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('foederis', 'DATE'): 1; ('18. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('EPULUM SACRIFICIALE', 'ORG'): 1; ('EPULUM', 'ORG'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Maimonides', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Moreh Nevochim', 'ORG'): 1; ('multarum legum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chaldeans', 'NORP'): 1; ('arabic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Joseph Scaliger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vento', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epist', 'GPE'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Casaubonum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the mahumetane arabian', 'LOC'): 1; ('Scaliger', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('licet sanguis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('immundus admodum fuerit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zabiorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daemonum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('communicationem aliquam cum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daemonibus haberet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('carnem comedentibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ILLUM', 'ORG'): 1; ('mensâ edunt', 'PERCENT'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1"
A30170,3,pilgrim progress similitude dream wilderness world place den place dream,man: 0.5; ch: 0.5; christian: 0.5; way: 0.5; gate: 0.5; place: 0.5; neighbour: 0.45; house: 0.45; thing: 0.4; pli: 0.3; book: 0.2; burden: 0.15; back: 0.05,"('christian', 'NORP'): 23; ('thou', 'GPE'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 3; ('Evangelist', 'PERSON'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('•', 'ORG'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'DATE'): 2; ('4', 'DATE'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ch•', 'DATE'): 2; ('Dispond', 'PERSON'): 2; ('inter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Lu', 'GPE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('sa•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('21 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('30. 33', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tophet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mat 3 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Mat 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('shine light', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Pedro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('the * Heb', 'FAC'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Craz', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Glo•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('13. 20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Plia le', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fellows', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('4 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('16. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Seraphim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('cherubin', 'GPE'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('6. 37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('free', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ch', 'LOC'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pro•', 'GPE'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('De•', 'GPE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('12. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gat•', 'ORG'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('ca•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('tian', 'NORP'): 1; ('g•', 'NORP'): 1; ('deat•', 'ORG'): 1; ('interpreter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('goodman', 'ORG'): 1; ('the mount Zion', 'LOC'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A30170,3 | 10688,hand parlour dust review while interpreter call man dust christian,man: 0.5; christian: 0.5; thing: 0.5; way: 0.5; interpreter: 0.5; passion: 0.5; hand: 0.45; chr: 0.4; patience: 0.4; world: 0.35; place: 0.15; heart: 0.1; wall: 0.1; fire: 0.05,"('christian', 'NORP'): 35; ('thou', 'GPE'): 13; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('inter', 'PERSON'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Hyp', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Ro', 'PERSON'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('14', 'DATE'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Slowth', 'NORP'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('R•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mor•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the next year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bu•', 'ORG'): 1; ('this year', 'DATE'): 1; ('next year', 'DATE'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cor 4', 'ORG'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('T•', 'ORG'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chr', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('6. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('10. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('tarry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mat 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12 gather', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Ch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sepulchre', 'GPE'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sepalcher', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('more than a thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('as above a thousand year', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1"
A30170,3 | 10803,christian loss blood glory grace love country household see speak,christian: 0.5; apollyon: 0.5; chr: 0.5; way: 0.5; man: 0.5; sword: 0.45; prince: 0.35; hand: 0.35; valley: 0.35; apol: 0.3; place: 0.25; thing: 0.15; service: 0.15; lord: 0.1; death: 0.05,"('christian', 'NORP'): 37; ('Apollyon', 'ORG'): 14; ('thou', 'GPE'): 13; ('Apollyon', 'GPE'): 10; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 9; ('Apol', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 3; ('pilgrim', 'ORG'): 2; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('late at night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11. 33', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sisera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gideon', 'ORG'): 1; ('six hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('Goliath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('33. 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Gat•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian s•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arm•', 'GPE'): 1; ('perhap•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('prey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apollyo•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Smoak', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('oth•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Apol', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•', 'ORG'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jam. 4. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('Apollyon', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christi•', 'ORG'): 1; ('sa•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Beelzebub', 'ORG'): 1; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sword', 'PERSON'): 1; ('C•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jeremiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ian', 'NORP'): 1; ('44. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('107', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ps', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('quagg', 'GPE'): 1; ('quagg', 'NORP'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('116', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('several mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1"
A30170,3 | 10863,thing slip notice Christian confound voice h• come mouth pit,chr: 0.5; faith: 0.5; christian: 0.5; man: 0.5; way: 0.5; god: 0.5; self: 0.5; valley: 0.5; thing: 0.4; day: 0.35; time: 0.15; pilgrim: 0.05; reason: 0.05,"('christian', 'NORP'): 19; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 2; ('pilgrim', 'ORG'): 2; ('d•', 'PERSON'): 2; ('ho', 'PERSON'): 2; ('T•', 'ORG'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Ps', 'ORG'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('9 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Quag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('I|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tra•', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('valley', 'LOC'): 1; ('espi•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bee', 'ORG'): 1; ('V•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('g d• … d y•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dispond', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mirc', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adam the •', 'PERSON'): 1; ('C•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eph.', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('216', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('about half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('Chr', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phi', 'ORG'): 1; ('3. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mar. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('R•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3 35', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A30170,3 | 11001,faith reason put question faithful deal talk notion truth hear,man: 0.5; town: 0.5; lord: 0.5; mr: 0.5; vanity: 0.5; make: 0.45; faith: 0.4; religion: 0.4; cage: 0.25; word: 0.25; name: 0.25; say: 0.15; time: 0.15; put: 0.05; thing: 0.05; pilgrim: 0.05; way: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 2; ('Rai•', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Judg', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 2; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('blindman', 'PERSON'): 2; ('malice', 'PERSON'): 2; ('love', 'PERSON'): 2; ('liveloose', 'PERSON'): 2; ('heady', 'PERSON'): 2; ('enmity', 'PERSON'): 2; ('cruelty', 'PERSON'): 2; ('implacable', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('C•', 'NORP'): 1; ('g•', 'NORP'): 1; ('C•', 'ORG'): 1; ('k•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•', 'ORG'): 1; ('VanityFair', 'ORG'): 1; ('the year long', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isa 40', 'DATE'): 1; ('11 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('almost five thousand year ago', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apollyon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Va•', 'GPE'): 1; ('last all the year long', 'DATE'): 1; ('p•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the Britain •', 'ORG'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Itali•', 'ORG'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('English', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Reelzebub', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pilgrim', 'ORG'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('2d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('behold', 'GPE'): 1; ('Traf•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('T•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pilgri•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('giv•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•', 'NORP'): 1; ('misfortun• … s', 'ORG'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hategood', 'GPE'): 1; ('Beelzebub', 'ORG'): 1; ('Picktbank', 'ORG'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pickth•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('V•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bespatter•', 'ORG'): 1; ('sirrah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sirrah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Fa•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('envy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('spok•', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pickthank', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day of Nabuchadnezzar', 'DATE'): 1; ('Darius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nogood', 'GPE'): 1; ('liar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nogood', 'PERSON'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Lyar', 'PERSON'): 1"
A30170,3 | 11161,Chr. master grace appear king champion t• king champion t•,chr: 0.5; man: 0.5; hopef: 0.5; way: 0.5; self: 0.5; thing: 0.5; sin: 0.5; god: 0.5; christian: 0.5; atheist: 0.5,"('christian', 'NORP'): 9; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('hopef', 'PERSON'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('n•', 'ORG'): 2; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('•', 'ORG'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Goliath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('their day', 'DATE'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arr•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thund•', 'GPE'): 1; ('quiv•', 'LOC'): 1; ('glit•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jo•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('such footman', 'DATE'): 1; ('the king highway', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa. 10. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ignoranc•', 'ORG'): 1; ('C•', 'NORP'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('l. 1• …', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11. 32', 'DATE'): 1; ('11. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('angel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ro , •', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deu', 'ORG'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rev', 'GPE'): 1; ('the mount Zion', 'LOC'): 1; ('this twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ec', 'ORG'): 1; ('10. 15. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('take heed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('10. 39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•', 'NORP'): 1; ('11 hopef', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Thes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('fault', 'ORG'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vanityfair', 'ORG'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('as•', 'FAC'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('d•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('64. 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('100', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('on•', 'GPE'): 1"
A30170,3 | 11241,hopef mind w• acquaint righteousness man sin righteousness world Chr.,chr: 0.5; god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; righteousness: 0.5; ignor: 0.5; man: 0.5; heart: 0.5; self: 0.45; word: 0.4; hopef: 0.25; thought: 0.15; faith: 0.15; soul: 0.05; lord: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 13; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 3; ('hopef', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mat 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('sa•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year long', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('89', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('heb 4', 'LAW'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Habb', 'ORG'): 1; ('19 min•', 'DATE'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('j•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jesus ◊ Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 4', 'LAW'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('a thousand gallon', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('28. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('nat•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('G• … d', 'ORG'): 1; ('125', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hea•', 'ORG'): 1; ('d•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Attribut•', 'ORG'): 1; ('•', 'ORG'): 1; ('the day of God Almi', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18 1 Co.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cond•', 'ORG'): 1; ('tal•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('about ten year ago', 'DATE'): 1"
A39696,20,stranger lord habitation place dwelling till field make prey another,god: 0.45; man: 0.45; emblem: 0.45; child: 0.45; lord: 0.45; people: 0.4; scripture: 0.35; place: 0.35; day: 0.3; fire: 0.3; care: 0.25; city: 0.15; midst: 0.1; indignation: 0.05; present: 0.05; popery: 0.05; prophet: 0.05; promise: 0.05; principal: 0.05; prey: 0.05; preservation: 0.05; propriety: 0.05; pity: 0.05; piece: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('the day', 'DATE'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 4; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ezek', 'GPE'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ascanio', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('45. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year 1072', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matthew par•s', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezek', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('136', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iudg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zeph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abrabam', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Storge', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isa. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa. 49', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A39696,24,CHAP. Vii attribute divine wisdom chamber security saint time sect,god: 0.5; wisdom: 0.5; lord: 0.5; thing: 0.5; counsel: 0.5; design: 0.5; enemy: 0.45; way: 0.35; man: 0.35; psal: 0.35; people: 0.25; danger: 0.1; thought: 0.1; self: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 15; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 10; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('David', 'PERSON'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 3; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 3; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8. 28', 'DATE'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Ezek', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 2; ('Julian', 'PERSON'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'DATE'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 2; ('Balak', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Balaam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15. 31', 'DATE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council chamber of heaven', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('147', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('139', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11. 36', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('2. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lo••', 'ORG'): 1; ('10. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('50. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ahithophel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('providence', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Job 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ahithophel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hushai', 'GPE'): 1; ('17. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sadducee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rabshakeh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'ORG'): 1; ('23.', 'DATE'): 1; ('21. 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Haman , Nero', 'LAW'): 1; ('9 15 , 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Higgajon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Selah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam necis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Suppressa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24. 49', 'DATE'): 1; ('Leviathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Moab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Shittim', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gilgal', 'GPE'): 1; ('126', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philippus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Davids', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Absalon', 'ORG'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('comfort', 'PERSON'): 1"
A39696,27,CHAP. care God people time trouble chamber rest believer sect,care: 0.45; god: 0.45; people: 0.45; child: 0.45; father: 0.45; danger: 0.45; lord: 0.35; promise: 0.35; thing: 0.25; psal: 0.2; life: 0.2; world: 0.15; isa: 0.1; want: 0.1; please: 0.05; pleasure: 0.05; pet: 0.05; phil: 0.05; place: 0.05; perplex: 0.05; possession: 0.05; portion: 0.05; peace: 0.05; port: 0.05; heart: 0.05; eye: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 19; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 9; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 8; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('daily', 'DATE'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('49', 'DATE'): 2; ('32', 'DATE'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 2; ('57 16', 'DATE'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('x.', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('solicitousness', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('40.', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nilus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Miriam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('6. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('121', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the part hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Io•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quoth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gen. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('southward', 'ORG'): 1; ('4. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('111', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('48', 'MONEY'): 1; ('6. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 26', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('94.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('10. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('138.', 'DATE'): 1; ('73.', 'DATE'): 1; ('144', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32. 40', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ioh. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('14. 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('Heb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11. 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 1; ('every morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Lam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the fatal hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('51.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gen. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('54', 'DATE'): 1; ('27. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day of the east', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Serena', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('4. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('coelis', 'GPE'): 1; ('si deus mei curam non habet', 'PERSON'): 1"
A39696,30,trouble conscience mind relief body sink weight people God relief,god: 0.5; trouble: 0.5; heart: 0.5; man: 0.5; self: 0.5; psal: 0.5; time: 0.5; lord: 0.45; hand: 0.4; people: 0.4; day: 0.15; soul: 0.1,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 36; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 23; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 16; ('thou', 'GPE'): 15; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 9; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 7; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('the day', 'DATE'): 6; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 5; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 3; ('14.', 'DATE'): 3; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('32', 'DATE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('a day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'DATE'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('102', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('uprightness', 'ORG'): 2; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6. 8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('3. 10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('god', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Medes', 'ORG'): 1; ('13.', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Job 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('146', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('78. 57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('48.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alamoth', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Julian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elijah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Medus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Assyrio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('indulge sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('ista litigandi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed orandi tempora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austine', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Medis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('52. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('the golden candlestick', 'FAC'): 1; ('so many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quarter', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('prey indesinent', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.', 'DATE'): 1; ('prey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 38', 'DATE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('86', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('94', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('62. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('59 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('130', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('such day', 'DATE'): 1; ('94. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou reader', 'PERSON'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('119.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('117', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('119. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('133', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('4. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('87.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sodom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isa', 'GPE'): 1; ('66.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('better day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zeph', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A31459,5 | 12900,preach time theme heresy pace kingdom Malleus preach sectary friend,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; thing: 0.5; faith: 0.5; world: 0.5; patience: 0.5; prison: 0.45; time: 0.4; council: 0.3; life: 0.25; mr: 0.2; suffering: 0.15; grace: 0.05; state: 0.05; heart: 0.05; death: 0.05; gatehouse: 0.05,"('Cawton', 'GPE'): 3; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('the council of state', 'ORG'): 2; ('Thomas Cawton', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 2; ('Gatehouse', 'ORG'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Malleus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('the year 1648', 'DATE'): 1; ('February', 'DATE'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that month', 'DATE'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('yesterday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Derby', 'ORG'): 1; ('the twenty six day of', 'DATE'): 1; ('February 1648', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hesilrige', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rowland', 'ORG'): 1; ('Richard freeman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('February , 1648', 'DATE'): 1; ('next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of estate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Oliver Cromwell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('irish', 'NORP'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('derby-house', 'ORG'): 1; ('this three day of march', 'DATE'): 1; ('1648', 'DATE'): 1; ('R. Denbigh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('prese', 'NORP'): 1; ('almost half a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('cawtons', 'PERSON'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a secret reserve', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nazianzeus', 'GPE'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('•ould', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gamzu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ochino', 'PERSON'): 1; ('un', 'ORG'): 1; ('chiuro', 'GPE'): 1; ('nella poverta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('la gloria nelle confusioni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('la securta', 'ORG'): 1; ('la', 'GPE'): 1; ('la quiet', 'GPE'): 1; ('la vita', 'ORG'): 1; ('nella morte', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('kuow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ipsam doloris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('immoti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('alii etiam laeti sint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul be buffet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Athauasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam syllabam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('trouuer de harnois', 'PERSON'): 1; (""que s'il se trouvoit des"", 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nazianzen', 'LOC'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adamas', 'ORG'): 1; ('quia molle patimur', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('necessitatis delinquendi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Reyner', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chrysost', 'ORG'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Martis', 'NORP'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augusti 1649', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cawton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scobell Cler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('re••tions', 'LAW'): 1"
A33333,4,scripture mention particular other persecution flood Gen. say earth God,people: 0.5; god: 0.45; king: 0.45; lord: 0.45; son: 0.45; verse: 0.45; jeremiah: 0.4; prophet: 0.4; babylon: 0.4; blood: 0.2; captivity: 0.1; persecute: 0.1; slay: 0.05; city: 0.05; sword: 0.05; paul: 0.05; pate: 0.05; person: 0.05; persia: 0.05; persecutor: 0.05; persecution: 0.05; perform: 0.05; peace: 0.05; jew: 0.05; earth: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Jeremiah', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 5; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 4; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jerem', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 4; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jehu', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Pashur', 'GPE'): 3; ('Zedekiah', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'DATE'): 2; ('4', 'DATE'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Manasse', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 2; ('6', 'DATE'): 2; ('37', 'DATE'): 2; ('38', 'DATE'): 2; ('Babylonish', 'NORP'): 2; ('Haman', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('19 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('Canaan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ishmael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'NORP'): 1; ('1. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Siphra', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Puah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Nilus', 'GPE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('quo magè sora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('justice', 'ORG'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam 22', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a few day', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hanani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 1; ('16. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Micaiah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 26', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34.', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jezreel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jezabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zimri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Assyria', 'GPE'): 1; ('33. 11. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('18. 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jeremiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('20. 2', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zedekiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Johanan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nabuchadnezzar', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43. 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('44. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seventy year', 'DATE'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ahasuerus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Esther 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fifty cubit', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Mordecay', 'GPE'): 1; ('Esther 7', 'ORG'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antiochus Epiphanes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Elymais', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judaea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Babylon', 'GPE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1"
