tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A18914,28,death latin tume Infernus depth word depth cast lake fire,church: 0.45; year: 0.45; time: 0.45; saint: 0.45; hand: 0.45; john: 0.45; glory: 0.45; christ: 0.45; description: 0.45; death: 0.35; life: 0.1; orpheus: 0.05; oration: 0.05; people: 0.05; peer: 0.05; paul: 0.05; patience: 0.05; part: 0.05; parioch: 0.05; oxford: 0.05; peter: 0.05,"('John', 'PERSON'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 3; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 2; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Iustin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Moravia', 'GPE'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('jubilee', 'PERSON'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Infernus', 'ORG'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('the universal day', 'DATE'): 1; ('saint John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Galat', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ierushalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezek', 'ORG'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('Magog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('only thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Benjamin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leuj', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezekiel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iehouah Shammah', 'ORG'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heauen,2', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein shall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('midday', 'TIME'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sibilla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orpheus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Suida', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('about some 1300', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isocrates', 'GPE'): 1; ('360', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('300. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('260', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iulius Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('between 40', 'DATE'): 1; ('50. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Horace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Martialis Cephas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about 58.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('73. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antioche', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about 112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('154', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('170', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ireneus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Polycarpe', 'GPE'): 1; ('200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('202', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('210', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('216', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('249', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('261', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('280', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('326', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('338', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('347', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nyssen', 'ORG'): 1; ('348', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('371', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('375', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('378', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('500 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('five hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('500 of year', 'DATE'): 1; ('399', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('402', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hesichius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('310', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexandr', 'ORG'): 1; ('418', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('427', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theodoret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('433', 'DATE'): 1; ('467', 'DATE'): 1; ('Fulgentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('468', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rhemigius', 'ORG'): 1; ('478', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('492', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('504', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('580', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregorius Mag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('591', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('660', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('720', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('767', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('848', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Giselbert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('879', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('885', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1102', 'DATE'): 1; ('1110', 'DATE'): 1; ('1148', 'DATE'): 1; ('decretal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1232', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aquin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1240', 'DATE'): 1; ('1287', 'DATE'): 1; ('1340', 'DATE'): 1; ('Wicliffe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('VVicliffe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bangor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Constance', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lutterworth', 'ORG'): 1; ('Parioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Prague', 'GPE'): 1; ('VVicliffe', 'ORG'): 1; ('fifty-four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bobemia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nobles', 'ORG'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('about the year 1385', 'DATE'): 1; ('L. Montague', 'PERSON'): 1; ('L. Clifford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salisbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('1400.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('1367', 'DATE'): 1; ('Walter Brutus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1384', 'DATE'): 1; ('Wideford', 'ORG'): 1; ('1396', 'DATE'): 1; ('1433', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sabellicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('1482', 'DATE'): 1; ('Virgil vrb .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1520', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul Ricius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1537', 'DATE'): 1; ('Wolphius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1544', 'DATE'): 1; ('their year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zegedin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Carranza', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Goropius Becanus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ja', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Brocard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('H. Br', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gerard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zuinglius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bullinger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('LECTORI', 'PERSON'): 1; ('herein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romanistes', 'ORG'): 1"
A17020,3 | 1246,testimony Sect. christian confession extinguish come Martin Luther reason assign,pope: 0.5; man: 0.5; time: 0.5; council: 0.5; church: 0.5; king: 0.5; god: 0.4; year: 0.4; bohemia: 0.3; priest: 0.25; hussites: 0.2; zisca: 0.2; john: 0.05; lib: 0.05; bohemians: 0.05; death: 0.05; cochleus: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('John', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Prague', 'GPE'): 7; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Zisca', 'ORG'): 5; ('Hussites', 'LOC'): 4; ('Bohemia', 'GPE'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('George', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ladislaus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Onuphrius', 'ORG'): 3; ('Bohemia', 'ORG'): 3; ('Hussites', 'GPE'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Pius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the council of Constance', 'ORG'): 2; ('Cochl', 'NORP'): 2; ('bohemians', 'NORP'): 2; ('forty thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Martin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Thabor', 'GPE'): 2; ('the council of Basil', 'ORG'): 2; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sigismond', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Bohem', 'GPE'): 2; ('130', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Aeneas Silvius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Constance', 'GPE'): 2; ('Poggius', 'ORG'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Coch', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Pragens', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Conradus', 'ORG'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Vratislauia', 'ORG'): 2; ('Silesia', 'GPE'): 2; ('seven year', 'DATE'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('english', 'NORP'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Io', 'LOC'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Martin Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cochleus l. 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Naples', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tabulo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('Constant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirty thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('icis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cochleus l. 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Messiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sigismundo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Johannes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Procopius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Historia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ref', 'ORG'): 1; ('qua••s Zisca', 'ORG'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Latines', 'ORG'): 1; ('Martine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tahul', 'GPE'): 1; ('Platin', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of Sess', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hungaria', 'LOC'): 1; ('Histor', 'GPE'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hierom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aretinum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Poggius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etiam appetiuisse', 'ORG'): 1; ('L. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nacti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pragensis Suff', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Suffragan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ita incipit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dom', 'ORG'): 1; ('incipit sancta syn•dus hibita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1421', 'DATE'): 1; ('Conrad', 'GPE'): 1; ('Conradus Archiep', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hussitis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('•d', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hussites', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year 1421', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lituania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hussites', 'NORP'): 1; ('vtri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('communi•ca•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('s• cross crdine• psomoueantar', 'ORG'): 1; ('ordine•tur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sigismond', 'GPE'): 1; ('the university of Prague', 'ORG'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Kakizana', 'GPE'): 1; ('Capistranus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the year 1453', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aeneas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('George of Gyrziko', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Georgius Girziko de cunstat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('podiebrat quem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Acneas Poggi', 'GPE'): 1; ('v•••re solebat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bohemis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hussititae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('haud immeritò', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year 1458', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pope Pius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year 1462', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hungary', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Moravia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mathias', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mathias', 'ORG'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('1471', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cochleus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apocalypse', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('monastéria quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bonorem', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam soli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iohann', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hussite', 'GPE'): 1; ('Puritan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Artic', 'ORG'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Artic', 'GPE'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('the holy day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eve', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('the year 1415', 'DATE'): 1; ('1517', 'DATE'): 1; ('Waldenses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year 1508', 'DATE'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('VValdensium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vnsauor•', 'ORG'): 1; ('execrabl•', 'ORG'): 1; ('raven wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seiden', 'GPE'): 1; ('li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Minerius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Merindol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luea•', 'ORG'): 1; ('the 16 century', 'DATE'): 1; ('about the year 1500', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luther ) Baptista Mantuanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Franciseus Picus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mirandula', 'GPE'): 1; ('Keiserspergius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hilton', 'GPE'): 1; ('Andreas Proles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sauanorola', 'ORG'): 1; ('Oratio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Picus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mantuan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arcana reuelo nonignota loquor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Europam', 'ORG'): 1; ('agre scurris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('venerabilis ara cynaedis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ganymedibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thuris', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('odorati globulos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mollis Arabs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('venalia nobis', 'FAC'): 1; ('Altaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Coronae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thura', 'ORG'): 1; ('coelum est venal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sauanorola', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ps', 'LOC'): 1; ('52', 'DATE'): 1; ('testi••', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trithemius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('m. Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laurentius Valla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('donationē Const', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('about the year 1420', 'DATE'): 1; ('Archdeacon de ann•tis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicholaus Clemang•is', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petrus de Aliaco', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cambray', 'ORG'): 1; ('holy day', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hypocritas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leonardus Aretinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Coloniensem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antonius Cornelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('decem grauami', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Catologus', 'ORG'): 1"
A17020,3 | 1253,time Sect. slander papist day m. Luther man religion time,pope: 0.5; man: 0.5; book: 0.5; doctrine: 0.5; time: 0.5; john: 0.5; king: 0.45; opinion: 0.4; papist: 0.3; wicklef: 0.15; bishop: 0.15; year: 0.1; god: 0.1; master: 0.1; burn: 0.1; church: 0.05; place: 0.05; day: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Wicklef', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Oxford', 'GPE'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 4; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('John', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Constance', 'GPE'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('John Wicklef', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('english', 'NORP'): 2; ('Hussites', 'LOC'): 2; ('Bohemia Wiclefs', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Wiclefs', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Wiclef', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Wiclef', 'GPE'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Richard 2', 'PERSON'): 2; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Marsilius of Padua', 'ORG'): 2; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Walter', 'NORP'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Lollards', 'ORG'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('Catal', 'ORG'): 2; ('Dulcinus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prague', 'GPE'): 1; ('Io', 'LOC'): 1; ('Wiclif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('platina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aeneas Silvius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Histor', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bohem', 'GPE'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Coehleus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vniuer', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('mihi quidam', 'FAC'): 1; ('sibi', 'GPE'): 1; ('VVitlefi', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('mol•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('videantur •quari opera', 'ORG'): 1; ('beati', 'ORG'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hussites', 'NORP'): 1; ('vviclefistis cum dulcinistis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ihi', 'NORP'): 1; ('VViclefi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romanistes', 'ORG'): 1; ('s•ss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of Constance', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 23', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cochl', 'NORP'): 1; ('VViclefi', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('quam •uit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Wilh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wideford', 'ORG'): 1; ('Wiclef', 'ORG'): 1; ('Artic', 'GPE'): 1; ('V•rg', 'ORG'): 1; ('Catalogo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gant', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apolog ▪ hicra•c', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Henry Percy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lancaster', 'ORG'): 1; ('Archb', 'ORG'): 1; ('Regist', 'NORP'): 1; ('G. Courtney', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lōdon', 'GPE'): 1; ('arthiepi•c', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leicester Abby', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Leicestrensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lutterworth', 'ORG'): 1; ('Albanes', 'GPE'): 1; ('R.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Simon Sudbury', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bailioll', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bali•l', 'ORG'): 1; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Robert Rigges', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fox', 'ORG'): 1; ('vit•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nicholas Herford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip Repington', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Ashton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Repington', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eleventh', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('the year 1378', 'DATE'): 1; ('literis Reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('henrici', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas Arundel archbishop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lollardy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Wicleuisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('1406', 'DATE'): 1; ('operib', 'GPE'): 1; ('I. Hus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('1476', 'DATE'): 1; ('Wicklefs', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Geoffrey Chaucer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year 1400', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('Chaucer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('lorell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hereford', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year 1393', 'DATE'): 1; ('Episcops Herefor•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three year and a half', 'DATE'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dux Cleri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('666', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('William Wideford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Waltherus Britta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('articul', 'GPE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hereford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erfordensem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Wicklefs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1400', 'DATE'): 1; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('William Sawtree', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Badby', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thorpe', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wicklef', 'GPE'): 1; ('246', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the first year', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cobham', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Claydon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry the sixth', 'FAC'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year 1371', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('•esitatis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Marsilius Patauinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the year 1324', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lewes of Bauiere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the supreme authority of the', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laity', 'ORG'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marsilius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Petrus Messiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bauiere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Occam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Erford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dulcinists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Franciscus Petrarcha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('libros de Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petrarch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Genebrard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1327', 'DATE'): 1; ('Petrus Johannes Biraensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Piranensis', 'GPE'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('a few year', 'DATE'): 1; ('l. 18', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Johannes', 'GPE'): 1"
A17297,15,destitution man comfort friend David right hand Psal. dear friend,friend: 0.5; god: 0.5; name: 0.5; man: 0.5; love: 0.5; david: 0.5; ill: 0.45; life: 0.4; self: 0.4; report: 0.35; world: 0.15; evil: 0.15; king: 0.05; time: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 10; ('David', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('142.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forlese', 'NORP'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hortano Car.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Suprema', 'ORG'): 1; ('last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('China', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bristol', 'ORG'): 1; ('indian', 'NORP'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('perpetuam rei infamiam .', 'ORG'): 1; ('ludibrium medicorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Att', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lacedaemon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Meribah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Absalon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ahimaas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Publicans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Shimei', 'GPE'): 1; ('Belial', 'GPE'): 1; ('17.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A19475,1,author reader work care evil way sin book end day,repentance: 0.35; god: 0.35; sin: 0.35; grace: 0.35; life: 0.35; man: 0.35; whole: 0.3; way: 0.25; thing: 0.25; soul: 0.2; evil: 0.15; preach: 0.15; prayer: 0.15; print: 0.15; prejudice: 0.15; precept: 0.15; preacher: 0.15; prophet: 0.15; pope: 0.15; potentate: 0.15; publish: 0.15; work: 0.1; faith: 0.05; andrew: 0.05; right: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Andrew', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('John Andrew', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Andrews', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nicholas Okes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1621', 'DATE'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Verulam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chanceller of England', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('thereon zealous', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christo', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('4. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Latins', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Resipiscentia', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Conuersio', 'GPE'): 1; ('Recessus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Accessus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Agrippa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lunam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rotam Solis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the first quarter of the moon', 'DATE'): 1; ('cor the circle of the sun', 'ORG'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1"
A19475,13,sin life God heaven Christ heaven hell reader name Jesus,sin: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; repentance: 0.5; christ: 0.5; heart: 0.5; friend: 0.5; time: 0.5; world: 0.5; court: 0.4; people: 0.05; day: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15. 14. 15', 'DATE'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Richard west', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Dick Whipper', 'PERSON'): 2; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('Deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Esqr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('F. S. A.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dick vvhipper', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('venite beati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Maledicti', 'GPE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Wright', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1607', 'DATE'): 1; ('William Durdant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Francis Moore', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iewrie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the next court day', 'DATE'): 1; ('R. W.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('each day', 'DATE'): 1; ('watery surge sea', 'ORG'): 1; ('asundry', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sinai', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iewrie', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('peacemaker', 'ORG'): 1"
A13294,26 | 3288,Nyssa Gregori•• Nyssenus city Mysia call Pythopolis brother Basilius Magnus,bishop: 0.5; lib: 0.5; cap: 0.5; emperor: 0.5; man: 0.45; reign: 0.45; time: 0.4; god: 0.4; book: 0.4; arrian: 0.25; council: 0.25; life: 0.15; year: 0.1; jerome: 0.05; theod: 0.05; town: 0.05,"('lib', 'PERSON'): 26; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 8; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Socrat', 'GPE'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 6; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 5; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 5; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('arrian', 'NORP'): 5; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 5; ('Valentinian', 'NORP'): 5; ('Magd', 'PERSON'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Constantius', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Theod', 'ORG'): 4; ('France', 'GPE'): 4; ('Iustina', 'GPE'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('Cappadocia', 'PERSON'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Didymus', 'ORG'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Jerom', 'GPE'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 3; ('Seleucia', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Milan', 'GPE'): 3; ('August', 'DATE'): 3; ('Bethlehem', 'ORG'): 2; ('sozom lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Palestina', 'GPE'): 2; ('Eleutheropolis', 'GPE'): 2; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 2; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 2; ('Sozom', 'GPE'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gaza', 'GPE'): 2; ('Basilius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Julian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Antiochia', 'GPE'): 2; ('Nisibis', 'GPE'): 2; ('Mesopotamia', 'GPE'): 2; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Thebaida', 'GPE'): 2; ('Eusebius Samosatenus', 'ORG'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Julian', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Valens', 'ORG'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 2; ('Maximus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Hilarius', 'ORG'): 2; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Honorius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Prudentius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Arrius', 'GPE'): 2; ('Athanasius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Paula', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Nyssa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nyssenus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mysia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pythopolis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Basilius Magnus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregorius', 'ORG'): 1; ('21.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('mount Olive•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salamina', 'LOC'): 1; ('Cyprus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Panarium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anchoratus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Oeconomus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pentapolis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('John Chrysostome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cyprus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Luci••', 'GPE'): 1; ('Adrianopolis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ancyra', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hellanicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tripoli', 'GPE'): 1; ('Spyridion', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trimythus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caesarea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constantius , Theod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Neocaesarea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Meletius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Edessa', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eulogius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Protogenes', 'NORP'): 1; ('Valens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Antinoe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trianopolis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Amphilochius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iconium', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lycaonia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pelagius Laodicenus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the first night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Meletina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Armenia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theodoretus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Massaliani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephem Syrus', 'ORG'): 1; ('syrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zenon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maioma', 'GPE'): 1; ('Phoenicia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sozomenus', 'FAC'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Habacuk', 'NORP'): 1; ('Micheas', 'ORG'): 1; ('bishop', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sozom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arnobius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arnob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('330', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lactantius F•rmianus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arnobius', 'LOC'): 1; ('Meleuitanum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Parmenianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('51.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thessalonica', 'GPE'): 1; ('Poitiers', 'GPE'): 1; ('the council of Milan', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thebaida', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phrygia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leonas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thessalia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hilarius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arrianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('six year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Symmachus , Ambrose', 'ORG'): 1; ('Valentinian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Liguria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ruffin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('perswas••e', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arrianisine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marcellina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Protasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gervasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gratianus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Illyricum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eugenius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aquileia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eugenius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hetruria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thessalonica', 'LOC'): 1; ('the three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('twentie-two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('albeit greek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('50.58', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('restat ut aëriam pingas ab origine gentem•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('iudam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aerium David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magnorum corpora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeria', 'GPE'): 1; ('ipsam', 'GPE'): 1; ('alvum acre fallaci', 'ORG'): 1; ('Osius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Corduba', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dioclesian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Maximianus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aegypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('easter day', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Sardica', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iulius', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('his decrepit year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the council of Syrmium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dalmatia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Stridon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Marcelia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sophronia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eustochium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Damasus B.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Palestina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epiphanius B. of Cyprus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nazianzenus B.', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judaea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paulinianus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('holy virgin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heliodorus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ruffinus', 'FAC'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('13.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaiam', 'GPE'): 1; ('angel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year of his age 91', 'DATE'): 1"
A13294,28,CENTVRIE patriarch room Anastatius Gelasius Anastatius year month day day,emperor: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; constantinople: 0.5; rome: 0.5; day: 0.5; year: 0.45; time: 0.4; church: 0.4; john: 0.3; anastatius: 0.25; council: 0.2; lib: 0.1; italy: 0.1; room: 0.1; town: 0.05; man: 0.05; cap: 0.05; gregorius: 0.05,"('Rome', 'GPE'): 24; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 23; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 18; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 17; ('John', 'PERSON'): 12; ('Antiochia', 'GPE'): 11; ('Mauritius', 'PERSON'): 10; ('the day', 'DATE'): 9; ('Johannes', 'GPE'): 9; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Justinian', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Euphemius', 'ORG'): 7; ('Anastatius', 'ORG'): 6; ('Platin', 'ORG'): 6; ('Theodora', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 6; ('Gregorius', 'ORG'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Magd', 'PERSON'): 5; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Narses', 'PERSON'): 5; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Anastatius', 'GPE'): 5; ('Theodoricus', 'ORG'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Justinian', 'NORP'): 4; ('Vigilius', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Timotheus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Evagrius', 'PERSON'): 4; ('platina', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Symmachus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Hormisda', 'ORG'): 3; ('John 2', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2. year', 'DATE'): 3; ('Bonifacius', 'GPE'): 3; ('Hist', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Anthemius', 'LOC'): 3; ('eutychian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Menas', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Silverius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Benedict', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Aquileia', 'ORG'): 3; ('Tiberius', 'ORG'): 3; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Macedonius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the council of Chalcedone', 'ORG'): 3; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 3; ('Macarius', 'GPE'): 3; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 3; ('this century', 'DATE'): 3; ('Gelasius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('August', 'DATE'): 2; ('Hippo', 'GPE'): 2; ('Bonifacius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('eleven month', 'DATE'): 2; ('one year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Narses', 'ORG'): 2; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Severus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Macedonius', 'NORP'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10. day', 'DATE'): 2; ('13.', 'DATE'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('Antiochia', 'PERSON'): 2; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Phocas', 'GPE'): 2; ('the council of Chalcedon', 'ORG'): 2; ('Cappadocia', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Anthimus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 2; ('Apollinarius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Flavianus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Flavianus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Severus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Antiochia', 'NORP'): 2; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 2; ('Evag', 'ORG'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Theodorus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Isicius', 'GPE'): 2; ('Caesarea', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.', 'DATE'): 1; ('year 2. month 24.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Photinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Foelix', 'NORP'): 1; ('Acatius', 'ORG'): 1; ('platina de vitispontif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arrius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Laurentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('platina de vit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ravenna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('6 month', 'DATE'): 1; ('22. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Symmachus', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('18. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('John B. of Constantinople', 'PERSON'): 1; ('imperari', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hermisda', 'GPE'): 1; ('Grecia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantina', 'LOC'): 1; ('arrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('8. month', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'DATE'): 1; ('year 2. month', 'DATE'): 1; ('foelix .', 'DATE'): 1; ('13. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('funct', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bonifacius 2', 'ORG'): 1; ('Agathon', 'GPE'): 1; ('2. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eulalius B. of Carthage', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aurelius B. of Carthage', 'ORG'): 1; ('Coelestinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aurelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of Carthage', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eulalius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aurelius B. of Carthage', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. B.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mercurius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('v•der', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amalasunta', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dioclesian', 'ORG'): 1; ('twenty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Belisarius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Menas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Belisarius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vigilius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pontia', 'ORG'): 1; ('five month', 'DATE'): 1; ('seventeen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('six and twenty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Onuphrius', 'ORG'): 1; ('sicrl•e', 'FAC'): 1; ('coelum subtato', 'FAC'): 1; ('baron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tomb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('538', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Siluerius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athemius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anthemius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Morenus', 'LOC'): 1; ('eleven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('twelve month', 'DATE'): 1; ('twenty eight day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Campania', 'GPE'): 1; ('late spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Totilas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Teias', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nuceria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theodoricus', 'GPE'): 1; ('seventy two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Honoratus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Milan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Istria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('Totilas', 'GPE'): 1; ('twelve year', 'DATE'): 1; ('twenty six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alboinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Longobards', 'LOC'): 1; ('Padus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Platin de vit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sophia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Longobards', 'GPE'): 1; ('Exarchatus Ravennae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chorepiscopi', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('70', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Benedictus', 'ORG'): 1; ('4. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('one month', 'DATE'): 1; ('28. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tiberius the', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pelagius 2', 'LAW'): 1; ('Mauritius', 'ORG'): 1; ('10. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('12. month', 'DATE'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lombardis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sigibertus', 'ORG'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eucharis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Magnus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pelagius 2', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('6. month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pelagius 2', 'ORG'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iustinius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('our day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Servus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ocumenicke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('indici', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phocas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac dicere', 'ORG'): 1; ('tempora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Europae', 'GPE'): 1; ('partibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('barbarorumiuri', 'ORG'): 1; ('eversa', 'ORG'): 1; ('depopulatae', 'GPE'): 1; ('nullus terram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sibi', 'GPE'): 1; ('nomina', 'GPE'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('vocabulis gloriantur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Melito', 'GPE'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Briton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the second century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Greg lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('uncouth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ariadne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gangra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Boeotia and Calchis', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.', 'TIME'): 1; ('Oecumenicke', 'ORG'): 1; ('Diogenes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tom 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'LOC'): 1; ('Scholasticus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John succeed Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chytreus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anthimus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Sophia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anthimus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lib. 4 , cap', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Menas succeed Eutichius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John call nonlatinalphabet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Johannes Cappadox', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gregor .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cyriacus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cyriacus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John call', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tabennesiota', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eutiches', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Severus of Antiochia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anthimus of Constantinople', 'PERSON'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zoilus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eulogius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mauritius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Palladius', 'GPE'): 1; ('xenaeas B.', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hierapolis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nestorius', 'ORG'): 1; ('xenaeas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paulus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Paulus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Euphraesius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euphraimius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theopolis', 'ORG'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('euphraimius follow Domnius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Germanus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Martyrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Helias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eustochius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nova Laura', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eustochius B. Johannes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Goth', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hun', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Schythians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Historio', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zosymas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('evag lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thomas B. of', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apamea', 'GPE'): 1; ('cro••e', 'ORG'): 1; ('Barsaunphius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gaza', 'GPE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eustochius B.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregorius B. of', 'PERSON'): 1; ('idem', 'ORG'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simeones', 'NORP'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('68 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the golden cross', 'FAC'): 1; ('Cosroes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sergiopolis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cosro', 'GPE'): 1"
A13294,34,CENTVRIE Xii pope room Vrbanus Pascalis Paschalis year month day,pope: 0.5; man: 0.5; time: 0.5; emperor: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; day: 0.5; year: 0.45; rome: 0.45; church: 0.45; people: 0.15; france: 0.15; life: 0.1; room: 0.1; month: 0.05; council: 0.05; patriarch: 0.05,"('Rome', 'GPE'): 18; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 17; ('France', 'GPE'): 14; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 12; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Antiochia', 'GPE'): 6; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 5; ('Sicily', 'GPE'): 4; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('Dabertus', 'ORG'): 4; ('Vualdus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('five year', 'DATE'): 3; ('one year', 'DATE'): 3; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('ten month', 'DATE'): 3; ('Arnulphus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('Eugenius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Adrian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Frederick', 'PRODUCT'): 3; ('Antiochia', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Bernardus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Vualdus', 'ORG'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the council of Nice', 'ORG'): 3; ('Paschalis', 'ORG'): 2; ('Lateran', 'GPE'): 2; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 2; ('Henry', 'GPE'): 2; ('Florence', 'ORG'): 2; ('Gelasius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Frangepanis', 'GPE'): 2; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 2; ('Calixtus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Honorius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two month', 'DATE'): 2; ('seven month', 'DATE'): 2; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four month', 'DATE'): 2; ('Tybur', 'ORG'): 2; ('Arnoldus', 'ORG'): 2; ('four year', 'DATE'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Saladin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Saracen', 'NORP'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('Tyrus', 'GPE'): 2; ('twelve year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Gibelinus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Guarimundus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Stephanus', 'GPE'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('Hildebertus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Hugo', 'EVENT'): 2; ('Nichetes', 'GPE'): 2; ('CENTVRIE Xii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pascalis 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eighteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. month', 'DATE'): 1; ('7. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Reginerus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Reginerus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leodim', 'ORG'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('three hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tretas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Albertus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theodoricus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maginulphus', 'ORG'): 1; ('five day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Henry 5.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cincius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregorius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caieta', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vier', 'ORG'): 1; ('kinsman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirteen day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mauritius Burdinus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rheims', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calixte', 'ORG'): 1; ('quondam presbyteri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vxoribus uti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Papa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Honorius 2', 'LAW'): 1; ('platina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arnulphus', 'ORG'): 1; ('fourteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('eight day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rogerius', 'ORG'): 1; ('William duke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calabria Rogerius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pisca', 'ORG'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('Clermont', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rheims', 'NORP'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lotharius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Coelestinus 2', 'ORG'): 1; ('Onuphrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the five month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pestilentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Magdeburg', 'GPE'): 1; ('the eleventh month', 'DATE'): 1; ('eight year', 'DATE'): 1; ('twenty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Clarauall', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty four day', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Noroway', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anastatius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Brixia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Frederick the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anagnia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Octavianus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Papia', 'ORG'): 1; ('h•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of Clermont', 'ORG'): 1; ('venetian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('this pope day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Thomas Becket', 'ORG'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Magd', 'PERSON'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('29 day', 'DATE'): 1; ('eighteen day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Verona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty five day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ferrara', 'LOC'): 1; ('fifty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Clemens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('five month', 'DATE'): 1; ('William king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tancredus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rogerius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Clemens', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six year', 'DATE'): 1; ('eleven day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Celestinus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Saxony', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mentz', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mauritania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Betica', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nicolaus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leo Styppiota', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Basilius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicetas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leontius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dositheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('thirty six year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Biblus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tripoli', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aradus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Raymond', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antiochia', 'NORP'): 1; ('Raimericus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Raynoldus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the summer day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Raynold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sotericus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sotericus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Theodorus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theodorus Balsamus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isacius Angelus', 'ORG'): 1; ('almericus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pisa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Godfrey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ebremarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pascalis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baldwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gulielmus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fifteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Fulcherus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Fulcherus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Raymond', 'GPE'): 1; ('Amalricus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two and twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Petrus Lombardus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lombardus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('the next century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Honorius', 'ORG'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('fifty other day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Waldenses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Lugduno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wolf|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vualdenses', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chronica', 'GPE'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Levit', 'GPE'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joshua 9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gibeonites', 'GPE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Berengarius', 'NORP'): 1; ('vel dominis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernard ,', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Claravall', 'GPE'): 1; ('Burgundy', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theobald', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the 64.', 'DATE'): 1; ('about he three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hildegardis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anselmus Ha•elburgensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Havelburg', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lotharius 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nicomedia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sophia', 'GPE'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('deus de deo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('17.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.18.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phocas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Arrius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Macedonius ,', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nestorius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eutiches', 'PERSON'): 1"
A13294,35,CENTVRIE Xiii pope room Caelestinus Innocentius year excommunicate John king,pope: 0.5; order: 0.5; year: 0.5; man: 0.5; rome: 0.5; monk: 0.5; bishop: 0.45; day: 0.4; rule: 0.35; sicily: 0.2; time: 0.2; friar: 0.2; life: 0.1; christ: 0.05; month: 0.05,"('Rome', 'GPE'): 24; ('Sicily', 'GPE'): 17; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 13; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 11; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('Nicolaus', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 8; ('the year', 'DATE'): 8; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 7; ('England', 'GPE'): 6; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 6; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 6; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one month', 'DATE'): 4; ('Arragon', 'GPE'): 4; ('Gibelines', 'ORG'): 4; ('latin', 'NORP'): 4; ('Colen', 'GPE'): 4; ('John', 'PERSON'): 4; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Frederick', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Frederick', 'PRODUCT'): 3; ('three month', 'DATE'): 3; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 3; ('four year', 'DATE'): 3; ('Johannes 22', 'DATE'): 3; ('Arsenius', 'ORG'): 3; ('Johannes', 'GPE'): 3; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('pope Gregory', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Caelestinus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Innocentius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Innocentius', 'NORP'): 2; ('Honorius 3', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Gregorius', 'ORG'): 2; ('one year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Manfred', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Naples', 'GPE'): 2; ('Vrbanus', 'ORG'): 2; ('three year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Clemens', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('Charles king', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Frenchman', 'NORP'): 2; ('evening', 'TIME'): 2; ('french', 'NORP'): 2; ('Honorius 4', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Gibelines', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('night', 'TIME'): 2; ('Thomas Maurocenus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Germanus', 'FAC'): 2; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Becus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Albertus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Albertus', 'NORP'): 2; ('Dominik', 'ORG'): 2; ('Alexander Neckam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Robertus Gallus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 2; ('Robert', 'PERSON'): 2; ('surge miser', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Clumacensis', 'ORG'): 2; ('Grandimontensis', 'ORG'): 2; ('Vrban', 'PERSON'): 2; ('S. Bernard', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Eugenius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 2; ('almost 200', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one day', 'DATE'): 2; ('CENTVRIE Xiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eighteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('John king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephen Langtowne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('yearly', 'DATE'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Franciscans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frederick the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Otto duke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Otto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten year', 'DATE'): 1; ('7. month', 'DATE'): 1; ('13. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Frederick 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Frederick', 'GPE'): 1; ('18. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Innocentius 4', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('year 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('month 12.', 'DATE'): 1; ('William', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Holland', 'GPE'): 1; ('surge miser ad iudicium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('William de sancto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Charles duke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Manfred', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calabria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apulia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. year 9 month 21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vrbanus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Conrad', 'GPE'): 1; ('Frenchmen', 'GPE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregorius 10', 'LAW'): 1; ('two month', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Michael Palcologus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('venetian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Gibelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Florence', 'ORG'): 1; ('Innocentius 5.', 'ORG'): 1; ('six month', 'DATE'): 1; ('two day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hadrianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hadrianus 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Adrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('8. month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Viturbium', 'ORG'): 1; ('fifteen day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hetruria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Flaminea', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bononia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ravenna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nicolas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('sicilian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Vesperae Siculae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Caelestinus', 'LOC'): 1; ('five month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Caietanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caietanus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Bonifacius 8', 'LAW'): 1; ('8.', 'DATE'): 1; ('year 9 month', 'DATE'): 1; ('17. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bonifacius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Porthecus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gibellinus', 'LOC'): 1; ('the first day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Harold', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philip king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('William Nogaretius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scarra Columnensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gibeline', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scarra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anagnia', 'GPE'): 1; ('200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Georgius Xiphilinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Johannes Cametarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('B. Innocentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Lateran', 'ORG'): 1; ('1215', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pantoleo Iustinianus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pantoleo Iustinianus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Michael Paleologus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Emp', 'LAW'): 1; ('Nicephorus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theodorus Lascaris', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hugolinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petrus Lombardus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aquinae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Magnus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexander 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Guil', 'LOC'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Thomas Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pro se ac si vita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('s•nctus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thomas de Aquino', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Angelicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Albertus Magnus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('William de S.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ingenij miraculū', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Excester', 'GPE'): 1; ('eclipsin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vir bene discretus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('erat', 'NORP'): 1; ('vitam duxit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Oxford', 'GPE'): 1; ('Subtilis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander de ale', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander de ale', 'ORG'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Petrus Lombardus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander de', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arnoldus de nova', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arnoldus de nova villa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('gulielmus de s.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Guilelmus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Laurentius Anglus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laurence a Englishman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petrus Ioannis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('1290', 'DATE'): 1; ('Robertus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Robert gostre bishop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lincoln', 'ORG'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Innocentius the', 'ORG'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Robert gostre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the ministry of the pastoral', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Giles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('heresy gracè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('humano sensu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sacrae contraria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three night', 'TIME'): 1; ('six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('more than thirty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('eius avaritiae totus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eius Luxuriae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('a few day', 'DATE'): 1; ('this century', 'DATE'): 1; ('the seven century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Benedict', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the mount Cassinus', 'LOC'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('182', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1464', 'DATE'): 1; ('archbishop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15000', 'DATE'): 1; ('70', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5655', 'DATE'): 1; ('scolastica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Otho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aquitania', 'ORG'): 1; ('913', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('850', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pope Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romoaldus of Ravenna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('every wednesday', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ierome', 'ORG'): 1; ('the late end', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregorian', 'NORP'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Andrew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregorians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Johannes Gualbertus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vallis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('the year , 1038', 'DATE'): 1; ('Stephen of Auernia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cistertiensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cistert', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Burgundy', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cistertians', 'NORP'): 1; ('wear red shoe', 'ORG'): 1; ('198', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fredericus Barbarossa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1166', 'DATE'): 1; ('Celestine', 'ORG'): 1; ('the year , 1297', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Gilbert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sirington', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year , 1148', 'DATE'): 1; ('Barbus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iustine', 'FAC'): 1; ('Padua', 'GPE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Charterhouse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bruno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gratianopolis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Curtusia', 'GPE'): 1; ('every Friday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gelasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Godfrey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lorraine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sepulchre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pilgrim', 'ORG'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames Burgonion', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('1110', 'DATE'): 1; ('Calixtus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Notorobertus', 'ORG'): 1; ('1119', 'DATE'): 1; ('mount Oliuet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Oliuet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bernardus Ptolemaeus', 'ORG'): 1; ('1406', 'DATE'): 1; ('Georgian', 'NORP'): 1; ('George of Alga', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laurence Justinian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year , 1407', 'DATE'): 1; ('Stephen Harding', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1135', 'DATE'): 1; ('Honorius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year , 1130', 'DATE'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('both morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('thirty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('twelve hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('133', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A19420,61,show mercy saint Christ sake Christ saint sake other prisoner,lord: 0.4; god: 0.4; death: 0.4; sin: 0.35; hand: 0.35; mercy: 0.35; man: 0.3; thing: 0.3; life: 0.3; heart: 0.25; sake: 0.25; christ: 0.2; prepare: 0.1; prayer: 0.1; property: 0.1; promise: 0.1; prisoner: 0.1; prison: 0.1; present: 0.1; provoke: 0.1; place: 0.1; piece: 0.1; body: 0.05; heaven: 0.05; spirit: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 11; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Gloucester', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cranmer', 'ORG'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Steven knight', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'PERSON'): 1; ('George marsh', 'PERSON'): 1; (""th'jnward"", 'DATE'): 1; ('outward sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nicholas Sheterden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1"
A19420,68,George Tankerfield GEorge Tankerfield fire death Alban put hose shoe,death: 0.5; christ: 0.5; god: 0.5; misery: 0.5; lord: 0.5; father: 0.5; sin: 0.45; spirit: 0.45; mercy: 0.45; life: 0.45; hand: 0.15; self: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 14; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jane', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thou', 'PERSON'): 2; ('George Tankerfield', 'PERSON'): 1; ('GEorge Tankerfield', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alban', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Richard brown', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1518', 'DATE'): 1; (""th'apostle st"", 'PERSON'): 1; ('Steven', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bartlet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('deliverer', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1"
A19543,21,CHAP. testimony emperor Zeno Justinian Charles Lewis Henry Frederick Charles,charles: 0.5; constantine: 0.5; empire: 0.5; italy: 0.5; lib: 0.5; marta: 0.5; faith: 0.5; pope: 0.45; ca: 0.45; city: 0.3; donation: 0.15; church: 0.1; king: 0.05,"('Charles', 'PERSON'): 39; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 29; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 26; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 19; ('Marta', 'GPE'): 18; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 10; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('christian', 'NORP'): 8; ('Justinian', 'NORP'): 8; ('774', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 6; ('France', 'GPE'): 5; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 4; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Italia', 'ORG'): 4; ('Justinian', 'PERSON'): 3; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('115', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Desiderius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('italian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Modoetia', 'GPE'): 3; ('796', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lewis', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Theod', 'ORG'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('111', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Steuchus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Steuchus', 'ORG'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('lib .', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Leo the', 'ORG'): 2; ('Italiae', 'ORG'): 2; ('Cont', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ticinum', 'ORG'): 2; ('Eginhertus Eginh', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sigon', 'GPE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sigonius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('772', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Frederick the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marta cit Mart', 'ORG'): 1; ('cit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christianorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('fort', 'GPE'): 1; ('fatui•ie', 'GPE'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Machiavelli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iosh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Euseb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lactantius Lactan', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cyrill', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cyril', 'PERSON'): 1; ('§', 'NORP'): 1; ('caeterū', 'GPE'): 1; ('Regiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nicholas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nich', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fundamenta de Electra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fundamenta', 'GPE'): 1; ('montibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('tota ecclesiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inni•itur', 'DATE'): 1; ('Livius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Camilli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iniqua Senec', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Medea', 'ORG'): 1; ('nunquam regna perpetuo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Senec', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thieste', 'GPE'): 1; ('vbi non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('iuris', 'NORP'): 1; ('pieta', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hippocrates', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arx', 'NORP'): 1; ('principibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Albanus Hier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Donat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romanum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('1559', 'DATE'): 1; ('Quarta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1607', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dionis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gothofr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Castrinsis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Diuum Constantinum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henoticum', 'NORP'): 1; ('Henot', 'LOC'): 1; ('Zenon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoniam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod expugnari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marta Mart', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constantinum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Naples', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romulus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Servius Tullus', 'ORG'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Justinian', 'GPE'): 1; ('leo Iustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Authent', 'GPE'): 1; ('Percurramus', 'NORP'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Steuchus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantinus edicto statuerat', 'LOC'): 1; ('Steuchus reci•es Pag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('114', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Carolini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('116', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Steuc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Charles', 'GPE'): 1; ('Steuchus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('1. Conc', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Horat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ode 16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salomon Prou', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Boet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('60.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('venerabilem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('decretal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Electra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('personā', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caroli', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('ait', 'PERSON'): 1; ('p•ntificis autho•ta •', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romano', 'ORG'): 1; ('impl••um affirma•us', 'PERSON'): 1; ('780', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Carerius Car', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Rome', 'ORG'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Charles overcome Desiderius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rhegino', 'ORG'): 1; ('Papia', 'ORG'): 1; ('the year 781', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aquitane', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hermanus Herm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cronic', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chron', 'ORG'): 1; ('maiori', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Otho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oth', 'GPE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('some year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Athelmus Annal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib authorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Masson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('carol pa 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adalguisus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marian', 'GPE'): 1; ('italiam totam subegit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sigebert Sigeb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('totam', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aimon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fran', 'PERSON'): 1; ('70', 'DATE'): 1; ('francorum potestati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lupoldus Lupold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Imp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Papia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Caroli', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pipine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Charles bello licito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('conque•ed', 'ORG'): 1; ('Saxony', 'GPE'): 1; ('Frisia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('bell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('127', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Siffrid', 'GPE'): 1; ('781', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sigonius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Milan', 'GPE'): 1; ('etiam legibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fidelity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sigonius', 'FAC'): 1; ('Hadriano', 'ORG'): 1; ('773', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('non ait factam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Synodus', 'NORP'): 1; ('idem declaratur Distinc', 'ORG'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de de Iur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gratian', 'NORP'): 1; ('locis citat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Naucl', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lupol', 'ORG'): 1; ('1 rod .', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('§', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mars', 'LOC'): 1; ('a hundred and fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•um', 'GPE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('811', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirty six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('eod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Naucl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1"
A18109,7,God regard will regard nature kind immutability comparison imagination man,thing: 0.5; religion: 0.5; custom: 0.5; man: 0.5; reason: 0.5; matter: 0.5; world: 0.5; god: 0.45; ground: 0.4; truth: 0.35; place: 0.15; nature: 0.05; point: 0.05; opinion: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 17; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 5; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 5; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 3; ('Diod', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nicetas', 'ORG'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athenagoras the', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apologie', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Volusi Bithinica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aegyptus', 'NORP'): 1; ('adorat', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sacri nitet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aegyptiorum morem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ignorat', 'NORP'): 1; ('pravitatis erroribus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aspidem', 'ORG'): 1; ('quippiam fecerint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Jew and Gentiles', 'ORG'): 1; ('Billius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Turk', 'GPE'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('de quibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('scriptura divina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mos populi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('canibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('his 22ae', 'DATE'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bona spiritualia', 'ORG'): 1"
A13804,10,Epilogus friend night appetite rise hand opportunity will plauditie welcome,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; meekness: 0.5; thing: 0.45; mother: 0.45; self: 0.45; time: 0.4; heart: 0.4; help: 0.3; peace: 0.15; pen: 0.15; word: 0.15; church: 0.15; liberty: 0.15; grace: 0.1; spirit: 0.05; love: 0.05; earth: 0.05; lord: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('meek', 'PERSON'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('John TRASKE', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('11. 29', 'DATE'): 2; ('1620', 'DATE'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('APPETITVS', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anamnestes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('ISID', 'ORG'): 1; ('praesentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nolle infer alteri', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod sibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('W. Stansby', 'PERSON'): 1; ('N.', 'NORP'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('IESVS', 'ORG'): 1; ('a few day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ismaclite', 'LOC'): 1; ('Isaac', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rabsakeh', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('a season', 'DATE'): 1; ('christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nemo inuitus bene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('almost a whole year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Johnh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('may 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Timothy', 'GPE'): 1; ('6. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jangler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10 , 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zephan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fail brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zephany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zeph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1"
A13174,12,CHAP. Viii pope time successor Peter Eleutherius pope Joan Robert,pope: 0.5; peter: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; matter: 0.5; eleutherius: 0.5; successor: 0.5; man: 0.5; saint: 0.45; apostle: 0.45; church: 0.25; history: 0.15; lib: 0.1; king: 0.05; succession: 0.05,"('Peter', 'PERSON'): 33; ('Eleutherius', 'ORG'): 13; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('Joan', 'PERSON'): 6; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Marianus Scotus', 'ORG'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('S. Peter', 'PERSON'): 4; ('John', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('Bernard lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Rob', 'PERSON'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Sigebertus Gemblacensis', 'ORG'): 3; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Eleutherius', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Eleutherius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Eugen', 'ORG'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Trithemius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sigebertus', 'ORG'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 2; ('Antonine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 2; ('Audomarus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 2; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Martinus Polonus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ioans', 'NORP'): 2; ('Robert Parsons', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmine de', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clement', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'ORG'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi ille', 'PERSON'): 1; ('conatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plane ab alterutro prohiberis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iulius Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Suitzers', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel sericis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non tectus auro', 'NORP'): 1; ('equo albo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec circumstrepentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('ministris .', 'GPE'): 1; ('satis impleri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petro', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantino', 'ORG'): 1; ('avari', 'ORG'): 1; ('simoniaci', 'GPE'): 1; ('sacrilegi', 'GPE'): 1; ('concubinarij', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('monstra hominum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ipsius apostolica', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('episcopatum desiderat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bonū', 'ORG'): 1; ('laborem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernard lib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eugenius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pastorem te', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('presbyteris illis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Irenaeus lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui successionem habent', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apostolis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Episcopatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tertullian de prescript', 'PERSON'): 1; ('haeret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('conjurer', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('Apostolicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('sermonem', 'GPE'): 1; ('conuersationem', 'GPE'): 1; ('apostolorū', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jonas Aurelianensis lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salesbury', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Babylon Apocalyp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('930', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('anno domini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('854', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johannes', 'GPE'): 1; ('two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('five month', 'DATE'): 1; ('four day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Clement', 'ORG'): 1; ('Martin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vlme', 'LOC'): 1; ('dutch', 'NORP'): 1; ('1486', 'DATE'): 1; ('quando recedam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Francis Petrarch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Florence anno Dom', 'ORG'): 1; ('1478', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Florence', 'ORG'): 1; ('§', 'NORP'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Boccaccio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacobus Gulielmus of Egmond', 'FAC'): 1; ('ridendi norma', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clementis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('855', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eleventh', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Raphael Volateran', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cosmograph', 'LOC'): 1; ('Ioanne', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sabellicus Aenead', 'ORG'): 1; ('Albert Crantz', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baptista', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mantua', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Lucidus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Stella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nauclerus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Henaldus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter Messiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clement at Rome', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sienna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tiber', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Onuphrius', 'ORG'): 1; ('389', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('165', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Martinus Polonus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anastasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luitprandus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Regino', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hermannus Contractus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lambertus Schafnaburgensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Otho Frisingensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vrspergensis', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Benedict', 'PERSON'): 1; ('William', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Malmesbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry Huntington', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Roger Houeden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Florentius Vigorniensis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 1; ('Radulphus Flauiacensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('two or three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('sixthly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Leo the', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anglicus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Maguntinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1"
A13017,6 | 10220,thing law assa bract man end gold commandment observe reward,heaven: 0.5; god: 0.5; earth: 0.5; life: 0.5; man: 0.5; temple: 0.5; world: 0.45; hell: 0.45; sin: 0.45; name: 0.2; thing: 0.15; christian: 0.1; lord: 0.1; father: 0.05; day: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 9; ('christian', 'NORP'): 7; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Martha', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 2; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Artifex', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('ita laborat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ita ludit', 'ORG'): 1; ('ita coenat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ita votat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ita loquor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ita vivit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a holy day', 'DATE'): 1; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sen••t', 'ORG'): 1; ('quādo', 'NORP'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Linacer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('profecto', 'GPE'): 1; ('Evangelium', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christiani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bashan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Martius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Capitol', 'FAC'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('ecclesiam diaboli tendere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scythians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Messala', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bethsheba', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bethsaba', 'GPE'): 1; ('cùm licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quando vitio honos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iephta', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bacchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ephramite', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Puritan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Simeon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Gadarens', 'LOC'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('caepe magis sapiunt', 'PERSON'): 1; (""quam coelum '"", 'PERSON'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Corah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sisera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cerberus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Saracens', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('dam domine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jehues', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed gladius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Russia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thales', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clemens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('poli•icke', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('viderit utilitas', 'PERSON'): 1"
A18772,22,definition priest preesthod general general person ordain God gospel sacrifice,priest: 0.5; god: 0.4; christ: 0.4; man: 0.4; sacrifice: 0.4; sin: 0.4; father: 0.4; epistle: 0.4; shape: 0.35; thing: 0.1; son: 0.1; sacrifyse: 0.1; phrase: 0.1; philip: 0.1; praise: 0.1; power: 0.1; po: 0.1; place: 0.1; preciousness: 0.1; passage: 0.1; paul: 0.1; whole: 0.05; robbery: 0.05; death: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Chryst', 'GPE'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('this day', 'DATE'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the very spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('iiij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Chryst', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Calchas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Po', 'LOC'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Ephe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('IESVS', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Morphe', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('haultye', 'GPE'): 1"
A18772,25,holiday easter week epistle Cor. brethren gospel accept save wit,christ: 0.5; god: 0.5; death: 0.5; life: 0.5; man: 0.5; resurrection: 0.5; body: 0.5; rise: 0.5; argument: 0.4; thing: 0.2; apostle: 0.2; day: 0.15; manner: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 21; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 9; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('John', 'PERSON'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 4; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Cephas', 'PERSON'): 3; ('more than five hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 3; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three day', 'DATE'): 2; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 2; ('every hour', 'TIME'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 2; ('xj', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Simon Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the ministry of the', 'ORG'): 2; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('lyghtsom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('liij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xiij Psalm xxij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jones', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psalm xv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xiij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xiij second', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('marie maudlin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xviij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xxviij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('mark xvj', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cleophas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nathanael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Emaus', 'FAC'): 1; ('the two and twentieth', 'DATE'): 1; ('sixthly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('the very day', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tyberias', 'GPE'): 1; ('xxj', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Esai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theogius', 'ORG'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Stigelius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('nine and three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the moon die', 'ORG'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Lenton', 'GPE'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('the season of the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('the winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the latter day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Io', 'LOC'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iewrie', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tusculane', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A18772,26,Sunday Sunday Easter name Introit take Pet. custom time babe,god: 0.5; son: 0.5; life: 0.5; christ: 0.5; faith: 0.45; water: 0.45; sin: 0.4; witness: 0.4; man: 0.3; blood: 0.3; bear: 0.2; word: 0.15; spirit: 0.15; world: 0.1; place: 0.05; jesus: 0.05,"('three', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('John', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 5; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('this day', 'DATE'): 4; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Introit', 'GPE'): 2; ('Albis', 'ORG'): 2; ('Chryst', 'GPE'): 2; ('iiij', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the first Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Easter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus be Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Chryst', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chryst', 'ORG'): 1; ('Esai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ebr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty-six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xvj', 'GPE'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the ministry of the gospel', 'ORG'): 1"
A18772,33,God ordain people Israel feast easter Pentecost tabernacle memory benefit,god: 0.5; ghost: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; father: 0.5; christ: 0.5; son: 0.5; man: 0.45; heart: 0.45; gift: 0.45; thing: 0.4; person: 0.2; law: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('Esai', 'PERSON'): 7; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('John', 'PERSON'): 5; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('viij', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('daily', 'DATE'): 3; ('Pentecost', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('xxviij', 'GPE'): 2; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Basill', 'PERSON'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Paracletus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Jesse', 'PERSON'): 2; ('••', 'ORG'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Israelite', 'NORP'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Whitsun', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the same year', 'DATE'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this feastful day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abba', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gen.', 'GPE'): 1; ('xxxiij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chryst', 'GPE'): 1; ('eight hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Whitsun', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sūday', 'DATE'): 1; ('cherishiug', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat xxviij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius Palestinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xv•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Roma', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fourteen', 'DATE'): 1; ('••ye •bba', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('m••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Steue•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Laurence', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Agatha', 'GPE'): 1; ('Agnes', 'LOC'): 1; ('•••ie', 'NORP'): 1; ('lyghtlesse hart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('fernoo••d', 'ORG'): 1; ('Esai .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•isdome', 'ORG'): 1; ('•ur lo•d Jesus Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('w••', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ephe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('o••', 'ORG'): 1; ('•••', 'GPE'): 1; ('herd', 'GPE'): 1; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('hereunto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xj', 'PERSON'): 1"
A18772,38,Sunday Trinity epistle John brethren world translate death life brethren,life: 0.4; world: 0.4; god: 0.4; death: 0.4; love: 0.4; man: 0.4; faith: 0.25; lovingness: 0.25; brethren: 0.25; place: 0.25; john: 0.2; argument: 0.15; deed: 0.15; possiblenesse: 0.1; point: 0.1; profitableness: 0.1; preface: 0.1; prayer: 0.1; put: 0.1; possession: 0.1; pinch: 0.1; quinquagesima: 0.1; hatred: 0.1; word: 0.05; sin: 0.05,"('John', 'PERSON'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 2; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 2; ('the second Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('iij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jugurtha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John comfort', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chryst', 'GPE'): 1; ('eschew sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euthymeme', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hart', 'LOC'): 1; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sophocles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plautus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Quinquagesima', 'GPE'): 1; ('a eight day ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('possiblenesse', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two .', 'DATE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A18772,46,faith assure trust settle God faith thing courage deliverance danger,life: 0.5; god: 0.5; tongue: 0.5; place: 0.5; gift: 0.5; man: 0.5; apostle: 0.5; christ: 0.4; day: 0.35; death: 0.3; whole: 0.2; body: 0.1; faith: 0.1; doctrine: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('John', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 3; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('xxj', 'PERSON'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 3; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Cephas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('more than five hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 2; ('Mat xxviij', 'PERSON'): 2; ('twenty-four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('our day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pantaleon', 'NORP'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Agabus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philip the gospeler .', 'ORG'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'GPE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hilarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Auxentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('viij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ierome', 'ORG'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('greek', 'GPE'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Chaldey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dutch', 'NORP'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Corinth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christe', 'ORG'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('Esa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('liij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ose', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jonas', 'GPE'): 1; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mawdline', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tyberias', 'GPE'): 1; ('Galilée', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1"
A18772,68,part Emmanuell virgin Marie say godhead son God word manhood,god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; son: 0.5; man: 0.5; lord: 0.5; nature: 0.45; day: 0.45; virgin: 0.45; sin: 0.4; father: 0.3; incarnation: 0.15; cause: 0.15; death: 0.05; say: 0.05; benefit: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Immanuell', 'ORG'): 5; ('this day', 'DATE'): 5; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('bliss', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Marie', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Athanasius', 'ORG'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Zacharie', 'GPE'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Emmanuell', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christe', 'GPE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Siloh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gabriell', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christe', 'ORG'): 1; ('deliverer', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Valentine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nestorius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apollinarius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('the day spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zacharie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('viij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chryst', 'GPE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xxxiij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ciij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xliij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xliiij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lij .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lxiij', 'PERSON'): 1"
A17387,3,sort place thing object practice example hate company neighbour matter,chapter: 0.45; place: 0.45; world: 0.45; chamber: 0.45; church: 0.45; book: 0.45; god: 0.45; law: 0.45; chap: 0.45; history: 0.3; prophet: 0.05; end: 0.05; people: 0.05; paper: 0.05; piety: 0.05; persuade: 0.05; peregrination: 0.05; posterior: 0.05; part: 0.05; objection: 0.05; order: 0.05; posterity: 0.05; abraham: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 11; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 5; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('chapter 4', 'LAW'): 3; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 3; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('chapter 8', 'LAW'): 2; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('40', 'DATE'): 2; ('44', 'DATE'): 2; ('14.', 'DATE'): 2; ('only six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Malach', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thy quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('thy year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the first week', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year end', 'DATE'): 1; ('farewell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hagiographa', 'LOC'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Exod', 'GPE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('leuiticus', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. third', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deuteronomy', 'GPE'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 2', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 3', 'LAW'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 5', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 6', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 7', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 9', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 10', 'LAW'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 14', 'LAW'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sarah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 16', 'LAW'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 17', 'LAW'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 19', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 20', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 21', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 22', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 23', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 24', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 25', 'LAW'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mesopotamia', 'GPE'): 1; ('chapter 28', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 29', 'LAW'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Esau', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter 32', 'LAW'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dina', 'GPE'): 1; ('chapter 34', 'LAW'): 1; ('Rachel', 'LOC'): 1; ('chapter 35', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 37', 'LAW'): 1; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 38', 'LAW'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 41', 'LAW'): 1; ('chapter 42', 'LAW'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 45', 'LAW'): 1; ('46.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 47', 'LAW'): 1; ('48.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('8. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('39', 'DATE'): 1; ('41', 'DATE'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('48', 'DATE'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('50', 'DATE'): 1"
A17299,12,CHAP. Viii nature kind union Christ fruit effect union make,christ: 0.5; union: 0.5; believer: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; life: 0.5; soul: 0.45; spirit: 0.4; friend: 0.4; grace: 0.25; father: 0.2; unity: 0.1; love: 0.05; make: 0.05; hand: 0.05; head: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 20; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 8; ('David', 'PERSON'): 8; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jonathan', 'PERSON'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('71', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('6. 17', 'DATE'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('{ que } Bern', 'DATE'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vnicè unum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cantica', 'ORG'): 1; ('singularis ac summa illa est vnitas', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('dignatiua vnitas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('17. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bern', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam continentia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('3. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Esa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mephibosheth Jonathan 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 9 son', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ziba', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sam 19', 'PERSON'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Suprema', 'PERSON'): 1; ('last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('20. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ Gal', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.', 'DATE'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('133', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hermon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('68 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iaphet', 'GPE'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paramount', 'ORG'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('145', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A17299,15,CHAP. faith self kind faith church Rome Christian faith faith,faith: 0.5; man: 0.5; vega: 0.5; justification: 0.5; christ: 0.45; god: 0.45; charity: 0.4; word: 0.35; form: 0.35; church: 0.35; love: 0.3; grace: 0.15; doctrine: 0.1; soto: 0.05; rome: 0.05,"('Vega', 'PERSON'): 17; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('christian', 'NORP'): 7; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Soto', 'PERSON'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 5; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 4; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Samaritan', 'ORG'): 3; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('licet non', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Soto de nat', 'ORG'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'ORG'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peters', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cisternes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('mount Garizim', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joseph .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abrahams', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Esa. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 1; ('9 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Siloam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Shilo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Soto', 'ORG'): 1; ('Soto de nat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Controuersia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Soto', 'LOC'): 1; ('lie haec de sola', 'PERSON'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('amittitur', 'ORG'): 1; ('sed etiam quocunque', 'PERSON'): 1; ('alio mortali peccato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quamuis non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('acceptam iustificationis gratiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('diuinae legis doctrinam defendendo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('maledico', 'ORG'): 1; ('•aeterosque', 'NORP'): 1; ('amissa per peccatum gratia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae remanet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui fidem sine charitate habet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Synodus Vega', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trent', 'LOC'): 1; ('Lutherus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Galathian', 'ORG'): 1; ('mortua propriè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('legitimè', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('duae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Soto', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('siue historiae sint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seu', 'ORG'): 1; ('iam gratiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Vega de iustif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paulus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Apostoli', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('ipse christus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('gratiam ;', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ista', 'NORP'): 1; ('institiam nostram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('siquidem illa iam habet', 'ORG'): 1; ('in•uidens', 'ORG'): 1; ('Titus Livius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('equidem', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('formatam', 'GPE'): 1; ('babylonish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cyrus king •erodot', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 1; ('a whole year', 'DATE'): 1; ('three hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the next summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('Babylonish', 'NORP'): 1; ('help•s', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Venus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apelles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ibid', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou', 'NORP'): 1; ('Agrippa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vega', 'GPE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A19506,1,treatise Christ genealogy baptism combat Satan meditation Christian consolation instruction,man: 0.5; honour: 0.5; lord: 0.5; god: 0.5; house: 0.45; name: 0.4; erudition: 0.4; land: 0.35; father: 0.35; praise: 0.35; glory: 0.3; light: 0.1; family: 0.1; word: 0.1; kingdom: 0.05; virtue: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Graeme', 'ORG'): 3; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('William Cowper', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('T. S.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John budge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('1612', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('earl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mugdok', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cens•ntur', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('generi suo dedecori', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Fergus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scot and Pict', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('the east sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('Victorine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gallio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('facta ducis viuunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ahasuerus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leontis', 'NORP'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vitellij', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fabius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antonius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aborigines', 'ORG'): 1; ('Insignia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('nam quae mox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('unquam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('claudian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tecu•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aul', 'ORG'): 1; ('turpe est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('viro', 'GPE'): 1; ('parem dignitatisuae virtutem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Babilonish', 'NORP'): 1; ('maiorem virtutem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epino', 'GPE'): 1; ('Deum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nazian', 'NORP'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('inn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hiero', 'ORG'): 1; ('cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrisost', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
