tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A00912,5,part treatise policy religion necessity religion conservation perfection world prove,thing: 0.45; god: 0.45; creature: 0.45; world: 0.45; end: 0.45; whole: 0.45; religion: 0.4; begin: 0.4; nature: 0.3; man: 0.25; part: 0.25; cause: 0.1; beginning: 0.1; philosopher: 0.05; perfection: 0.05; pillar: 0.05; philosophy: 0.05; philosopho: 0.05; pithagorians: 0.05; perform: 0.05; partaker: 0.05; participation: 0.05; platonicke: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Mercuri', 'GPE'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Dionysius Areopagita', 'PERSON'): 2; ('metro', 'PERSON'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Laertius proem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Philosopho', 'GPE'): 1; ('Plato', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Orpheus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mercurius Trismegistus', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Timaeo', 'GPE'): 1; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jamblicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iambli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timaeum', 'GPE'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thelog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('d• divine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Proclus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Boetius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dux', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dionys', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('nom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Boetius', 'GPE'): 1; ('redituque suo singula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec manet', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Boëtius de consol', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi quod fini iunxerit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Microcosmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('tri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mar. 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('omnis creatura', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euangelium', 'NORP'): 1; ('creaturae aliquid habet homo', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Gregor .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cicero', 'NORP'): 1; ('de vniuersit .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('the whole year', 'DATE'): 1"
A08966,7,reader survey fault book heart wage prevent page nonsense find,god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; verse: 0.5; gospel: 0.5; minister: 0.5; thing: 0.5; saint: 0.45; man: 0.45; church: 0.4; king: 0.3; nature: 0.3; creature: 0.05; grace: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 27; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 23; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 20; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul Bayne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('B. D. London', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Richard Badger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nicholas Bourne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the royal exchange', 'ORG'): 1; ('1634', 'DATE'): 1; ('MARY', 'ORG'): 1; ('Westmorland', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('the university of Cambridge', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Justinian Stubbs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nazianzene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('these last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('exemplary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae sparsa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Macedon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 1 minister', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A05999,11,will God think thing belove sin reformation other thing counterfeit,knowledge: 0.4; god: 0.4; lord: 0.4; tree: 0.4; fruit: 0.4; cause: 0.35; man: 0.35; thing: 0.35; christ: 0.35; power: 0.3; water: 0.2; strength: 0.1; pet: 0.1; perish: 0.1; plant: 0.1; plague: 0.1; place: 0.1; persecution: 0.1; patience: 0.1; paul: 0.1; pray: 0.1; child: 0.05; virtue: 0.05,"('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Obs', 'GPE'): 2; ('15.3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Vinyard', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('92.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('27.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('over night', 'TIME'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.3', 'MONEY'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('sixty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('81', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A04597,5,spiritval armovr choice Zion sovldier war rumour war soldier country,god: 0.5; war: 0.5; soldier: 0.5; king: 0.5; man: 0.5; lord: 0.5; people: 0.5; armour: 0.4; camp: 0.3; zion: 0.15; israel: 0.15; way: 0.15; call: 0.1; name: 0.1; captain: 0.05; life: 0.05; profession: 0.05,"('Israel', 'GPE'): 9; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 7; ('thou', 'GPE'): 6; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 4; ('this day', 'DATE'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('23.21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Iosuah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Baal Peor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Moab', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 2; ('8', 'DATE'): 2; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('10.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sam 23.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('indecti', 'ORG'): 1; ('our day', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.15', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Cain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cain', 'ORG'): 1; ('Habel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Habel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.13.14.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ierico', 'DATE'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.19', 'MONEY'): 1; ('impart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('14.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fidelity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sam 23.8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thraso', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('19.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ierico', 'GPE'): 1; ('the very day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 1; ('24.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Achan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zeuah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Achor', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zion', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('20.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('25 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israelite', 'NORP'): 1; ('Balak', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('58.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hauilah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Shur', 'GPE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam 15.7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1"
A07629,3,death nature depart breath earth enliven breath cast dimension point,death: 0.5; man: 0.5; life: 0.5; soul: 0.5; god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; body: 0.5; nature: 0.45; saint: 0.4; sin: 0.35; pleasure: 0.25; self: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('thou', 'GPE'): 6; ('nec', 'ORG'): 5; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 2; ('finis', 'NORP'): 2; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 2; ('ista', 'NORP'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Job', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rogatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pauor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latro hominis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('omne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam acceperat posse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('accepimus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('velle', 'GPE'): 1; ('ille posse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Satan', 'NORP'): 1; ('saint John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Steven', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('transitum', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('dormiente appellat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('euigilaturo minimè desperemus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('vox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Exitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('transitus quem ire non intelleximus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fati', 'NORP'): 1; ('quisquis ad vitam nascitur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('licet impare nascimur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pares morimur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nunquam enim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('semel mori', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hêu quàm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zenophon', 'GPE'): 1; ('habes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod mortempetam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quaeris', 'NORP'): 1; ('phoenix sponte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ste', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('a season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Onesimus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam vivere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('felicitas', 'NORP'): 1; ('licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('diligimus', 'GPE'): 1; ('mortem pariter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ipse metus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('discedam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('mortis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam ictum', 'ORG'): 1; ('oculi', 'GPE'): 1; ('vita aeterna est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tantùm mortalis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fuiuri', 'GPE'): 1; ('laborat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nimis angustat gaudia', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui praesentibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('scrutatur quod ultra mundum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diuinae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mihi quidem nunquam persuaderi potuit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('animos dum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mortalibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Maecenas', 'GPE'): 1; ('quaero', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Adueniat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('querela', 'PERSON'): 1; ('recusans', 'NORP'): 1; ('non tergiuersatur', 'GPE'): 1; ('fortunatiorem Marcellum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romano', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('qui mori sperat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hunc fert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('patientia', 'GPE'): 1; ('vitam acciperet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('scientibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('placet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('licet counterfeit reuerti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Magistra', 'NORP'): 1; ('faciatne finem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mori nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mortis generosum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui mori', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod vitari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mortis mori', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vinci', 'PERSON'): 1; ('si coeperat suspecta', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cato', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nerua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Siluianus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucretia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae placet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed quaedecet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui miser', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three degree', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('malis', 'ORG'): 1; ('peius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('anfert vitam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('erit somnus dilectis', 'ORG'): 1; ('scala montis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ianua', 'ORG'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('familiarem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('illi laetus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph of Arimathea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('certamina', 'GPE'): 1; ('tactu compressa quiescunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seraphim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canaan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Siloam', 'GPE'): 1; ('neminem aduersa conuincunt', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi quem secunda decipiunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('habitu casto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cum non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nil meretricis habet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('benè', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('nec paena', 'ORG'): 1; ('sepultura', 'GPE'): 1; ('Delineamenta', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam remedia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('podagraesuae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('occupatum mori', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('nam', 'PERSON'): 1"
A07629,5,man aim man David Ezechias Christ man man saviour Christ,death: 0.45; life: 0.45; christ: 0.45; man: 0.45; body: 0.45; soul: 0.45; world: 0.45; joy: 0.35; thing: 0.3; saint: 0.2; day: 0.15; faith: 0.1; sin: 0.1; heaven: 0.1; god: 0.05; per: 0.05; paul: 0.05; poer: 0.05; pleasure: 0.05; plato: 0.05; place: 0.05; pilgrimage: 0.05; person: 0.05; possession: 0.05; peace: 0.05,"('Egypt', 'GPE'): 4; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Austine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('quam nos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Prophetae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apostoli', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Lucili', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('laborem vir', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nulla voluptas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Syrach', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam', 'NORP'): 1; ('amantibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('non horrendâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed blandâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non terribili', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed amabili', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this very day', 'DATE'): 1; ('natalis erit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de contemptu mortis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fortiùs loqueris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ille dicebat non quemadmodum viueret ,', 'FAC'): 1; ('quemadmodum viuendum esset', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Samson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 1; ('fiam farina christo .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sunder million of mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('qui praedixit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('reuixit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('winter season', 'DATE'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('hominem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arbour inuersa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Moab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezekiel', 'ORG'): 1; ('vitam assumeret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam', 'ORG'): 1; ('non eripit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Job', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Naomi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Latium', 'GPE'): 1; ('benè', 'ORG'): 1; ('dici', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('natalem quidem excipit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Goshen', 'GPE'): 1; ('hanc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('homo sperat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Poer', 'ORG'): 1"
A07629,6,division Iii death prepare say divine philosopher Plato time meditation,death: 0.5; man: 0.5; time: 0.5; day: 0.5; life: 0.5; sin: 0.5; god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; soul: 0.45; end: 0.25; world: 0.2; way: 0.1,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 15; ('thou', 'GPE'): 15; ('the day', 'DATE'): 8; ('nec', 'ORG'): 8; ('David', 'PERSON'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('daily', 'DATE'): 5; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Austine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('mortis', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nescis enim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('cozen', 'GPE'): 2; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('quam nescire mori', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sirach', 'GPE'): 2; ('every day', 'DATE'): 2; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('perpetua mortis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mortis meditatio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Totâvitâ', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Totâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Job', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vespasian', 'NORP'): 1; ('first day', 'DATE'): 1; ('last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the first day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Fabianus', 'DATE'): 1; ('tria', 'GPE'): 1; ('tempora vita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod acturisumus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod egimus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('multis', 'NORP'): 1; ('de nullis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('merita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam quibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('praemeditatur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Canos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rugas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pete vina', 'GPE'): 1; ('nardo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('meminisse', 'ORG'): 1; ('nam facilè sustinet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui expectat mortem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('debemus mori', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi senes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Coruina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cras', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tibullus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed credula vitam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vixit heri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quaeque', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mortalibus aui', 'ORG'): 1; ('unum tua tēpora mensem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forsitan', 'GPE'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('man day', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty or fifty year of day', 'DATE'): 1; ('mortalitatis obliuio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vitam incoare', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Barzillai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tempora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mortis nuntij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('iniucunda est', 'ORG'): 1; ('nam serum est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('flower spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('the winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('omnis motus naturalis', 'ORG'): 1; ('mortantur', 'GPE'): 1; ('thy day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gallicinium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Signicinium', 'GPE'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('four day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Proserpina', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('ecce venio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pauci', 'ORG'): 1; ('bene moriuntur .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sibi', 'GPE'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 1; ('Am•liat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vir bone', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('their day', 'DATE'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('viuitur mortuis', 'LOC'): 1; ('Mammon', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('viuamus dum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vita iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•mnes', 'NORP'): 1; ('vitam ordinat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('vita qualem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('velis reperiri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a night', 'TIME'): 1; ('itur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('erat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quando non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('erat', 'NORP'): 1; ('erit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zacheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Totâ', 'ORG'): 1; ('herodian', 'NORP'): 1; ('saint cyprian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam gerimus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('domine domine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ita mortem uti', 'ORG'): 1; ('Stultè', 'ORG'): 1; ('vitam alijs approbare quisquam debet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Tully', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vero', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('some year of day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Improuisa', 'NORP'): 1; ('quod manet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('septima', 'GPE'): 1; ('finem', 'GPE'): 1; ('quando vult', 'PERSON'): 1; ('adrem non', 'ORG'): 1; ('bene mori', 'PERSON'): 1; ('adrem spectat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cain', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('natura', 'ORG'): 1; ('peregi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cernitur', 'GPE'): 1"
A04970,4 | 6264,hope day stone Zion day day death regard assurance engrave,day: 0.5; god: 0.5; david: 0.5; sam: 0.5; tear: 0.45; lord: 0.45; vestro: 0.4; israel: 0.35; people: 0.35; victorinus: 0.3; man: 0.25; page: 0.2; psal: 0.2; pet: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('David', 'PERSON'): 5; ('nec', 'ORG'): 4; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Victorinus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Neh', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Par', 'ORG'): 2; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 2; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Zion die day', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lo••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Babylon', 'ORG'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('immo••••', 'GPE'): 1; ('•elleth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zachar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('270', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('R. Mylbourne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pauls', 'GPE'): 1; ('1620', 'DATE'): 1; ('IACOBO', 'ORG'): 1; ('gratià magnae brittanniae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hyberniae regi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('moderatori summo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oratio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Principum', 'GPE'): 1; ('publicis distentam negotijs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deo', 'ORG'): 1; ('myrrhae fasciculum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('humando iam corpori Dominico', 'PERSON'): 1; ('A. V.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nomē', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('neminem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quenquam accedere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 5.11 .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fateor haud rege', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nec cuiquam', 'ORG'): 1; ('9.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('conatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi patriae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ab Jove principium Musę', 'ORG'): 1; ('mae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caesari', 'GPE'): 1; ('deferat', 'NORP'): 1; ('archetypo laudem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('æquè mandatur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aequè mactatur ipsi deo', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet menstruum desudat', 'ORG'): 1; ('maleuolorū cuncos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rituū Ecclesiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Bern', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pactum', 'ORG'): 1; ('societatis humanae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Aug. vbi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iudae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dominatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('mandantibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fecerim ego meum quò mihi discutere vestrum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 12.3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('si annuitis', 'ORG'): 1; ('cognoscentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('vspiam contradocuerim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel gesserim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('poena', 'ORG'): 1; ('ipsi luant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('degentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('35.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Cypr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil haec', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ad conscientiam fidei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('viribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('16.14.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('serenissime', 'DATE'): 1; ('rex ( cvius ira nuncij mortis', 'ORG'): 1; ('haesitantia linguae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('angustia temporis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae rursus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quo fato nescio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('retardante praelo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paschalia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Parua Tyrrhenum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('haerese retusa', 'ORG'): 1; ('nouae', 'ORG'): 1; ('allisit summos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nimbus vocum', 'ORG'): 1; ('sylua', 'ORG'): 1; ('luminibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('accensa regijs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('auribus illi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('longùm pressos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Victorinus Romae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('secretò', 'GPE'): 1; ('frendentibus demonicolis', 'ORG'): 1; ('suspicientibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('stupentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('viritim sonitu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('strepētibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('intro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cor cuique', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vegetij', 'GPE'): 1; ('praedicantibus exterae regionis', 'ORG'): 1; ('religionis hominibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('5.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('gemino', 'PERSON'): 1; ('piscina', 'NORP'): 1; ('salutis hominū', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Relatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('sepulcra', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ioiadas Pontificum', 'GPE'): 1; ('24.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('domū', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('deleri benignitate vestras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cius officiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('erit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Basilius', 'ORG'): 1; ('anglici', 'NORP'): 1; ('maximus eloquij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apelles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('facta tua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cum fueris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.7', 'MONEY'): 1; ('senio satur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ceu maturarum metafrugum', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Charolus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('tradentibus vobis', 'ORG'): 1; ('lampada posteris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('throno amplior vestro', 'ORG'): 1; ('ipse interim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Serus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Loetus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Britanno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ocyor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tollat', 'GPE'): 1; ('æternùm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Principum', 'NORP'): 1; ('arbitrio viuendi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42.3', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hezekias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('39.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rehoboam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Benjamin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A04034,3,right right right London favour tie ministry be countenance way,tear: 0.5; god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; man: 0.5; david: 0.5; psal: 0.4; cause: 0.35; eye: 0.3; ier: 0.25; israel: 0.25; amos: 0.25; easie: 0.2; kind: 0.15; prayer: 0.15; king: 0.1; voice: 0.05; sam: 0.05,"('David', 'PERSON'): 10; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('9.13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('ark', 'GPE'): 2; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ierome', 'ORG'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psal 36', 'LAW'): 1; ('Bethlehēs gate', 'FAC'): 1; ('outward chase', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.1', 'DATE'): 1; ('Senacherib', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rabshakeh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('god', 'PERSON'): 1; ('69.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam 2.32', 'PERSON'): 1; ('78.61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amos 5.2', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.3 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('12 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hezekias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.7 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Urias', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ioah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abner', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sam 3.32', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal 137.1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Benjamin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('amazonian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Holophernes', 'NORP'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bethulians', 'NORP'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('24.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plaut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aug. Ciuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('relinquamus tarentinis Deo•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aug.', 'GPE'): 1; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fabius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tarentum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ieremiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Psal', 'ORG'): 1; ('62.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jonathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arist', 'ORG'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Aug', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezekiel', 'LOC'): 1; ('8.13.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vnda quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dipnosophist', 'NORP'): 1; ('Phryne', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athen', 'GPE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('amoris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prou', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iudg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xerxes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Amens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Magirus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Geographia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Heliodorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('episaphio', 'GPE'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Eclogis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hieroglyph', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sigismond Gonzaga', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leo the', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Crocodili', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bassian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Geta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Demoneta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cnemon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ishmael', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nethaniah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samaritan', 'ORG'): 1; ('41.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ieremiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mizpeh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cassia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Collat', 'GPE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paral', 'GPE'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('23.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Esa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('69.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hester', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hest', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mordecai', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Shushan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Amos 5.16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'GPE'): 1; ('9.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A03817,3 | 6484,Caluin devil ghost day study writing life time forsake church,god: 0.5; lib: 0.5; cap: 0.5; papist: 0.5; church: 0.5; priest: 0.5; gospel: 0.5; scripture: 0.4; pope: 0.35; law: 0.35; time: 0.15; bellar: 0.1; epist: 0.05; john: 0.05; polyd: 0.05,"('lib', 'PERSON'): 36; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 16; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 15; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('Bellar', 'PERSON'): 8; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('John', 'PERSON'): 7; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('platina', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Hieron', 'PERSON'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 3; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 3; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('li', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Bethauen', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 2; ('de Monach', 'GPE'): 2; ('Aquin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('haeret', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hossius', 'ORG'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Alex', 'PERSON'): 2; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Euang', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Lactan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('quorū', 'GPE'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Gregory', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sigebert', 'PERSON'): 2; ('de missa lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sixtus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Sergius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Boniface', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Gratian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Guliel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Caluin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('diabolus cum tota', 'PERSON'): 1; ('su• caterua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epist', 'GPE'): 1; ('tolerantia perseuerem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theod Reza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('••oan', 'NORP'): 1; ('•ccles', 'GPE'): 1; ('geneuen responsioon put•diss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac totius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theodorus Beza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pleno', 'GPE'): 1; ('geneuensi palinodiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hortans', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caluinismi', 'GPE'): 1; ('catholicae s•dis obseruanti•m', 'ORG'): 1; ('ini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('naziacez', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('plura', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam christus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pomormitan', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('nisi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quantum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aesopi', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Aesop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nouum Euangelium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('andrad lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lindan lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ioh', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cuspian de saracenis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mahomet', 'NORP'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baptista', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Clemens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apocripho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aegiptios', 'LOC'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aug. lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Euah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nicodemus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tatian', 'NORP'): 1; ('de verbo de lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isodorus Clarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bibliorū', 'GPE'): 1; ('8 thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nicodemus Prochorus', 'ORG'): 1; ('John the Euangelist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Martialis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cyrilli', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Carmelitae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Camelite Monk', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Guid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fasci•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gerardus Saragellus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Parma', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sedulius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichristum', 'ORG'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Euscb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.15.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ritus', 'ORG'): 1; ('legis cessabat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.2 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('103', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Boemus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ , Guicciard', 'ORG'): 1; ('Blondus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mantuan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Belethus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. de confess', 'PERSON'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('10 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dagon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('Ashteroth', 'GPE'): 1; ('Amonites', 'GPE'): 1; ('Moloch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Syrians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rimnon', 'GPE'): 1; ('arrian', 'GPE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psa', 'GPE'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pla•o m•haed', 'ORG'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eos', 'ORG'): 1; ('nominibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Boemus de gentleman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. •', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('heathens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Siricius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('storm .', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clemens', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hi••on .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('absistat à', 'ORG'): 1; ('hesterna gaudia', 'FAC'): 1; ('Venus', 'ORG'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'NORP'): 1; ('Adamite', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Haeresib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abdias', 'ORG'): 1; ('contra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Belsar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rhem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Math', 'LOC'): 1; ('Lent', 'EVENT'): 1; ('4. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de cultu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Silvester', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Damasus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antiphonae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kyrieleison', 'ORG'): 1; ('Celestine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gelasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregorian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('the year 656', 'DATE'): 1; ('miss•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Centuar', 'FAC'): 1; ('Stephanus', 'DATE'): 1; ('de missa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('the year 707', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year 731', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bellar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gratian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug.', 'GPE'): 1; ('Petri', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Extrau•gan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Candlemas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Corpus christi day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leo hymn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Naucler', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isidor', 'GPE'): 1; ('festival day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zozimus the Pascall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antiphones', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vrbanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('88', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Martin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hugo', 'EVENT'): 1; ('Floria', 'GPE'): 1; ('matin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mass', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sensing', 'GPE'): 1; ('compleine , litany', 'ORG'): 1; ('Viterbius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anronius', 'ORG'): 1; ('John ru•us', 'PERSON'): 1; ('banner', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bethen', 'GPE'): 1; ('enim quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vocabatur domus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Osea', 'ORG'): 1; ('postquam vittuli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inutilis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Idoli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bethel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Whita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('praefat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scotus', 'NORP'): 1; ('caueantque eaquae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fugienda', 'NORP'): 1; ('Barnard de .', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('omnia sapiente', 'PERSON'): 1; ('blandissimi asimplicissimi dissimulatore', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Holcot', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sap', 'GPE'): 1; ('183', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('deep dissembler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baal', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dagon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Priapus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Didym', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tu sancto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('conuer•', 'LOC'): 1; ('angel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Coloni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iericho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Soph', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iericho', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Grego', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezechi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ier', 'GPE'): 1; ('ecclesiam porcos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('veneri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('somnoque', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bernard .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('147', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nertarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sagittario', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iohan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henricus Agrip', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marozia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peter Lombard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Johan Textor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip the holy abbot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vallisolet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alphonsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mendosa', 'GPE'): 1; ('Valens', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ferdinand', 'GPE'): 1; ('100', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('some 200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Agrippa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Agrip', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('64.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eleven thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gozilon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lambard Shaffan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cronicis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Johannes de Cremona', 'ORG'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1"
A06685,6,face sight lineament draught shadow beauty face contrary peace effect,peace: 0.5; god: 0.5; word: 0.5; man: 0.5; heart: 0.5; lord: 0.4; conscience: 0.4; king: 0.3; soul: 0.2; sin: 0.2; wrath: 0.2; fire: 0.2; jesus: 0.15; quarrel: 0.1; christ: 0.1; father: 0.1; saint: 0.1; world: 0.05,"('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 4; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('saint Augustine', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('bee', 'ORG'): 2; ('5.23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('August', 'DATE'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Coloss', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('qualis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rigour', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Leo', 'ORG'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil gratiu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil desiderabilius concupisci', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tranquillitas', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('simultates tollit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inimicos concordat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('extolli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui acceperit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui amiserit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoniam qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eadem', 'GPE'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('haereditatem domini poterit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('paci', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xenophon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hilarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chrisostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Euthymius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theophylacte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.18.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the ministry of reconciliation', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('polish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Matthew 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Melchisedeck', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter 19', 'LAW'): 1; ('Elijah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.27', 'MONEY'): 1; ('membra nisi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi pace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Basil nonlatinalphabet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Candiaa', 'ORG'): 1; ('decet ira fera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fig', 'ORG'): 1; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 1; ('85.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('duae sunt amicae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non facis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('operari justitiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 32.17', 'LAW'): 1; ('72', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('165', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ill luck', 'PERSON'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('erit cum illo', 'ORG'): 1; ('miseriae', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam beatitudinis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('all the day', 'DATE'): 1"
A06685,7 | 6952,self rose prickle crown glory fight foot Canaan red sea,god: 0.5; king: 0.5; word: 0.5; fear: 0.5; man: 0.5; honour: 0.5; subject: 0.45; prince: 0.45; commandment: 0.45; soul: 0.4; father: 0.25,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Haman', 'PERSON'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('amoris Ianua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('plena', 'ORG'): 1; ('timoris', 'NORP'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iezahel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Oreb', 'GPE'): 1; ('un', 'ORG'): 1; ('bee', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('anchora cordis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scripturel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nilus', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Esther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elders', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.7 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam Chap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abiram', 'ORG'): 1; ('two hundred and fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nadab', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abihu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Levit', 'GPE'): 1; ('10.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abishai', 'ORG'): 1; ('Absalon', 'ORG'): 1; ('22.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sinai', 'ORG'): 1; ('a hundred pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('three hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('prona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wherein reason', 'PERSON'): 1; ('46.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eden', 'GPE'): 1"
A07625,62 | 7604,danger strike dint Heb. thing apostle heart grace service God,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; prayer: 0.5; thing: 0.5; pag: 0.5; mind: 0.5; woman: 0.5; soul: 0.5; body: 0.35; work: 0.3; saint: 0.2; riches: 0.1; self: 0.05,"('§', 'NORP'): 12; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 9; ('lin', 'PERSON'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 6; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Marc', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 2; ('37', 'DATE'): 2; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hieron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tom 1', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Amb', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tha h confide', 'ORG'): 1; ('Esai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Acton', 'GPE'): 1; ('Melforde', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Southfolke', 'GPE'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('127', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('summa ingenuitas ista est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Henry', 'GPE'): 1; ('November , 1272', 'DATE'): 1; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('April 1509', 'DATE'): 1; ('Arthur Plantagenet', 'FAC'): 1; ('the four year', 'DATE'): 1; ('1513', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam praestat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('auferenti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('his young year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Worcester', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Robert Dudley', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('John Throkmarton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('B.', 'NORP'): 1; ('H. cross', 'ORG'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Rheims', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thomas Mores', 'PERSON'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('11.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('grace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('depart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tobias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('16.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('53', 'DATE'): 1; ('Clem Alex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Helisaeas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezechias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anthony of Padua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thaumaturgs', 'ORG'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Avicenna', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jamblicus de Aegyptiorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trismegist', 'NORP'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('132', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tymaeo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Marsilius Ficinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('Georgius Harmonia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. modul', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('64', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dionys', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Max.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('59 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de s. Eusebio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.17.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ierem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ante finem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ad hedibiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('B. Laurent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Justinian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('lib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Machab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heliodor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pieta cum sufficiētia', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.6 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hiero', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Tomo 1', 'LAW'): 1; ('vlti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tom 3.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paulinum', 'FAC'): 1; ('Tom 3', 'PERSON'): 1"
A07625,62 | 7712,vice man avarice Aug. sermon covrtesie thanks benefit hold man,charity: 0.5; man: 0.5; friend: 0.5; bestow: 0.5; pag: 0.5; self: 0.5; seneca: 0.5; tom: 0.45; benefit: 0.3; another: 0.3; chastity: 0.25; vice: 0.05; lib: 0.05; gift: 0.05; rom: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 11; ('§', 'NORP'): 7; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('lin', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 4; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Prou', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 3; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hieron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tom 6', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Amb', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('54', 'DATE'): 2; ('Tom 1.', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca l. 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Micheae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('161', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tom 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('195', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de morib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('10 24', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Bon.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('discip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('§', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('excell•nt', 'NORP'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mor', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iuvenilia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('415', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('embrace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 1; ('advent', 'PERSON'): 1; ('domini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lapsam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. l. 10', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eustoch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('B. MARIAE', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nehem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ezech', 'ORG'): 1; ('18.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('s. leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de ieiunio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. de 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('virtutibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('haeresib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('careat aeterna', 'ORG'): 1; ('voluntati', 'NORP'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1590', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('i of a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('prima', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae vitam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hora', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nullius', 'ORG'): 1"
A03738,6,kind prophecy ascribe time oracle number kind oracle be answer,god: 0.5; oracle: 0.5; man: 0.5; time: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; christ: 0.5; place: 0.45; apollo: 0.45; devil: 0.35; prophet: 0.3; saint: 0.15; lib: 0.1; son: 0.05; world: 0.05; reg: 0.05; name: 0.05,"('Apollo', 'ORG'): 13; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 8; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 4; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 3; ('daily', 'DATE'): 3; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 3; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Delphos', 'GPE'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Boeotia', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Theod', 'ORG'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('qualefie', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cidnus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Plut.', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alpheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thuciddi', 'LOC'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Muse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anhelitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quosdam fuisse terrarum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('inflatá mente oracula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil tam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('quae sursum sunt sapere', 'ORG'): 1; ('non quae', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Antechrist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hetruria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Newbrigensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Wolpit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Suffolk', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('the ministry of his', 'ORG'): 1; ('quosdam amne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gross misconceit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cleombrotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plutarch', 'GPE'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('some other quarter', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vbi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pimander', 'ORG'): 1; ('nempe remota', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec Jupiter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('18. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bell', 'ORG'): 1; ('14. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leviathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('saltfish', 'NORP'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Micha', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leuite', 'NORP'): 1; ('17. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('ephesian', 'NORP'): 1; ('19 34', 'DATE'): 1; ('shaum', 'ORG'): 1; ('gulf', 'LOC'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('67. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the golden day', 'DATE'): 1; ('8. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Ose', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('acknowledge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('34. 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('36.', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 1; ('8. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bethel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sila', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the Munks of Palestine ▪ Herode', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stupens', 'GPE'): 1; ('saint luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apollo Chrisost', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Homi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('a joyful day', 'DATE'): 1; ('hart afford one', 'LAW'): 1; ('coffi•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peter ▪ A', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Paul ▪', 'ORG'): 1; ('19 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•a•mes', 'ORG'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Euseb', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Julian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daphne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Socrat', 'GPE'): 1; ('Babilam', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Babylas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Valens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('famuli christi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('reuerentiam Christianae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euse', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('saint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('every year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('vera loqueretur', 'ORG'): 1; ('the tender spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Esai .', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('7.', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the ministry of saint', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chamberlayne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epitherses', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thamos', 'ORG'): 1; ('Echinades', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Penelope', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tiberius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Esai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21. 44', 'DATE'): 1; ('21. 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('videbantur sapiente', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dionysius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A03738,14,another reason gild peel sugar bait prophecy prophet counterfeit prophet,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; time: 0.5; year: 0.5; prophet: 0.5; life: 0.5; astrologer: 0.4; truth: 0.4; knowledge: 0.25; day: 0.2; lie: 0.2; prophecy: 0.15; thing: 0.15; manner: 0.15; death: 0.1,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the year', 'DATE'): 3; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14.', 'DATE'): 2; ('Pompey', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two hundred year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Christe', 'ORG'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8 Leu', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Mel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('homo meet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ose', 'GPE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vento turbinem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('etiam cum iob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('poterit cogitare quid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezech', 'GPE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('maris sedi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gen. 3. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quod ingreditur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ignorans', 'NORP'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Helen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('senate', 'ORG'): 1; ('the spring 2', 'DATE'): 1; ('23. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bethel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dauidhad', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Galen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quaeque', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sententiam non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('peruersam quam mutare defensam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Socrat', 'GPE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Brittanicus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dion', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nierone', 'GPE'): 1; ('saint Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ambr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hexam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 1; ('Claudius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Albumazar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('1464', 'DATE'): 1; ('that very year', 'DATE'): 1; ('about the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('1375', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antechriste', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Saturn', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Scorpio', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('about eight year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alliacensis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constance', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mahomet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ordelaphius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('October', 'DATE'): 1; ('Julian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five day', 'DATE'): 1; ('ecce quam vera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the end of the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Crassus , Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('85.', 'DATE'): 1; ('year of age', 'DATE'): 1; ('1558', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bohem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('shun nonlatinalphabet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chremes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Terence', 'GPE'): 1; ('Robin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('cord pveri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Signa', 'ORG'): 1; ('44.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('1. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('erat', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cleombrotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diodorus Siculus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alphonsus de Castro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('our day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Julian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Velleda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tacit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mat 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plenitudine', 'NORP'): 1; ('1. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sequitur ventum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eccl', 'GPE'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aesop', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zaca .', 'DATE'): 1; ('twenty cubit', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('honicombe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ionathas', 'PERSON'): 1"
A03780,4,cry people voice Iames king country art father triumph peace,god: 0.5; king: 0.5; kingdom: 0.5; house: 0.5; lord: 0.5; iames: 0.35; peace: 0.35; christ: 0.35; religion: 0.3; christian: 0.3; england: 0.3; david: 0.2; nation: 0.1; father: 0.1; blood: 0.05; scotland: 0.05; man: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 2; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Iames of England', 'ORG'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('nurese', 'NORP'): 2; ('Kirk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('ergo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Lancaster', 'ORG'): 1; ('the house of York', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ezechiel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezech', 'ORG'): 1; ('37.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iohuda', 'ORG'): 1; ('their golden day', 'DATE'): 1; ('85.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Albion', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hart', 'LAW'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry prince', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('twenty-five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xxvii', 'GPE'): 1; ('Xxviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty-nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iames', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xi', 'ORG'): 1; ('twelve', 'DATE'): 1; ('Edinburgh', 'GPE'): 1; ('1589', 'DATE'): 1; ('cum privilegio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Reider', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('18.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('72.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Saintis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ya ▪ stoke', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.16 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Kirkes', 'ORG'): 1; ('forshaw', 'DATE'): 1; ('writtin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Kirk', 'ORG'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l•ng', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('thaiof', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Patrick gallow•y', 'PERSON'): 1; ('epigramma', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qvo videri', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dauidica', 'LOC'): 1; ('DAVIDICA', 'ORG'): 1; ('stirpe satum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rex sancte', 'ORG'): 1; ('scripto hanc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('potius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dauidis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('regi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dauidis exit', 'ORG'): 1; ('hinc tua laus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod meditetur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dauidem ut ornauit dominus', 'ORG'): 1; ('gloria prima tuus', 'ORG'): 1; ('mirificè multis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('regem hunc', 'ORG'): 1; ('dotibus auxit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('d exculta', 'ORG'): 1; ('David domini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hostibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('choro', 'GPE'): 1; ('hoc ( rex sancte', 'ORG'): 1; ('calamo', 'ORG'): 1; ('moribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('stirpe', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dauidis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dauide Scotos', 'FAC'): 1; ('Scotia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tantum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('foeliciter annis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('prosperiora tuis', 'ORG'): 1; ('M.I.M.', 'PERSON'): 1"
A04262,6,fir part hypocrisy person Michol Sauls daughter David wife woman,sin: 0.5; life: 0.5; god: 0.5; sinner: 0.5; penance: 0.5; soul: 0.45; religion: 0.45; ill: 0.45; believer: 0.4; david: 0.2; grace: 0.15; place: 0.15; liver: 0.15; repentance: 0.05; world: 0.05,"('David', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('Kirk', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Luc', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Catholicque', 'NORP'): 2; ('micholis hypocrisy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Michol', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sauls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kirk', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philistinis', 'NORP'): 1; ('castellis', 'NORP'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christianis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Serpentis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christianis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mars', 'LOC'): 1; ('idem latinè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ausae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vltro', 'NORP'): 1; ('ciese', 'NORP'): 1; ('mar seize accinxit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('agmina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Visa', 'ORG'): 1; ('mari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('montibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('aequor', 'NORP'): 1; ('reliquos misero deglutit abyssus hiatu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quì', 'PERSON'): 1; ('totq́ue stupenda peregit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vanos', 'GPE'): 1; ('Metellanum Cancellarium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('anno m.dc.xxxv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Urias', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bersabee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('IESVS Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezech', 'ORG'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. Luc', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hieron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('4 Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('epla ad Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iames', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Iacobi 5', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'EVENT'): 1; ('Chrysost', 'ORG'): 1; ('Corinth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('nullius rei', 'ORG'): 1; ('anima conferendun', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidem mundus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('innumera dederis pauperibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 1"
A06676,26,Zion Jerusalem lord will Zion wall Jerusalem build imponent altar,temple: 0.5; jerusalem: 0.5; god: 0.5; sacrifice: 0.5; build: 0.5; david: 0.5; christ: 0.5; church: 0.5; stone: 0.5; honour: 0.2; offer: 0.1; faith: 0.1; saint: 0.05; salomon: 0.05,"('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 38; ('David', 'PERSON'): 19; ('thou', 'GPE'): 10; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Par', 'ORG'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('daily', 'DATE'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('136', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Agg 2', 'PERSON'): 3; ('England', 'GPE'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('benign fac domine', 'ORG'): 1; ('muri', 'GPE'): 1; ('holocausta', 'ORG'): 1; ('altar tuum vitulos', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('131', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ophir', 'GPE'): 1; ('seven thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Salomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nehemias', 'GPE'): 1; ('Herode', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aggeus', 'ORG'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the Messiah Christ IESVS', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ievvrie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iewrie', 'GPE'): 1; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('milliōs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iulius Cesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Salomons', 'NORP'): 1; ('seventy thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eighty thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three thousand three hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4 million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Medes', 'ORG'): 1; ('persian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. Reg', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('3 one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Optatus Mileuitanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Donatistas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Optatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('sedem corporis domini', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aggeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hebr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ institute', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('the holy altar', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('s John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; (', morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('without night', 'TIME'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Baruc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ps', 'ORG'): 1; ('Osee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tunsionibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('pressuris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('permansuri Sacris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('IESVS', 'ORG'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1"
A05289,44,CHAP. issue hattle general issue battle party victory other overthrow,overcome: 0.5; victory: 0.4; god: 0.4; enemy: 0.4; battle: 0.4; conqueror: 0.4; roman: 0.4; general: 0.25; hand: 0.25; commander: 0.15; lib: 0.1; people: 0.1; party: 0.1; plague: 0.1; placentinus: 0.1; place: 0.1; philistines: 0.1; perazin: 0.1; plant: 0.1; ordinance: 0.1; pursuit: 0.1; name: 0.1; thankfulness: 0.05; lose: 0.05; token: 0.05; obtain: 0.05; defeat: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 2; ('Alex', 'PERSON'): 2; ('xxxvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('pret•ie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fort', 'GPE'): 1; ('ac passim sequente reparatis viribus interimit', 'ORG'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('osculana pugna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pyrrhus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Valerius Laevinus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Q. Fulvius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Carus', 'ORG'): 1; ('six thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Hannibal', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('boris sapit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('scis h•mb•l', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Barchab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hannibal', 'ORG'): 1; ('•hey', 'ORG'): 1; ('prae•ae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hantbal', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scotus Placentinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Horminius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saxo Gramaticus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('auro', 'ORG'): 1; ('anr•', 'ORG'): 1; ('german', 'NORP'): 1; ('Erlam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hungary', 'GPE'): 1; ('1596', 'DATE'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirty-nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('acknowledge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('c•emencie', 'NORP'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('josuab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deborah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Melchizedeck', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ahraham', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iehovah', 'ORG'): 1; ('I•hovab Nissi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baal Perazin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Baal Perazin', 'GPE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 Sam 4.6.7', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dagon', 'ORG'): 1; ('thracian', 'NORP'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mars', 'LOC'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iehovah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jack', 'PERSON'): 1"
A05289,47,CHAP. moderation conqueror passion temperance conqueror carriage moderation self thing,soldier: 0.5; victory: 0.5; man: 0.5; king: 0.5; captive: 0.5; blood: 0.45; thing: 0.4; life: 0.3; god: 0.15; conqueror: 0.15; carriage: 0.15; general: 0.15; conquer: 0.1; body: 0.1; service: 0.1; self: 0.1; arm: 0.1; glory: 0.1; enemy: 0.1; spoil: 0.05,"('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('France', 'GPE'): 3; ('Tacitus', 'ORG'): 3; ('Themistocles', 'ORG'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('Capua', 'ORG'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Alex', 'PERSON'): 2; ('luctris', 'GPE'): 2; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gloria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('claudian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Honorius', 'ORG'): 1; ('India', 'GPE'): 1; ('inordinate', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phillip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cheronea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Archidamus Agiselaus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two .', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustus Caesar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Severus', 'GPE'): 1; ('the Lombard and Saxons', 'ORG'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneas Silvius lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Frederick', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Gunzians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hungary', 'GPE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Stephanus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Norice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('58.11 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scipio', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Darius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Demades', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Agamemnon', 'FAC'): 1; ('Thersites', 'GPE'): 1; ('Demades', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Hannibal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hannibal', 'GPE'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Iulius Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sueton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('humando corpora captivorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scipio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tiberius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Babel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('lacedaemonian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Charles the 9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam bone', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vitellius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Otho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hannibal Scotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Parisian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Capitol', 'FAC'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('yesterday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Corinth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Athenians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Plutarch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lacon', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam mille', 'PERSON'): 1; ('antonius pius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Capitolinus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('1000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('70', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tigranes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Armenia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tamarlan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Floudon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iulius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thomas Howard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Surry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('lih', 'ORG'): 1; ('422', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pavia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lanoy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alphonsus Vastius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Borbon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bartholomeus Chasaneus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dane', 'GPE'): 1; ('Io', 'LOC'): 1; ('6.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amalekits', 'ORG'): 1; ('200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lincoln', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marcus Salinator', 'ORG'): 1; ('l. 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Denmark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Georgius Fronsbergius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maximilian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•nd Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caligula', 'GPE'): 1; ('Xerxes', 'PERSON'): 1"
A05289,54,CHAP. patience conquer conquer place behaviour continue patience powder adamant,patience: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; cross: 0.5; burden: 0.5; self: 0.5; thing: 0.5; evil: 0.35; christ: 0.35; suffering: 0.35; fire: 0.2; affliction: 0.15; sin: 0.05; lord: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('David', 'PERSON'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('21', 'DATE'): 2; ('Scipio', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Pompey', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 2; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('xlvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('prosperis nota', 'ORG'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('justi', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Divin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('optab•lia', 'GPE'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ignotinuil• Cupid', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luc', 'DATE'): 1; ('Melancthon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Marius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fabricius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mithridates', 'GPE'): 1; ('50 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Febris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Apologet', 'ORG'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('god saint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Job', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal. ••', 'ORG'): 1; ('one degree high', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Panacea', 'ORG'): 1; ('ureris', 'GPE'): 1; ('secaris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Super Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.10 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('•ong', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jove', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('no day', 'DATE'): 1; ('21.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cedamus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lev•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('amor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.27.28 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hyerogliffe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('flecti nervos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou fall', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pondus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('la••atione incomodius', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Alexander Aphrod .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.4', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1"
A05289,55,CHAP. hope conquer conquer patience hope sheet-anchor man storm patience,hope: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; enemy: 0.5; king: 0.5; thing: 0.5; heart: 0.35; action: 0.35; cause: 0.35; ground: 0.3; lord: 0.25; soul: 0.25; life: 0.15,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('David', 'PERSON'): 7; ('senate', 'ORG'): 6; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Hungary', 'GPE'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Hollander', 'ORG'): 3; ('one day', 'DATE'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Bohemia', 'GPE'): 2; ('Robert', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Haman', 'PERSON'): 2; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Iehovah', 'ORG'): 2; ('erat', 'PERSON'): 2; ('xlviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('116.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•1 .', 'DATE'): 1; ('2•.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam 27.1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('noon day', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('••esid• humana ••fecerint', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nū•il', 'ORG'): 1; ('s•e r•ed d•speret n•bil', 'ORG'): 1; ('48.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forlese', 'NORP'): 1; ('Joseph , Job , Mordecai', 'FAC'): 1; ('Antonius Grimanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one degree', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sporades', 'NORP'): 1; ('Melchior Trivisan', 'FAC'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lauderanus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Mathias Hunniades', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Viadislaus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bohemia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vladislaus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Katherine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bohemians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mathias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frederick', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('every hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Eccles 4.14 •', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Massinissa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Numidia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Syphax', 'ORG'): 1; ('6000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('70', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scipio Africanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Valerius Max', 'PERSON'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('100 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Publius Scipio', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lucius Paulus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cannas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lentulus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Varro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Marcus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Brutus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cato', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hamilton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spencer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zion', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mordecai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hamans', 'NORP'): 1; ('the king gate', 'FAC'): 1; ('Sagitta', 'GPE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'LOC'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('imo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('esech', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('16.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Roma', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Otto Frisingensis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1161', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hildegard', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abbas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ioachimus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrisostom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romae', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Goth', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vandal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Applicatiin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('monsieur de Lemmay', 'ORG'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orange', 'GPE'): 1; ('Babilonish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ralph Winwod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('holland', 'GPE'): 1; ('71', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zedechiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ezech', 'ORG'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Babel', 'LOC'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eze', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Senec', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Barus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('adjubat deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Democritus', 'ORG'): 1; ('abandon sloth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('seu', 'ORG'): 1; ('bella parabat .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iosiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Maximilian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Magorat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•• de fini•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('a week', 'DATE'): 1; ('a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Benhadad', 'GPE'): 1; ('Janus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Parma', 'NORP'): 1; ('Granvil', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1"
A05289,56,CHAP. end war point end war reserve end treatise word,end: 0.5; god: 0.5; abridgement: 0.5; lord: 0.5; war: 0.5; work: 0.5; man: 0.5; book: 0.4; church: 0.3; history: 0.2; thing: 0.2; self: 0.15; peace: 0.15; use: 0.05; labour: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jehu', 'PERSON'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('cum gratia', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Maius', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rhet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Horat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Publica', 'GPE'): 1; ('pecuniae suftuleris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('feret minueris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Ordin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Iehonadab', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('scottish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Babel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('egiptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Virginia', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ita sustipiatur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quaesita', 'DATE'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('Marg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('87', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. ult .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('159', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('186', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('l. 32', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1180', 'DATE'): 1; ('11800', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('208', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. 18', 'PERSON'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('John fox :', 'PERSON'): 1; ('all day', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Windet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('1589', 'DATE'): 1; ('John fox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iustine', 'FAC'): 1; ('Trogus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Livy', 'GPE'): 1"
A08427,50,sonnet quiet life estate wealth honour envy part accompany danger,christ: 0.5; apostle: 0.5; time: 0.5; prophet: 0.5; jesuit: 0.4; saint: 0.4; man: 0.4; life: 0.4; god: 0.4; friar: 0.2; paul: 0.15; satan: 0.15; truth: 0.15; heed: 0.1; come: 0.05; day: 0.05; saviour: 0.05; spirit: 0.05; kingdom: 0.05,"('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 3; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 3; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 2; ('John 8.44', 'PERSON'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 2; ('Flora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cynthia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('CYnthia quel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('che', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lasciando', 'GPE'): 1; ('inuita', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sarai', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alma', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ebella', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Paradis•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lewis Owen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('quae nascentia mala sunt', 'ORG'): 1; ('ea crescentia peiora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('J. H. for George Gib•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('1628', 'DATE'): 1; ('John Lloyd', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.24,25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 7.15', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.14,15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Galathian', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 1 Ioh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the latter day', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('take heed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.4,5,11,23,24,25,26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.1,2,3,4,5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.1,2,3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the late day', 'DATE'): 1; ('1 Thes', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.3,4,8,9,10,11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('the Jesuit , Capuchin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Benet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dominick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Denmark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Swethland', 'GPE'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A08690,28,author congregation fullian Frier rule compose rule truth fullian kind,jesus: 0.5; jesuit: 0.5; society: 0.5; name: 0.5; ignatius: 0.5; god: 0.5; fire: 0.45; saint: 0.45; father: 0.45; page: 0.2; pope: 0.15; son: 0.1; year: 0.05; saviour: 0.05; christ: 0.05; man: 0.05,"('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 14; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 8; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 6; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 4; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 2; ('Valderama', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 2; ('Frier', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cistercians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ignatius Loyola', 'ORG'): 1; ('Biscaya', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pampelona', 'GPE'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year 1504', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ignat', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Bellar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chronolog', 'LOC'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year 1622', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bavaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Maphaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Loyola', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Digitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('1.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Watson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sixtus', 'ORG'): 1; ('de Consuetudine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lindwood', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theol', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Melchior Canus', 'FAC'): 1; ('de Vaderama', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Monach', 'GPE'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these fourscore year', 'DATE'): 1; ('de vald', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Serm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ignatius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ʋalderama preach', 'PERSON'): 1; ('74', 'DATE'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aetna', 'ORG'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Valderama', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('mount Aetna', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eglog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('canibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('matribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Noram', 'PERSON'): 1"
A08690,30,observation sleight pretence necessity confession people imposture priest sin man,confession: 0.5; sin: 0.5; church: 0.5; priest: 0.5; purgatory: 0.5; man: 0.5; monk: 0.5; pope: 0.5; time: 0.4; friar: 0.3; god: 0.25; soul: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Limbus', 'ORG'): 5; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 3; ('Aeneas', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('many year ago', 'DATE'): 2; ('Nectarius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Garnet', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rumford', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Aeneid', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Patrick', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 2; ('poenitenti ad salutem animae sufficit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cassander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('multis', 'NORP'): 1; ('inutilibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petrus Oximensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salamanca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bonaventure', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Medina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('socrat', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zozom .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ni•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('parley', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bi•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Michael Bonon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 1; ('256', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caietan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Tom 3.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter Lombard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eudaemon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Johannes Apol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a whole hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('no penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year 1538', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tom 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Crabb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1551', 'DATE'): 1; ('Diximus', 'ORG'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('rationem', 'ORG'): 1; ('the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('Baptista Mantuanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('eglog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('templa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Coronae', 'ORG'): 1; ('coelum est venal', 'ORG'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Circe', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sibylla', 'ORG'): 1; ('Odyss', 'GPE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ovid Met', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter of Amiens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the eight , 1000 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cluny', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sicilia', 'GPE'): 1; ('the hill Aetna', 'ORG'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gibello', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('the first day of November', 'DATE'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('gulf', 'LOC'): 1; ('the month of November', 'DATE'): 1; ('the month of February', 'DATE'): 1; ('Numa Pompilius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. • .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Decad', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the second day of November', 'DATE'): 1; ('all the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Norway', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Timarchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trophonius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Homer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alcestis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Protesilaus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theseus', 'GPE'): 1; ('elysian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frier', 'ORG'): 1; ('many hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucretius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Martin Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Caluin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Limbus Infantium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orpheus , Homer', 'ORG'): 1"
A08319,9,argument faith miracle limit bound will God other faith faith,thing: 0.5; faith: 0.5; prayer: 0.5; god: 0.5; promise: 0.5; word: 0.5; lord: 0.4; paul: 0.4; saint: 0.3; way: 0.3; deny: 0.2; doubt: 0.15; ground: 0.1; name: 0.05; point: 0.05; pleasure: 0.05,"('Paul', 'PERSON'): 10; ('Trophimus', 'PERSON'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 2; ('5.15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('12.9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Vrsin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Catech', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 3.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Miletum', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('2 Corinth', 'DATE'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('15.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eliezer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Damascus', 'GPE'): 1; ('17.18', 'MONEY'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ishmael', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('84.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('magis novit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam agr•tus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('21.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('12 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('1 and', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('652', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bucan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('673', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gualther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tenent of the reform church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Preston', 'PERSON'): 1; ('99', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iam. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('234', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Math', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('nilergo', 'ORG'): 1; ('optabunt', 'ORG'): 1; ('n•••inibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Conveniat', 'GPE'): 1; ('nam', 'GPE'): 1; ('quaeque', 'NORP'): 1; ('estilli homo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Impulsiu ▪', 'ORG'): 1; ('peri•••', 'GPE'): 1; ('N••u••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui', 'PERSON'): 1"
A07557,15,man prerogative majesty set honour sovereignty honour call Latria Pag.,saint: 0.5; god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; image: 0.5; honour: 0.5; father: 0.45; man: 0.4; saviour: 0.4; sin: 0.35; thing: 0.3; face: 0.2; advocate: 0.2; merit: 0.1; church: 0.1,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Rheims', 'NORP'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Apol', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Kellison', 'ORG'): 3; ('Latria', 'GPE'): 2; ('Dulia', 'GPE'): 2; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 2; ('S. Francis', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Nicene', 'ORG'): 2; ('683', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('bishop jewel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 2; ('S. Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Deutronomy', 'GPE'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('350', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hiperdulia', 'GPE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•nd', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hiponianus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('682', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clare', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Adelmes', 'ORG'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dominicke', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('S. Bennet', 'ORG'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 2', 'LAW'): 1; ('brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pa.', 'GPE'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Permenius', 'ORG'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hieren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Therasius', 'NORP'): 1; ('710', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('789', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bish', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('jewel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacobus Nauclatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('353', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Robertus Holcot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nissa', 'GPE'): 1; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marcelia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephen the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pope Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of elibertine', 'ORG'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ambraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David Ezechiel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Clare', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius Emissenus', 'ORG'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('471', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the holy catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('354', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('42.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Emanuell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the golden altar', 'FAC'): 1; ('S. Amb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Isaac Euanua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30.38', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
