tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A91526,11,CAP. v. prayer another refuge misery man thing self-love man,prayer: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; sin: 0.5; heart: 0.5; heaven: 0.45; thing: 0.4; cap: 0.4; petition: 0.3; mercy: 0.25; lord: 0.2; soul: 0.15; people: 0.1; say: 0.1; nation: 0.1; self: 0.05,"('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('night', 'TIME'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Chemosh', 'NORP'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('CAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tobit', 'NORP'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('those solemn day', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judith', 'NORP'): 1; ('4. 9 , 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('all night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 1; ('7 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('from morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('45.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cyrus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('mahometan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('m. Greg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('165', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jeremiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('28.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('4.22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Niniveh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jonah 3.5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cyril of Alexandria', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isa', 'GPE'): 1; ('58.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('numina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Deos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Moab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa', 'DATE'): 1; ('16.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezekiel', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Noah , Job and', 'ORG'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clemens Alex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('all day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Josiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seventy year', 'DATE'): 1; ('26.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1"
A91526,22,CAP. Xvi caution reason sin other clear reason man incline,man: 0.5; thing: 0.5; god: 0.5; sin: 0.5; matter: 0.45; people: 0.35; self: 0.35; piece: 0.35; injustice: 0.3; duty: 0.3; world: 0.3; justice: 0.25; nation: 0.2; lord: 0.15,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Tereus', 'LOC'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('CAP', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('19.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Punctilio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nulli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam superstitiosi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Plut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Poetis', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Crete', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('turcograec', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('luke 3.14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('30.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('Kimchi', 'GPE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('17th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('uprightness', 'GPE'): 1"
A90963,3 | 4992,thing Leagu• covenant turn thing scripture reason civility justice honesty,king: 0.5; people: 0.5; covenant: 0.5; authority: 0.5; person: 0.5; blood: 0.5; law: 0.45; murderer: 0.45; man: 0.4; death: 0.4; religion: 0.1; parliament: 0.1; army: 0.05; scripture: 0.05,"('Scotland', 'GPE'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('love', 'PERSON'): 3; ('James', 'PERSON'): 3; ('John Knox', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('Subscribers', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Brutus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Netherlands', 'GPE'): 2; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 2; ('Leagu•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Samuels', 'ORG'): 1; ('Parl', 'ORG'): 1; ('prele•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('tha•', 'GPE'): 1; ('vein•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('John of Leyden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jenkin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cauton', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tyranni•ll', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prinne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35.', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Divinee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christopher', 'PERSON'): 1; ('anne Aldersgate', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ʋxbridge', 'ORG'): 1; ('R••hel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Achan', 'ORG'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Achan', 'GPE'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('scottish', 'NORP'): 1; ('78', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John ponnet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1556', 'DATE'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('carri••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Phinea•', 'GPE'): 1; ('ahud king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vindiciae', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('118', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Manlius Capitolinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Valerius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Manlius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Capitol', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucretius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tarquinius Superbus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tarquinius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Denmark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sweden', 'GPE'): 1; ('mary steward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Waldenses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('goodman', 'ORG'): 1; ('94', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Parreus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Knox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dudley Fennor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mecca', 'GPE'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zwinglius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rutterford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('callee lex rex :', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('190', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('191', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('192', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('193', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('the ministry of London', 'ORG'): 1; ('the house of commons', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 1643', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Philip', 'GPE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arguile', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hamil•on', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Scot', 'PERSON'): 1"
A95899,1,scripture glass characterize sort schismaticks looking-glass face face scripture seducer,man: 0.5; face: 0.5; god: 0.5; apostle: 0.5; christ: 0.5; word: 0.5; time: 0.4; scripture: 0.4; lord: 0.3; independent: 0.3; sectary: 0.2; looking: 0.15; evil: 0.1; minister: 0.05; church: 0.05; glass: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Moses', 'PRODUCT'): 4; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('13', 'DATE'): 4; ('18', 'DATE'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('14', 'DATE'): 3; ('8', 'DATE'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('daily', 'DATE'): 3; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Deodate', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('4', 'DATE'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('12', 'DATE'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 2; ('30. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa. 65', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('KOrah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abiram', 'ORG'): 1; ('250', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas Iscariot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeroboam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Liberty', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cephas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('T. Goodwin', 'ORG'): 1; ('J. Goodwin', 'ORG'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('deer brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul Best', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quarterman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. Tho', 'ORG'): 1; ('the marriage day', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cann', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Southwark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gen 3. 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magician', 'GPE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('magician be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'DATE'): 1; ('T. G. P. N. W. G. S. S. J. G.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about four or', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Kiffin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gorton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('treason', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caughton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('proselyte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Kain', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lusts', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cain', 'ORG'): 1; ('autumn', 'DATE'): 1; ('unsettle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Baal priest', 'GPE'): 1; ('Belial', 'ORG'): 1; ('jack presbyter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 15', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 38', 'DATE'): 1"
A95899,2,independent sectary schismatic scripture looking-glass sin ghost fear Jesus Romanis,tithe: 0.35; reason: 0.35; committee: 0.35; man: 0.35; conscience: 0.35; heb: 0.35; christ: 0.35; gentile: 0.3; people: 0.25; ministry: 0.2; prayer: 0.15; practise: 0.15; print: 0.15; priesthood: 0.15; priest: 0.15; present: 0.15; profit: 0.15; pettioner: 0.15; pleasure: 0.15; promise: 0.15; right: 0.1; maintenance: 0.1; ipswich: 0.05; honour: 0.05,"('Ipswich', 'GPE'): 4; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('Thomas Edgar', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Suffolk', 'GPE'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('7.12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 2; ('qui cum Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel Romanis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel schismaticis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('shun Romish', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sectarian Jesuit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Vicars', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fox', 'ORG'): 1; ('T. m. 1649', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Brandilin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the worshipful committee', 'ORG'): 1; ('William', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas PUCKLE', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Clowes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1650', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Brandlin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('W. W. T. P.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Brandlin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('10.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.8.9.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul be .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33.34.35', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A96257,3,reason gentile tithe apostle elder brethren Jerusalem act gentile circumcision,thing: 0.5; tithe: 0.5; god: 0.5; gentile: 0.5; apostle: 0.5; man: 0.5; law: 0.5; church: 0.45; christ: 0.35; word: 0.3; magistrate: 0.1; scripture: 0.1; conscience: 0.1; rom: 0.05; elder: 0.05,"('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 4; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 2; ('the ministry of England', 'ORG'): 2; ('the ministry of Christ', 'ORG'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3. third', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('brethren meet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ierusulem', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vinyard', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('it|be truth', 'ORG'): 1; ('•umb', 'ORG'): 1; ('14.5', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apostles Elders', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lithurgy', 'GPE'): 1"
A95529,1,London print T. H. Francis Coles sell shop old-bayly reader,day: 0.5; christ: 0.5; god: 0.5; master: 0.5; bear: 0.5; word: 0.5; son: 0.45; shepherd: 0.4; send: 0.35; give: 0.25; glory: 0.2; bless: 0.15; angel: 0.1; name: 0.05; christmas: 0.05,"('this day', 'DATE'): 15; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Christmas', 'DATE'): 4; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('10 11', 'DATE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cratch', 'GPE'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('T. H.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Francis Coles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1653', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gibeon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aialon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the yearly day', 'DATE'): 1; ('thy John Taylor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('December', 'DATE'): 1; ('Massa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christi missi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('56', 'DATE'): 1; ('ABRAMAM', 'ORG'): 1; ('the peculiar day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christmas Carroll', 'FAC'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('more than two thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('600 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('IMMANUELL', 'ORG'): 1; ('Emanuell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Natus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Datus', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('saint luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christmas day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('46.', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('85', 'DATE'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('these last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the first day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1"
A91524,15,self soul body self choice self world other man resolution,trouble: 0.45; self: 0.45; thing: 0.45; god: 0.45; man: 0.45; rule: 0.45; heart: 0.45; world: 0.4; nature: 0.35; fear: 0.3; hope: 0.2; time: 0.05; poverty: 0.05; pride: 0.05; part: 0.05; passion: 0.05; peace: 0.05; perplex: 0.05; piece: 0.05; pleasure: 0.05; poet: 0.05; pot: 0.05; thought: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 14; ('CAP', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('nil admirari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Horat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Numici', 'PERSON'): 1; ('x.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('praesentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nihil sperandi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('perpetuis annis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maximo labour incubui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cardan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fifteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Superbus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Kemp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epictetus', 'ORG'): 1"
A94862,1,episcopacie three-fold order bishop God another man another devil pluck,bishop: 0.45; man: 0.45; church: 0.45; elder: 0.45; authority: 0.45; apostle: 0.45; god: 0.45; timothy: 0.4; call: 0.35; another: 0.25; paul: 0.1; word: 0.1; pastor: 0.1; place: 0.1; prayer: 0.05; priest: 0.05; phil: 0.05; philippian: 0.05; plant: 0.05; pluck: 0.05; point: 0.05; possession: 0.05; power: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 3; ('Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three-fold', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('more than one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Proestota', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elders', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rebuke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Euangelist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Macedonia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Euangelist', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Miletians', 'NORP'): 1"
A91894,1,triumph unity truth treatise intend preservative error division time point,truth: 0.5; god: 0.5; sun: 0.5; unity: 0.5; cloud: 0.5; read: 0.5; lady: 0.3; man: 0.3; verse: 0.3; word: 0.25; saint: 0.2; light: 0.2; cap: 0.15; jerusalem: 0.1; ladyship: 0.1; john: 0.05; lib: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 3; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('John Robinson', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('122', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thomas Johnson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the golden key', 'FAC'): 1; ('S. Paul be Church-yard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1657', 'DATE'): 1; ('mens emblematis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bright truth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('magno conatv nihil agimvs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('reader', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theorem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aegyptii', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Valerius lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Parelii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui s. scripturas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvinus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; (""sh'expect"", 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hussey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Doddington', 'GPE'): 1; ('the golden candlestick', 'FAC'): 1; ('Nazianzenus', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('John verse 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gal', 'GPE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'MONEY'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rebekah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nec militarem qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec palmam', 'ORG'): 1; ('1 29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('phoebi redeuntis à', 'ORG'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Shiloh', 'NORP'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('read liv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('108', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('141', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 10', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zebedee', 'ORG'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herod Agrippa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alpheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('saint mark verse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Galathian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mariae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bucholc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('63', 'DATE'): 1; ('Spalata', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ecclesiastica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cousingerman', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cognatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hebraeorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gagu', 'ORG'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Euseb', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Doroth', 'ORG'): 1; ('synopsi', 'GPE'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1"
A91894,9,god truth peace magistrate people rank desire curse mischief source,god: 0.5; truth: 0.5; lord: 0.5; psal: 0.5; word: 0.45; praise: 0.45; name: 0.45; scripture: 0.45; encage: 0.4; man: 0.25; way: 0.15; church: 0.15; people: 0.15; self: 0.05; selah: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 48; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 28; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 19; ('thou', 'GPE'): 8; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 7; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Selah', 'PERSON'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Berachah', 'PERSON'): 3; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('92.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('20. 26', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('James 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3 proposition', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 meditation', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antiochus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Julian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oure', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('15.', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('western church', 'ORG'): 1; ('HonestGood', 'GPE'): 1; ('finis .', 'ORG'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('JER', 'ORG'): 1; ('10. 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Robert earl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Essex', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thomas Fairfax Captin', 'ORG'): 1; ('68 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('twenty thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; (""ex'lency"", 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('20. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bristol ,', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bolton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('68 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('when|it', 'GPE'): 1; ('12 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('higgai•n Selah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('148', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Neh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('76', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iun', 'GPE'): 1; ('grape', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sam 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('48.', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iehovah Shammah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Taunton', 'GPE'): 1; ('Selah Iohovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gloucester', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bristol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('nick of time', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal 93.', 'LAW'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('145', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('berachah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Berachah', 'GPE'): 1; ('75. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('147', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A93917,1,commentary whole MALACHY reverend divine mr. Richard stock rector All-hallows,saint: 0.5; word: 0.5; year: 0.5; time: 0.5; scripture: 0.5; paul: 0.5; thing: 0.45; man: 0.4; church: 0.35; john: 0.25; bible: 0.2; stamp: 0.15; christ: 0.15; god: 0.05,"('Paul', 'PERSON'): 8; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('latin', 'NORP'): 5; ('London', 'GPE'): 3; ('greek', 'NORP'): 3; ('Breadstreet', 'GPE'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Aloisius', 'GPE'): 2; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 2; ('Sixtus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel torshell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('T.H.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('R. H.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel Enderbey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1641', 'DATE'): 1; ('Stockès', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward Rudge', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Ven', 'PERSON'): 1; ('William Kendal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Richard Ellis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('shine light', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 5.35', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 Thes', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('45.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.3.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apostles', 'ORG'): 1; ('Typus Gregis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antitypon Pastoris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('these fifteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('TORSHELL', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysost', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('every year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul Warnenfrid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Charlemain', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aponius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Claudius Sesellius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Angelomus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('VValafridus Strabus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haimo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paschasius Rabertus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Corbey', 'ORG'): 1; ('Remigius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Auxerre', 'ORG'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ansbertus', 'ORG'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('890', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pentateuch', 'GPE'): 1; ('937', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1054', 'DATE'): 1; ('Serlo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dover', 'GPE'): 1; ('956', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1100', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luca', 'GPE'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('Stephanus Anglicus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rupert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heinalt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peter Comestor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dominick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('an . 1205', 'DATE'): 1; ('John Wolfius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Andreas Carolostadius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Albert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ausbourg', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ludovicus Vives', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ludov', 'ORG'): 1; ('Corrup', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Arias Montanus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Oxford', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Catanea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cajetan', 'GPE'): 1; ('eleven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('ten year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vulg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isidorus Clarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Benedictine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Santa croce', 'GPE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('more than 20 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lucas Burgensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('two or three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Viii', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('46.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bibles', 'GPE'): 1; ('Clements Breve Apostolicum', 'ORG'): 1; ('162', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antibarbarus Biblicus', 'ORG'): 1"
A93917,4,strife translation be sense act be use Romanists right interpretation,father: 0.5; use: 0.5; man: 0.5; text: 0.45; sense: 0.45; word: 0.45; god: 0.45; hand: 0.4; lord: 0.35; reason: 0.25; book: 0.2; time: 0.15; pope: 0.15; scripture: 0.15; picture: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1608', 'DATE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Busbeq', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('209', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('John de Puente', 'PERSON'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Duplessis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bononia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Naples', 'GPE'): 1; ('1609', 'DATE'): 1; ('wherein pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('crown', 'ORG'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('America', 'GPE'): 1; ('Esai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('49.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Schroles', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bitonto', 'GPE'): 1; ('the council at Trent , Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('15.45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eaas Colleq', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mornay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D. Fr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('White Orth', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cajetans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dominicus à Soto', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luth', 'GPE'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('marry person', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Morton Appl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Luke 5.4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Duc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('crow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eliah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antonius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Florence', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zach', 'GPE'): 1; ('11.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dominick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zachariah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tit. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('prolog', 'NORP'): 1; ('Obad', 'FAC'): 1; ('Obadiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salmeron', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ribera', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Malachy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Glassius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Septem', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('William knowl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('TORSHELL', 'PERSON'): 1"
A93917,20,end catalogue exercitation MALACHY whole book Malachy prophecy sermon prejudice,word: 0.5; name: 0.5; angel: 0.5; burden: 0.5; lord: 0.5; malachy: 0.5; prophecy: 0.5; israel: 0.5; hand: 0.3; prophet: 0.3; title: 0.2; ezra: 0.1; translation: 0.05; cap: 0.05,"('Israel', 'GPE'): 12; ('Ezra', 'PERSON'): 7; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hebr', 'ORG'): 2; ('french', 'NORP'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Benjamin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Montan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Loc', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. second', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mintan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Winkleman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nasa', 'ORG'): 1; ('verbum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Latines', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lemma be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lemmata', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epigr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('docebo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('malueris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mortua ponis Lemmata', 'PERSON'): 1; ('intercalaris', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Schindler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('2 kin', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('9.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nasa eth hammassa', 'GPE'): 1; ('Schindler', 'ORG'): 1; ('Drusius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nahum', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('proph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('humh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('liberty', 'PERSON'): 1; ('78.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ieroboam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judaea', 'ORG'): 1; ('amama', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antibarb', 'GPE'): 1; ('428.429', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32.28', 'MONEY'): 1; ('par le moyen de Malachi', 'ORG'): 1; ('the ministry of Malachy', 'ORG'): 1; ('Catachresis', 'NORP'): 1; ('3.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Targum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Maleaci', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Maleachi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Malachias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Engl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Malach', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isidore', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Etymon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ioel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('42.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mordecai', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Zachary', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Masoretico', 'ORG'): 1; ('Elias Levita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aala Ezrahu Malachi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('R. David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Malachy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chichester', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Norwich', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apparatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saraiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezr', 'ORG'): 1; ('7.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Ki', 'PERSON'): 1; ('130', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Remigius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rupertus', 'ORG'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dav', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athanasius , Chrysost', 'ORG'): 1; ('theo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. Lyran', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vatabl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Genebrard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('180.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob Bonfrerius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iudic', 'GPE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gabriel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Raphael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ʋriel', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pareus', 'ORG'): 1; ('David Pareus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('John Pecham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('nomina quae', 'ORG'): 1; ('lasciviam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lyndw', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de Bapt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('circ', 'PERSON'): 1"
A93917,29 | 8835,son Christ call nonlatinalphabet Schemesch God sun minister light heat,day: 0.5; sun: 0.5; moses: 0.5; christ: 0.5; saint: 0.5; law: 0.45; god: 0.4; call: 0.4; calf: 0.35; wing: 0.3; lib: 0.25; place: 0.15; man: 0.15; book: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 17; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 7; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Vulg', 'PERSON'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 3; ('this day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Lxx', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Exercit', 'ORG'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Luc', 'PERSON'): 2; ('chapter 5', 'LAW'): 2; ('Baptist', 'NORP'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Arab', 'NORP'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 2; ('Vatabl', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('lib .', 'PERSON'): 2; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Chald', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hebr', 'ORG'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Horeb', 'GPE'): 2; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Moses', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Syrians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Horeb', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Eliah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 2; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Schemesch', 'NORP'): 1; ('impart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Syriack', 'ORG'): 1; ('20.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('deneschtammasch', 'GPE'): 1; ('24.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('103.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zach', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iunius ( Paral', 'ORG'): 1; ('par', 'ORG'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('George Pasor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('british', 'NORP'): 1; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christus lux est electorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bonfrerius', 'ORG'): 1; ('his noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('John the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the Ordinarium Divin', 'FAC'): 1; ('Sarum', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zachary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('139.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneid', 'GPE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('nox rvit', 'GPE'): 1; ('fuscis tellurem complectitur alis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canaph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Natur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ionston', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Maiola', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dier', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tom 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theolog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('217', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('474', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('proem', 'GPE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Asterius', 'LOC'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tertul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lxx', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tigurine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anomaly', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tigur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('50.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marbek be Saginarium', 'ORG'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Transl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertul', 'ORG'): 1; ('Montan', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cutlu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Drus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diodorus Siculus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Monios', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Loco', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Amalek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sinai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sinai', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Catharius', 'NORP'): 1; ('10.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('weemse Expos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mont.', 'GPE'): 1; ('H. Mason', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alphonsus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Arragon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Herebert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thomas a Kempis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('his hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nisi', 'ORG'): 1; ('angelo cum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iraeneus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('D. Pareus', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Newerus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heidleburg', 'GPE'): 1; ('more than forty year of age', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zicru', 'GPE'): 1; ('Recordamini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bibles', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Buxtorf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Masor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vatican', 'FAC'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tom 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrys', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eliah the Thisbit', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Benedict Pererius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Disput', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Enoch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gabriel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Suffolk', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ann', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1635', 'DATE'): 1; ('2 Thess', 'GPE'): 1; ('Quirinus Reuterus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Reuterus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day of the', 'DATE'): 1; ('28.17', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Casp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theol', 'GPE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('831', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A93702,1,Printer spectator emblem shadow book tell figure pope fraternity prelate,god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; pope: 0.5; viz: 0.5; lord: 0.5; self: 0.5; church: 0.5; man: 0.45; jacob: 0.45; prediction: 0.3; rev: 0.25; christians: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 6; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'DATE'): 2; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Prelacy', 'PERSON'): 2; ('18. 27', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('21', 'DATE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('presbiterians', 'NORP'): 1; ('18. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniels', 'ORG'): 1; ('susannas chastity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anti•rinitarians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('they|will', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('18. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bayes', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prellat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('three degree', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Cerberus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaiah 40. 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('John spittlehouse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fairfax', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jennings', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Redcrosse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1650', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('o••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('30. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('•2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 4. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('b•aines', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Merlinus Calc•donius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bridget', 'ORG'): 1; ('Joaohim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Joannes de', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scissa', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joannes Wolsius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('genitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('aequus Pastor', 'ORG'): 1; ('•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('122.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two grand moth', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('the supreme power', 'ORG'): 1; ('Martha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'MONEY'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1"
A93702,9,fiend treatise gradation self midheaven whole world path truth discover,church: 0.5; book: 0.5; christ: 0.5; government: 0.5; contrary: 0.45; power: 0.35; synod: 0.35; world: 0.3; error: 0.25; ordinance: 0.2; self: 0.2; truth: 0.2; people: 0.15; notice: 0.15; point: 0.15; name: 0.05; spirit: 0.05; lord: 0.05; viz: 0.05; mr: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('lily', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Prelacy', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('Mari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canaan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johns', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Annakim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Goliath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the last first', 'DATE'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Novemb', 'GPE'): 1; ('2 1649', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Janes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Laytie', 'ORG'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('up many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lilly', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Scot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baal priest', 'GPE'): 1"
A93702,13 | 8997,Christ say ascension father right hand respect divine nature nature,god: 0.5; nature: 0.5; christ: 0.5; word: 0.5; father: 0.5; man: 0.5; divine: 0.5; son: 0.5; spirit: 0.45; thing: 0.4; substance: 0.1; enemy: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('luthreans', 'NORP'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('32', 'DATE'): 2; ('20. 30', 'DATE'): 2; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1. 3. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('38', 'DATE'): 2; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the virgin mary', 'GPE'): 1; ('Corinthus and Ebion', 'ORG'): 1; ('1. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arius', 'ORG'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('outward appearance', 'FAC'): 1; ('manache', 'ORG'): 1; ('24. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 47', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apollonaris of La•dicea', 'ORG'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Mat 26', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Swen•feildius', 'ORG'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('11. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rabbie', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rubbie Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jamblicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aemelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heraclitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Suidas', 'GPE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cananite', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mat 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('11. 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A93702,13 | 9051,sect object testament lord say man heart evil work god,god: 0.5; image: 0.5; christ: 0.5; law: 0.5; testament: 0.5; man: 0.5; gospel: 0.5; ans: 0.5; obj: 0.3; object: 0.15; make: 0.15; substance: 0.1; idol: 0.1; sect: 0.05; eye: 0.05; nature: 0.05; see: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Diana', 'PERSON'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('harden', 'GPE'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('93.', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('8. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('publican', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mat 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('19 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l•t', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sodeme', 'GPE'): 1; ('••i•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('babylonians', 'NORP'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('81. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theodotius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Za•', 'GPE'): 1; ('10. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Epist', 'PERCENT'): 1; ('johnh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('heterogen•ae', 'ORG'): 1; ('deus vinci', 'PERSON'): 1"
A93702,15 | 10162,apostle man thing God other This other reason mention magistrate,apostle: 0.5; christ: 0.5; tithe: 0.45; ans: 0.45; obj: 0.4; degree: 0.4; contrary: 0.35; viz: 0.35; part: 0.3; thing: 0.3; minister: 0.25; maintenance: 0.25; presbytery: 0.15; covenant: 0.15; god: 0.1; law: 0.05; time: 0.05,"('three', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 6; ('three degree', 'QUANTITY'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Prelacy', 'PERSON'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('21', 'DATE'): 2; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Deanes', 'ORG'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('presbyterian', 'NORP'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Classis', 'ORG'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•ish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mari Mortuum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('27.', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hosea 2', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hydra', 'GPE'): 1; ('bishop', 'ORG'): 1; ('so many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('so many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a•e antichristian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Melchisadeck', 'GPE'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cain', 'ORG'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('practi•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('•x•n', 'NORP'): 1; ('11. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('n•nth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('co•i•th ▪', 'ORG'): 1; ('Obj', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a• d••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('t•e', 'LOC'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('mil•e', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ti•hes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Piggs', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichristians', 'NORP'): 1; ('ne•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1"
A92303,2,love service expression apprehension time constancy station settle resolution cause,tithe: 0.45; god: 0.45; law: 0.45; nature: 0.45; part: 0.45; nation: 0.45; pay: 0.45; man: 0.4; rob: 0.2; blessing: 0.15; parish: 0.15; number: 0.15; church: 0.1; perform: 0.05; pen: 0.05; place: 0.05; piety: 0.05; philosopher: 0.05; person: 0.05; plin: 0.05; people: 0.05; paulus: 0.05; payment: 0.05; service: 0.05; abraham: 0.05; curse: 0.05; day: 0.05,"('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('3.8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'DATE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 2; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Melchisedeck', 'ORG'): 2; ('600.', 'DATE'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('Bacchus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Diodorus Siculus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('R. R.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bevill Turmiger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('R. Lowndes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul be Church-yard', 'ORG'): 1; ('1653', 'DATE'): 1; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Decimae', 'ORG'): 1; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelicall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Henry Spelman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Decima', 'GPE'): 1; ('x.', 'NORP'): 1; ('xi xum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Decimus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Decimum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('x.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam petit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ergo citus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caesaris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cesar Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('502', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('209', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('100 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('400.', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cordibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi ipse deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dyonisius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('magno jovi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sicilian', 'NORP'): 1; ('arabian', 'NORP'): 1; ('aethiopian', 'GPE'): 1; ('decimas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julius Cesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cyrus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Furius Camillus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Herodotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Livi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A94173,8 | 10913,word saviour Mat eye whole body light eye evil whole,god: 0.5; evil: 0.5; man: 0.5; law: 0.5; thing: 0.5; intention: 0.5; sin: 0.5; glory: 0.45; act: 0.4; place: 0.4; word: 0.1; end: 0.1; take: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 3; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Uzzah', 'ORG'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('x.', 'ORG'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('st Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Attic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Xii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Saul', 'GPE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petronius', 'NORP'): 1; ('non dicatur fieri posse', 'ORG'): 1; ('malis', 'NORP'): 1; ('operibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('cum concesseris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('admittatur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sva cuique', 'ORG'): 1; ('deceit', 'GPE'): 1; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('10 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvin , Bucer , Zuinglius', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Jerome Zanchius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mundi theologiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zanchius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('domini incipit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('benè', 'ORG'): 1; ('viam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristot', 'GPE'): 1; ('Id. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('mens inter minora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maxima', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('the nineteenth', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Vid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Arist', 'ORG'): 1; ('de Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1"
A94173,8 | 10924,Xviii Caius sin Titius commit larceny other murder saint Augustine,evil: 0.45; another: 0.45; man: 0.45; sin: 0.45; thing: 0.45; saint: 0.45; god: 0.45; power: 0.45; place: 0.4; way: 0.3; glory: 0.1; commit: 0.05; principal: 0.05; priest: 0.05; proverb: 0.05; propound: 0.05; pronounce: 0.05; profit: 0.05; procure: 0.05; punishment: 0.05; potuit: 0.05; word: 0.05; answer: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('contraria', 'GPE'): 2; ('Sparta', 'GPE'): 2; ('Xviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Titius', 'ORG'): 1; ('quaeratur', 'GPE'): 1; ('potius', 'GPE'): 1; ('potius', 'NORP'): 1; ('quam alienum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nollem', 'GPE'): 1; ('quod erat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('distet inter tuum', 'ORG'): 1; ('erit tuum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('malis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Scylla', 'GPE'): 1; ('Charybdis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Esculapius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('contrariis curari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stobaeus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ajax', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chaiphas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('senate', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('subservie•t', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1"
A94173,9,lecture declare example man judgement experience man protection conscience gall,example: 0.5; man: 0.5; thing: 0.5; saint: 0.5; god: 0.5; peter: 0.45; paul: 0.4; law: 0.4; act: 0.4; conscience: 0.25; jew: 0.2; opinion: 0.1; self: 0.1; gentile: 0.1; judge: 0.05; apostle: 0.05,"('Peter', 'PERSON'): 11; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 11; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('Barnabas', 'PERSON'): 5; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('James', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Galatians', 'NORP'): 1; ('the christian •iberty', 'EVENT'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('inter Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierou', 'PERSON'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jove', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Capitol', 'FAC'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apostle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Barnabas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Judaism', 'PERSON'): 1; ('frailty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('10 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('ut fugerem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('exemplis viti•rum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nota•do', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hoc quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nunquid ego illi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Imprudens', 'ORG'): 1; ('Horat', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('careful•y', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('x.', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phineas', 'NORP'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 54', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('haec quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etiam facienda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sanctis et justis', 'ORG'): 1; ('viris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fabius', 'NORP'): 1; ('nullam repertam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('causam quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tota alteri similis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A94173,9 | 10959,Xxiv saint James apostle chapter fervency prayer example Elias importunity,man: 0.45; example: 0.45; judgement: 0.45; self: 0.45; conscience: 0.4; god: 0.4; word: 0.35; church: 0.35; authority: 0.3; place: 0.2; apostle: 0.2; thing: 0.15; mind: 0.15; another: 0.15; pleasure: 0.05; pravity: 0.05; praeceptor: 0.05; practice: 0.05; power: 0.05; pope: 0.05; prejudice: 0.05; person: 0.05; people: 0.05; affection: 0.05; reason: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('James', 'PERSON'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Jove', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xxvi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Muli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mutuo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Xxvii', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Magister', 'ORG'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('James Chap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('st Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xxviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('these many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Xxix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'DATE'): 1; ('bellua ruptis', 'ORG'): 1; ('prava catenis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Horat', 'ORG'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apollos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cephas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arminius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Socinius', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Xxx', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xxxi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1"
A90025,3,vigour conjunction self counsel action February April present nation England,church: 0.5; blood: 0.5; man: 0.5; time: 0.5; saint: 0.5; soul: 0.5; god: 0.4; body: 0.4; pope: 0.35; protestant: 0.25; world: 0.25; error: 0.25; power: 0.05; wine: 0.05,"('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 3; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 3; ('John', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 2; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Laity', 'ORG'): 2; ('about February , march ,', 'DATE'): 1; ('April', 'DATE'): 1; ('T. O.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('• ▪ •', 'ORG'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('T.O. D.D.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Roman catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('west', 'LOC'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mauritius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phocus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('saint John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vio••nce', 'PERSON'): 1; ('s•••', 'GPE'): 1; ('m••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mosses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Shouldir', 'ORG'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1"
A92720,2,overture endeavour promise expect help defer malignant disappointment alienation affection,god: 0.45; self: 0.45; difficulty: 0.45; cause: 0.45; man: 0.45; army: 0.45; friend: 0.45; heart: 0.4; winter: 0.35; money: 0.3; power: 0.1; make: 0.1; part: 0.1; covenant: 0.05; oxford: 0.05; order: 0.05; people: 0.05; peace: 0.05; passage: 0.05; pass: 0.05; parliament: 0.05; paral: 0.05; papist: 0.05,"('winter', 'DATE'): 6; ('England', 'GPE'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('Newcastle', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the general assembly', 'ORG'): 1; ('26.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.24', 'DATE'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Eccl', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philistin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iehovah Iireh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Edinburgh', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the king army march', 'ORG'): 1; ('Oxford', 'GPE'): 1; ('Brainford', 'GPE'): 1; ('November', 'DATE'): 1; ('Northumberland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Decem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cicester in Glocestershire', 'ORG'): 1; ('Feb. 2', 'DATE'): 1; ('1642', 'DATE'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('winter night', 'TIME'): 1; ('bee daily', 'ORG'): 1; ('the king army', 'ORG'): 1; ('churlish', 'NORP'): 1; ('1 Sam 25.5', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Davids', 'GPE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Joab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abishai', 'GPE'): 1; ('10.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('arise', 'PERSON'): 1"
A95952,4 | 11516,N. truth estate kingdom church whole work lord parliament leaguer,god: 0.5; king: 0.5; lord: 0.5; parliament: 0.5; john: 0.5; man: 0.5; heart: 0.5; leaguer: 0.35; honour: 0.3; thing: 0.25; london: 0.25; labour: 0.2; people: 0.05; life: 0.05; epistle: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 21; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 5; ('London', 'GPE'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('daily', 'DATE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Essex', 'GPE'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('John Trappe', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 2; ('Cato', 'ORG'): 2; ('3000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('400', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Robert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Banbury', 'ORG'): 1; ('Warwick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('afeast day', 'DATE'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Weston', 'GPE'): 1; ('Avon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. London', 'PERSON'): 1; ('G.M.', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Bellamy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cornhill', 'GPE'): 1; ('1646', 'DATE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Euseb', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Lang', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pauls', 'GPE'): 1; ('1179', 'DATE'): 1; ('god grace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John cheek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cranmer', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ridley', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salvian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tekoah , Neh', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('3.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('eternalize', 'GPE'): 1; ('21.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thomas Fairfax Silius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Silius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fabius Maximus', 'ORG'): 1; ('muri', 'GPE'): 1; ('Plutarch', 'GPE'): 1; ('bos armenta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Atticum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cassius', 'GPE'): 1; ('119.63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('101.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Themistocles do Miltiades', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexander do Achilles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tully', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysost', 'ORG'): 1; ('quosdam svi temporis nonlatinalphabet vocat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mat Heb', 'GPE'): 1; ('11.38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('63.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Novemb', 'ORG'): 1; ('12. 1645', 'DATE'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mag', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cantabrig', 'GPE'): 1; ('reader', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('St Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A94796,9,CHAP. verse baptise moor disciple use Jew John Christ Broughton,verse: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; son: 0.5; word: 0.5; jew: 0.5; samaritan: 0.5; thing: 0.35; truth: 0.3; sword: 0.1; faith: 0.1; prayer: 0.05; prophet: 0.05; father: 0.05,"('Jew', 'NORP'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 6; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Antiochus', 'NORP'): 3; ('Nazareth', 'PERSON'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 2; ('Antiq', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Broughton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judaea', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Masim', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christ•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Luth', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gen.', 'GPE'): 1; ('48.22', 'MONEY'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('miseriam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sauls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jonathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samaritesse', 'GPE'): 1; ('frailty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('non ignara mali', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England Elizab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('186', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Festus call Canalicolas', 'ORG'): 1; ('quòd circa canalem fori consisterent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Berman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Giraldus Cambrensis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('irish', 'NORP'): 1; ('quanquam honorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('honorari', 'ORG'): 1; ('Josephus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samaritan', 'LOC'): 1; ('Epiphan', 'GPE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.2 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('goliath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob ] Josephus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ovid Metamor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('overfloweth molehill', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lucretius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sphinx Philos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('iesuitae etiam sunt Connubisanctifugae', 'ORG'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Speiser', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ausborough', 'GPE'): 1; ('118', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1523', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('m••n', 'ORG'): 1; ('14.4.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('proh stuporem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Herod', 'NORP'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Delphi', 'ORG'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Godw', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('iehovae', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alsted', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Isid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Osirid', 'GPE'): 1; ('Amon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heus tu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('si scirem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deus essem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Messiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zacheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tantum', 'ORG'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Indies', 'ORG'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Naamans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.33', 'MONEY'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vail', 'GPE'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 21.17.33', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three month', 'DATE'): 1; ('many month', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Damascus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Petrus de Valle', 'ORG'): 1; ('1626', 'DATE'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Camerarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('magnus', 'GPE'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Florence', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('767', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('fox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chaucer', 'ORG'): 1; ('750', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('lo ••acitatem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('intùs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two day', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quod acceperla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel haerese', 'PERSON'): 1; ('evada', 'ORG'): 1; ('aridas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rolloc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Galileans', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zurich', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zanchius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Argentina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Clavenna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('beseech', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Darius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ezra 6.10', 'LAW'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('669', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('the selfsame day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('53', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A94270,3,discovery God wonder manifest time rain water blood be see,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; time: 0.5; year: 0.5; blood: 0.5; day: 0.5; see: 0.4; city: 0.35; heaven: 0.3; make: 0.25; place: 0.15; word: 0.15; people: 0.1; evil: 0.05; christ: 0.05; lord: 0.05; power: 0.05; use: 0.05; sin: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 4; ('Plin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the year', 'DATE'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('three day', 'DATE'): 3; ('England', 'GPE'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 3; ('Uladislaus', 'ORG'): 3; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Funccius', 'GPE'): 2; ('dec .', 'DATE'): 2; ('Naucler', 'ORG'): 2; ('Polydor Virgil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Polydor', 'GPE'): 2; ('Crantzius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('lo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Gideon', 'ORG'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Argobastus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Julian', 'NORP'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('teratologia', 'GPE'): 1; ('28.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lycosthenes', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year of the world 3729', 'DATE'): 1; ('Marca Ancona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Garcaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Meteorolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('477', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Picenum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Toscana', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tuscia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the same year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ariminum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rimine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year also 3783', 'DATE'): 1; ('Concordia', 'GPE'): 1; ('two day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Livy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('624', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vulcani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Decad', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('610', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('H. Nat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marcus Acitius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caius Portius', 'ORG'): 1; ('about the year of the world 3852', 'DATE'): 1; ('C. Coecilius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('C. Papyrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the next year', 'DATE'): 1; ('noctu luceret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pliny', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Basilicata', 'GPE'): 1; ('Marcus Crassus', 'ORG'): 1; ('about the year of the world 3910', 'DATE'): 1; ('about 856', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lewis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Brixia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lombary', 'ORG'): 1; ('naucler', 'ORG'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('713', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year 879', 'DATE'): 1; ('about the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('935', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Genua', 'ORG'): 1; ('Saracen', 'NORP'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('728', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1104', 'DATE'): 1; ('Spira', 'GPE'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('801', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about the year of Christ 1180', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('236', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mirkalow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Odera', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nissa', 'GPE'): 1; ('Silesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('about the year 1269', 'DATE'): 1; ('l. 9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('162', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year 1274', 'DATE'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Virgil l. 17', 'PERSON'): 1; ('H. anglic statim ab initio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rufus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Normandy', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abington', 'GPE'): 1; ('idem l. 10', 'PERSON'): 1; ('176', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constantes', 'NORP'): 1; ('Normandy', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year of Christ 1464', 'DATE'): 1; ('Kalenburg', 'GPE'): 1; ('Crantz', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about the same year 1464', 'DATE'): 1; ('vail', 'GPE'): 1; ('noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('Saxionae', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Saxony', 'GPE'): 1; ('Barnwood', 'ORG'): 1; ('the month of February , 1648', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cavenda praemonuerunt superna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amos 6.3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('22.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about fifty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hegesippus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 4.24', 'PERSON'): 1; ('50.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('more than over ninety nine', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 1; ('Horat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 6.33', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Proba', 'GPE'): 1; ('istas quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('poena', 'ORG'): 1; ('Senec', 'PERSON'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('81.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('el Schaddai', 'ORG'): 1; ('17.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.14', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Jericho', 'GPE'): 1; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('300', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Goliath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julian', 'GPE'): 1; ('308', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrys', 'ORG'): 1; ('NaZianZen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Valentinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alps', 'LOC'): 1; ('Ruffin', 'GPE'): 1; ('l. 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eugenius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('claudian', 'NORP'): 1; ('militat aether', 'PERSON'): 1; ('classica venti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hungary', 'GPE'): 1; ('Amurath the Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alcoran', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('462', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('some few day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Varna', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mysia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Amurath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Turks', 'NORP'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year 1573', 'DATE'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('regno galliae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eighty eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cavenda superna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 12.36', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magnū', 'ORG'): 1; ('103', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hondorf', 'ORG'): 1; ('114', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about 170 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Louvain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Friday', 'DATE'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year 1553', 'DATE'): 1; ('Helvetia', 'GPE'): 1; ('ZwitZerland', 'ORG'): 1; ('115', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Lucerna', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ulrichus Schrolerus', 'ORG'): 1; ('modò fortuna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ulrichus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Andreas Hendorffius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('coelestibus doctrinae praeco', 'ORG'): 1; ('Historicum', 'ORG'): 1; ('dutch', 'NORP'): 1; ('Philippus Lonicerus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hendorffius', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('68.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zecharies', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Shadrach', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abednego', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chrysost', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antioch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lindum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rhodes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('86', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hosea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sirach', 'GPE'): 1; ('23.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jansenius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam religiosa affirmation confirmare', 'ORG'): 1; ('mihi haec translatio verbi nonlatinalphabet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('orationem fraudulentam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Locum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1"
A96144,2,while mr. Gardell moderator part bear witness thing God man,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; self: 0.5; mr: 0.5; learning: 0.5; thing: 0.5; sin: 0.5; world: 0.45; spirit: 0.25; respect: 0.25; politicus: 0.2; england: 0.15; ministry: 0.1; hollowness: 0.05; erbery: 0.05,"('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('Politicus', 'ORG'): 3; ('Nineveh', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 2; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Gardell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Politicus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ishmael', 'NORP'): 1; ('Politicus', 'EVENT'): 1; ('antichristian ministry', 'ORG'): 1; ('•nivers', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('•nd', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('October 25.', 'DATE'): 1; ('1653', 'DATE'): 1; ('Freland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zion', 'GPE'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jove', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('1641', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matthew 21.43', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('blasphemer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tamar', 'GPE'): 1; ('38.26', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1"
A96039,4 | 12603,mean ear charm devil temptation meditation end serpent other ear,death: 0.45; devil: 0.45; man: 0.45; meditation: 0.45; evil: 0.45; hand: 0.45; simplicity: 0.4; work: 0.25; day: 0.2; sin: 0.2; dove: 0.2; temptation: 0.2; thought: 0.15; god: 0.1; end: 0.05; soul: 0.05; pleasure: 0.05; piece: 0.05; pot: 0.05; port: 0.05; plume: 0.05; plot: 0.05; pliny: 0.05; precept: 0.05; place: 0.05; period: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7.40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Beelzebub', 'ORG'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('each morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('China', 'GPE'): 1; ('a hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeroboam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharaohs', 'LOC'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.40', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A94533,1,THEAVRAU John EPITAH evrops looking-glass dear belove brethren divine light,gospel: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; law: 0.5; root: 0.5; word: 0.5; priest: 0.5; life: 0.4; people: 0.4; truth: 0.25; state: 0.25; light: 0.15; self: 0.05,"('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 12; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 7; ('England', 'GPE'): 7; ('english', 'NORP'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('latin', 'NORP'): 3; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 3; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('••e', 'ORG'): 2; ('Jes••', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Stats', 'ORG'): 2; ('Theaurau John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('EPITAH', 'ORG'): 1; ('Son••', 'ORG'): 1; ('ORI', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mikrakessoamoas', 'GPE'): 1; ('un•• God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theaurau', 'ORG'): 1; ('••ey', 'NORP'): 1; ('HOIRE', 'FAC'): 1; ('Theavrau John', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('ackklah-sabie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou Shutter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('horat o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'NORP'): 1; ('•ell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•im', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alliah Saby Ory Hesseon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jehouah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Massah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eorum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wh••', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ierus•lem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rens magih', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Senter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('••y k•ow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('yo• day', 'DATE'): 1; ('s••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('assum•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Stats', 'PERSON'): 1; ('KIO', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('CAPH', 'ORG'): 1; ('•and', 'ORG'): 1; ('•n that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Scorn•', 'ORG'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Sabi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ory Alpha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Threapha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arrat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('selex si vea sabini', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Selah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ruben', 'PERSON'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel my brother', 'PERSON'): 1; ('brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hallelujah', 'GPE'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5 of April', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('madad el', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thi•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ori el arki scab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nephushim aga zim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saphel', 'GPE'): 1; ('hushi', 'ORG'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('na•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pheaurau John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eltham', 'ORG'): 1; ('April the 28. 1652', 'DATE'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A72059,7,conversion signior Melchior Roman Spaniard proctor order jacobine Rome province,god: 0.5; saint: 0.5; christ: 0.5; life: 0.5; jesus: 0.5; man: 0.4; lord: 0.4; grace: 0.35; country: 0.25; world: 0.25; truth: 0.25; time: 0.2; end: 0.15; father: 0.1; place: 0.1; son: 0.05,"('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 12; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Laban', 'ORG'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('John', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 4; ('Melchior Roman', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('daily', 'DATE'): 3; ('Thoulouse', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ierome', 'ORG'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 2; ('Jesus Christe', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Arragon', 'GPE'): 2; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('August 1600', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Galaad', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pagnine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philo', 'NORP'): 1; ('Anatheme', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('1.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('less than half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the first Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Octaue', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dominick', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Barselon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sixtus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Florence', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pope Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ebora', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry the 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Babylon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a few day past', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezechiell', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter 3', 'LAW'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jonas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Barnard', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mat Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('Janus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Berosus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('2. corinth', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Barnard', 'ORG'): 1; ('thy day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('the pope bull', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caphas', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Macharus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('50000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('crown', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Portugal', 'GPE'): 1; ('Shee', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrisostome', 'ORG'): 1; ('Esau', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aran', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Esai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Helias , Elizeus', 'ORG'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('saint John the Euangelist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Patmos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Candacis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ethiopia', 'GPE'): 1; ('saint luke act', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euangelist', 'ORG'): 1; ('the mount Sinai', 'GPE'): 1; ('the mount Sinai', 'LOC'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jeremie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fidalgo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ferrer', 'GPE'): 1; ('Frague', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isabella Roman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. Vincent Ferrer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('S.', 'ORG'): 1; ('Balbastre', 'ORG'): 1; ('Xamora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saragoussa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dodon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peter Capdeuile', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sidera perlegerem semper', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi', 'ORG'): 1; ('amor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Johannes', 'GPE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mi s•r', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de tu', 'PERSON'): 1"
A79937,3 | 15130,other Xvii year see Tiberius Caligula end Claudius Peter be,place: 0.5; paul: 0.5; word: 0.5; peter: 0.5; gr: 0.5; nero: 0.45; cap: 0.4; church: 0.4; law: 0.4; year: 0.35; christ: 0.3; epistle: 0.15; thing: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 22; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 21; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 13; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Nero', 'ORG'): 5; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 5; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Nero', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Claudius', 'NORP'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 3; ('Xvii', 'GPE'): 2; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('§', 'NORP'): 2; ('Galatians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tacitus', 'ORG'): 2; ('fuisse', 'ORG'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 2; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 2; ('Rob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Bibles', 'GPE'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tiberius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Caligula', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joan Xviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('amender of time', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christi', 'NORP'): 1; ('Neronis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four .', 'DATE'): 1; ('some two or', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pareus', 'ORG'): 1; ('16.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('saint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('101', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romae', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('tanta animus coelestibus ira ?', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('some few year', 'DATE'): 1; ('28.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two whole year', 'DATE'): 1; ('ephesian', 'NORP'): 1; ('colossian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timothy , Philemon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antioch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Henr', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.6.7.8.10.12.11 .', 'DATE'): 1; ('Crescens', 'ORG'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tychicus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Hypobolimaeo', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marcian', 'NORP'): 1; ('21.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scaliger', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Asiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pontus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Galatia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cappadocia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Bithynia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tacit', 'ORG'): 1; ('pereuntibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('102', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('illius temporis ita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('episcopum', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('persuaderi nequeo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trajan', 'NORP'): 1; ('l. Tacitus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Suetonius of the persecution of', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ner', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Id.', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Clariss', 'ORG'): 1; ('Occisus est Petrus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Xxii', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Evangelium Marci', 'FAC'): 1; ('Marco', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ita Arabib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Selden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('romana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Linus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Patriarcha Romanus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('24.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ep', 'NORP'): 1; ('quis nesciat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gelasio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Beatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thomas Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. Dominicus Soto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theodoret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ep.', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. spiritu prophetico', 'PERSON'): 1; ('profectionem praedictam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('idcirco', 'NORP'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('116', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hispanias', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('insulis quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mari', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gaul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sophronius Serm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pauli', 'GPE'): 1; ('Venantius de', 'ORG'): 1; ('Martini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fortunatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Britannus', 'GPE'): 1; ('3b', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('angliae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Richard Vitus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Brit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Relat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anglicis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Antiq', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nicephorus Callistus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Niceph', 'ORG'): 1; ('yesterday', 'DATE'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dorotheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('synopsi .', 'GPE'): 1; ('Salm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Ep.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Crit', 'ORG'): 1; ('sacri lib 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('115', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jacobus de voragine', 'ORG'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sym', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xxix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Junii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Symeon Metaphrastes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod perîsse videmus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('apud Dn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clement', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sophronius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Symeon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fran', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Convers', 'ORG'): 1; ('Britan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('D. Ʋsser', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Primordiis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jerom Catal.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paulo', 'GPE'): 1; ('CC', 'ORG'): 1; ('year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul : Evangelium Christi', 'ORG'): 1; ('partibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('young', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('IIX', 'ORG'): 1; ('Xiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrinus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Ark.', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('19.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('luke , Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xii', 'LOC'): 1; ('throne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('pillar', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('a hundred and', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Sulpicius Severus', 'ORG'): 1; ('300.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('dicto audience', 'PERSON'): 1; ('reflexit oculos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('N. Vii .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus christus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jactantiâ superbiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jerom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xxvii', 'GPE'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('quoniam vult eum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('liberet nunc eum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('70', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Regi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('70', 'DATE'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Pentateuch', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Josippus', 'ORG'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eclog', 'GPE'): 1; ('243', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alios', 'ORG'): 1; ('Graecos', 'GPE'): 1; ('illis collegiis', 'ORG'): 1; ('234', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ri', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Biblioth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quaest', 'LOC'): 1; ('120', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('82.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ch', 'LOC'): 1; ('Xii .', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('35.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('28.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heinsius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Meditat', 'ORG'): 1; ('luke Xxiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Galeato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet possidet :', 'ORG'): 1"
