tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A17304,2,Achans wisdom knot iniquity opinion leave divine lot God word,popery: 0.45; god: 0.4; israel: 0.4; achans: 0.4; king: 0.4; church: 0.4; joshua: 0.4; book: 0.4; elder: 0.25; wisdom: 0.15; hand: 0.15; authority: 0.1; paw: 0.1; partaker: 0.1; poet: 0.1; plague: 0.1; philistines: 0.1; people: 0.1; potentate: 0.1; pack: 0.1; owl: 0.1; lord: 0.05; arminian: 0.05; truth: 0.05; zeal: 0.05,"('Israel', 'GPE'): 20; ('Achans', 'NORP'): 14; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 9; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Babylonish', 'NORP'): 2; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Dagon', 'ORG'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Deuteronomy', 'GPE'): 1; ('•f Achans', 'NORP'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eliah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Babylon', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('November', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the holy catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('god', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('principibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('viris non vltima', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('herein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('crown', 'ORG'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Prudens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hippo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Posidon', 'NORP'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hostibus circundatam liberare dignetur', 'ORG'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Israel Elders', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry Burton', 'PERSON'): 1"
A17304,4 | 47,ioshua fast humiliation soul spirit dust self man help hope,israel: 0.5; god: 0.5; sin: 0.5; lord: 0.5; fast: 0.5; heart: 0.5; joshua: 0.5; prayer: 0.5; achans: 0.3; hypocrisy: 0.25; elder: 0.2; accurse: 0.1; ioshua: 0.1; cause: 0.05,"('Israel', 'GPE'): 88; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 20; ('Achans', 'NORP'): 12; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Babylonish', 'NORP'): 6; ('the day', 'DATE'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('58', 'DATE'): 3; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Niniveh', 'PERSON'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Naboth', 'ORG'): 2; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('gloriam quaerit', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Achan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Achan', 'ORG'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('58', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('those vacant hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('last', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jezebel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ahab kingdom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hypocrisy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('66.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('Esau', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('•biece', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gilead', 'ORG'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('ioshua heart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iam. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('1. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezech', 'ORG'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezechiels', 'GPE'): 1; ('2. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Esa 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('may spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israelites', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('babylonian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Achans Babylonish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Zimri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canaanite', 'NORP'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('4ly', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 14', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A19798,8 | 1293,Anthony body find chamber bed be meet other place Theophil,satan: 0.5; anthony: 0.5; thing: 0.5; body: 0.5; man: 0.5; sorcerer: 0.5; chapter: 0.45; word: 0.4; god: 0.3; power: 0.25; theophil: 0.2; verse: 0.15; theophilus: 0.1; mean: 0.05; self: 0.05; miracle: 0.05,"('Anthony', 'PERSON'): 25; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 23; ('Theophil', 'PERSON'): 11; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 5; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christe', 'ORG'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Satan', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Theophilus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Daemonum', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Michol David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bruno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a minute of a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Satan', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Alexander Neopolitanus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thomas Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Romulus', 'GPE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aristeus Proconesiensis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cleomedes Astipaleensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Crotona', 'GPE'): 1; ('Calabria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cleomedes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sextus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Susan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xxxv', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judaea', 'ORG'): 1; ('hart i', 'LAW'): 1; ('Irenaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xliij', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pliny', 'ORG'): 1; ('xxviij', 'GPE'): 1; ('58', 'DATE'): 1; ('magician', 'GPE'): 1; ('Satan', 'LOC'): 1; ('magician', 'NORP'): 1; ('thessalonians', 'NORP'): 1; ('saint John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sixteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1"
A19552,12,CAP. Vii reason Vigilius chapter Theodorus Mopsvestia condemn peace communion,church: 0.5; communion: 0.5; peace: 0.5; theodorus: 0.5; vigilius: 0.5; condemn: 0.5; error: 0.5; faith: 0.45; heretic: 0.35; council: 0.25; doctrine: 0.25; heresy: 0.1; whole: 0.1,"('Theodorus', 'GPE'): 32; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 16; ('Vigilius', 'NORP'): 12; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 11; ('Nepos', 'ORG'): 9; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Vigilius', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Dionysius', 'ORG'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 4; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Irene', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Mopsvestia', 'GPE'): 3; ('553', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ierome', 'ORG'): 3; ('179', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('184', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Nestorius', 'ORG'): 2; ('§', 'NORP'): 2; ('Justinian', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Papias , Irenee , Iustine', 'ORG'): 2; ('cyprian', 'NORP'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Aug. lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Austen', 'PERSON'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Apollinarius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('heresy', 'GPE'): 2; ('Nepos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cerinthus', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('CAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sup', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vigloc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('176', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Binius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Conc', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iustinianus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Conc', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('552', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a. .', 'ORG'): 1; ('calumnia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gregory Nissen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('Shee', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('233', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many thousand million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('african', 'NORP'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Multiple•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('loco as•et aliquem decessisse', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('synod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fuisse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. Austen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austen Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint cyprian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sine dubio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Theologorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Loc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theol', 'GPE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Febr', 'GPE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ieremiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('haec licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ista', 'NORP'): 1; ('one thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jerome Hieronimi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil adhuc', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de Civit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('118', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('373', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Damasus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nulli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quicquam contrarium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nullo bell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de Pont', 'ORG'): 1; ('652', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Papias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cyprianus ita dixit', 'FAC'): 1; ('qui•ci', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('etiam cum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui de', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austen Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('•aith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mil•t', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Schisma', 'GPE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Papias Natalis beati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Feb. 2•', 'DATE'): 1; ('Martyris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Menal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aug. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vig', 'GPE'): 1; ('loc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('178', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nepos', 'GPE'): 1; ('Epicurcae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chil•astae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullianum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Feb. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Valentinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christopherson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vita migravit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christopher', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Musculus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('qui jam ad quietem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bar', 'ORG'): 1; ('491', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catholica', 'LOC'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Conc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ita ait de symbolo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theodori', 'ORG'): 1; ('537', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a. proclaim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eutiches', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eunomius', 'ORG'): 1; ('— nullus amor populis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec foedera', 'NORP'): 1; ('littora littoribus contraria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fluctibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('arma armis', 'ORG'): 1; ('nati natorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui nascentur ab ipsis', 'ORG'): 1"
A18933,9 | 10506,meaning m. Bunny protestant esteem England protestant reason doctrine wip,church: 0.5; protestant: 0.5; time: 0.5; michaeas: 0.5; age: 0.5; visibility: 0.5; god: 0.4; point: 0.35; self: 0.35; reason: 0.3; apostle: 0.3; say: 0.15; invisibility: 0.1; want: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Bunny', 'PERSON'): 5; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('D.', 'NORP'): 5; ('OCHINVS', 'ORG'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Michaeas', 'GPE'): 4; ('Joan', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 3; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 2; ('will|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('D. Reynolds', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Caluin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('108', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vbi', 'ORG'): 1; ('92', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('adigat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Erebi', 'ORG'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cont', 'GPE'): 1; ('•4', 'ORG'): 1; ('torm•nt', 'GPE'): 1; ('controuer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('319', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('muscovit', 'ORG'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Stopleton', 'GPE'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('D. Parkins', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oecolampadius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1605', 'DATE'): 1; ('916', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theolog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('308', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('394', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tom .', 'DATE'): 1; ('lenae Germ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('491', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luthers', 'NORP'): 1; ('Vibanus', 'GPE'): 1; ('176', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Regius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luthers', 'FAC'): 1; ('400', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day of', 'DATE'): 1; ('many hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Caelius Secundus de amplitud', 'PERSON'): 1; ('212', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('vix ab alijs', 'ORG'): 1; ('ac ne vix quidem', 'ORG'): 1; ('agnosci potuerint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bonifac•', 'ORG'): 1; ('607', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Napper', 'ORG'): 1; ('twelve hundred and', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Brocard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Reuelat', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sebastianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('these thousand and', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('D. Downham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de antichristo l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D. Reynolds', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('magis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam pro ◊ •egantes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the apostle day', 'DATE'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('age and century', 'DATE'): 1; ('testament•s', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Neuserus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ochinus', 'DATE'): 1; ('many century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ochinus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('stear•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romish Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quod de deo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hebr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•eui•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('tenebris lucet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mors illi vltrà', 'PERSON'): 1"
A16795,6 | 11092,ask John follower religion profess England Aeneas Silvius opinion repute,church: 0.5; lib: 0.5; pope: 0.5; time: 0.5; john: 0.5; man: 0.5; book: 0.45; god: 0.45; wiclef: 0.4; doctrine: 0.35; council: 0.15; opinion: 0.1; king: 0.05; day: 0.05,"('Lib', 'PERSON'): 14; ('John', 'PERSON'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 6; ('Wiclef', 'ORG'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Constance', 'GPE'): 4; ('Oxford', 'GPE'): 4; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 4; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 3; ('english', 'NORP'): 3; ('Cochleus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 3; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Wiclefs', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Aeneas Silvius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('Oratio', 'ORG'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Martin Luther', 'PERSON'): 2; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Hussites', 'LOC'): 2; ('Wiclef', 'GPE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Histor', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bohem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('130', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cochl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apocalypse', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Zisca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hussites', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thabor', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zisca', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hussite', 'GPE'): 1; ('Puritan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Artic', 'ORG'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Articul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sacramēt•', 'ORG'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bohemia', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year 1415', 'DATE'): 1; ('Martin An. 1517', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year 1508', 'DATE'): 1; ('Augustinū', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('de•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Waldensium', 'ORG'): 1; ('false prophet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('raven wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sleidan', 'GPE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Minerius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Merin•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. ◊ .', 'ORG'): 1; ('the sixteenth century', 'DATE'): 1; ('about the year one thousand five hundred', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baptista', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Franciscus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('earl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('K•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Johannes', 'GPE'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Andreas Proles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Picus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of Laterane', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mantu•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arcana revelo non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Europam', 'ORG'): 1; ('exirpat honestos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('agre scurris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ara cyaedis servit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('honorandae divûm ganymedibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thuris', 'LOC'): 1; ('mollis Arabs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('venalia nobis temple', 'FAC'): 1; ('altaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('coelum est venal', 'ORG'): 1; ('English', 'NORP'): 1; ('woder', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Savanarola', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Wiclef', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laurentius Valla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Patritius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laterane', 'GPE'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('about the year 1420', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nicolaus de ◊', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rebuke de Annatis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cambray', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of Constance', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leonardus Aretinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Coloniensem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antonius Cornelius Lynnichanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prague', 'GPE'): 1; ('John VViclef', 'PERSON'): 1; ('platina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('Histo Bohemia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bohemia Wiclefs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Hussitis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bohemia wiclef ▪ book de realibus vniversalibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bohemia', 'ORG'): 1; ('ibidem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hussites', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dulcinists', 'NORP'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('VViclef', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cochl', 'NORP'): 1; ('li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constance', 'ORG'): 1; ('five and forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Respo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Wideford', 'GPE'): 1; ('eighteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Articul', 'GPE'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Aeneid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Foxe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John of Gaunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hie•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Henry Percy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lancaster', 'ORG'): 1; ('G. Courtney', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Oxon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Richarde', 'PERSON'): 1; ('preach day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gu•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leicester Abbay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Leicestershire', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leicestrensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lu•', 'GPE'): 1; ('R. Edward 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Colleg', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('John Vviclif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Io', 'LOC'): 1; ('Wiclif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Robert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nicolas Herford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip ◊', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Ash•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Annot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('R. Richard•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('78', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marsilius of pa•', 'ORG'): 1; ('John of Gand•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('literis Reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas Arondell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('operibus', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Hus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John VViclif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day of An. 1476', 'DATE'): 1; ('king Edvvard', 'ORG'): 1; ('VViclif', 'ORG'): 1; ('Reginald Pecocke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('VViclif•', 'GPE'): 1"
A16795,6 | 11101,Howe kingdom position spread collect Geffrey Chaucer year right suppose,pope: 0.5; man: 0.5; doctrine: 0.5; lib: 0.5; church: 0.5; time: 0.5; god: 0.4; christ: 0.4; opinion: 0.35; bishop: 0.15; thing: 0.15; year: 0.1; papist: 0.1; rome: 0.1; albingenses: 0.1; john: 0.05; book: 0.05; saint: 0.05,"('lib', 'PERSON'): 10; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('France', 'GPE'): 5; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 4; ('•', 'ORG'): 4; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Catal', 'ORG'): 4; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('England', 'GPE'): 3; ('John', 'PERSON'): 3; ('VValdenses', 'PRODUCT'): 3; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Serm', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('VValter', 'ORG'): 2; ('Hereford', 'GPE'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('•', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('vv•', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gregor', 'GPE'): 2; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Dulcinists', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 2; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Waldenses', 'PERSON'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Arragon', 'GPE'): 2; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Geffrey Chaucer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year 1400', 'DATE'): 1; ('John uuictef', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chaucer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('lorell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ta•', 'TIME'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romanistes', 'ORG'): 1; ('the year 1393', 'DATE'): 1; ('Registro Episcopi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hereford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three year ◊ a half', 'DATE'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dux Cleri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('666', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('William Wideford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Brutus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Waltherus Britta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wiolif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('VViclif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Wiclif•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bul•', 'ORG'): 1; ('fox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('William Sa•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Ba•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thorpe', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('p•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('24•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('long•', 'ORG'): 1; ('beside•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1; ('John VViclef', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year , 1371', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marsilius of Padua', 'ORG'): 1; ('verle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marsilius Patavinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the year 1324', 'DATE'): 1; ('Levvis of Bav•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the supreme authority of the', 'ORG'): 1; ('Magistra•', 'ORG'): 1; ('bee ◊ Ui•', 'ORG'): 1; ('destruct•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marsilius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Petrus Messiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ludovico', 'GPE'): 1; ('C•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bav•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pap•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hay•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('A•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('hussit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dul•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Poesi Italica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Franciscus Petrarche', 'ORG'): 1; ('ad lib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Romano', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ballarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('Petrarch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylon , Apocal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Genebr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chronogr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clement', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a few year', 'DATE'): 1; ('te•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ssa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Johannes', 'GPE'): 1; ('papae ab Ecclesia', 'ORG'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cochleus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Wal•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leonists', 'ORG'): 1; ('VValdenses', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aeneas Silvius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bohem', 'GPE'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Genebrarde', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1170', 'DATE'): 1; ('1218', 'DATE'): 1; ('Silvius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ber•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hussites', 'LOC'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('VViclef', 'ORG'): 1; ('UUaldenses', 'ORG'): 1; ('Du Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('livre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip the', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lombardy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sicily', 'GPE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philippus Augustus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1180', 'DATE'): 1; ('more than four hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Du', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tholouse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cominges', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bigerre', 'ORG'): 1; ('Car•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Raimund', 'ORG'): 1; ('Saracens', 'NORP'): 1; ('Foix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cominges', 'NORP'): 1; ('Raimund', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('kinsman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Du Haillan', 'ORG'): 1; ('about one hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luthers', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Reinerius', 'ORG'): 1; ('three hundred year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sylvester', 'GPE'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('I|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Petrus VVald•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Par•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Genebrard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chronogr', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('4. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('1088', 'DATE'): 1; ('Berengarius', 'LOC'): 1; ('Bertram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bertramo', 'ORG'): 1; ('expurgatorius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Resp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('258', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eureux', 'PERSON'): 1; ('la saint', 'FAC'): 1; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernardi•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eugen', 'ORG'): 1; ('2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eugenius', 'GPE'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canti•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('190', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('freewill', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rhemens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('scan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor 3. 11', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('via', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ•', 'ORG'): 1; ('sa•', 'PERSON'): 1"
A16795,9 | 11188,T. hill number miracle wrought catholic conversion country Indies father,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; vow: 0.5; pope: 0.5; time: 0.5; day: 0.4; religion: 0.4; body: 0.35; another: 0.25; heaven: 0.25; country: 0.25; rome: 0.15; soul: 0.1; england: 0.1; christ: 0.1; college: 0.05; name: 0.05; part: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('England', 'GPE'): 6; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 4; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 4; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('english', 'NORP'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 2; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 2; ('G. abbot', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 2; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thirteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 2; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 2; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 2; ('Indies', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Portugal', 'GPE'): 1; ('Italians', 'NORP'): 1; ('german', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hungarians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Fleming', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('irish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Frier', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Muscovite', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phara•', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luk 82', 'LAW'): 1; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Campians', 'NORP'): 1; ('d•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salomon Eccl', 'ORG'): 1; ('Resp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('99', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iustine', 'FAC'): 1; ('cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epiphan', 'ORG'): 1; ('611', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ierome', 'ORG'): 1; ('thirty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Austen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. de bono', 'PERSON'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Calvine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luther , Calvin and Martyr', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Cranmer', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bucer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fagius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frierly', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oxford', 'GPE'): 1; ('Histor', 'GPE'): 1; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Foxe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward day', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Q. Mary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pascitur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romani', 'NORP'): 1; ('facilis responsio danda', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hūgary', 'DATE'): 1; ('•', 'LOC'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fisco', 'ORG'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bonony', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bo•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vineola', 'ORG'): 1; ('Flora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cicer•', 'ORG'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Stukley', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cōcenat', 'GPE'): 1; ('Angl•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cāpian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rheims', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lauretum', 'GPE'): 1; ('sclavonians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gregor', 'GPE'): 1; ('p•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Italye', 'GPE'): 1; ('Uienna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Danubius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vilva', 'ORG'): 1; ('Claudiopolis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Transylvania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iaponia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Colledg•', 'ORG'): 1; ('monthly', 'DATE'): 1; ('Apolog.', 'FAC'): 1; ('three hundred crown', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('one hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('no more than fifteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixteen hundred pound english', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Io', 'LOC'): 1; ('298', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seculars', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Curti•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Curia', 'GPE'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('C•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Julio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Q.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Par', 'ORG'): 1; ('Henric', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three hundred year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('indian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Clemens', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Dovv•', 'TIME'): 1; ('Validolid', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Weston', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cr•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('UUorthington', 'ORG'): 1; ('VVeston', 'PERSON'): 1"
A16795,10,reason largeness dominion multitude believer T. hill church m• vv•,church: 0.5; year: 0.5; part: 0.5; man: 0.5; time: 0.5; world: 0.5; age: 0.5; nation: 0.4; christ: 0.35; religion: 0.25; thing: 0.2; god: 0.15; king: 0.1; land: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 6; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 6; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 5; ('the day', 'DATE'): 4; ('•', 'NORP'): 3; ('G. abbot', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 3; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Portugal', 'GPE'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('pl•', 'NORP'): 2; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('•', 'ORG'): 2; ('80', 'DATE'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 2; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 2; ('the year', 'DATE'): 2; ('America', 'GPE'): 2; ('•', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iohan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8. 44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('19 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome 1. 20', 'ORG'): 1; ('ca•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bellar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dei lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('west', 'LOC'): 1; ('Iordon', 'GPE'): 1; ('72', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sheba', 'GPE'): 1; ('Messiah', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Agrippa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Domitian', 'NORP'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•', 'GPE'): 1; ('these thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('•', 'LOC'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nsfaith', 'ORG'): 1; ('many hundred of year', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Media', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arabia', 'GPE'): 1; ('these 300.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aegypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Morocco', 'GPE'): 1; ('Granado', 'GPE'): 1; ('hundred of year', 'DATE'): 1; ('indian', 'NORP'): 1; ('african church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hannibal Phormio', 'ORG'): 1; ('cosmographer', 'ORG'): 1; ('be•••s', 'GPE'): 1; ('these sixscore year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christopherus Columbus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Decad', 'ORG'): 1; ('Benzo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nov•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1492', 'DATE'): 1; ('Europa', 'LOC'): 1; ('Emanucl', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calecut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the sea coast', 'LOC'): 1; ('Columbus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Barbarye', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aegypte', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sultanes', 'ORG'): 1; ('seven or eight hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('these last thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Malmisb', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gulielm', 'GPE'): 1; ('a. lib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Godfrey of Bullion', 'ORG'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Henry', 'GPE'): 1; ('seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Saracen', 'NORP'): 1; ('Eugan', 'GPE'): 1; ('council of Florence', 'ORG'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Muscovite', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Possevin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Muscovit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scythia Europaea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tartar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Europ•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peru', 'GPE'): 1; ('Brasile', 'GPE'): 1; ('Magellanus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Terra Patago•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hispania', 'GPE'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('the south sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('Hacklan', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nova Albion', 'ORG'): 1; ('frauncis-drake', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the north sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('Florida', 'GPE'): 1; ('Virginia Norimbega', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mediterrane', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Groneland', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nova', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Scandinaviasas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Finland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dam •', 'PERSON'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tartary', 'GPE'): 1; ('so many million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Russia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aeg', 'GPE'): 1; ('de • … uss .', 'ORG'): 1; ('four thousand mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Caspian', 'NORP'): 1; ('China', 'GPE'): 1; ('the east Indies', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aethiopia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Turkey', 'GPE'): 1; ('venetian', 'NORP'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian Pilgrime•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Colos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ireneus l. 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iudens c .', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cypr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athana', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epist', 'GPE'): 1; ('78', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leo m•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petro', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paulo', 'ORG'): 1; ('the catholic roman church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theodoretus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petri', 'NORP'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('honoris facta caput mundo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('west Indies', 'GPE'): 1; ('18. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('their young year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('almost 2000 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Exod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('12 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seminary', 'PERSON'): 1"
A16795,10 | 11244,Shee apostle time world question gospel way coast world sense,world: 0.5; time: 0.5; nation: 0.45; church: 0.45; gospel: 0.45; pope: 0.4; faith: 0.35; place: 0.3; room: 0.2; day: 0.2; religion: 0.15; word: 0.15; saint: 0.15; christ: 0.15; whole: 0.15; leo: 0.1; name: 0.1; part: 0.1; man: 0.1; apostle: 0.05,"('France', 'GPE'): 7; ('England', 'GPE'): 7; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 6; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 5; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 5; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 5; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 5; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Austen', 'PERSON'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Sicily', 'GPE'): 4; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Leo', 'ORG'): 3; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 3; ('Aethiopia', 'GPE'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('west', 'LOC'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('India', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 2; ('78', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Prosper', 'GPE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 2; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 2; ('those day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 2; ('Portugal', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Hungary', 'GPE'): 2; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('Alps', 'LOC'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Euse', 'LOC'): 1; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Polycarpus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John the Evangelist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pope Eleutherius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mauritania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('prelato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel de vnirat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nat', 'ORG'): 1; ('verbi', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('muchlesse', 'GPE'): 1; ('80', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Talia', 'GPE'): 1; ('coelestib•', 'NORP'): 1; ('hisdem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petri', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pastorales', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gratian', 'NORP'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('99 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leonis Mapni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prosp', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aquitan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('76', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prosper', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leo Serm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nativit', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pauli', 'GPE'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antioch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Loco', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('scan', 'NORP'): 1; ('overturneth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hesychius', 'ORG'): 1; ('80', 'DATE'): 1; ('african', 'NORP'): 1; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('and many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hart', 'LAW'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bede', 'NORP'): 1; ('G. abbot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('some hundred of year', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about six hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Saracen', 'NORP'): 1; ('Turks', 'NORP'): 1; ('Europa', 'LOC'): 1; ('the age of sixteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aggeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hart .', 'LAW'): 1; ('Tartary', 'GPE'): 1; ('Manicongo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Finland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iseland', 'GPE'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bede', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adole', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernard .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('L•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('217', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petrus Leonis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Robert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Palestina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('the barbarian kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Poleland', 'GPE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Indies', 'ORG'): 1; ('America', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iaponia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Brasilia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Africa G.', 'GPE'): 1; ('9 as many', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('hart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lutheranisme', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Generali', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one hundred of year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the next age God almighty', 'DATE'): 1; ('more than seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('Polonia', 'GPE'): 1; ('•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Canaanite', 'NORP'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('prick', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sleidan', 'GPE'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('manifold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ferdinandus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bellamine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saxony', 'GPE'): 1; ('Germanye', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Denmark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Norway', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sueden', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gotheland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pannonia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Fraūce England', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('venetian', 'NORP'): 1; ('pilgrim', 'ORG'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('some one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aethio', 'PERSON'): 1"
A16795,12,reason vision gift prophecy T. hill miracle wrought church vision,god: 0.5; vision: 0.5; prophecy: 0.5; man: 0.5; saint: 0.5; thing: 0.5; christ: 0.45; gift: 0.4; time: 0.35; church: 0.2; word: 0.15; revelation: 0.1; book: 0.1; lord: 0.05; act: 0.05; th: 0.05; lib: 0.05; cap: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 6; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('John', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 5; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 5; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Montanus', 'NORP'): 3; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 3; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 3; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Agabus', 'ORG'): 3; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 3; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Apocalypse', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('our day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Johnh', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ioel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 2; ('Muncer', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gregor', 'GPE'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('A•', 'ORG'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iocl', 'ORG'): 1; ('G. abbot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bristol Motiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quarter', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saracen', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sozom', 'GPE'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'NORP'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the three hour of the day', 'TIME'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('tong continue', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. John make canonical', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hea•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Uis•', 'ORG'): 1; ('a long day', 'DATE'): 1; ('February', 'DATE'): 1; ('a• … Euseb', 'ORG'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Kenites', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caiphas', 'ORG'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caiphas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balaam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lacta', 'GPE'): 1; ('d•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Angles', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('saint de civit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dei l. 18', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sibilla Erithrea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('L. Vives', 'ORG'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('un', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Virgile', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sibilla ◊ Cumaea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregory Nazi•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemesium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caiphas', 'NORP'): 1; ('Priscilla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Maximilla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccl', 'GPE'): 1; ('Miltiades', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Sleid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('contra', 'ORG'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paulus Abb•', 'ORG'): 1; ('A•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1534', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ•', 'NORP'): 1; ('fal•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('C•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gregory Thaumaturge so Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anthony the Abb•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aug. l. 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Benedict s•', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Bernarde', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. S. Frau•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ventura', 'GPE'): 1; ('vv•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Claudius Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gregorius Thaumaturgus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Socrat', 'GPE'): 1; ('Basile sette•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('n•', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Bec•', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. de civit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maximus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Monica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Maniche•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ince•', 'ORG'): 1; ('impor•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('9 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theobald', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'DATE'): 1; ('months end', 'DATE'): 1; ('Frācis', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bonavētura', 'GPE'): 1; ('Franciscanes', 'ORG'): 1; ('condescensionibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nutum factis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('melancholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lucian', 'GPE'): 1; ('•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Motiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bristol', 'ORG'): 1; ('Allington', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('winter night', 'TIME'): 1; ('hart', 'ORG'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A16795,15 | 11411,suppose ordinance archbishop matter length time council Orleans order canon,saint: 0.5; man: 0.5; day: 0.5; monk: 0.5; time: 0.5; god: 0.5; thing: 0.35; life: 0.35; ambition: 0.3; gluttony: 0.3; sin: 0.15; basile: 0.1; covetousness: 0.1; christ: 0.05; doctrine: 0.05; monastery: 0.05; another: 0.05; sunday: 0.05; self: 0.05; pope: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 7; ('England', 'GPE'): 5; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Austen', 'PERSON'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Homil', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 4; ('thou', 'GPE'): 4; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 2; ('quadragesima', 'GPE'): 2; ('forty day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Lent', 'EVENT'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Richardson', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Orleans', 'ORG'): 1; ('aurelian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quinquagesima', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fifty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('saint sermon de Eb•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven week', 'DATE'): 1; ('five day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sundaye', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thursdaye', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sundaye', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Thursday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lente', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Telesphorus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quinquagesima', 'GPE'): 1; ('fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('at least forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty and two day', 'DATE'): 1; ('vbi', 'ORG'): 1; ('thirty and six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Poli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four day', 'DATE'): 1; ('VVednesday', 'PERSON'): 1; ('easterday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gregory', 'GPE'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Virgil : Aeneid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('erat romanam', 'ORG'): 1; ('the first four day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the forty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gregory Nazianzene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('s. Chrysostome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('S. Austen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('G. abbot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('their fish day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bacchus and Ceres', 'ORG'): 1; ('sty-fed', 'ORG'): 1; ('amphora bacchi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('turpissima pestis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abbay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matthew Paris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('York', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Quodl', 'LOC'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('meek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Recucil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('767', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('liken', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diomedes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Homer', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Colein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas Becket', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cāterbury', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peregrin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Relig', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fulco', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cistertian', 'NORP'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hannibal', 'GPE'): 1; ('Phormio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Staphyl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rhemens', 'FAC'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the ascension week', 'DATE'): 1; ('Friday', 'DATE'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Oxford', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry', 'GPE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Parma', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romanist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vvitchcraft•', 'ORG'): 1; ('heresy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hebr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cyprian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('kinsman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Johnh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Eugen', 'ORG'): 1; ('A•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a few day', 'DATE'): 1; ('ca•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Basile , S. Chrysostome', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Basile', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregor', 'GPE'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gregory Nazianzen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the Basil : Hex•', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('6. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chrysostom', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('saint Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nunryes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aeneas Silvius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Hierome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Palestina', 'GPE'): 1; ('cloister virgin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ps', 'GPE'): 1; ('99', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('137', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Posidonius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Observat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hippon', 'GPE'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A15525,1,commentarie divine epistle saint Paul roman matter degeneration nature Adam,epistle: 0.5; jew: 0.5; god: 0.5; doctrine: 0.5; part: 0.5; matter: 0.5; christ: 0.45; reason: 0.4; thing: 0.4; paul: 0.4; text: 0.2; man: 0.05; law: 0.05; faith: 0.05,"('Jew', 'NORP'): 10; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Silas', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Moses', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('TLMOTHEVS', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thomas Wilson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('AVGVST', 'ORG'): 1; ('W. Iaggard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Barbican', 'NORP'): 1; ('1614', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nonum', 'ORG'): 1; ('some seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('more than one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('1. first', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('at least every week', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('howbeit', 'GPE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Candidus imperti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('impart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thy inn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wilson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('TIMOTHEVS', 'ORG'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('I. Timotheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'NORP'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about day', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A15525,15 | 18420,Tim. command Silas fear care God sin frailty favour deprive,god: 0.5; fear: 0.5; faith: 0.5; tim: 0.5; sin: 0.5; severity: 0.5; silas: 0.5; christ: 0.4; jew: 0.4; child: 0.2; psal: 0.15; goodness: 0.15; unbelief: 0.1; man: 0.1,"('Tim', 'PERSON'): 22; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 17; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 13; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('14', 'DATE'): 5; ('Prou', 'PERSON'): 5; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('5', 'DATE'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('12', 'DATE'): 4; ('4', 'DATE'): 4; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('35', 'DATE'): 3; ('17', 'DATE'): 3; ('6', 'DATE'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('13', 'DATE'): 2; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'DATE'): 2; ('130', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('32', 'DATE'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Math', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Peter 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('secondlie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('15 , 33', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('128', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joseph', 'GPE'): 1; ('39', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15 , 58.', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('34 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('2 4 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Deut', 'GPE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Neh', 'LOC'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('15 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('116', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand six hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jeremy , Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iezabel', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Steven', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ely', 'PERSON'): 1; ('last', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('forlese', 'NORP'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('58', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('chapter 18', 'LAW'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1"
A18610,18 | 21927,measure injustice creed point belief point belief practice D. potter,creed: 0.5; potter: 0.5; point: 0.5; belief: 0.5; thing: 0.5; apostle: 0.5; faith: 0.5; church: 0.5; answer: 0.45; question: 0.4; man: 0.1; matter: 0.05,"('D.', 'NORP'): 24; ('christian', 'NORP'): 7; ('§', 'NORP'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 2; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three year', 'DATE'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('58', 'DATE'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('qualis ab', 'ORG'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ausonius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fescennine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Virgil', 'ORG'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('64', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two .', 'DATE'): 1; ('buil•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('Valentia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nicene', 'ORG'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•aith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('damnabitur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('O.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('s. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('70', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('223', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('71', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('every one night', 'TIME'): 1; ('72', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Answ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Creed', 'ORG'): 1; ('74 four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pontius Pilate of Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('76', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gordonius Huntlaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cont', 'GPE'): 1"
A18610,20 | 22039,syllogism grant reason pomp word plenty reason build confession D.,church: 0.5; communion: 0.5; protestant: 0.5; schismatics: 0.5; man: 0.5; reason: 0.5; cause: 0.4; error: 0.4; corruption: 0.35; thing: 0.3; truth: 0.25; separation: 0.15; roman: 0.1; god: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 8; ('D.', 'NORP'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Donatus', 'ORG'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('greek', 'NORP'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Waldenses', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hussites', 'GPE'): 2; ('armenian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Georgians', 'NORP'): 2; ('America', 'GPE'): 2; ('Luther , Calvin', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Muscovite', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aethiopian', 'GPE'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('48. 49', 'DATE'): 1; ('50. 51', 'DATE'): 1; ('52', 'DATE'): 1; ('53. 54', 'DATE'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sodom', 'GPE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('§', 'NORP'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Muscovite', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aeneas Silvius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('at least as', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Austine', 'ORG'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every night', 'TIME'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42 third', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('saint cyprian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nova', 'LOC'): 1; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fugati', 'GPE'): 1; ('Casaubon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Card', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Perron', 'PERSON'): 1"
A18610,20 | 22097,reason schism church cut body Christ Ans. difference separation schism,church: 0.5; error: 0.5; reformation: 0.5; man: 0.5; monastery: 0.4; schism: 0.35; corruption: 0.35; doctrine: 0.35; god: 0.3; protestant: 0.3; self: 0.25; case: 0.25; hope: 0.1; company: 0.1; thing: 0.1; communion: 0.05; point: 0.05; disease: 0.05,"('D.', 'NORP'): 8; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('S. John', 'PERSON'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('81', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('§', 'NORP'): 2; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('76', 'DATE'): 1; ('78', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('79', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('80', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Felicissimus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four and five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('85', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('86 third', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cummin', 'ORG'): 1; ('87 four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('88', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('89', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mundus contra Athanasium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athanasius contra', 'ORG'): 1; ('so many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('90', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('91 four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Goulartius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theologi', 'ORG'): 1; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luthero', 'GPE'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luther', 'GPE'): 1"
A18610,24 | 22315,defence make lead error supposition confession confession concession doctor assertion,church: 0.45; error: 0.45; doctrine: 0.45; man: 0.45; faith: 0.45; salvation: 0.4; point: 0.4; protestant: 0.4; justify: 0.35; work: 0.35; truth: 0.3; sense: 0.05; physician: 0.05; phrase: 0.05; pope: 0.05; pollute: 0.05; poli: 0.05; plague: 0.05; place: 0.05; possibility: 0.05; person: 0.05; justification: 0.05,"('D.', 'NORP'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('§', 'NORP'): 4; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('79', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('78', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Crimina', 'ORG'): 1; ('Librat', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvinist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dominicans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Calvinists', 'NORP'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Corinth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Stephen', 'GPE'): 1; ('S.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aristotle de anima', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•libi', 'GPE'): 1"
A17294,16,CHAP. degree simony commit ordination simony commit ordination money give,money: 0.5; man: 0.5; simony: 0.5; sin: 0.5; hand: 0.5; church: 0.5; ghost: 0.4; grace: 0.3; reward: 0.3; priest: 0.3; lord: 0.2; port: 0.15; ordination: 0.15; god: 0.1; prophet: 0.1,"('Judas', 'PERSON'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 4; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 3; ('deleatur', 'GPE'): 3; ('illis', 'GPE'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 3; ('five half-penny', 'MONEY'): 3; ('France', 'GPE'): 3; ('10.10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('sibi', 'GPE'): 2; ('vinere qui capitis', 'ORG'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Romae', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 2; ('Ambros', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Naamans', 'NORP'): 2; ('Simons', 'ORG'): 2; ('Gihezi', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eccl', 'GPE'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('these three or', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('less than these hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Madrid', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alph••sus Gomezius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1584', 'DATE'): 1; ('Salmur', 'LOC'): 1; ('P•rtaw', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1601', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Michael Sonnius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('74', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('romanam curiam repurgare', 'PERSON'): 1; ('76', 'DATE'): 1; ('78.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('venda•t', 'ORG'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Romae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Roma viris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('auibus quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('noctua', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Camer•', 'ORG'): 1; ('curiam repurgare', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nummo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('profano qu•rit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cum alia vendaut', 'FAC'): 1; ('•obis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Altaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Coronae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thura', 'ORG'): 1; ('altar', 'ORG'): 1; ('crown', 'ORG'): 1; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ieroboam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lycurgus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('malis', 'NORP'): 1; ('moribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gratian .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pope Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('profecto', 'GPE'): 1; ('gratis accipitur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('procul dubio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('p•r', 'GPE'): 1; ('d•tionem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Whos•euer', 'ORG'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('quisquis per pecuniam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ambros•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('reperiuntur quamplurimi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gratiam spiritus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dum illi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of Chalcedon', 'ORG'): 1; ('pecuniam ordinationem fecerit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deacon', 'ORG'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('inexpiabi•is', 'NORP'): 1; ('vindicte gratiae coelestibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Posteros', 'GPE'): 1; ('Simoniaci', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simoniaci', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Beelzebub', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iudaeis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jew', 'GPE'): 1; ('Brachar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Balack', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balaam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('prophe•ie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Naaman', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mich.', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fac eum accepisse', 'ORG'): 1; ('twenty halfpenny', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Sauls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prophetiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui ariolos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gratian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sacerdotes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Cathedris', 'LOC'): 1; ('flagell•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('qui utinam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cathedralls', 'LOC'): 1; ('only five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('114', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theodorico', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theoberto Rogib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Francorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theodoricke', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theobert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae autem opera esse', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui honorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sacris ordimbus prohibi••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ordinatoris', 'GPE'): 1; ('episcoper•m', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sacerd••i•', 'NORP'): 1; ('•ur••a', 'ORG'): 1; ('pram••r•m', 'ORG'): 1; ('nihil sibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesiastico•', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paterno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fluibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nulla contra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Albion', 'ORG'): 1; ('Custom', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paul d•d', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('7.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam 15', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Archiep•scopo', 'DATE'): 1; ('gratiam consequi mer••ssem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aurum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sacerdotium', 'ORG'): 1; ('aurum ded•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ordino Presbyteros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('accipio aurum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('de alijs nihilominus', 'ORG'): 1; ('ordinibus pecunia quaestum profligare confido', 'ORG'): 1; ('Milan', 'GPE'): 1; ('penitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('mill•n', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui talia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aquila', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioh', 'ORG'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Laban', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nihil est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eden', 'LOC'): 1; ('Cypr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iereboam vend•ntem Sacerdotia', 'ORG'): 1; ('hic simonem gratiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nundinatorem à sanctorum consorti• exheredat', 'ORG'): 1; ('ruina', 'ORG'): 1; ('claudicantem ad propria remisit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iereboam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dis-inheriteth Simon', 'ORG'): 1"
A17867,15,reason sophism i• outwear saying fellow eye gallant varnish an•,word: 0.45; saint: 0.45; side: 0.45; eye: 0.45; adversary: 0.45; church: 0.45; god: 0.45; scripture: 0.3; christ: 0.3; man: 0.3; heaven: 0.2; sort: 0.15; sermon: 0.05; blood: 0.05; proof: 0.05; priest: 0.05; reason: 0.05; qui: 0.05; question: 0.05; queen: 0.05; purity: 0.05; purgatory: 0.05; prophet: 0.05; religion: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Logomachia', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 2; ('fifteen hundred year', 'DATE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Damas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Euseb', 'GPE'): 2; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hat•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Schiamachia', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cor 7', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Homonymia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('58', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two or three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a week', 'DATE'): 1; ('consult herein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Meandrian', 'GPE'): 1; ('calumny', 'GPE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('erit', 'ORG'): 1; ('directa via', 'GPE'): 1; ('mean•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirty three', 'DATE'): 1; ('Roman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a••me', 'ORG'): 1; ('Igna•ius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ignat•us', 'NORP'): 1; ('•pi••', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ierome', 'ORG'): 1; ('Catal', 'ORG'): 1; ('•u•eb', 'GPE'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tomb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('c•n de ◊ d', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Telesphorus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lent', 'GPE'): 1; ('Victo•', 'ORG'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Irenaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Polycarpus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('-day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Smyrna', 'GPE'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('anniversary day', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de saint Laurent', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laurence', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laurent amb l. 1', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('laur•nt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sixtus', 'FAC'): 1; ('twelve hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('P•udentius', 'NORP'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Laur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('annuis .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hos inter', 'ORG'): 1; ('Audi', 'ORG'): 1"
A17867,16,English servant Christ power g•u•n roman joy favour accord troop,church: 0.5; christ: 0.5; man: 0.5; witness: 0.5; faith: 0.5; side: 0.5; religion: 0.4; christians: 0.4; doctrine: 0.25; god: 0.15; king: 0.15; prince: 0.15; silver: 0.15; saint: 0.1; luther: 0.1; place: 0.05; heaven: 0.05; day: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 7; ('thou', 'GPE'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 5; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('this day', 'DATE'): 3; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Turks', 'NORP'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 2; ('Caluin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('jovinian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jerom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('earth', 'LOC'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 2; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 2; ('wh•ch troop', 'ORG'): 1; ('•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('Prudentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Metaph', 'ORG'): 1; ('90', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cecilia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Agatha', 'GPE'): 1; ('Barbara', 'GPE'): 1; ('Agnes', 'LOC'): 1; ('Lucia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dorothea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Catherina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Russin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Monica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug l. 9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pauliae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bethleem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paulus', 'GPE'): 1; ('e•a S. Anto', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ambr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nicolau• Joan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. •acon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('D•a', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fath•r', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten year', 'DATE'): 1; ('so many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Surij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sanct', 'GPE'): 1; ('Roman Catholiks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eith•r', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mat 16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marcel', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Epist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('three hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Laurence', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vestris orgijs morem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('auro', 'ORG'): 1; ('argenteis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('all night', 'TIME'): 1; ('that thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('church golden goblet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nimtof Gen 10', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Damas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sylu', 'LOC'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Soractes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Eus••', 'ORG'): 1; ('l. 2 d•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7 8.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Helena', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marcus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iulius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicolaus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('A•han', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vita s. An•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sergius Zonaras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sa•acens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('l. 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solyman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Saraceus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('spoy•ed', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cypr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iubaian', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haeret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Persa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aerius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arian', 'NORP'): 1; ('haer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aug. haer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aetius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Socrates l 2.28', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vigilantius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iero', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Aust', 'LOC'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Macedonius ,', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('N•storius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eutiches', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iconomach•', 'ORG'): 1; ('•aluin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•nd', 'GPE'): 1; ('19•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apostolicae Cathedrae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Catal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theophilus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cyrill', 'ORG'): 1; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cappadocia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Smyrna', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iustinu•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dionysius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nyssa : Methodius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Optatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('Gaudentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Faustus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vigilius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Irenaeus , Martinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hilarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eucherius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregory', 'GPE'): 1; ('Saluianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hildefonsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Britanny', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Damianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iustus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mellitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Su•ij de Sanct', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward of England', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hermingildi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry of Saxony', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wenceslaes of Bohemia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Steuens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hungary', 'GPE'): 1; ('India', 'GPE'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('Reginae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('IESVS', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('count•yes •onuerted', 'ORG'): 1; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 1; ('Diana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christi•n', 'ORG'): 1; ('irish', 'NORP'): 1; ('scottish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Palladius', 'GPE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Austin', 'GPE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Witn•sses', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Charke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('king|be', 'PERSON'): 1"
A15529,6,rule take m. Luthers scripture understand Christ Christ precept faith,thing: 0.5; god: 0.5; answer: 0.5; scripture: 0.5; case: 0.5; question: 0.5; man: 0.45; knowledge: 0.4; christ: 0.4; understanding: 0.3; place: 0.25; sense: 0.15; riddle: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('4 many', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hysteron proteron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('T. W. London', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward Griffin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Francis Burton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1615', 'DATE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('phoenician', 'NORP'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hiram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tirus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abdenan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sphinix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('last', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('farewell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('T. W. advertisement', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sam 2.2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('103', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20. 21', 'DATE'): 1"
A19248,1,work masse-priest nvmber verse lord Moses M•dianites suit wile depiction,king: 0.5; pope: 0.5; sin: 0.5; priest: 0.5; man: 0.5; lib: 0.5; book: 0.45; papist: 0.4; cap: 0.35; page: 0.3; another: 0.15; write: 0.1; part: 0.1; martyr: 0.1; depose: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 9; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 5; ('France', 'GPE'): 5; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('contra', 'NORP'): 3; ('England', 'GPE'): 3; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('illi qui', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1586', 'DATE'): 2; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('english', 'NORP'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Scot', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Boniface', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('William Jones', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1621', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cyclops eat Ulysses', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gibeonites', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haere• co•••a col ▪ y•id••n•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Religioni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('B. virginem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vili•ie', 'GPE'): 1; ('Turk', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jew', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('2. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Auron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Melchisedek', 'GPE'): 1; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('pro•••lgat', 'ORG'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1591', 'DATE'): 1; ('157', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('149', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quemcunque', 'NORP'): 1; ('ac dignitate', 'ORG'): 1; ('subdito posse', 'ORG'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dominicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salamanca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Excusandi Anglicani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('quoniam communiter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gerenda', 'GPE'): 1; ('Saxony', 'GPE'): 1; ('467', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 12', 'LAW'): 1; ('parson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the eleventh year', 'DATE'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('1608', 'DATE'): 1; ('Louaine', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Henrice', 'ORG'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gutgnard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clemens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('79', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year 1584', 'DATE'): 1; ('potius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Martyrum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Parry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hannibal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('B. Bilson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1584', 'DATE'): 1; ('rare jewel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('platina de vit Pontif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cromerus de •cbus', 'PERSON'): 1; (""Bo'eslaus"", 'PERSON'): 1; ('Poland', 'GPE'): 1; ('15.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('alius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zachary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Childericke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bonifac', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antonin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Otho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('i•h', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frederike', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baldwin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Michael Pael•eologus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Massonius de v•bis Episcop', 'ORG'): 1; ('Johnh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lewis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bavaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('George king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Navarre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iulius', 'ORG'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saunders de', 'ORG'): 1; ('108', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rochester', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('thirteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Sixtus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plagina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Imperia', 'GPE'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('apud b••niam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. Cone .', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('coeles•is quibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('platina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quaeritur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quaritur', 'GPE'): 1; ('haereticus', 'GPE'): 1; ('vel fautor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('661', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('iur be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tyrannus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('k Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('660', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Azor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mosco•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Episcopos', 'GPE'): 1; ('clertco suo officto fungi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sapientes de regno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('zero•e de quadr', 'ORG'): 1; ('Albericus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Para', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Mosein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cit', 'ORG'): 1; ('601', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Glossa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Papa', 'ORG'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de potestat', 'PERSON'): 1"
A19248,3 | 25733,book have pope Ga•riel btbd praparat bishop make deacon stead,god: 0.5; pope: 0.5; lib: 0.5; priest: 0.5; christ: 0.5; man: 0.5; cap: 0.5; saint: 0.5; sacrament: 0.5; poison: 0.2; ioh: 0.2; thing: 0.05; blood: 0.05,"('3', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 10; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 6; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 5; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Missa', 'ORG'): 3; ('Bellar', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 3; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Chronol', 'ORG'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Sienna', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sixtus 5', 'LAW'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sixtus', 'FAC'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Quast', 'GPE'): 2; ('Theol', 'GPE'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('de Missa', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sacramenta Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('quot sunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tres', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thuribulum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iulius', 'ORG'): 1; ('penitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('haer•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alfonsus de Castro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Andr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baldus Jason', 'PERSON'): 1; ('201', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quod de mane faciebat gratiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('twelve year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pope baron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('an . 955 •u', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 12', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lateran', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luitprandus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Masson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sergius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Platin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Boniface', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rob saint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sixtus', 'ORG'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Agrippa de vanitaic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('64', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Onuph', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plat', 'ORG'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('heretical pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Honorius', 'ORG'): 1; ('13 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('synod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leo the', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Donat', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cons•antini', 'ORG'): 1; ('quantum prisci', 'ORG'): 1; ('fuerunt sapiente', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('970', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('parum solliciti de Rep.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1026', 'DATE'): 1; ('partibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Formoso 1', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('platina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('954', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('O••ph', 'ORG'): 1; ('vita marcell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antonin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('par', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('romana', 'GPE'): 1; ('a hundred mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('T•codoricus', 'GPE'): 1; ('inaquos• trac', 'ORG'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('virgin marry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bridget', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mantuans', 'NORP'): 1; ('qui cupitis sancte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('romoe omnia cum liceant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sheepish pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('boy pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('whoremaster pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('asheisticall pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year 1590', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('62', 'DATE'): 1; ('de Bibl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Valt•', 'ORG'): 1; ('10. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('•ondita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('229', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•nd', 'PERSON'): 1; ('m. S.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('1592', 'DATE'): 1; ('Clemens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Athanas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Comelin', 'GPE'): 1; ('1600', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Discip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('111', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('gloria mundi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bi•l', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sacer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Creatoris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ho•• B. virgo Salu•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('1516', 'DATE'): 1; ('72', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Ciuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cyclops', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ulysses', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bacchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alleu de sacrifi• .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bristo', 'GPE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Laban', 'ORG'): 1; ('insipientiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tales', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Non erubescis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lindwood conslit Prouine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euchar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the Joseph Angles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cicero ▪ lib', 'ORG'): 1; ('d• Na•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nuncuparit•d', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod vero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tandem ipse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Espene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christiana deteriorem aut tam fatuam', 'ORG'): 1; ('dentibus deuorabant', 'ORG'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('1095', 'DATE'): 1; ('1094', 'DATE'): 1; ('Henricus Archiep', 'ORG'): 1; ('Henry archbishop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('York', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephan', 'GPE'): 1; ('1154', 'DATE'): 1; ('122', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matthew Paris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henricus 7', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eucharistian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Henry 7.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('1314', 'DATE'): 1; ('nuper prio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('noster misericordiae venetijs veneno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('Monita Poluica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1609', 'DATE'): 1; ('John Baptista Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vrbinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Sacram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Angelica', 'GPE'): 1; ('Encharistia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Simusca', 'GPE'): 1; ('aranea cadat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sanguinem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Conc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Annot in Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de sacram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('etiam intentio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Patolus Langius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chron', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ann', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thelauro', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Bodin Damond', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mania lib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('loco', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iudicis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi', 'GPE'): 1; ('idcirco', 'NORP'): 1; ('muneribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('iob', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaak', 'GPE'): 1; ('4. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32.', 'DATE'): 1; ('33. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Math', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('George', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christopher', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Katharin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ursula', 'GPE'): 1; ('Margaret', 'PERSON'): 1"
A19248,3 | 25765,Mariae thing god virgin Maries spouse mother God chrysost verb,virgin: 0.5; christ: 0.5; lib: 0.5; cap: 0.5; sin: 0.5; god: 0.5; commandment: 0.5; part: 0.45; man: 0.45; son: 0.35; church: 0.2; honour: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 17; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 14; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Mariae', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Prou', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Dist', 'NORP'): 4; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Bernard .', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Saturday', 'DATE'): 3; ('Bellar', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Azor', 'ORG'): 3; ('quaritur', 'GPE'): 3; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('de Busti', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sanct', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Relig', 'PERSON'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('some year', 'DATE'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('matris', 'GPE'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 2; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Discip', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Navarre', 'PERSON'): 2; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Euangelicall', 'ORG'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9 7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tolet', 'ORG'): 2; ('49', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the virgin Maries', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mariae virgi•i', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ma•ial•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mar •', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ibid', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paterno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mater num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Assump', 'NORP'): 1; ('duae Cathedra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Assump', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gabriel Biel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lect', 'PERSON'): 1; ('80', 'DATE'): 1; ('Maria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrysost', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisp•ijs', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam invocate', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the virgin marry ▪', 'FAC'): 1; ('Bern de Busti', 'ORG'): 1; ('assi••l', 'ORG'): 1; ('2. Sedul', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Douai 1604', 'EVENT'): 1; ('304', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the virgin marie', 'FAC'): 1; ('quidam Lu•etiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fide•', 'NORP'): 1; ('duceretur', 'GPE'): 1; ('ac palo inspecto subind• exclamaret', 'ORG'): 1; ('domine deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('miserationem mer', 'ORG'): 1; ('quidam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theologus', 'ORG'): 1; ('ide••idem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mari• mater gratiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mater misericordiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Consultas', 'ORG'): 1; ('•ij', 'GPE'): 1; ('Marie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Instr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 8', 'LAW'): 1; ('Bernard lib cit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Maria', 'GPE'): 1; ('impetranda', 'NORP'): 1; ('Angelica', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bernardinus de Busti', 'ORG'): 1; ('Greg de Vale•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('beru•r lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de visuas maria .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seu villa', 'GPE'): 1; ('capellam', 'ORG'): 1; ('ci intitulasae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam in', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mariae Augustae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('weekly', 'DATE'): 1; ('D. Mortons', 'NORP'): 1; ('soct', 'PERSON'): 1; ('242', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('iumarg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('200 pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Loretto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Liguria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sauona', 'ORG'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('the mount Serrato', 'LOC'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hales', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ipswich', 'GPE'): 1; ('Walsingham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('195', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marialipar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('diebus', 'ORG'): 1; ('maxim de mane', 'ORG'): 1; ('ipsam immaculatam virginem genibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac beatificent', 'ORG'): 1; ('mary bell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cassand', 'GPE'): 1; ('Noftr•', 'ORG'): 1; ('6. Psal', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('481', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bonaventure', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•dem', 'ORG'): 1; ('466', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bonaventure', 'GPE'): 1; ('Corona B. Mariae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('delectissimo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('54', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catal', 'ORG'): 1; ('1608', 'DATE'): 1; ('qui parum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('turris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ipsam confugiet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('turris furtissima', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Discip de Tep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('Exempl• 97', 'DATE'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Locrius Mariae Augusta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('loco cis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('99', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('videntur B. virginem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Quta', 'NORP'): 1; ('redundat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('patientiam habet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('del de', 'ORG'): 1; ('vir orem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mulierem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Institutio', 'GPE'): 1; ('initiū', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ledesma', 'GPE'): 1; ('lib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bruno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the holy day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine and ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ledesina', 'GPE'): 1; ('134', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('143', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten .', 'DATE'): 1; ('Radford', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter 16', 'LAW'): 1; ('115', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•nchirin', 'GPE'): 1; ('n•', 'ORG'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vincent Bruno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 10', 'LAW'): 1; ('Vaux', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Catech', 'NORP'): 1; ('225', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1549', 'DATE'): 1; ('1592', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apparat', 'ORG'): 1; ('verbo', 'NORP'): 1; ('possevin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vega de Iuslif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14 cap', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ioh.', 'ORG'): 1; ('l', 'LOC'): 1; ('70', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ludolph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de vita christi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 1; ('58', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rada', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Racaing', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ioh', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rada 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('par', 'PERSON'): 1; ('The•l', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bonauent', 'LOC'): 1; ('loco citato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('6. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('periuri', 'GPE'): 1; ('mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the sabbath day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Enchirid', 'GPE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1"
