tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A61471,3 | 181,Nothing divine face truth whole nature thing beauty eye mind,divine: 0.5; god: 0.5; love: 0.5; self: 0.5; thing: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; work: 0.45; whole: 0.4; nature: 0.25; beauty: 0.25; part: 0.25; end: 0.1; truth: 0.1; man: 0.05; saint: 0.05; motion: 0.05; christ: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('thou', 'GPE'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Sin', 'ORG'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Helena', 'ORG'): 1; ('Castor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pollux', 'ORG'): 1; ('jewel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('the spring of', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Neptune , Minerva', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('Parelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('frailty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('the golden altar', 'FAC'): 1"
A61471,5 | 336,will God right distinguish evil will God determination motion will,thing: 0.5; divine: 0.5; god: 0.5; self: 0.5; form: 0.5; part: 0.5; number: 0.5; understanding: 0.4; unity: 0.4; whole: 0.15; image: 0.15; knowledge: 0.15; word: 0.1; idea: 0.1; proportion: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 21; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('thou', 'GPE'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('greek', 'NORP'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('God .', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('only two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('each day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pythagorean', 'NORP'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Numeration', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ark', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vandike', 'GPE'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Augustus Caesar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('•', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Modes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the supreme king', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacobs', 'ORG'): 1; ('Angelick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1"
A61471,7 | 1261,This piece variety self piece riches light glory scene form,thing: 0.5; motion: 0.5; god: 0.5; variety: 0.5; evil: 0.5; self: 0.5; act: 0.5; understanding: 0.45; spirit: 0.3; divine: 0.3; principle: 0.2; man: 0.1; reason: 0.05; nature: 0.05; form: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 14; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Medea', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Crassâ Minervâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('actibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('imperatis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Beloved', 'ORG'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('automaton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('Proclus', 'GPE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evil', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicodemus', 'ORG'): 1; ('3. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('saint John say', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('thrice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('supreme mystery', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1"
A65276,14,CHAP. check discontent christian reproof discontent condition reproof disease sta•••,god: 0.4; child: 0.4; discontent: 0.4; man: 0.4; want: 0.35; thing: 0.35; self: 0.35; apology: 0.3; sin: 0.3; take: 0.25; reply: 0.2; another: 0.1; people: 0.1; peace: 0.1; pillow: 0.1; piece: 0.1; philos: 0.1; pet: 0.1; poet: 0.1; peg: 0.1; part: 0.1; paul: 0.1; condition: 0.05; mercy: 0.05; christian: 0.05; life: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Boëtius de Consol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('superbia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('svae quemque', 'ORG'): 1; ('ille nup•iis foelix', 'NORP'): 1; ('orbus', 'ORG'): 1; ('liberis alieno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('membra labour', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Horat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Maecenas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemo quam sibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seu', 'ORG'): 1; ('diversa sequente', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jonah 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gore', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rachel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('CHAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('x.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 7.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Answ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paulina', 'GPE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lent', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hanna', 'ORG'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('57 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('23.', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('15. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lachryma', 'PERSON'): 1"
A65276,16 | 1919,sect argument contentation argument heart contentment consideration god providence believer,god: 0.5; discontent: 0.5; affliction: 0.5; man: 0.5; evil: 0.5; faith: 0.45; thing: 0.45; sin: 0.45; grace: 0.4; water: 0.2; cause: 0.15; heart: 0.15; glory: 0.1; spirit: 0.1; fire: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('thou', 'GPE'): 8; ('christian', 'NORP'): 6; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 3; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Epigr', 'PERSON'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('God Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('litora quot concha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quot amoena Rosaria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quótve soporiferum grana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sylva', 'ORG'): 1; ('quot piscibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('unda natatur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Catholicon', 'GPE'): 1; ('R.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Schola', 'GPE'): 1; ('disciplinaris', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Mica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tekoah', 'GPE'): 1; ('6. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('58', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31• 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('navi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jonah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('66.', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('arians', 'NORP'): 1; ('winter-season', 'DATE'): 1; ('12 94', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa 27', 'LAW'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cypress', 'FAC'): 1; ('Ps', 'ORG'): 1; ('91. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('54', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sceptrum Regale', 'ORG'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jonathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('miseria', 'GPE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fer mansuetè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fortunam tuam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 10 25', 'PERSON'): 1; ('outward comfort', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('prior•m', 'GPE'): 1; ('parem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('alienis semperin agris', 'ORG'): 1; ('moss•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('plebeian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Behemoth', 'GPE'): 1; ('jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Job 40', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two .', 'DATE'): 1; ('100', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jonah 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sarepta', 'NORP'): 1; ('17. 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lucian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ingratus', 'NORP'): 1; ('nec cogitari', 'ORG'): 1; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam •o', 'PERSON'): 1"
A65276,16 | 1957,man devil devil swell poison envy malice devil spirit Pet.,man: 0.5; discontent: 0.5; world: 0.5; god: 0.5; estate: 0.5; life: 0.5; heart: 0.5; thing: 0.4; argument: 0.35; content: 0.3; prosperity: 0.25; condition: 0.1; sun: 0.05; isaac: 0.05,"('christian', 'NORP'): 7; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Seneca', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cato', 'ORG'): 2; ('about 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ionah', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jam. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Absalon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Naboth', 'ORG'): 1; ('39 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('autumn', 'DATE'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('15. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('11 day', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('nunquam nimis', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod nunquam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James Jam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phocilides', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('noonday', 'DATE'): 1; ('opibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the twelve hour of the day', 'TIME'): 1; ('two or three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('non vinci', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aug. de verb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('qui abundantiâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('celsae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fulmina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hortano', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hominem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paradiso', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('Turpi', 'ORG'): 1; ('luxu divitiae molle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Juvenas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fulmi•ans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Job 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('nimiae sternit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucillium Ep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('80', 'DATE'): 1; ('18 24', 'DATE'): 1; ('a thousand to one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Laert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diogenes de vit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Damsin', 'LOC'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('grace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isaac gen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('promis•i', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isaac', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isaac', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abrahams', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('11. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Charron', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mesopotamia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sichem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bethlem', 'NORP'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('one foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philosophari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('elysian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Michah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Regulus', 'GPE'): 1; ('distract•s', 'GPE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A65276,16 | 1981,sect argument contentation argument contentment change child God hell eclipse,man: 0.45; hell: 0.45; sin: 0.45; estate: 0.45; god: 0.45; house: 0.45; content: 0.45; family: 0.45; heart: 0.35; sinner: 0.3; soul: 0.15; contentation: 0.05; self: 0.05; plant: 0.05; plague: 0.05; prayer: 0.05; power: 0.05; pour: 0.05; poison: 0.05; pluck: 0.05; prisoner: 0.05; physician: 0.05; philistine: 0.05,"('it|be', 'PERSON'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Albus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hortano Ode 7.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a wet night', 'TIME'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Cannium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 1; ('4. 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('1. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Xii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the enemy quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('4. 4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Sodom Gen.', 'ORG'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('3. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('consuctudinem est dur•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jer 6.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharaohs', 'LOC'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('42 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('vivitur', 'NORP'): 1; ('legibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('8. 38', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('Kedar', 'ORG'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zach', 'ORG'): 1; ('bee', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nymphas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A65276,19,disquiet unbelief storm discontent heart set faith work property faith,god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; heart: 0.5; man: 0.5; contentment: 0.5; condition: 0.5; world: 0.5; conscience: 0.4; content: 0.4; faith: 0.3; sect: 0.1; rule: 0.1; soul: 0.05; christ: 0.05; discontent: 0.05; spirit: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 15; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 15; ('thou', 'GPE'): 13; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('christian', 'NORP'): 11; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 8; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('14.', 'DATE'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Abram', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Answ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('polish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('12. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('84. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('47 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sam 30', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ziklag', 'NORP'): 1; ('3. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sin lie as', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ionah', 'NORP'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marah', 'GPE'): 1; ('1. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David harp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nehemlah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Neb. 2', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('62.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rachel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jonathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('63.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zach 1', 'ORG'): 1; ('8. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pilgrim', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ps', 'ORG'): 1; ('39 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('4 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('outward comfort', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Soliloq', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11. 37', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('8. 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 7.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('India', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vetera •rangantur •epulchra', 'ORG'): 1; ('•ssa divi•um', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sed qui plus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a few acre', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Pythocles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cupidi•tatibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jonah 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('virens hedera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae textili', 'PERSON'): 1; ('paravit deus vermem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('subi••ò', 'LOC'): 1; ('Drexel', 'ORG'): 1; ('163', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('thousand than hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('achesilaus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dulcis prosilien', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petra', 'ORG'): 1; ('mel agreste possunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aequè', 'GPE'): 1; ('cibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('6. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pyrrhus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('— contentus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fabricius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Serranus', 'LOC'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregory Nazianzen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christianorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nunquam parvo', 'ORG'): 1; ('lautae gloria mensae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('discite quàm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucan', 'NORP'): 1; ('15. 15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('surfeit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('horseleech', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lutenist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('57 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jam. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('prayer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oratio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leviathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('grace be crown', 'PERSON'): 1; ('goliath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rebecca', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Job', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nathaniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 1', 'PERSON'): 1"
A64622,10 | 10318,nature Joh. father father Esa. Mat servant say God father,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; son: 0.5; debt: 0.5; flesh: 0.45; father: 0.45; death: 0.45; life: 0.4; nature: 0.3; lord: 0.2; power: 0.15; heb: 0.15; generation: 0.15; christ: 0.1; sin: 0.1; joh: 0.05; thing: 0.05,"('5', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 5; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 5; ('14', 'DATE'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 3; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Esa', 'PERSON'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('18', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('26', 'DATE'): 2; ('5', 'DATE'): 2; ('8', 'DATE'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('2. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'DATE'): 2; ('2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6. 15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('27', 'DATE'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('14. 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('53. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zach', 'GPE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('this hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('6. 38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('6. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.', 'DATE'): 1; ('8. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ib', 'NORP'): 1; ('7. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('22. 44', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('10. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('8. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('53. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('26. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('18. 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('ten thousand million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 24', 'DATE'): 1; ('8. 33', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('Goël', 'PERSON'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('15. 47', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Davids', 'ORG'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('139', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 8. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bradwardin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22. 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jam. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ibid', 'ORG'): 1; ('4. 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nicodemus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Progenerant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A64173,2,speak apology man hour be spend industry search father comment,man: 0.5; religion: 0.5; church: 0.5; saint: 0.5; god: 0.5; hair: 0.5; roundhead: 0.4; head: 0.35; thing: 0.35; divine: 0.25; law: 0.25; house: 0.1; peace: 0.1; temple: 0.05; judge: 0.05; government: 0.05; inspiration: 0.05,"('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('Roundhead', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('elishaes chariot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Randolph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ri••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernard , S. Chrisostome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('B. saint Ba', 'NORP'): 1; ('saint P. marry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('h•s', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Whittington', 'PERSON'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('the day of the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('festival hymn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('J. F. for R. Royston', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1655', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('de gloriâ minimè certandum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balaam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bosor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Moses', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1"
A63950,7,AGENDA thing apex nonlatinalphabet hymn diary day day day business,prayer: 0.5; god: 0.45; day: 0.45; self: 0.45; time: 0.45; thing: 0.35; business: 0.35; whole: 0.35; soul: 0.3; servant: 0.25; action: 0.25; dress: 0.2; matter: 0.15; act: 0.05; piety: 0.05; person: 0.05; precept: 0.05; praise: 0.05; portion: 0.05; present: 0.05; open: 0.05; part: 0.05; provide: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('•', 'ORG'): 5; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('inscripta christo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet hymn', 'ORG'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('each day', 'DATE'): 1; ('§', 'NORP'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('hat•', 'ORG'): 1; ('for•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the night past', 'TIME'): 1; ('God .', 'DATE'): 1; ('festival day', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Homil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Lazaro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('tem•', 'NORP'): 1; ('thi•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('al•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A67906,11,muse eye lover lordship happiness performance task lord lordship|be oblige,god: 0.5; world: 0.5; life: 0.5; time: 0.45; virtue: 0.45; use: 0.45; book: 0.4; self: 0.4; part: 0.4; endeavour: 0.25; nature: 0.2; person: 0.2; lib: 0.15; reason: 0.1; soul: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('Bentivolio', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Theoprepia', 'ORG'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 3; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Urania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Phronesium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theonoe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Irene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theriagene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tully', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 12', 'LAW'): 1; ('243', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('un', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chrestien', 'GPE'): 1; ('la', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ion', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Delphi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ion', 'GPE'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Phoebus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tripos', 'ORG'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eurip', 'GPE'): 1; ('Platonists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Enn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Moxus', 'ORG'): 1; ('crambians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Plut', 'PERSON'): 1"
A67906,15 | 12156,reader Theriagene victory be tell day princess Agape marry Alethion,god: 0.5; name: 0.5; man: 0.5; person: 0.5; book: 0.5; thing: 0.5; use: 0.5; call: 0.45; life: 0.4; see: 0.35; world: 0.25; word: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 195; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 21; ('80', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('152', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('333', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('167', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 5; ('201', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('131', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('203', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Urania', 'GPE'): 3; ('Bentivolio', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Theoprepia', 'ORG'): 3; ('153', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Eurip', 'ORG'): 3; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('161', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('202', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Theosebes', 'GPE'): 2; ('Panaretus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Alethion', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 2; ('Agazelus', 'GPE'): 2; ('117', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('200', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('178', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lucian', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Eusebia', 'GPE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('158', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('235', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Eros', 'GPE'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('78', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Apollyon', 'GPE'): 2; ('134', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('317', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'DATE'): 2; ('92', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('298', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('151', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('341', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Grapton', 'PERSON'): 2; ('103', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Exosemnon', 'GPE'): 2; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('195', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Theriagene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a few day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Theonoe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Irene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Agape', 'NORP'): 1; ('the end of the six', 'DATE'): 1; ('ABaddon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Asmodaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('251', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ult', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abulus', 'GPE'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Achamoth', 'GPE'): 1; ('Epiphan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tom 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('301', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Acephalus', 'GPE'): 1; ('174', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Achrestus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Achthedon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Acolastus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Acrasia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Adicus', 'GPE'): 1; ('adynaton', 'GPE'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hel', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aganacton', 'GPE'): 1; ('Agape', 'GPE'): 1; ('Phronesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Agatha', 'ORG'): 1; ('Agathorryton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet .', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'LOC'): 1; ('115', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Agnoea', 'GPE'): 1; ('122 ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Akeraea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('137', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alazon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('182', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alethea', 'GPE'): 1; ('Charinda', 'GPE'): 1; ('158 Alethion', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pistalethes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psoudomantis', 'GPE'): 1; ('310', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epiphanius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('312', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alopex', 'GPE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alypia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Indolentia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Piacenza', 'FAC'): 1; ('78 Amaranth', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('280', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amasia', 'NORP'): 1; ('237', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ametameletus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amiantus', 'NORP'): 1; ('246 Amphibius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amphibians', 'NORP'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('amphilogia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Amphisbeton', 'GPE'): 1; ('157', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anaedea', 'ORG'): 1; ('303', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anaeschyntus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ananephon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('173', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adynaton', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anaxagathus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Anaxanacton', 'GPE'): 1; ('136', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anelpistus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Angerona', 'GPE'): 1; ('16b', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anonomasta', 'GPE'): 1; ('302', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anopheles', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ishmael', 'NORP'): 1; ('156', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antinomus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isosthenes', 'GPE'): 1; ('163', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antichristus', 'NORP'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('128', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('132', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('140', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('143', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('144', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apateon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apateonia', 'GPE'): 1; ('296', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apeirus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Venus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Helen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Venus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aphron', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apiston', 'GPE'): 1; ('102', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Asmodeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Apronoeus', 'ORG'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aquedon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eaton', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epistola', 'GPE'): 1; ('Archibius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Archicacus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nicomachus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Argentora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Argento', 'ORG'): 1; ('Oromasdes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arimanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isid', 'GPE'): 1; ('Osir', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Max', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dissert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('306', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Asemnus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abaddon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Talmudists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aspasia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Asphaltites', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('149', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Roccabella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('86', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Astorgus', 'ORG'): 1; ('105', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Asynetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Insipiens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pasenantius', 'ORG'): 1; ('187', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Autautus', 'ORG'): 1; ('196', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Autocatacritus', 'ORG'): 1; ('arcadian', 'NORP'): 1; ('145', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Axiarchus', 'NORP'): 1; ('335', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('BAthypogon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ital', 'LOC'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('heavenly light', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mud', 'ORG'): 1; ('197', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cacodulus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Callicarpus', 'GPE'): 1; ('384', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calliphon', 'GPE'): 1; ('289', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Callistus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cantharus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Catasarkus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('230', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Centaurus', 'GPE'): 1; ('170', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Charinda', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('318', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('euergesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('260', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chelidones', 'NORP'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrematophilus', 'GPE'): 1; ('aurelian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Chrysus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Colax', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tuphlecon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Colpia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bau', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bohu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('AEon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Engastrimuthus', 'ORG'): 1; ('299', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('88.92', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cotta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tully de Nat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('94', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antistoichon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 1; ('262', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9,15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David George', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('university of Basil', 'ORG'): 1; ('1559', 'DATE'): 1; ('Verar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('138', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epicurus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Agellius', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('58', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dyselpis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dysemeria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dyspithea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('122', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Misoplanus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Charenton', 'GPE'): 1; ('Kingsham', 'ORG'): 1; ('Stockholm', 'GPE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('315', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nicephorus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Morophilia', 'GPE'): 1; ('92.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ekaephon', 'GPE'): 1; ('89', 'CARDINAL'): 1; (""E'pis"", 'GPE'): 1; ('Elpiscale', 'NORP'): 1; ('2d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pythonis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gr', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vespae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eurycles', 'ORG'): 1; ('142', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('109', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eristes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Erotocleus', 'NORP'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('165', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eudaemon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euergesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Philothea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('259', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eugenius', 'GPE'): 1; ('180', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('118', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eupathe', 'GPE'): 1; ('Euphron', 'GPE'): 1; ('295', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eupistia', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eupistus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Euprepes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pseudenthea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Euprosopon', 'NORP'): 1; ('Euthanatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('281', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('euthymia', 'GPE'): 1; ('exetazon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Exorcista', 'GPE'): 1; ('Exorcista', 'PERSON'): 1; ('exosemnian', 'NORP'): 1; ('139', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('outward .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('133 F', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('376', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('inganna', 'GPE'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('239', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gelosia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Geron', 'GPE'): 1; ('Glycypicron', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plotin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Platonists', 'NORP'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Achamoth', 'ORG'): 1; ('188', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('189', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('191', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('194', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('distinctiù', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cogitationem ◊ magis', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('limitationibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('parte primâ', 'PERSON'): 1"
A67906,16,pen nonlatinalphabet Dion nonlatinalphabet see God please manner see essence,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; book: 0.5; thing: 0.5; name: 0.5; world: 0.5; soul: 0.45; life: 0.3; describe: 0.25; lover: 0.25; nature: 0.2; person: 0.15; use: 0.15; mind: 0.15; write: 0.05; virtue: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 203; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('152', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('155', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('298', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('201', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('178', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('80', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('79', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('121', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('156', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('114', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('341', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('302', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Urania', 'GPE'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('296', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Agathorryton', 'PERSON'): 3; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('199', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('297', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('193', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('167', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('195', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 2; ('303', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hierocles', 'GPE'): 2; ('131', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('171', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('149', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('115', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('177', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('281', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('139', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Bentivolio', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Panaretus', 'ORG'): 2; ('179', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('91', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('168', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Polyglotta', 'GPE'): 2; ('333', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('153', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('92', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('239', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('133', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Philadelphia', 'GPE'): 2; ('208', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('200', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('86', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('316', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 2; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Dion', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Grapton', 'GPE'): 1; ('Empsychon', 'ORG'): 1; ('103', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gynaeceus', 'GPE'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gynaepicria', 'GPE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hamartolus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Piacenza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hemicalus', 'GPE'): 1; ('251', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hesychia', 'GPE'): 1; ('159', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hierographon', 'ORG'): 1; ('206', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hieromimus', 'GPE'): 1; ('187', 'CARDINAL'): 1; (""se'l"", 'PERSON'): 1; ('Imperfetta', 'ORG'): 1; ('troppo', 'GPE'): 1; ('dura leg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Natura', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nunquam est utile peccare', 'ORG'): 1; ('191 Hipponyx', 'PERCENT'): 1; ('Hoof', 'PERSON'): 1; ('317', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Histrionia', 'GPE'): 1; ('quisquis fere histrionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Holochrysus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hybris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hydraula', 'GPE'): 1; ('Proclus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Timaum', 'GPE'): 1; ('197', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hylotes', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hyperenor', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hypernephelas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hyperoncus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hyperurania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hypnotica', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hypsagoras', 'LOC'): 1; ('Megalophron', 'ORG'): 1; ('142', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('IAckleid', 'ORG'): 1; ('John becold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epiphan', 'GPE'): 1; ('James Nailor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lentulus', 'NORP'): 1; ('the senate of', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('temporibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orthodoxogr', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theolog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iconecron', 'GPE'): 1; ('355', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('372', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Andr', 'GPE'): 1; ('Androm', 'DATE'): 1; ('inganna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Irene', 'GPE'): 1; ('Amaranth', 'LOC'): 1; ('280', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sextus Empiricus', 'ORG'): 1; ('136', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('KAlobulus', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Kalodoxus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Kepanactus', 'ORG'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Kiskildrivium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('166', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Klerotheron', 'GPE'): 1; ('196', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Krimatophobus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sin', 'ORG'): 1; ('apud Petron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lampromeld', 'GPE'): 1; ('trifle', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lestocharis', 'ORG'): 1; ('lestrygon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lestrygones', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thucydides', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sicily', 'GPE'): 1; ('Campania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('odyss', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ulysses', 'ORG'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leucas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Epirus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Actium', 'GPE'): 1; ('minatur', 'GPE'): 1; ('mascula lesbiacis Sappho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Auson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Menander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('— nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('87', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Logomachia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('160', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Loxias', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('265', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('237', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lunia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('230', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lusingha', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lysander', 'GPE'): 1; ('288', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('MAngibella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mantimans', 'NORP'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Agape', 'ORG'): 1; ('Narrative', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Venus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plotin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Theosebes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alethion and Agape', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Nicomachus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Arete', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theonee', 'ORG'): 1; ('Irene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plotin Enn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.lib.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mataeogenes', 'NORP'): 1; ('Medenarete', 'GPE'): 1; ('344', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Megabronchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('105', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Megalophron', 'GPE'): 1; ('Meleta', 'ORG'): 1; ('Metamelusa', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Metanoea', 'GPE'): 1; ('Miasmasarkus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Misoplanus', 'GPE'): 1; ('305', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Moira', 'GPE'): 1; ('Monogrammus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Monogrammi', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nonius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucilius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gassendus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Monogrammi', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui ◊ coloribui quasi corporentur', 'ORG'): 1; ('lineis quibusdam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam prisci', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Latini', 'NORP'): 1; ('Deor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epicurus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tully', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Moronesus', 'GPE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Morpheolus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Morpheus', 'GPE'): 1; ('NArcissus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Philostratus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('80 narke', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Oedip', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antigone', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philo', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Justin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christianae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pol. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('202', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Naupactus', 'ORG'): 1; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Necrogaea', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nemesis', 'GPE'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('148', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nynhapanta', 'GPE'): 1; ('ODax', 'ORG'): 1; ('aeonian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Scrofam aeoniam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullianum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bythi', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Ontagathus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Catachresis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Orgilus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('117', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Orphana', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arimanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orthodus', 'GPE'): 1; ('PAmmachia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Simoni', 'ORG'): 1; ('Simon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Martyr Apol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pammelaena', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bentivolio', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pancratus', 'ORG'): 1; ('74', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pandacryon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pervigilium', 'GPE'): 1; ('all night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Priapus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Venus', 'LOC'): 1; ('etiam ◊ vobis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Priapi', 'GPE'): 1; ('deberi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('libris continentur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('terrestrem eruditionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('necessaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('finem vixit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel etiam scribi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rosicrucian', 'NORP'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Panthnetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Panurgus', 'GPE'): 1; ('273', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Parresia', 'GPE'): 1; ('118', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pasenantius', 'ORG'): 1; ('295', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peirasmus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Penia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Petalism', 'GPE'): 1; ('Syracuse', 'GPE'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philandra', 'GPE'): 1; ('286', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philedones', 'GPE'): 1; ('Philopantas', 'GPE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Orthocrinon', 'GPE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philothea', 'GPE'): 1; ('259', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philoxenus', 'GPE'): 1; ('116', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pierudor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pinodipson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pistalethes', 'GPE'): 1; ('140', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pleonectes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pluterastes', 'NORP'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Polistherium', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theriagene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Polymachus', 'GPE'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Proselenus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antelunaris', 'GPE'): 1; ('the moon', 'LOC'): 1; ('argon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Circe', 'ORG'): 1; ('154', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Libya', 'GPE'): 1; ('Max', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dion', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chrysoft', 'PERSON'): 1; ('310', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pseudenthea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pseudognosis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pseudolus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Salmasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psychopannyx', 'ORG'): 1; ('a dark night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Montanus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Prisca', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Maximilla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quintilla', 'GPE'): 1; ('Quartilla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('125 riches contemptible', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('SAprobius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seeker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('211', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('165', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Septicollis', 'NORP'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plutarch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Spaniards', 'NORP'): 1; ('306', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('180', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simmagus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Siopelus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sophiarete', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sophron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('225', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sosandra', 'GPE'): 1; ('132', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Streblodespotes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sympathus', 'GPE'): 1; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Synaxis', 'GPE'): 1; ('taano', 'GPE'): 1; ('Takato', 'GPE'): 1; ('the spring of spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Synesius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Syrians', 'NORP'): 1; ('arabian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Fagius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('R. D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rad', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet ◊', 'ORG'): 1; ('Teraphim', 'ORG'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Laban', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aben Ezra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Michol', 'ORG'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gregorie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('H. more|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter 15', 'LAW'): 1; ('157', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tapanta', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jew', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tapeinophrosyne', 'ORG'): 1; ('192', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Temperanza', 'ORG'): 1; ('talismans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Terpsithea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pythagorean', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 3.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Irenaeum contra gnostico', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thanatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thelgomenus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theonoe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theophila', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theoprepia', 'ORG'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('Theosebius', 'GPE'): 1; ('201 Theostyges', 'PERCENT'): 1; ('Theromachia', 'GPE'): 1; ('176', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thrasymachus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Crates', 'GPE'): 1; ('Diog', 'GPE'): 1; ('Laert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timautus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trimalcio', 'GPE'): 1; ('Petronius Arbiter', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tuphlecon', 'ORG'): 1; ('122', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('VAghezza', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vanasembla', 'ORG'): 1; ('111', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Velleda', 'GPE'): 1; ('German', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tacitus Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('299', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Veneriola', 'GPE'): 1; ('274', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('340', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('XEnodochium', 'GPE'): 1; ('175', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A67662,5,scripture example drunkenness sin drunkenness sin Hos. heart God goodness,king: 0.45; drink: 0.45; man: 0.45; wine: 0.45; david: 0.45; drunkard: 0.45; sin: 0.4; benhadad: 0.35; servant: 0.3; take: 0.15; health: 0.15; drunkenness: 0.1; sam: 0.1; heart: 0.1; woe: 0.05; pavilion: 0.05; overcome: 0.05; poverty: 0.05; philistine: 0.05; peter: 0.05; peace: 0.05; prince: 0.05; noon: 0.05; odiousness: 0.05; proverb: 0.05; israel: 0.05; spoil: 0.05,"('David', 'PERSON'): 9; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Benhadad', 'GPE'): 6; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 4; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Zimri', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Tirzah', 'GPE'): 3; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4. 11', 'DATE'): 2; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20.', 'DATE'): 2; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Syrians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Mene', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Germani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('vera salute', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('23. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lemuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('5. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('early in the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24. 49', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('12. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('107', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('19 32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sam 30', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amnon', 'ORG'): 1; ('13. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Amnon', 'GPE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Uriah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Belshazzar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nabuchadnezzar', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sam 25', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nabal', 'ORG'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('30.', 'DATE'): 1; ('the evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('four hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Assiria', 'GPE'): 1; ('thirty two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('thirty and two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Elah king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('the twenty and six year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baasha', 'GPE'): 1; ('two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the twenty and seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the same hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Tekel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Upharsin', 'GPE'): 1"
A64002,10 | 13022,Seneca divine will divine operation tragedian term fate divine decree,god: 0.5; sin: 0.5; way: 0.5; man: 0.5; opinion: 0.5; divine: 0.5; author: 0.45; decree: 0.45; reason: 0.4; word: 0.3; absurdity: 0.2; nature: 0.1; necessity: 0.05; arminius: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 17; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Arminius', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('quae', 'GPE'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Iunius', 'ORG'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Arminius', 'ORG'): 3; ('Deus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Corona', 'GPE'): 2; ('Grevincovius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('mihi erat furari', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Crates', 'GPE'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Hague', 'GPE'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Junius', 'GPE'): 2; ('Moulin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 2; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tragedian', 'NORP'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('meae fecêrunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Venus', 'ORG'): 1; ('91', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quaeris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Quaeris ab illo', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pelagians', 'NORP'): 1; ('gratiam antecedi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fati', 'NORP'): 1; ('nuncupari', 'ORG'): 1; ('profanas quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed de verbis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Corusca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('unquam rependam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nexa', 'ORG'): 1; ('multis ipsum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nocet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Venere', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jocasta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec damnatio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('testibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Corona', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 12', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Seneca', 'FAC'): 1; ('Diogenes Laertius', 'ORG'): 1; ('deprehensum verberavit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysippus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cicero de fato', 'ORG'): 1; ('etiam videtur', 'ORG'): 1; ('Stilpo', 'GPE'): 1; ('vim egeris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('corpus quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('apud stilponem erit .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('malis , de affectibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('de actibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac de Officiis', 'ORG'): 1; ('de adhortationibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dehortationibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Diogenes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Austin de Civit', 'ORG'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam formidando', 'PERSON'): 1; ('subtraherent necessitati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etiam nostras voluntate', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam dicimus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel ita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nescio cur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('herein Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dort', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoad sententiarum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('doctrinae non pertinet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christiana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('holland', 'GPE'): 1; ('consideravit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Synodal', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('48', 'DATE'): 1; ('pari statu', 'ORG'): 1; ('maxima', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tenent', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('no less than four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('condito ceu', 'GPE'): 1; ('providentiae administrantis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gubernātis', 'NORP'): 1; ('vel proposito creandi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('homo praedestinationis objectum', 'ORG'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bonorū', 'GPE'): 1; ('naturaliū', 'ORG'): 1; ('administratio praedestinationis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ergo creatio prio est', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vindic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Grat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Praedestin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('de Civit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 12', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vorstius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arminians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Navarettus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dominican', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesuite', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi omnipotens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fieri', 'GPE'): 1; ('fiat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('statis peccati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('162', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Armin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('157', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A64002,10 | 13128,credit story whole Faustus relation honesty man church Austin doctrine,faustus: 0.5; god: 0.5; doctrine: 0.5; author: 0.5; cause: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; heresy: 0.45; reprobation: 0.45; vossius: 0.35; austin: 0.25; sin: 0.25; beza: 0.15; man: 0.1,"('Faustus', 'ORG'): 26; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 9; ('Lucidus', 'NORP'): 9; ('Vossius', 'ORG'): 7; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('pelagians', 'NORP'): 5; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Vossius', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Austin', 'GPE'): 3; ('Sigibert', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Tyro', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the council of Arles', 'ORG'): 2; ('Cataphronius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('huius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('grey hair', 'PERSON'): 2; ('about the year', 'DATE'): 2; ('850', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('predestinarian', 'NORP'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Alvarez', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Fulgentius , Petrus Diaconus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alchimus Avitus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('492', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Faustus ex Abbate Monasterii', 'ORG'): 1; ('conatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('errorem unde qui', 'ORG'): 1; ('catholicos', 'NORP'): 1; ('Germadius de Viris', 'ORG'): 1; ('ita enim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christianorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('Avitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('redarguens errorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joannes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Viris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fulgentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Catholicus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pelagianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('5ti', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Fulgentio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fausti de Grat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Liber', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arbitrio .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petrus Diaconus', 'ORG'): 1; ('libris Fausti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eutropius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Agricii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caesarius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leontius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eucherius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Florentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Galliani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joannis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Severi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Libelli', 'ORG'): 1; ('Concilii', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Synodus Lugdunensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Binnius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('duae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Biblioth', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sanct', 'GPE'): 1; ('Loentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('de Grat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('neutiquam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leontinum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Maxentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('proferendum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('conventibus exponendam', 'LOC'): 1; ('relegi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('meae relegi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paulus Episcopus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henricus Canisius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Manuscripto Codice', 'ORG'): 1; ('70', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('3d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leucippus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nazianzen', 'LOC'): 1; ('Praedestinatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arnobius', 'LOC'): 1; ('Praedestinatians', 'NORP'): 1; ('the day of', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hinemarus', 'GPE'): 1; ('lick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year 415', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sigibertus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Castro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haereses', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Sigibert', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bernard of Lutzenburg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('almost a thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('John Husse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dux', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gerardus Vossius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adrumetum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Historiá Godescalci', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adrumetine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Coccius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Adrumentum', 'FAC'): 1; ('Corvinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('some three year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Godescalcus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Haeresis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haeresis ab', 'ORG'): 1; ('augustino orta est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gennadius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustin', 'ORG'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pelag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Bono', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sigebertus', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quosdam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eos', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('elegendo praedestinavit', 'ORG'): 1; ('quosdam verò sic praedestinavit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gehennae', 'ORG'): 1; ('voluntati divinae subjicerent', 'ORG'): 1; ('vitam illis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sigebert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tenent', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2dò', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('1586', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacobus Andreas', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('375', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vide etiam Osiander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year 1611', 'DATE'): 1; ('holland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Westfrizland', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year 1618', 'DATE'): 1; ('1619', 'DATE'): 1; ('133', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nihil ad dicendum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 1; ('139. 23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('3. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('heresy', 'GPE'): 1; ('1200 year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('auxil', 'ORG'): 1; ('110', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('866', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dominicans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inn fine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Durand', 'ORG'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nullus meretur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('paenam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gandavensis , Scotus , Halensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vindiciae', 'GPE'): 1"
A64002,13 | 13708,discourse sect Iii exercise affair folly misery folly Nemo philosopher,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; mean: 0.5; decree: 0.5; thing: 0.5; author: 0.5; salvation: 0.5; end: 0.45; word: 0.25; paul: 0.2; grace: 0.2; ship: 0.15; determine: 0.15; power: 0.05; use: 0.05,"('Paul', 'PERSON'): 11; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Sisyphus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 2; ('Niniveh', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12. 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sisyphus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Domitian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Balaam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mortales ammos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ignaviam Instit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Heisterbachius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nulla bona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Josiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pontius Pilate', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mary day', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('17. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('grace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Regni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('this night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('the fourteenth day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ship', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('solliciti de vestitu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('two hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezechiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fifteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fig', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ionahs', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ion', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ninivites', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('1500 year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elizabeth day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('impostoribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Thess', 'PRODUCT'): 1"
A64002,23,man praise knave author perspicuity modesty part stile desire foppery,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; adversary: 0.5; author: 0.5; world: 0.5; work: 0.5; pleasure: 0.45; cause: 0.4; self: 0.3; reprobation: 0.3; grace: 0.25; decree: 0.15; condition: 0.1; damnation: 0.05,"('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John Norris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bradwardine Stiles', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('hord', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Raynold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fox', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Palestine', 'GPE'): 1; ('pelagians', 'NORP'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Achates', 'PRODUCT'): 1"
A64002,25 | 13953,Sect. m. mason addition p. D. Twis Vindiciae l. p.,man: 0.5; hell: 0.5; argument: 0.5; reason: 0.5; god: 0.5; misery: 0.5; author: 0.5; thing: 0.4; judas: 0.25; torment: 0.2; arminius: 0.15; place: 0.15; pain: 0.1; condition: 0.05; judgement: 0.05; answer: 0.05; scripture: 0.05; self: 0.05,"('Judas', 'PERSON'): 11; ('Austine', 'PERSON'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Arminius', 'ORG'): 6; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Arminius', 'PERSON'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('austin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Durandus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesuite', 'ORG'): 2; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Austin', 'GPE'): 2; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vindiciae', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('127', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Durandus', 'ORG'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ipsam veritatem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ricardus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Diagoras', 'GPE'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nimirum', 'NORP'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('D. Hoskins', 'ORG'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('19 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Aug. Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bon', 'GPE'): 1; ('160', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Whitgift', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Vulcan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('rationem', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Duns', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Penotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Franciscus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lychetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maldonat', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gabriel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('torment one hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('half a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('a quarter', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('half a minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('Sophocles', 'GPE'): 1"
A64002,25 | 13975,place author opinion Solomon be word Solomon Eccles. deprive oppress,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; damnation: 0.5; sin: 0.45; pain: 0.45; hell: 0.45; author: 0.4; grace: 0.4; condition: 0.35; solomon: 0.3; world: 0.25; thing: 0.2; turn: 0.1; evil: 0.1; christ: 0.05,"('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 13; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isaak', 'GPE'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 2; ('a hour', 'TIME'): 2; ('Austin', 'GPE'): 2; ('so many million', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phallaris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solomo Iarhi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('974', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rabbi Aben Ezra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('magnitudine', 'ORG'): 1; ('huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui persecutionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('patiuntur', 'GPE'): 1; ('justitiam maximè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('hydra est', 'GPE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('aut etiam nunquam fuisse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('judicio dolore corrupto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nostrorum nonnulli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quomodo', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('dicebat de Juda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('homini illi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Latines', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam ocyssime aboleri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('epigramma inquit nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cicero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tusculans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Iunius', 'ORG'): 1; ('ista', 'NORP'): 1; ('Solomon', 'GPE'): 1; ('fran•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('the m. mason adait', 'ORG'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l•e', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('recomp•nc• ◊ pain•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('•inch', 'ORG'): 1; ('good•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('••eth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('plutar•h', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Crowder', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a thousand degree', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('this very day', 'DATE'): 1; ('quod jubes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('ten thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Arminius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('103', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Martin Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Miseria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arminius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Manasses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Durand', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Durand', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mat 26', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D. Iackson', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gerardus Vossius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('harden', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pelagianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('2 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('13. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Palestine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Diagoras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Logicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paynims', 'NORP'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('libertas sine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed contumaciam :', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1"
A64002,51,knowledge quality habit produce power knowledge gain get way discourse,god: 0.45; thing: 0.45; foreknowledge: 0.45; knowledge: 0.45; perfection: 0.4; ascribe: 0.4; cap: 0.35; future: 0.35; suarez: 0.3; lib: 0.3; man: 0.25; argument: 0.2; attribute: 0.1; page: 0.05; ponuntar: 0.05; point: 0.05; preexistence: 0.05; prediction: 0.05; praevide: 0.05; praesente: 0.05; praesense: 0.05; praesens: 0.05; power: 0.05; posset: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Suarez', 'PERSON'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 5; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Twisse', 'GPE'): 3; ('Bradwardine', 'ORG'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('futura contingentia', 'PERSON'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('quam habet', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jackson', 'PERSON'): 2; ('314', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('D.', 'NORP'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('scientiam dei', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Analogum', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('contra', 'NORP'): 2; ('Rada', 'GPE'): 2; ('quando', 'PERSON'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('Cumel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('sva causâ', 'GPE'): 2; ('Dominicans', 'NORP'): 2; ('nam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Suarez Met', 'ORG'): 1; ('nullam imperfectionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('puram perfectionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam aliquà', 'PERSON'): 1; ('perfectionibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('cogitari altiorem modum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam formaliter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rationem', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec limitationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec imperfectionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('entis', 'NORP'): 1; ('quam ille', 'PERSON'): 1; ('alia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anselme', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Monolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('suo incompossibili', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nullam perfectionem creatam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('adaequatam rationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('convenientiam cum creaturâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seu conceptum', 'ORG'): 1; ('attribuitur', 'GPE'): 1; ('salvâ analogiâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae inter deum', 'ORG'): 1; ('quando vero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec formalis denominatio', 'ORG'): 1; ('convenientiam eminentialem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi vel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('recte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod de divinis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('altiorem', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui omnem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('imperfectionem creatutarum excludat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('D. Twisse', 'ORG'): 1; ('313', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('316', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de scientia', 'ORG'): 1; ('futurorum absolutè cap', 'ORG'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de analogo proportionis', 'ORG'): 1; ('vel metaphoram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cum de risu loquor', 'ORG'): 1; ('de risu hominis', 'ORG'): 1; ('non de risu prati', 'ORG'): 1; ('lib', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Civit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Armachanus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('402', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('403', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jeffery', 'NORP'): 1; ('Henry Savill', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bradwardin', 'GPE'): 1; ('many hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Schooleman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Occam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gordian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Deum', 'GPE'): 1; ('quot fecit prophet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('foreknowledge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('139', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jackson', 'GPE'): 1; ('existentiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arminianisme', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D. Jackson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('105', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('246', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam ignorare', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vera nesciret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('immutailis penitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('tertiam', 'NORP'): 1; ('ergo aeternalitèr', 'LOC'): 1; ('vera novit', 'FAC'): 1; ('Durand , Cumel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Durand', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Socratem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('alioquin ego cognoscerem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ignoraret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sequeretur quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('scientiae quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quando ponuntar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel homo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magis deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('augeri non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('confirmatur', 'GPE'): 1; ('aliquid de novo', 'ORG'): 1; ('velle', 'GPE'): 1; ('imperfectionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magis •• aliquid de novo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('artis', 'NORP'): 1; ('etiam ea quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('artificiara cognoscir', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•orm•', 'ORG'): 1; ('exteriorem materiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('artificiatorum constiturionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('unde nihil prohibet', 'ORG'): 1; ('scientia artificis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('formas quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil prohibet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('notitiam habere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Summ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('scientiam practicam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('futura couringentia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('artificiati', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam efficiat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deus qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam illa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rada', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Controv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('487', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('siet', 'NORP'): 1; ('218', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('224', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('producatur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Astrologo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ergo deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('propriam scientiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('priusquam praesens fiat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('praevide•', 'GPE'): 1; ('nulla nisi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('futura sunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('futura non veni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('potius quam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Par', 'ORG'): 1; ('controv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('trige', 'PERSON'): 1; ('493', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('enim quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('intu•tur', 'GPE'): 1; ('quandam exaggerationem locuti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('perfectionem scientiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('habet de futuris', 'ORG'): 1; ('nam', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ac si pra sentia', 'ORG'): 1; ('ideoq', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hoc ergo significandum dixerunt', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam scientiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae prasciuntur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non ita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vero deus ram', 'ORG'): 1; ('Quocirca', 'ORG'): 1; ('realem existentiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etiam praesentiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cogniti', 'GPE'): 1; ('D. Twisse de scientia', 'ORG'): 1; ('390', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Boetius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anselme', 'GPE'): 1; ('above 200 year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('futura', 'GPE'): 1; ('Austin', 'GPE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Becanus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustini', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('quam prasentia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('praesentiam perfectam nobis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quando futura est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deus semel', 'FAC'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregorius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theolog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 1.', 'PERSON'): 1"
A65264,2 | 14767,god word bread word word mystery difficulty doubt sort Roman,church: 0.45; general: 0.45; council: 0.45; thing: 0.45; word: 0.45; infallibility: 0.45; bishop: 0.35; god: 0.35; know: 0.3; error: 0.2; counsel: 0.2; representative: 0.15; doubt: 0.1; part: 0.05; page: 0.05; pen: 0.05; patience: 0.05; pastors: 0.05; party: 0.05; person: 0.05; opposite: 0.05; orthodox: 0.05; plenary: 0.05; decision: 0.05; scripture: 0.05; acception: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Mountagu', 'ORG'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 2; ('Chalcedon', 'GPE'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('it|be god', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Roman - catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Conf', 'GPE'): 1; ('192', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Q. Mary day', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cranmer', 'ORG'): 1; ('405', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('406', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trent', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Artic', 'ORG'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ely', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('fisher', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('146', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('147', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A65264,6 | 14861,sacrilege Christ institution command separation blood body christian soul right,church: 0.5; declaration: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; god: 0.5; time: 0.45; man: 0.45; self: 0.35; soul: 0.35; place: 0.25; people: 0.25; highness: 0.15; faith: 0.15; rest: 0.15; religion: 0.1; hand: 0.1; lay: 0.05; take: 0.05; protestant: 0.05; motive: 0.05; reason: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('R. H.', 'PERSON'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jones', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Maimburg', 'PERSON'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Modrevius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('cur ab Ecclesia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ecclesiae Reformatae', 'ORG'): 1; ('fuisse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apologet', 'ORG'): 1; ('87', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sanguinem redemti amarunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('81', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('jewel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alphonsus de Castro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Gerson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Harding', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apol', 'ORG'): 1; ('318', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bishop tailor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('469', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('D. Rivet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gerson', 'ORG'): 1; ('outdo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('a morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('23. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('crown', 'ORG'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('the eight of August , 1670', 'DATE'): 1; ('Epiphonema', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Luther , Calvin ,', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zuinglius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Realls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('above 400 year before', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five or six first century', 'DATE'): 1; ('English', 'NORP'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('generalibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paragraph', 'GPE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('qui fraudem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('injustam machinatur alteri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Suo ipse damno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Reserve', 'ORG'): 1; ('more than twice', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('P. Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cathedralls', 'LOC'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Andrew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mountagu', 'ORG'): 1; ('Taylor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bramhall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylonish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pervert', 'PERSON'): 1"
A66685,11,moderator oppression Moses Joseph court time restorer lose freedom creation,peace: 0.5; officer: 0.5; government: 0.35; law: 0.35; preservation: 0.35; freedom: 0.35; earth: 0.35; root: 0.3; commonwealth: 0.3; man: 0.3; overseer: 0.15; oppression: 0.15; peacce: 0.15; paul: 0.15; person: 0.15; original: 0.15; occasion: 0.15; place: 0.15; adam: 0.1; magistracy: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('spring', 'DATE'): 2; ('Moses', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('many year past', 'DATE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('England', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the half day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Samuels', 'ORG'): 1; ('1 Sam', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('therein Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35.', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1"
A64057,5 | 16183,resolve Quaest. Vet. N. queen opinion S. Austin case Nemo,saint: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; iames: 0.5; jerusalem: 0.5; paul: 0.5; lib: 0.5; apostle: 0.45; timothy: 0.45; church: 0.4; tim: 0.3; presbyter: 0.25; scripture: 0.05; cap: 0.05; lord: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 23; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 18; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 17; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 16; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 15; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 14; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 12; ('S. Iames', 'ORG'): 11; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 9; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 7; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 5; ('Jacobus', 'ORG'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 5; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 4; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 4; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 4; ('S. Austin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Apostolorum', 'ORG'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('S. Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('S.', 'ORG'): 3; ('Iacobo', 'ORG'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Hegesippus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Anicetus', 'ORG'): 2; ('caeteris', 'GPE'): 2; ('S. Irenaeus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Apostolus', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Theodoret', 'PERSON'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 2; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Episcopal', 'ORG'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Simeon', 'ORG'): 2; ('Anacletus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Catech', 'ORG'): 2; ('Apostolis', 'ORG'): 2; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 2; ('Hegesippus', 'GPE'): 2; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('S. Simeon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('S. Timothy', 'PERSON'): 2; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Quaest', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vet', 'GPE'): 1; ('N.', 'NORP'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ignorat', 'NORP'): 1; ('salvatorem ecclesiis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ipse enim priusquam in', 'PERSON'): 1; ('coelos ascenderet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apostolis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Episcopos', 'GPE'): 1; ('Euseb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Corinth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Soter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eleutherius', 'ORG'): 1; ('habebantur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Prophetae', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Sylvester', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prophetis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Patre', 'ORG'): 1; ('singulis ecclesiis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sacerd', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcopalis', 'ORG'): 1; ('nullis poterit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('comparationibus adaequari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangelicis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('B. Petrum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petre', 'GPE'): 1; ('Homil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Graec.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elders', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Miletus', 'ORG'): 1; ('spiritus s. posuit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hom', 'GPE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iohan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of Carthage', 'ORG'): 1; ('saint cyprian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Martinus Bracarensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Toledo', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. Sixtus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pentecost', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bede', 'NORP'): 1; ('lucam', 'GPE'): 1; ('presbyteris praelatione distincti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apostoli', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('veritati', 'ORG'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lactantius l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iames', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Silas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quosdam venisse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iudaeâ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ecclesiae Hierosolymitanae Jacobus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Stephen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Trall', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ordinarius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1600 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Clement', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Simeon Cleophae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('traditur apostolos qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('iacobum fratrem domini cui', 'ORG'): 1; ('APOSTOLIS', 'ORG'): 1; ('omnem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('malevolentiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Porrò', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hierosolymitarum', 'ORG'): 1; ('B. Jacobus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('secundùm carnem domini nuncupatus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petro', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iohanne Apostolis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('decret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Cyrill', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam de', 'PERSON'): 1; ('IACOBO', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('huius parochiae episcopum', 'ORG'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Crescon', 'ORG'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cathedra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anastasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ecclesiae Hierosolymitanae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Johannes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ierome', 'ORG'): 1; ('passionem domini statim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of cap', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trullo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gregorius Turonensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Simeon', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Cleophas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apostolos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('electus ab', 'ORG'): 1; ('Simeon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Timothy at Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('gratiam quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('impositionem manuum mearum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tychicus', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet .', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christianity', 'GPE'): 1; ('Suidas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Budaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deacon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laity', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('meek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Neophytes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Episcopo', 'GPE'): 1; ('collegio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'GPE'): 1; ('jus nisi', 'NORP'): 1; ('testimonio', 'GPE'): 1; ('Homer Iliad', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('aliquis accipiat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('probari qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Lucas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('actibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Timothei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephesi', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hunc', 'ORG'): 1; ('creatum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Contr', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marcion •', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('S.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tim. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Timoth', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pastor', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aërius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Apostoli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui erat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bassianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Stephanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leontius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Magnesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('titum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timothy be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcopum Asianorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timothy Biblioth ▪', 'ORG'): 1; ('254', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Photius', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. Ierome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('87', 'DATE'): 1; ('88', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isidore', 'ORG'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A64057,5 | 16411,saint Hierome Riparius Epist. Miror presbyter inutile fiat bishop move,bishop: 0.5; power: 0.5; church: 0.5; council: 0.5; thing: 0.5; case: 0.5; censure: 0.5; cause: 0.5; saint: 0.4; king: 0.15; canon: 0.15; faith: 0.1; christ: 0.1; emperor: 0.05; lib: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 16; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 7; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 5; ('Laity', 'ORG'): 4; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Palladius', 'GPE'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 3; ('Honoratus', 'ORG'): 3; ('the council of Aquileia', 'ORG'): 2; ('Milan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Basilius', 'ORG'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Triferius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Exuperantius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Episcopi', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Episcopo', 'GPE'): 2; ('the council of Chalcedon', 'ORG'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Nestorius', 'ORG'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 2; ('Episcopal', 'ORG'): 2; ('S. Matris Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 2; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 2; ('quando', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Constantius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Valentinian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Lampsacum', 'GPE'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Riparius', 'GPE'): 1; ('53', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vigilantius', 'ORG'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Palladius the Arian ▪', 'ORG'): 1; ('de laicis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laici', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Catholicus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ancyra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Galatia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theodoret Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('admonitionibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('cùm verò eum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('facinora praedicare', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of Taurinum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ann', 'PERSON'): 1; ('397', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('qui ad injuriam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('frequentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam causam ab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fuerat dominicâ communion', 'ORG'): 1; ('Triferio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Concilii', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('quando voluerit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('H.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Agatho', 'GPE'): 1; ('council of Carthage', 'ORG'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vel superbiâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sacrificia offerenda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel aliud', 'PERSON'): 1; ('erigendum altar contra', 'ORG'): 1; ('the Greeke Code', 'LAW'): 1; ('african', 'NORP'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Antioch', 'ORG'): 1; ('Carosus', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('318', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Balsamon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Metropolitans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pastoralis', 'NORP'): 1; ('dira contagia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ovibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('c•p', 'ORG'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mucro Episcopalis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint au•tin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tantummodò nobis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoniam doct•res', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apostoli', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('corripiantur', 'GPE'): 1; ('correptionibus de charitate venientibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('vel minoribus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('amplioribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Episcopale judicium', 'GPE'): 1; ('quâ poenâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ecclesiâ', 'GPE'): 1; ('correptionem saluberrimam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcopale', 'NORP'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paragraph', 'ORG'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ignatius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Materiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of', 'ORG'): 1; ('hostis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Herodes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be new', 'ORG'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pretiosae illi sint credita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clerus', 'ORG'): 1; ('finem religionis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aëtius the Arian', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aëtius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Macedonius ,', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eleusius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ortasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dracontius', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Ambros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('laicos de Episcopo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of Ariminum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aëtius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Suidas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leontius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tripoli', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lydia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bithynia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hellespont', 'GPE'): 1; ('Respondens Valentinianus', 'ORG'): 1; ('mihi quidem quum vnus de populo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mihi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam s. mater', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('suo acceperat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Auxentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theodoret lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian Subjects', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ruffinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philadelph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diaconi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clerus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('militibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('principibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caesare', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sacerd', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcopalis', 'NORP'): 1; ('comparationibus adaequari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('regum fulgori', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hominibus judicari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nicene', 'ORG'): 1"
A67746,12,CHAP. Viii prepare combat lord end prepare tribulation mariner calm,man: 0.45; enemy: 0.45; time: 0.45; god: 0.45; day: 0.4; know: 0.4; battle: 0.4; armour: 0.35; soldier: 0.35; persecution: 0.2; calm: 0.15; hypocrite: 0.1; assault: 0.1; believer: 0.1; quiet: 0.05; put: 0.05; report: 0.05; repair: 0.05; reason: 0.05; race: 0.05; resolution: 0.05; question: 0.05; prescribe: 0.05; prosperity: 0.05; set: 0.05; city: 0.05; hand: 0.05,"('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 2; ('summer', 'DATE'): 2; ('winter', 'DATE'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scipi•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pontus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amorites', 'ORG'): 1; ('Canaanite', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peresites', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hivites', 'GPE'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alfreds', 'PERSON'): 1; ('modò victor', 'ORG'): 1; ('bank•s', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('•ight', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Argente', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hazael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('pomecitron', 'ORG'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pilate', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Claudius Taurinensis', 'ORG'): 1"
A67746,25,CHAP. Xxi suffering counterpoise make blessing counterpoise make blessing Satan,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; conscience: 0.5; peace: 0.5; heaven: 0.5; joy: 0.4; heart: 0.4; world: 0.35; comfort: 0.3; soul: 0.25; another: 0.25; sin: 0.2; christ: 0.2; suffering: 0.15,"('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Anaxarchus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Xxi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('outward peace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Agrippa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Steven', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred fold', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nicocreon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cyprus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antiochus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Maryes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tully', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Roscius Amerinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Antisthenes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aptisthenes', 'ORG'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sidrack', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mishack', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abednego', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 ••r', 'MONEY'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52', 'DATE'): 1; ('abound•th', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('90', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('•ll', 'ORG'): 1; ('demosthe••s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israelites', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
