tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A58194,3,P. alderman Canterbury transcript passage write hand leaf bible passage,richard: 0.5; man: 0.5; king: 0.5; master: 0.5; reformation: 0.4; england: 0.4; canterbury: 0.35; cathedral: 0.35; day: 0.3; church: 0.3; law: 0.3; commissioner: 0.15; god: 0.1; alderman: 0.1; house: 0.1; minister: 0.05; culmer: 0.05; get: 0.05,"('Richard', 'PERSON'): 15; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 7; ('England', 'GPE'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('8 year', 'DATE'): 3; ('night', 'TIME'): 3; ('Richard Culmer', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7.5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Amaleck', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Scot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry Vane', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1643', 'DATE'): 1; ('tinker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hatter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Levites', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thomas Becket', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Magdalen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('Troy', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saturday', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ordain', 'PERSON'): 1; ('300', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oakes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cathedralls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Babylo•', 'ORG'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('sixty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('maul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('2 Chro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iraell', 'ORG'): 1; ('33.52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the king party', 'ORG'): 1; ('33.52.53', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.19.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Westm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aluuredi', 'ORG'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('falsi rumoris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fuisse deprehendetur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('poena non mulctator', 'ORG'): 1; ('Edgar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canuti', 'GPE'): 1; ('rumoribus dissipatis', 'ORG'): 1; ('quamobrem', 'GPE'): 1; ('damnum inferatura', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aut de fortunis imminuatur aliquid', 'ORG'): 1; ('Stat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ishmael', 'GPE'): 1; ('16.12', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Ierem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zipporah', 'NORP'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('the committee of England', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('non lucet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1"
A57545,11,thief scripture language thief thief name nature black white white,thief: 0.5; man: 0.5; hand: 0.5; life: 0.5; god: 0.5; good: 0.5; heart: 0.45; mat: 0.45; thing: 0.35; another: 0.25; time: 0.2; eye: 0.2; theft: 0.05; law: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('thievish', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 2; ('Simeon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('6.30', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12.7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('5.8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('5.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('the Canaanite , Iud', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('18.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27.38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('22.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('crescentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('lyra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mich. 2.2', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.28 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ablato', 'ORG'): 1; ('22.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.2 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('furis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zach', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 6.19 .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Divitias', 'NORP'): 1; ('13.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nebuchadnezer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Belshazzar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Acham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Job', 'ORG'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('49.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('four hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred thousand footman', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('nine thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vandal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Goth', 'ORG'): 1; ('one half penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Hilary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mich.', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('omnem vitam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iudg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.24', 'DATE'): 1; ('ravish matron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 13.19', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4 15 Luk', 'DATE'): 1; ('8.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Proteus', 'GPE'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nimrod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.8', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Mat 4.6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zacheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 4.9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canaanite', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('1.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 1; ('142.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nomina mille', 'ORG'): 1; ('mille', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mat 13.4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six thousand ,', 'DATE'): 1; ('elisha•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philip king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maced•n', 'ORG'): 1"
A57545,19,Samaritane Samaria city tribe build Omri chief seat kingdom kingdom,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; mercy: 0.5; enemy: 0.5; person: 0.5; king: 0.5; salvation: 0.4; saint: 0.4; rom: 0.2; thing: 0.2; name: 0.15; necessity: 0.1; mat: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 16; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('thou', 'GPE'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 8; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Samaritane', 'PERSON'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('David', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Assyria', 'GPE'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('20', 'DATE'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('11', 'DATE'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 3; ('ark', 'GPE'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 2; ('28', 'DATE'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'DATE'): 2; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('28.2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 2; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13.8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12.20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Chrys', 'ORG'): 2; ('Tom 2', 'PERSON'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.45', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12.14', 'DATE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 2; ('53.1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 2; ('Samaritane', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Omri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Salamansur the assyrian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('esur-haddon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Senacherib', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ezra 4.2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cuthah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ava', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hemath', 'GPE'): 1; ('17.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cuthah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mesopotamia', 'GPE'): 1; ('17.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bethel', 'ORG'): 1; ('26.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 4.25', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 8.42', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17 9 , 42 ,', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('51', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.53', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levite', 'LOC'): 1; ('Samaritan', 'LOC'): 1; ('17.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12 12.20', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mich.', 'GPE'): 1; ('19.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gibeah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Levite', 'FAC'): 1; ('19.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42.18', 'MONEY'): 1; ('1.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('111.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.12', 'MONEY'): 1; ('3.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.19', 'MONEY'): 1; ('10.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('24.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philemon 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 third', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ieremias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chaldeans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Anathoth', 'GPE'): 1; ('11.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Philistin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 Sam 27.3', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('29.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('fidelity', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aegypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('41.40', 'MONEY'): 1; ('17.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sarepta', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.12 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ireneus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. encage', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Camden', 'GPE'): 1; ('William', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'GPE'): 1; ('23.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('2.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('69.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nehe', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('cozen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jew', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henthen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('23.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 5.44 Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Atticus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calliopius the Nicene', 'ORG'): 1; ('Niceph lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Lazaro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam', 'NORP'): 1; ('Amb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Austine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('miseriae', 'ORG'): 1; ('nostro cord compassio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dei lib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heredotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('miseria', 'GPE'): 1; ('digna misericordiâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Lazàro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1350', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nazianz', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laert l. 8.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•u•anitati dan•an si non ipsi homini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca l. de benefi•tjs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tuum', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aug. e•ch .', 'DATE'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hea•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Syrians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dothan', 'GPE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philip king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Macedon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Archadius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nicanor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apol', 'ORG'): 1; ('reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nicanor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alphonsus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Aragon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 1; ('5 45', 'DATE'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('16.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('41.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 25.35', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ep', 'NORP'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lacon', 'GPE'): 1; ('nourish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Idler', 'ORG'): 1; ('lacaedemonian', 'NORP'): 1; ('tria committunt absurda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 nam', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bonos contumeliosi su•t', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deut', 'GPE'): 1; ('15.4', 'DATE'): 1; ('the christian magistrate', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('some one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('kinsman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Samaritanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('significa tur hoc nomine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. qua', 'DATE'): 1; ('evang l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hypog', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.21', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('68', 'DATE'): 1; ('69', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 4.1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samaritane', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Melancthon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aretius', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 6.27', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('15.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('17.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('actual•y', 'NORP'): 1; ('John 3.16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levite', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sink', 'PERSON'): 1; ('infaelix ego', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mart', 'GPE'): 1; ('Epig', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cicero Hortensius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi legam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iosephs', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('John point', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ecce aguus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 5.40', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gideon', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.74', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samaritan', 'FAC'): 1; ('4.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A59937,5 | 4501,Babylon ruin raise Zion Antichrist destruction Christ say exaltation world,glory: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; light: 0.5; angel: 0.4; scripture: 0.35; principle: 0.35; rev: 0.3; lord: 0.3; saint: 0.3; time: 0.2; sir: 0.1; earth: 0.05; cause: 0.05; judge: 0.05; quakers: 0.05,"('Quakers', 'ORG'): 4; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one day', 'DATE'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('William Penn', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.5 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('bless•d', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isangeloi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven day', 'DATE'): 1; ('30.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('60.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 14', 'DATE'): 1; ('the thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('21 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('W. l', 'PERSON'): 1; ('N. L.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('W. L.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('W. R.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tuum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoniam contra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cicero Orat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('L. Q. p.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cornhil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1674', 'DATE'): 1; ('W. l confession', 'GPE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A57953,3,pagan principle opinion Quakers light man light man enlighten God,part: 0.5; god: 0.45; soul: 0.45; man: 0.45; make: 0.45; time: 0.45; word: 0.45; spirit: 0.4; beginning: 0.4; opinion: 0.25; pagan: 0.1; quakers: 0.1; heathen: 0.05; hudibras: 0.05; question: 0.05; place: 0.05; poet: 0.05; page: 0.05; pain: 0.05; party: 0.05; pass: 0.05; person: 0.05; philosopher: 0.05,"('W. L.', 'PERSON'): 10; ('W. P.', 'PERSON'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('T. H.', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Quaker', 'ORG'): 3; ('Hudibras', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('pagan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Quakers', 'ORG'): 2; ('57 16', 'DATE'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Geo', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('reader', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam deum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam in', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Divini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('reader thou', 'PERSON'): 1; ('November 11. 1662', 'DATE'): 1; ('267', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('W. P.', 'GPE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hudibras', 'LOC'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adam', 'GPE'): 1; ('2', 'MONEY'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simonides', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1"
A52464,16 | 11369,be satisfaction self design applause duty sovereign desert resentment rebel,charity: 0.5; god: 0.5; saint: 0.5; self: 0.5; law: 0.5; neighbour: 0.45; church: 0.4; thing: 0.4; paris: 0.3; practise: 0.3; subject: 0.25; piety: 0.2; pastors: 0.05; life: 0.05; duty: 0.05; whole: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 6; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 4; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Thomas Carre', 'PERSON'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('they|will', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vincent', 'GPE'): 1; ('lxvi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('W. D.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the catholic roman church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Noe S.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Bap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra dona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hon S. July 20', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1666', 'DATE'): 1; ('thirty three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('one half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('article ii', 'LAW'): 1; ('Sorbonne', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('Artes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sorbon', 'LOC'): 1; ('vincents', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam effundere', 'PERSON'): 1"
A56404,2,inop bereave wit print practice credit water fable undesert pursue,say: 0.45; circumcision: 0.45; baptism: 0.45; lord: 0.45; life: 0.45; sin: 0.45; god: 0.35; innocent: 0.35; word: 0.3; kingdom: 0.25; heaven: 0.1; circumcise: 0.1; heart: 0.1; state: 0.1; thing: 0.1; mystery: 0.05; people: 0.05; person: 0.05; opposition: 0.05; ordain: 0.05; order: 0.05; ordinance: 0.05; parker: 0.05; pass: 0.05; pattern: 0.05; paul: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('quis nisi', 'ORG'): 1; ('mentis inop', 'ORG'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('sva practica scribit', 'FAC'): 1; ('quae venit', 'ORG'): 1; ('paena dolenda', 'ORG'): 1; ('William Parker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Exitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('bliss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 3.16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 1.3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('59.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.21.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('21.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israelites', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Gen.', 'ORG'): 1; ('17.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arius Montanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('3.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('7.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1"
A56404,3 | 12049,saviour apostle prophet Matt. martyr Christ apostle letter letter intend,say: 0.5; foot: 0.5; saviour: 0.5; letter: 0.5; baptism: 0.45; water: 0.45; mystery: 0.4; christ: 0.35; thing: 0.35; scripture: 0.25; lord: 0.25; sin: 0.2; ceremony: 0.15; god: 0.15,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 10; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 8; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11.29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hosea', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nine and thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19.20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('28.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.8 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mille', 'ORG'): 1; ('19.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hagar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fall•n', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jerem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Armenians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Charles the I.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('doctori cum culpa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 16.12', 'PERSON'): 1; ('snarl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tatt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('12.24.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Charles the I. be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 7.17', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 14.23', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 13.5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('13.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this eighteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paschal', 'ORG'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('7.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter , Ver', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('53.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27.60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Corin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 9.40', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Publicans', 'NORP'): 1; ('8.38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('relinquimus disquiri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 Corin', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('16.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('15.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Galathian', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Galathian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.40', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A52303,35,lord light salvation lord strength life experience verse experience find,part: 0.5; lord: 0.3; prayer: 0.3; god: 0.3; face: 0.3; heart: 0.3; enemy: 0.3; thing: 0.25; life: 0.2; plot: 0.2; praise: 0.2; patience: 0.2; pavilion: 0.2; peace: 0.2; perjure: 0.2; persecution: 0.2; persuade: 0.2; place: 0.2; man: 0.2; experience: 0.1; tabernacle: 0.1; time: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 11; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the next two', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('destitu•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xxviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. to', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. to 9 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A52303,41,consideration Epiphonema bless nation god lord people people bless God,people: 0.5; god: 0.4; lord: 0.4; mercy: 0.4; man: 0.4; heart: 0.4; strength: 0.35; earth: 0.35; hope: 0.3; word: 0.3; help: 0.2; preparation: 0.1; proof: 0.1; place: 0.1; pleasure: 0.1; plot: 0.1; power: 0.1; praise: 0.1; prayer: 0.1; oul: 0.1; name: 0.05; providence: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 15; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('earth', 'LOC'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Epiphonema', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirty three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'NORP'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xxxiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('1. to', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•oul', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A52303,72,God God God God find morning light time banish force,god: 0.4; tongue: 0.4; secret: 0.4; heart: 0.4; counsel: 0.4; punishment: 0.4; man: 0.25; enemy: 0.25; fear: 0.25; arrow: 0.25; iniquity: 0.2; life: 0.2; prayer: 0.2; protection: 0.1; psal: 0.1; persuasion: 0.1; place: 0.1; power: 0.1; practise: 0.1; presence: 0.1; prey: 0.1; protect: 0.1; part: 0.05; mischief: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 13; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the morning light', 'TIME'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('night-season', 'DATE'): 1; ('lxiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. to 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('i .', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Digitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('sixty four', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A52303,98,confidence reliance God lord God salvation earnestness cry assiduity day,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; life: 0.5; prayer: 0.5; grave: 0.5; trouble: 0.5; lord: 0.45; wave: 0.45; soul: 0.35; friend: 0.25; darkness: 0.15; hand: 0.15; wrath: 0.1; afflict: 0.05; terror: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 18; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('daily', 'DATE'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three degree', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Moribundus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. yea', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeremiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('assidun', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('frailty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('Simul', 'GPE'): 1; ('7. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tempora cum fiunt nubila', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eighty eight', 'DATE'): 1; ('i , day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1"
A52303,99,PSAL. psalm prophet God goodness faithfulness covenant David seed stability,god: 0.5; mercy: 0.5; covenant: 0.5; david: 0.5; seed: 0.5; lord: 0.45; heaven: 0.45; kingdom: 0.4; part: 0.35; enemy: 0.25; truth: 0.2; man: 0.2; throne: 0.1; make: 0.1,"('thou', 'GPE'): 33; ('David', 'PERSON'): 28; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 16; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 15; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('the day', 'DATE'): 5; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('David', 'GPE'): 3; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 2; ('Epiphonema', 'PERSON'): 2; ('justice', 'ORG'): 2; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christ kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('15.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 to 28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prosopopeia', 'ORG'): 1; ('2 Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.11', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('Hermon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('west shall', 'GPE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('clangor regis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euphrates', 'ORG'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('new moon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pasch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Resp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Verbera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('his year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jehoiakim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 1; ('Benedictus', 'ORG'): 1; ('eighty nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Belial', 'ORG'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hebrves', 'ORG'): 1"
A52303,102,part verse part assurance God protection nonlatinalphabet proposition contain promise,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; way: 0.5; evil: 0.5; promise: 0.5; secret: 0.5; life: 0.5; angel: 0.45; prophet: 0.4; lord: 0.3; love: 0.2; hand: 0.05; foot: 0.05; place: 0.05,"('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 15; ('thou', 'GPE'): 15; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('noonday', 'DATE'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 2; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Dathan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Abiram', 'ORG'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ithlonan', 'GPE'): 1; ('refrigerio', 'GPE'): 1; ('Shaddai', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.1', 'MONEY'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Egyptians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chasak', 'NORP'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1"
A52303,103,PSAL. psalm song sabbath-day nonlatinalphabet title psalm end compose viz.,work: 0.5; lord: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; time: 0.45; end: 0.4; world: 0.4; enemy: 0.4; faithfulness: 0.35; power: 0.25; church: 0.15; heart: 0.15; horn: 0.1; lovingkindness: 0.1; tree: 0.05; cedar: 0.05; spirit: 0.05; fool: 0.05; creation: 0.05,"('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('thou', 'GPE'): 11; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lebanon', 'GPE'): 2; ('xcii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; (', morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Expleri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tuendo', 'GPE'): 1; ('a night', 'TIME'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('10 , 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nititur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1"
A52303,107,PSAL. nonlatinalphabet psalm compose David bring ark Chr. voice christian,god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; king: 0.5; earth: 0.5; world: 0.5; fear: 0.45; glory: 0.45; honour: 0.4; heaven: 0.4; man: 0.25; praise: 0.15; kingdom: 0.15; name: 0.1; heathen: 0.05; christ: 0.05; beauty: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('thou', 'GPE'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Christ kingdom', 'GPE'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Elilim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('earth', 'LOC'): 2; ('Hosannah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 2; ('16.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cantando', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangelium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Judaea', 'NORP'): 1; ('from day to day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Moller', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Muscul', 'ORG'): 1; ('supreme', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('god', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deiculi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('assyrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('thirty thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Neptune', 'ORG'): 1; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nebo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('46.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('8. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('facti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orbs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alms', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Regnat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'NORP'): 1; ('Judaea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 to 22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1"
A52303,119,PSAL. nonlatinalphabet title psalm Allelujah set praise God oppress misery,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; work: 0.5; mercy: 0.45; heart: 0.45; land: 0.4; goodness: 0.35; way: 0.35; soul: 0.3; misery: 0.3; death: 0.1; word: 0.1; course: 0.1; trouble: 0.05; prophet: 0.05,"('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 32; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 24; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 20; ('thou', 'GPE'): 20; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 13; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 3; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('egeni', 'NORP'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Aegypt', 'GPE'): 2; ('ten acre', 'QUANTITY'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ephah', 'GPE'): 2; ('3. to 9 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('8.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.16', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('exul', 'NORP'): 1; ('Deos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('casibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('pilgrim', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eliah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baal priest', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('fig', 'ORG'): 1; ('Wisd', 'ORG'): 1; ('16.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('incutit vim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fluctus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aeneae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tres curus ab alto', 'ORG'): 1; ('Brevia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Syrtes', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('meminisse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Denegat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jonah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jonah 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dicto cirius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aequora placat', 'GPE'): 1; ('magno telluris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egressi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nazianzen', 'LOC'): 1; ('maris Deo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Epicurus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Pallio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nilus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sodom , Gomorrah', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cyclops in Euripides', 'ORG'): 1; ('spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epiphonema', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one hundred and seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1"
A52303,120,PSAL. nonlatinalphabet Psalm whole compose draw psalm part verse take,prayer: 0.4; god: 0.4; judas: 0.4; christ: 0.4; jew: 0.35; man: 0.35; word: 0.35; malice: 0.3; psalm: 0.25; part: 0.2; heart: 0.15; mouth: 0.15; hatred: 0.15; praise: 0.1; peccator: 0.1; people: 0.1; persecutor: 0.1; person: 0.1; peter: 0.1; place: 0.1; point: 0.1; power: 0.1; imprecation: 0.1; enemy: 0.1; satan: 0.05,"('Judas', 'PERSON'): 9; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 7; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 3; ('6th', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('cviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the 57th', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Doeg', 'GPE'): 1; ('Achitophel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'GPE'): 1; ('6. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. to', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30 , 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('meae', 'ORG'): 1; ('deus laudabilis mihi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('domine laudem meam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('John 17.5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('impiety', 'ORG'): 1; ('deceit', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Belzebub', 'ORG'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 15', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theognis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christ', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A52303,126,premise psalm describe condition Jew deliverance Aegypt say bondage idolator,god: 0.45; sea: 0.45; lord: 0.45; sanctuary: 0.45; mountain: 0.45; heart: 0.35; presence: 0.35; water: 0.35; people: 0.35; jordan: 0.3; deliverance: 0.25; part: 0.1; aegypt: 0.1; psalm: 0.1; piety: 0.05; pharaoh: 0.05; power: 0.05; policy: 0.05; point: 0.05; pleasure: 0.05; prayer: 0.05; pass: 0.05; premise: 0.05; spirit: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('Jordan', 'GPE'): 3; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 2; ('jordan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Sinai', 'ORG'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('Aegypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 8.7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seasaw', 'FAC'): 1; ('all night', 'TIME'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jordan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Wisd', 'ORG'): 1; ('19.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Prosopopeia', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one hundred and fourteenth', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('wherein thou', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canaan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. to 9 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. to 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1"
A52303,127,leader nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet name praise reason name glory whole self,lord: 0.45; god: 0.45; earth: 0.45; blessing: 0.45; idol: 0.45; heaven: 0.45; man: 0.45; part: 0.35; name: 0.35; end: 0.35; people: 0.2; portion: 0.05; pleasure: 0.05; praise: 0.05; power: 0.05; posterity: 0.05; possession: 0.05; presence: 0.05; priesthood: 0.05; nation: 0.05; mercy: 0.05; truth: 0.05; dew: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 12; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 7; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('God .', 'DATE'): 1; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Naaman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deutr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27.28', 'MONEY'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('one hundred and fifteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou lord', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1"
A52303,131,PSAL. nonlatinalphabet psalm rest use happiness obtain wit keep God,god: 0.5; way: 0.5; word: 0.5; man: 0.5; heart: 0.5; law: 0.5; grace: 0.5; commandment: 0.45; lord: 0.3; statute: 0.3; david: 0.25; testimony: 0.1; obedience: 0.05; impediment: 0.05,"('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 18; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 17; ('thou', 'GPE'): 15; ('David', 'PERSON'): 13; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Aleph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('beth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('outward', 'PERSON'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('122', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten .', 'DATE'): 1; ('Torah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ALEPH', 'ORG'): 1; ('4. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('domine da quod jubes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('overlong', 'GPE'): 1; ('mount Sinai', 'GPE'): 1; ('Beth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('all the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('vail', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abner', 'ORG'): 1; ('Achitophel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Doeg', 'GPE'): 1"
A52303,150,part psalm exhortation God goodness majesty encage declaration goodness majesty,people: 0.4; pleasure: 0.25; praise: 0.25; orb: 0.25; order: 0.25; palace: 0.25; part: 0.25; pharaoh: 0.25; philistines: 0.25; place: 0.25; mercy: 0.25; god: 0.25; thank: 0.25; heaven: 0.25; work: 0.25; earth: 0.25; lord: 0.25; israel: 0.2; prophet: 0.2; creature: 0.1; enemy: 0.05; food: 0.05,"('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('the night', 'TIME'): 2; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 2; ('Ver', 'GPE'): 2; ('4. to 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. to 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Musculus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Ʋersicle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Moller', 'PERSON'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sihon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Amorites', 'NORP'): 1; ('Og', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bashan', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Canaan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('babylonian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gideon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cyrus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('135.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one hundred and thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A52303,158,Psalm ode David psalm mix kind contain thanksgiving prayer doctrine,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; people: 0.5; lord: 0.5; david: 0.5; son: 0.5; hand: 0.5; thing: 0.5; blessing: 0.3; psalm: 0.2; plant: 0.2; strength: 0.1; part: 0.1; enemy: 0.05; vanity: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 13; ('David', 'PERSON'): 11; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('Goliath', 'PERSON'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Incrementum', 'ORG'): 1; ('18.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sam 18.5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hebron', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sam 7.18', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Benedictus', 'ORG'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('domus tota', 'PERSON'): 1; ('assidui domini lccuples', 'PERSON'): 1; ('abundat haedo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Referta', 'NORP'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epiphonema', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. yea', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one hundred and forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('amaze', 'PERSON'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('shéepco•e', 'GPE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('polish', 'NORP'): 1; ('h••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1"
A52303,159,PSAL. Hallelujah hymn hymn matter pen manner matter god praise,god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; king: 0.5; kingdom: 0.5; work: 0.5; man: 0.45; praise: 0.45; mercy: 0.45; glory: 0.35; christ: 0.35; verse: 0.25; power: 0.15; thing: 0.05,"('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('thou', 'GPE'): 12; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('David', 'PERSON'): 6; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('season', 'DATE'): 3; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('6. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thy saint shall bless', 'ORG'): 2; ('thirteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('Alpha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Omega', 'PERSON'): 1; ('proem', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Noah', 'GPE'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('Corah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abiram', 'ORG'): 1; ('vulgar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the season of the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('103.8 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.4.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('arabic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Kimhi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Moller', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nun', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pastoralis', 'NORP'): 1; ('David', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('65.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God .', 'DATE'): 1; ('justice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('licet non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Superbos', 'GPE'): 1; ('nec deseruit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epiphonema', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one hundred and forty five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1"
A52993,13,bishop church power ordination minister consent presbyter Chrys. Hom. Tim.,church: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; presbyter: 0.5; people: 0.5; peace: 0.5; act: 0.5; consent: 0.5; hand: 0.5; minister: 0.45; person: 0.25; ordination: 0.1; cor: 0.1; apostle: 0.05; imposition: 0.05,"('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('5.22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('111', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Chrys', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hieron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ep', 'NORP'): 1; ('4.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Autiochia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Concilio', 'ORG'): 1; ('clericos non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the four council of Carthage', 'ORG'): 1; ('Firmilianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Caesarea Cappadocia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Askelon', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Th', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Presbyters', 'ORG'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('diebus nostris', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('kind reader', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('conventy', 'ORG'): 1; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('85', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('87', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36 ,', 'DATE'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.7 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('103', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet r', 'ORG'): 1; ('but a. p. 115.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('118', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('121', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('169', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('172', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('195', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('214', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A58032,1,hue cry conscience sinner alarm conscience order discovery hide gild,conscience: 0.35; day: 0.35; sin: 0.35; gild: 0.35; god: 0.35; soul: 0.35; reader: 0.35; evil: 0.35; hand: 0.15; sinner: 0.15; pray: 0.15; pollution: 0.15; prize: 0.15; print: 0.15; presence: 0.15; prayer: 0.15; providential: 0.15; post: 0.15; paul: 0.15; perplex: 0.15; hell: 0.15; blood: 0.15; truth: 0.1,"('thou', 'GPE'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jane', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('90.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Ryther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('J. D. for', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John white', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Minory', 'GPE'): 1; ('1680', 'DATE'): 1; ('the present day', 'DATE'): 1; ('noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('the clear day', 'DATE'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the ministry of the word', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('another day', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joseph be brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Paschal', 'ORG'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Professon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.2 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pashur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Agrippina', 'GPE'): 1; ('nor night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bosworth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Morgan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('unseen pollution spring', 'DATE'): 1"
A56361,94,CHAP. Xxiv word Easie expound have occasion word text word,christ: 0.5; god: 0.5; word: 0.5; sense: 0.5; easie: 0.5; chastisement: 0.5; hebrew: 0.45; sin: 0.45; wound: 0.3; obedience: 0.25; mr: 0.15; suffering: 0.1; say: 0.1; job: 0.1; peace: 0.05; fear: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 18; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 16; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 10; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('53. 5', 'DATE'): 7; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 7; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Annot', 'ORG'): 7; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 7; ('Norton', 'ORG'): 7; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 5; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('53.', 'DATE'): 4; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 4; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Chalal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('24', 'DATE'): 3; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('38', 'DATE'): 3; ('178', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 2; ('39 1', 'DATE'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 2; ('51.', 'DATE'): 2; ('17', 'DATE'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 2; ('37', 'DATE'): 2; ('9 4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('Lev', 'GPE'): 2; ('Eze. 7', 'DATE'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Daca', 'PERSON'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ver', 'GPE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('164', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('Job 15. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('Deut', 'GPE'): 1; ('2. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Job 26', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 2', 'LAW'): 1; ('15. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 40', 'DATE'): 1; ('j•r', 'PERSON'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Carlile', 'PERSON'): 1; ('166', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('167', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('107', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('61. 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 10. 18.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eze. 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('109', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Easie 43.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Easie 47', 'DATE'): 1; ('44. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('23. 40', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 16 , 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('31.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Exod', 'GPE'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22 26', 'DATE'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('10 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Odium', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('89', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Kircherus', 'ORG'): 1; ('greek Lexicon', 'ORG'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hebrews', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bilson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gen. 3. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('no•ton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('94.', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psalm 51', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34. 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('162', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Belzchu•', 'ORG'): 1; ('5th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17. 18 , 19', 'DATE'): 1; ('26.', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Easie 26', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('78.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abimclech', 'ORG'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ainsworth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Confes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('121', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('165', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('193', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('275', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('461', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('woodbridge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cledon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Justifica', 'GPE'): 1; ('Repl', 'ORG'): 1; ('18. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jonah', 'GPE'): 1; ('P.', 'NORP'): 1; ('364', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('169', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('266', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('311', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('375', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('No•ton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('p•g', 'ORG'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('69.', 'DATE'): 1; ('h•m', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zach', 'GPE'): 1; ('13 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('26. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('heb 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paideia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('50. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Exo', 'LOC'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('93', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('171', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Wilson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43.', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hil•o•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eph', 'GPE'): 1; ('2 14', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('66.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('159', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('marty•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('m•tth .', 'DATE'): 1; ('inf•r•••m', 'ORG'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Parad', 'GPE'): 1; ('un', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam', 'NORP'): 1; ('Norton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('their day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Arian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pilate', 'ORG'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('19 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('•n•th•r', 'PERSON'): 1"
A52246,5,man animate hope matter faith obligation duty allegiance prince ʋsurper,church: 0.5; commin: 0.5; queen: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; majesty: 0.5; people: 0.5; prayer: 0.5; england: 0.45; council: 0.4; papist: 0.25; man: 0.1; pope: 0.1; protestant: 0.1; day: 0.05; god: 0.05,"('England', 'GPE'): 17; ('Commin', 'ORG'): 15; ('Commin', 'PERSON'): 14; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Dominican', 'NORP'): 4; ('F. C.', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 3; ('London', 'GPE'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Puritan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 2; ('John Clerkson', 'PERSON'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('L. A. B.', 'PERSON'): 2; ('L. A. B. do', 'PERSON'): 2; ('A. B.', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Omers Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Quakers', 'ORG'): 1; ('Parag', 'GPE'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gavan the Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('proselyte people', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2d', 'DATE'): 1; ('Avatice', 'LOC'): 1; ('envenom arrow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James wear', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nonconformists', 'ORG'): 1; ('Robert wear', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Esq', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year 1567', 'DATE'): 1; ('the nine year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eliz', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dominick', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicholas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('marry dean', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Monday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matthew Parker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('L.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the holy catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('about a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('J. Clerkson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('J. C. first', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('draper', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Maidstone', 'GPE'): 1; ('groan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('draper maid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mary dean', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about two hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('about ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Richard Bland', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mothersside', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('the 12th . day of April', 'DATE'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('April 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bland', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Commin be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('some month', 'DATE'): 1; ('the fourteenth of September', 'DATE'): 1; ('John baker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Portsmouth', 'GPE'): 1; ('Amsterdam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Martin van Daval', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('2000', 'DATE'): 1; ('baker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('every Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('twelve penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('English', 'NORP'): 1; ('Licenses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1"
A50740,2,parliament time man evil king authority dignity government contrary apostle,porridge: 0.5; prayer: 0.5; pottage: 0.5; herb: 0.4; god: 0.4; soul: 0.4; lord: 0.35; meat: 0.35; man: 0.3; people: 0.25; body: 0.2; pottag: 0.1; power: 0.1; precept: 0.1; pot: 0.1; pity: 0.1; place: 0.1; priest: 0.1; world: 0.05; heart: 0.05; flesh: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pottag', 'GPE'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Kitching', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('today', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('abbacuc', 'ORG'): 1; ('our day', 'DATE'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1"
A56588,5,fault escape page line marge Serm. p. l. marge nonlatinalphabet,god: 0.45; thing: 0.45; miracle: 0.45; substance: 0.45; host: 0.4; body: 0.35; wine: 0.3; consecrate: 0.3; eucharist: 0.25; father: 0.25; whole: 0.25; christ: 0.25; bread: 0.2; nature: 0.1; partaker: 0.05; parochos: 0.05; paten: 0.05; passion: 0.05; particular: 0.05; pererius: 0.05; part: 0.05; order: 0.05; origen: 0.05; person: 0.05; sacrament: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 6; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nourish', 'NORP'): 2; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 2; ('fault escape', 'ORG'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('53', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('149', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('152', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evagrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('171', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('the Trent council', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trent', 'LOC'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the Jesuite Pererius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Joan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('48', 'DATE'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('as many divine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('apollinarians', 'NORP'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Contr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('praesumptionibus', 'NORP'): 1; ('nostris', 'GPE'): 1; ('hâc sententiâ', 'ORG'): 1; ('quidvis de deo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etiam quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nyssen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hexaemeron', 'GPE'): 1; ('assert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexandria Stromat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('finem', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet .', 'GPE'): 1; ('Origen L. 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('Jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. Ambrose de iis qui initiantur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('superveniens spiritus s.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('conceptionem operatus est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('P. Leo Mag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('aquae', 'ORG'): 1; ('s. quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maria pareret salvatorem', 'PERSON'): 1"
A56588,9,another book Lib. cap Angelo Angelus thing assume matter assume,species: 0.35; wine: 0.35; body: 0.35; bread: 0.35; nature: 0.35; thing: 0.35; christ: 0.35; lib: 0.35; cap: 0.35; word: 0.3; port: 0.15; plain: 0.15; priest: 0.15; prater: 0.15; potuit: 0.15; prove: 0.15; point: 0.15; photium: 0.15; phrase: 0.15; quality: 0.15; church: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 10; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('paris', 'GPE'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 3; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('230', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cod', 'PERSON'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cùm autem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Angelo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('specie quae', 'FAC'): 1; ('Gaudentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('etiam vini specie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vitis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('satis', 'NORP'): 1; ('sanguinem suum esse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('Succurrit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('administrans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sedulius Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('operis Paschal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('munera regi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thura', 'ORG'): 1; ('Myrrham', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sepulchro', 'GPE'): 1; ('myrrh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Gub', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baluz', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Walafridus Strabo de rebus Eccles.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('corporis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sacramenta', 'GPE'): 1; ('nihil ergo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('speciebus', 'ORG'): 1; ('significandam capitis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abbas de Offic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nihil de Sacrificio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salmasius Simplicius Verinus de Transubst', 'ORG'): 1; ('the theodosian Code', 'LAW'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('only two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dionysius the Areopagite Eccles', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet .', 'GPE'): 1; ('Marc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bertram Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Corp.', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sang', 'GPE'): 1; ('substantiam .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Modes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmine de eucharist', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Trent say Sess', 'ORG'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('integer sub', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian de resurrect', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam — quod videtur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod tenetur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phatium Cod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('234', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eustathius Antioch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Engastrimytho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Didymus Caten', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nazianzen Orat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nyssen de Opific', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Austin de Verb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('domini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ser', 'ORG'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quidem divinitate nobiscum est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed nisi corporaliter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephrem Antioch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Photium', 'ORG'): 1; ('229', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('valentinians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Eulogius Ibid', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vigilius Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('necesse erit', 'PERSON'): 1"
A54576,23 | 25052,Fulbert bishop charty man sermon treatise work saint Augustine say,body: 0.5; christ: 0.5; berengarius: 0.5; blood: 0.5; bread: 0.5; man: 0.5; flesh: 0.4; sacrament: 0.4; heaven: 0.35; doctrine: 0.2; bishop: 0.2; soul: 0.2; word: 0.15; thing: 0.1,"('Berengarius', 'NORP'): 17; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 7; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('France', 'GPE'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('Adelman', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Iohan', 'GPE'): 3; ('Guitmund', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 2; ('Fulbert', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Io', 'LOC'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Lanfrank', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1059', 'DATE'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 2; ('Usser', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('albeit outward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Biblioth', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Maurice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Angiers', 'GPE'): 1; ('Archiepisc', 'GPE'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Normandy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Capernaitis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Brixia', 'GPE'): 1; ('howbeit', 'GPE'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Scotus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('oecolampad', 'PERSON'): 1; ('154', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Basil', 'ORG'): 1; ('1536', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bellarm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('book de Pon', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('the council of vanity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pontificem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('episcopum', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sed pompificem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rheims', 'NORP'): 1; ('Leo ix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Verceles', 'GPE'): 1; ('200.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aversa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1056', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hildebrand', 'LOC'): 1; ('pope Nicolaus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sigon', 'LOC'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Leo Ostien', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chron', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cassin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pa. Masson', 'FAC'): 1; ('Franco', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Humbert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gratian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Berengarius', 'LOC'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Semeca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('speciebus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lombard li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmin', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nicolaus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one hundred and fourteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Blondus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1079', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bercold', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constance', 'GPE'): 1; ('1083', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ja', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cosina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hildebert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Guil', 'LOC'): 1; ('Malmesbu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Gest', 'PERSON'): 1; ('modò miratur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quem sacrae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quinta', 'GPE'): 1; ('quâ gloria cleri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rvit', 'GPE'): 1; ('procor', 'ORG'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('platina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('1087', 'DATE'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sigebert Gemblac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antwerp', 'GPE'): 1; ('1608', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vsser de eccle', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1589', 'DATE'): 1; ('Thuan', 'LOC'): 1; ('Bruno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Treveres', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tossington', 'ORG'): 1; ('1380', 'DATE'): 1; ('the second thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('380.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('3. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lateran', 'GPE'): 1; ('Carnotum', 'GPE'): 1; ('1092', 'DATE'): 1; ('Catalo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Capernaitism', 'ORG'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A54576,24 | 25083,Henry son Frederick father ambition elder brother crown empire Henry,pope: 0.5; church: 0.5; man: 0.5; roman: 0.5; emperor: 0.5; time: 0.45; lord: 0.45; peter: 0.45; god: 0.4; thing: 0.35; bernard: 0.1; son: 0.1; people: 0.05; cardinal: 0.05; father: 0.05; king: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 32; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 19; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 12; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 7; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Innocentius', 'ORG'): 6; ('Eugenius', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 5; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 5; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 5; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Callistus', 'ORG'): 4; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 4; ('Celestin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('William', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Celestin', 'GPE'): 3; ('France', 'GPE'): 3; ('Anaclet', 'ORG'): 3; ('Lotharius', 'ORG'): 3; ('Innocentius', 'NORP'): 3; ('Pisa', 'PERSON'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Saxony', 'GPE'): 2; ('Clemens', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Clemens', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tancred', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sicilies', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 2; ('Platin', 'ORG'): 2; ('two year', 'DATE'): 2; ('five year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Saladin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 2; ('the year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Gregory Viii', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Gelasius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Petro', 'GPE'): 2; ('Gregory Vii', 'PERSON'): 2; ('those day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Sicily', 'GPE'): 2; ('Raynold', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Onuphr', 'GPE'): 2; ('York', 'LOC'): 2; ('naucler', 'ORG'): 2; ('Patricius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Conrade', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Pisae', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Henry vi .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frederick', 'ORG'): 1; ('Henry duke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the next year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Constantia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tusculo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Roger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ventura', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thesor', 'GPE'): 1; ('Quomodo Imperium', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tusculum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Coelestin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Almarik', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cyprus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('John de bregna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isobel', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('german', 'NORP'): 1; ('Japha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Messina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Frederick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('duke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Suevia', 'ORG'): 1; ('1198', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alexius', 'ORG'): 1; ('1099', 'DATE'): 1; ('cry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rainer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lateran', 'GPE'): 1; ('Clemens Iii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Richard earl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Campania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Albert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four month', 'DATE'): 1; ('105. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paschalis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Henry V.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paschalis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eighteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('six month', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cincius Patricius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cluniak', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cluniak', 'ORG'): 1; ('Imperialists', 'NORP'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Papalis', 'NORP'): 1; ('dans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aethera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Papa', 'ORG'): 1; ('lexque', 'PERSON'): 1; ('respicio jura dei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mens tua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fifty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Henry IV.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lataran', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sutrio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Leo Frangepanis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Honorius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Claremont', 'ORG'): 1; ('124', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('126', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'GPE'): 1; ('France Innocentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Roger duke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('130', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pisa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cassino', 'ORG'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('emperor|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('114', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter Abaillard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('eight year', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('siquis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('plati', 'GPE'): 1; ('1143', 'DATE'): 1; ('thirteen year and seven month', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Celestin Iii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('his five month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Innoc', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('192', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Guido de Castello', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peter Abailard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Soisson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('196', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arnald of Brixia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Brixia', 'GPE'): 1; ('234', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gath', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ascalon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phinehas', 'NORP'): 1; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eleven month', 'DATE'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jordanes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alfonso', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lusitania', 'GPE'): 1; ('baron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eugenius Iii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Viterbio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tibur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Justinian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iustinianus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Caesaris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('christus jussit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Frider .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('236', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Simon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cephas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sarai', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sarah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('caesaris constat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Ro.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernard be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Convers', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Melchisedek', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sed qualis natus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jewel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1152', 'DATE'): 1; ('the eight year', 'DATE'): 1"
A54576,24 | 25095,Anastasius IV. worthy memory cup gold Lateran church Pantheon saint,pope: 0.5; god: 0.5; emperor: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; alexander: 0.45; year: 0.4; lib: 0.4; church: 0.4; cap: 0.35; clergy: 0.3; grace: 0.2; city: 0.2; christ: 0.1; cardinal: 0.05; roman: 0.05; victor: 0.05; time: 0.05,"('lib', 'PERSON'): 15; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 14; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 4; ('Naucler', 'ORG'): 3; ('Platin', 'ORG'): 3; ('France', 'GPE'): 3; ('Denmark', 'GPE'): 3; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paschalis', 'ORG'): 3; ('Lateran', 'GPE'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Anagnia', 'GPE'): 2; ('Romulus', 'GPE'): 2; ('four year', 'DATE'): 2; ('ten month', 'DATE'): 2; ('Frederick', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Frederick', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Alfonso', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tancred', 'PERSON'): 2; ('platina', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Florence', 'ORG'): 2; ('Arnulph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('Gesner', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anastasius IV', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pantheon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maries', 'GPE'): 1; ('Io', 'LOC'): 1; ('two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hadrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hildebrand', 'LOC'): 1; ('his first year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Arnold of Brixia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eugenius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pudentiana', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arnold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the late end of his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mat Parisien', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander Iii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Remus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve day', 'DATE'): 1; ('fourteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Crema', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lombardie', 'GPE'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Radevicus', 'GPE'): 1; ('cit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hungary', 'GPE'): 1; ('Papia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Justinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('late day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Otho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rowland', 'ORG'): 1; ('Octavian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Claremont', 'FAC'): 1; ('1162', 'DATE'): 1; ('the next year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Wirtzburgh An.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1165', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mentz', 'GPE'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('Callistus Iii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1178', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('annual', 'DATE'): 1; ('Callistus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bellarm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Martin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Po', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Verg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thomas Becket', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gratian .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Cler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('prop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lusitania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Saracen', 'NORP'): 1; ('twenty and one year', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lucius Iii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Verona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Armenia', 'GPE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1185', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saladin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('one year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the 57 day', 'DATE'): 1; ('fifty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Philip king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('otho duke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Burgundy', 'ORG'): 1; ('Flanders', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sicily from', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Capua', 'ORG'): 1; ('Poland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bohemia', 'GPE'): 1; ('1196', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('§', 'NORP'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('five year', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Celestin IV.', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tusculo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1198', 'DATE'): 1; ('that century', 'DATE'): 1; ('this century', 'DATE'): 1; ('eighteen day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year 1117', 'DATE'): 1; ('1000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paschalis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fluentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('340', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Ro.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nobles', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('holy day', 'DATE'): 1; ('P. Mornay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hirsaug', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Panormitan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sicily', 'GPE'): 1; ('Roger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petrus Alfonsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the 44.', 'DATE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Scythians', 'NORP'): 1; ('deceit', 'GPE'): 1; ('fox', 'ORG'): 1; ('Honorius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Vrbs', 'ORG'): 1; ('illa careret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel dominis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Honorius Augustodunensis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year 1110', 'DATE'): 1; ('Imperatore', 'ORG'): 1; ('libe .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('their tender year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ps', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ser', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Natal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rupert Tuitiensis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Colein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year 1112', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cephas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Vict', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Verbi', 'NORP'): 1; ('prolog', 'NORP'): 1; ('Apocalyp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('meek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Clemens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Nicolaus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A54576,24 | 25124,Waldenses persecute persecution Waldenses year Ecbert monk dispute Colein August,man: 0.5; church: 0.5; god: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; pope: 0.5; peter: 0.5; power: 0.4; prelate: 0.35; roman: 0.3; day: 0.3; faith: 0.3; christ: 0.15; lord: 0.1; reason: 0.05; thing: 0.05,"('Peter', 'PERSON'): 18; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Arnold', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Antiochia', 'GPE'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('France', 'GPE'): 4; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 4; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Waldenses', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Tolouse', 'GPE'): 3; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 3; ('Theodorick', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Alexander Iii .', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ann', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1170', 'DATE'): 2; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 2; ('William', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Lucas', 'GPE'): 2; ('Catal', 'ORG'): 2; ('Pontificalia', 'GPE'): 2; ('festival day', 'DATE'): 2; ('other day', 'DATE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Arrius', 'GPE'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('year 1163', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ecbert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Colein', 'ORG'): 1; ('August 2', 'DATE'): 1; ('Arnold Marsilius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Flanders', 'ORG'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Caesari', 'GPE'): 1; ('heisterb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Binna', 'LOC'): 1; ('the same year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hovedan Annal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oliverius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Narbon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Girald Albien', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lombardy Consolati', 'LOC'): 1; ('1178', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Chysogono', 'ORG'): 1; ('Henry king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Albigenses', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Rober', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bathonien', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry abbot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clareval', 'GPE'): 1; ('Albia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Roger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hov', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the next year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tom 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abbot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Albanen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gascony', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Altisiod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1181', 'DATE'): 1; ('1183', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bituricen', 'ORG'): 1; ('5000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Catharelli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ruptarii , Guil', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Armorica', 'LOC'): 1; ('Gestis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Radulph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rheims', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Verona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frederik', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clemens Iii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Andr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Navarre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ja', 'PERSON'): 1; ('statu cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Radevic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frederick i lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexander Iii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('baron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephan', 'GPE'): 1; ('86', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('Gerebert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the 1000 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('3. 22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Parisian', 'NORP'): 1; ('1167', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hungary', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucas', 'ORG'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernard Clunicen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cord probavit', 'ORG'): 1; ('contenebravit Pontificum', 'ORG'): 1; ('integer antè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nunc labat ille', 'PERSON'): 1; ('plebibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('stat sibi', 'ORG'): 1; ('gloria', 'GPE'): 1; ('pompa', 'ORG'): 1; ('superbia divitiarum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Presbyteratus', 'ORG'): 1; ('officio brevis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pseudoprophetas', 'GPE'): 1; ('numerosius hâc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tegmina', 'GPE'): 1; ('corda superba', 'ORG'): 1; ('tunica', 'GPE'): 1; ('latet anguis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('herba', 'GPE'): 1; ('improbus extat', 'ORG'): 1; ('nullus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simone', 'ORG'): 1; ('venditur infula pontificalis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('venditur annulus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quando', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arida corruit', 'ORG'): 1; ('plena clamitat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tacet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romae', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('juris ibi via', 'PERSON'): 1; ('moribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('aurea pectora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tempora pessima', 'PERSON'): 1; ('scilicet ultima', 'ORG'): 1; ('stat simulatio', 'ORG'): 1; ('sva propria', 'FAC'): 1; ('deputat', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('rex Babylonis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that century', 'DATE'): 1; ('vult marcas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Papas and Patriarchas', 'ORG'): 1; ('dederis marcas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('impleveris arcas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('culpâ solveris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Staforis', 'DATE'): 1; ('intra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tom 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Colein An. 1551', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Opusculum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'GPE'): 1; ('one festival day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a whole week', 'DATE'): 1; ('fifteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('working-day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the canonical hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('our day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Trutannii', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the twelve century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Catalo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Henry archbishop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mentz', 'GPE'): 1; ('within few day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('some day', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter Abailard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('192', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Guido', 'GPE'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Soisson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'GPE'): 1; ('191', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epist', 'GPE'): 1; ('190', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zacharias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paschal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bernard the cxciv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anselm', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nice', 'GPE'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antiochia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Macedonius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nechites', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Phocas', 'GPE'): 1; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Maximus Ennius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apolinaris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Thracia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pontus', 'ORG'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chalcedon , Constantinople , Ephesus ,', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antiochia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A54576,25 | 25193,CHAP. Iii country honour Iii earthquake description century mountain Salvii,man: 0.5; church: 0.5; friar: 0.5; christ: 0.5; pope: 0.5; time: 0.45; order: 0.4; bishop: 0.35; god: 0.35; power: 0.25; contrary: 0.15; word: 0.15; thomas: 0.1; pardon: 0.1; queen: 0.1; priest: 0.05; sin: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 26; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 15; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 14; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 10; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 8; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Dominicus', 'ORG'): 7; ('Dominicans', 'NORP'): 6; ('Franciscans', 'NORP'): 6; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Innocentius', 'NORP'): 5; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Dominicus', 'NORP'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Honorius', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Durand', 'NORP'): 4; ('Lateran', 'GPE'): 3; ('Waldenses', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Pol', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Alexander the IV', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Aquin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 3; ('Hugo', 'EVENT'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Scotus', 'ORG'): 3; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Dominicus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Gregory', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('37', 'DATE'): 2; ('loc', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 2; ('John the Xxii', 'PERSON'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sum', 'GPE'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Peter Lombard', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Agrip', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Aureolus', 'NORP'): 2; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('platina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Salvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tibris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dominicus Calaguritanus a Spaniard', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petrus Auratus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scintilla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('amor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antonius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Florence', 'ORG'): 1; ('about the year 1420', 'DATE'): 1; ('four hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tolouse', 'GPE'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Monasterii Cassamariae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('par', 'PERSON'): 1; ('§', 'NORP'): 1; ('Francis of Assisio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christus oravit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Franciscus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('B. Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Barth .', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bononia An.', 'ORG'): 1; ('1510', 'DATE'): 1; ('Legenda', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mantuanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fastor', 'GPE'): 1; ('viderat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('somnis laterani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tecta', 'ORG'): 1; ('utrumque supposuisse humeris', 'ORG'): 1; ('sustinuissi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('taliter admonitus pastor', 'ORG'): 1; ('legenda', 'GPE'): 1; ('Legen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aurea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bonaventura', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antonin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Honorius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('John bishop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sabinien', 'GPE'): 1; ('1235', 'DATE'): 1; ('Petrus de vineis Epist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Beguini', 'ORG'): 1; ('John condemn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Directori', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alvar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pelagius de planctu', 'ORG'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('219', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('48', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matiscon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('87', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bellarmin de Monach', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Francis Pegna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fransciscans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Agrippa de vanitat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Catal', 'ORG'): 1; ('546', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('augustinians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Clara', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bridget', 'ORG'): 1; ('about the year 1252', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('IV', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year 1120', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year 1212', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anselm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('Richard de saint victor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gratian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Blandinus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rupertus Tuitiensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leo Tuscus , Gulielm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vincentius Gallus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander de ale', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fons', 'ORG'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Gualther Pictaviensis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alfonsus Tostatus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abulensis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Albertus Magnus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Colein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas de Aquino', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aegidius Romanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aquitania', 'GPE'): 1; ('richardus de media villa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicolaus de Lyra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bonaventura Sepharicus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Durandus de saint', 'ORG'): 1; ('Portiano', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gulielmus Occam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year 1330', 'DATE'): 1; ('Novatians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aristotle and Lombard', 'ORG'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('76', 'DATE'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thomas Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('outward punishment', 'ORG'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Frier', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gratian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Supplem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('german', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hadrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('that century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Boniface the Viii', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Roffen .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra', 'ORG'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('so many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Roffensis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Parisien', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregorius de arimino', 'ORG'): 1; ('Biel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('114', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('j•ct', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('109', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregor .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustin', 'ORG'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. Capreolus', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Durand , Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmin de Euchar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•aith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Triden', 'GPE'): 1; ('three hundred year', 'DATE'): 1"
