tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A02484,13,Iephtah daughter lord Iunius annotation place virginity nature Iud. Hebr.,man: 0.5; opinion: 0.5; history: 0.5; cap: 0.5; kind: 0.5; lib: 0.5; part: 0.45; nature: 0.45; language: 0.45; truth: 0.25; wolf: 0.15; name: 0.15; reason: 0.05; thing: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 7; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('ark', 'GPE'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 3; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 3; ('Brutus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Scaliger', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Armenia', 'GPE'): 2; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Nazarite', 'NORP'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cambden', 'GPE'): 2; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 2; ('phrygian', 'NORP'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Collen', 'PERSON'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('french', 'NORP'): 2; ('Saxons', 'NORP'): 2; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tacitus', 'ORG'): 2; ('british', 'NORP'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('swan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Exercit', 'ORG'): 2; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 2; ('pelican', 'NORP'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Iephtah', 'GPE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('12 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Walter Raleigh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1a', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('70', 'DATE'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Shinar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Babel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Armenia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ararat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Noah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iaphet', 'GPE'): 1; ('10. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 24', 'TIME'): 1; ('Lyranus , Tostatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('agatharchidem de rub•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dec. 2a', 'DATE'): 1; ('80', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the red bank', 'ORG'): 1; ('Castro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Barros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Idumaea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scaliger', 'ORG'): 1; ('34. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nazarene', 'ORG'): 1; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hippocrates', 'ORG'): 1; ('Galen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ventricles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laurentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fernelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the 20th', 'DATE'): 1; ('East', 'LOC'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bec', 'PERSON'): 1; ('melabdim E•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Magore', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pilgr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3ia', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Simon Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('falsam plerique', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('86', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Graecam', 'ORG'): 1; ('natu', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Graecia mendax audet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('historia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sat.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Exer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Colos•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Causabon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('the Gentiles Plato', 'FAC'): 1; ('Theophrastus', 'ORG'): 1; ('George', 'PERSON'): 1; ('idol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 10.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epiphanius ,', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory Nazianzen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('apparet totam illam de act', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arrianorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('George be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('jour', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de trois', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mantuan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Historiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herodes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('hospitibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('assyrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('John Bodin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Inveteratus', 'NORP'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('Briton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dutch', 'NORP'): 1; ('Verstigan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gaul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Walch', 'ORG'): 1; ('Wales', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aeneas', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Loegrius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Albanak', 'GPE'): 1; ('Britan ▪ de primis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Boccaccio', 'GPE'): 1; ('Adryanus Iunius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Polydorus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Buchanan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vignier', 'GPE'): 1; ('Molinaeus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bodine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John of Wethamsted', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Albon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('A•', 'ORG'): 1; ('1440', 'DATE'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ninius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bede', 'GPE'): 1; ('William of Malmesbery', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year 1160', 'DATE'): 1; ('Geoffrey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about four hundred year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Henry the', 'FAC'): 1; ('Giraldus Cambrensis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('William', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Newberry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fabulosam historiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Fabulosa', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae de illis vel poetae', 'ORG'): 1; ('ultimo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tradiderunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cardan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pigmeiorum historiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Strabo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Strabo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gellius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rhodogin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egppt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('grecian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Claudius Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pliny', 'ORG'): 1; ('•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('10. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nec visum', 'ORG'): 1; ('cardan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('233', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('as much as two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ioachimus Rheticus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gesnerus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucretius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('certius', 'GPE'): 1; ('sensibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Castor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Egyptians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bever', 'GPE'): 1; ('Natur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Olorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('suavissimo quem cum', 'FAC'): 1; ('Graecia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luciani', 'ORG'): 1; ('232', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('apud quem aliquid novi dicas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aelian', 'NORP'): 1; ('iam communi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nunquan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Galen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dioscorides de Temp', 'ORG'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioubertus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Radi•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('201', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('foetibus numerosissimis', 'ORG'): 1; ('irco erumpentibus rumpi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Camerini ligneatheca vidimus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Viperillas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vincentius Camerinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abbatium de Viper•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bustamentitinum de animaentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. S.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rondeletius', 'ORG'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lupi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Moeris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phillip Camerarius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('344', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lupis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('restitui sibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Laurentius Ioubertus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tryphon', 'ORG'): 1; ('securi examinis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Panormitan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Duarenus de', 'ORG'): 1"
A02484,14,CAP. reason author writing discourse sect captivate truth beauty sovereignty,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; truth: 0.5; world: 0.5; nature: 0.5; thing: 0.45; age: 0.4; power: 0.4; reason: 0.4; end: 0.35; day: 0.2; mean: 0.15; self: 0.05; opinion: 0.05; regard: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 2; ('french', 'NORP'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Dis', 'ORG'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('CAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucretius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mari magno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('turbantibus aequora ventis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('decay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('placet laudem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('humilitas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lib de Nat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Job', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('omnia de mendacio ad Consen•', 'ORG'): 1; ('dubia remanebunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('will|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('nunquam errari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam cùm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('2. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the Ioel 2', 'LAW'): 1; ('Isaak', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scaliger', 'ORG'): 1; ('Exercit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Max', 'PERSON'): 1; ('potestas', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae eodem nutu gubernat infinite quo creavit', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('secunda compacta', 'ORG'): 1; ('alia', 'GPE'): 1; ('sed solum ab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('Timoeo', 'GPE'): 1; ('nisi ab', 'ORG'): 1; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sirach', 'GPE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28 , year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('13.', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('fig', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hercules foot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Francis Marquesse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Sauanarola', 'ORG'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Naples', 'GPE'): 1; ('Varro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Civit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dei lib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lubens agnosco', 'PERSON'): 1; ('viri fort etiamsi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fiduciam gerens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magnas aggrediendas presumat audaciùs', 'ORG'): 1; ('the Druides Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('excitari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mortis neglecto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucan', 'NORP'): 1; ('authoribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('vmbrae non', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Erebi', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pallida', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arctos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Maximus', 'GPE'): 1; ('prona viris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('capace mortis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erebus', 'ORG'): 1; ('thrice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Camden', 'GPE'): 1; ('Glocestershire', 'GPE'): 1; ('si hanc cogitationem homines', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemo se meliorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eo qui optimus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arbitraretur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Quintilian', 'NORP'): 1; ('quod faciente', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orat', 'ORG'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ingenio illi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Libr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Norinberg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1562', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the very day', 'DATE'): 1; ('every minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('Espencaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bullinger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'GPE'): 1; ('the end of the year the last hour', 'DATE'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the last month', 'DATE'): 1; ('quarter', 'DATE'): 1"
A02484,16,CAP. world decay general sect general reason almighty hand world,man: 0.5; world: 0.5; reason: 0.5; time: 0.5; thing: 0.5; nature: 0.5; whole: 0.45; body: 0.4; part: 0.4; decay: 0.3; another: 0.2; cap: 0.15; day: 0.1,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 4; ('nec', 'ORG'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Centenary', 'GPE'): 3; ('Galen', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Boetius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Saturn', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('CAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('rebus subtraheret , sicut de nihilo facta sunt omnia', 'ORG'): 1; ('principio caelum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('globum Lunae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mens agitat molem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magno', 'ORG'): 1; ('Platonists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Philo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philo', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('11.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vtrum Mundus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('generali concursu', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ruvio de caelum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alba', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 1; ('1. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('natura tenorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pontanus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vertumnus', 'EVENT'): 1; ('Proteus', 'GPE'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lucret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('corpora consiciat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the whole year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luc•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'LOC'): 1; ('Ovid', 'ORG'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('alijs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('reparat', 'NORP'): 1; ('figuras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec perit', 'ORG'): 1; ('tanto', 'GPE'): 1; ('quidquam', 'GPE'): 1; ('huc forsitan illa', 'ORG'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the very day', 'DATE'): 1; ('24 38', 'DATE'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Libr', 'GPE'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('annis ante judicium non videbitur arcu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('coelestibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('etiam naturaliter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('desiccationem aeris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Henricus Mecliniensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Albertus Magnus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Albumazar', 'GPE'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Boethius Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('certa', 'NORP'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred year of age', 'DATE'): 1; ('one inch', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('almost five foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('sixteen hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about ten foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Goliath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Walter Rauleigh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Galen', 'GPE'): 1; ('six pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('six ounce', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Galens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gesner', 'PERSON'): 1; ('at least two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('about fourteen hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Phoebus', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('their season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lib de Con', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('viribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lodovicus Regius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rodogin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vicibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae renascantur denuò', 'ORG'): 1; ('manet incolumis mundus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('idem', 'ORG'): 1; ('erit quoniam semper', 'PERSON'): 1"
A02484,17,CAP. general argument world decay refute sect objection draw reason,world: 0.5; time: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; age: 0.5; thing: 0.5; reason: 0.45; decay: 0.45; nature: 0.4; end: 0.2; strength: 0.2; christ: 0.15; art: 0.1; part: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 15; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('daily', 'DATE'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('nec', 'ORG'): 4; ('cyprian', 'NORP'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 3; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Hebr', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('CAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('inaudita altera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Med•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('licet statuerit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('haud aequus fuit :', 'FAC'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine hundred and fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nine hundred and thirty year', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('a worse season', 'DATE'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('langu•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Crea•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('iam mundum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('viribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('sto', 'ORG'): 1; ('tacentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nulla de scripture', 'ORG'): 1; ('promentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('mundus ipse iam loquor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non hyeme', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seminibus', 'GPE'): 1; ('nec adeò', 'ORG'): 1; ('montibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('eruuntur', 'NORP'): 1; ('auri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('exhausta iam metalla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('agris agricolam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('artibus peritia', 'GPE'): 1; ('moribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('tantam substantiam rei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fine iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('occasu suo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cornubus', 'ORG'): 1; ('arbour quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fuerat', 'ORG'): 1; ('ramis', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui exundantibus prius venis', 'ORG'): 1; ('vix modico sudore distillat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magna minuantur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('about forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tu miraris et quereris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contemptu vestro', 'ORG'): 1; ('rara desuper pluvia descendat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Squalleat', 'ORG'): 1; ('pallidas herbas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('reliquae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('rebus', 'ORG'): 1; ('huius effector', 'ORG'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lucretius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epicurus', 'ORG'): 1; ('versus finem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Soecla', 'GPE'): 1; ('nec fluctus', 'ORG'): 1; ('n•', 'ORG'): 1; ('mortalibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('pabula laeta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae nunc vix', 'ORG'): 1; ('jamque caput', 'PERSON'): 1; ('grandis suspirat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Crebrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('laborem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cum tempora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('temporibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Praeteritis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('laudat fortunas saepe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('crepat', 'GPE'): 1; ('finibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adscopulum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('defessa vetusto', 'PERSON'): 1"
A02484,19,observe sail Tropic set wind east west sailor breeze sun,heaven: 0.5; body: 0.5; garment: 0.5; regard: 0.5; thing: 0.5; matter: 0.45; earth: 0.4; word: 0.35; year: 0.35; moon: 0.3; say: 0.15; sun: 0.1; god: 0.1; place: 0.05; form: 0.05; end: 0.05; substance: 0.05; time: 0.05; saint: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('S. Augustine', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thy year', 'DATE'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15. 15', 'DATE'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('mutabuntur', 'GPE'): 2; ('Tropic', 'GPE'): 1; ('noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('Peru', 'GPE'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('midnight', 'TIME'): 1; ('omma qui videt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Citima', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zanchius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hesiod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hesiodus', 'GPE'): 1; ('de operibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('incrementis totius agricolationis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('signa notet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hesiod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arist', 'ORG'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('99', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Selenites', 'ORG'): 1; ('Georgius Agricola', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de civit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dei lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Galen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('erat', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Claudius Espencaeus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the hundred forty eight', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hexam', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Civit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pareus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pererius', 'ORG'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('the hundred forty', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hipparchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Job', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bildad', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iunius', 'ORG'): 1; ('4 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('saint depart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nineteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Augustinum', 'NORP'): 1; ('de Perenni Philosoph•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a. millia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam habuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('pulchrit•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eadem permansit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec quicquam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('last above 5000 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alstedius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mille', 'ORG'): 1; ('sexcentos ita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dimin•', 'ORG'): 1; ('5600 year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('102', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the hundred and second', 'TIME'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ps', 'ORG'): 1; ('19 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('8. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cessationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('his year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('quod sumitur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vsu deponitur', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dydimus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psaltes', 'ORG'): 1; ('abijsse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dydimus', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Perenni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('senio quo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('abolentur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isayah', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('34.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('fifteen hundred year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lunae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Medcaea', 'ORG'): 1"
A02484,21,CAP. pretend decay light body sect reason take nature light,light: 0.5; heaven: 0.5; sun: 0.5; nature: 0.5; body: 0.5; father: 0.5; brightness: 0.45; part: 0.35; angel: 0.35; water: 0.2; god: 0.15; beauty: 0.1; world: 0.1; matter: 0.1; self: 0.1; star: 0.05; man: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Pareus', 'ORG'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('CAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hugo', 'EVENT'): 1; ('quae cum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('se colorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bartas', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eucherius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rupertus', 'ORG'): 1; ('videntur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam fuerant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epistolam', 'GPE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Moll•', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('102', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Metaphoricè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('millibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('about so many thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('perpetuo motu', 'ORG'): 1; ('circumactum coelum non atteritur', 'FAC'): 1; ('nec absumitur', 'ORG'): 1; ('sed manet quale', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heaveus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Camden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Yorkshire', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantius Chlorus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about three hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lazius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romanes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nicene', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hebr', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Futuri', 'GPE'): 1; ('ac senescentiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('non eadem', 'ORG'): 1"
A02484,23,CAP. pretend decay body regard iufluence sect kind influence heaven,star: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; heaven: 0.5; influence: 0.5; body: 0.5; earth: 0.5; effect: 0.35; virtue: 0.35; light: 0.2; beast: 0.15; kind: 0.1; divine: 0.1; reason: 0.05; thing: 0.05; plant: 0.05; course: 0.05; aspect: 0.05,"('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Bartas', 'ORG'): 2; ('Saturn', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 2; ('frustrà', 'GPE'): 2; ('CAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Empyraeum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Auerroes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Georgius Agricola Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('contra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de Causis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the thirty eight of Job', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pleiades', 'ORG'): 1; ('W. R.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the winter and', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Duditius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Poli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Redemer', 'GPE'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sisera', 'GPE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('moon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('thou Lyons', 'ORG'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iam. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('July 9 1623', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phavorinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gellius', 'GPE'): 1; ('aut Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('adversa eventura', 'ORG'): 1; ('mentiuntur', 'GPE'): 1; ('animo miser', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hominibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('2 day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the first week', 'DATE'): 1; ('under night', 'TIME'): 1; ('the half of half a hour', 'DATE'): 1"
A02484,29,grant Moses computation year patriarch time proof bring be decrease,year: 0.5; man: 0.5; age: 0.5; time: 0.5; moses: 0.5; god: 0.5; life: 0.5; number: 0.5; find: 0.5; live: 0.5,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('David', 'PERSON'): 5; ('the year', 'DATE'): 4; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('year', 'DATE'): 3; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 3; ('fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('french', 'NORP'): 3; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one hundred year', 'DATE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('a hundred year', 'DATE'): 3; ('one hundred and', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 2; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('a hundred and', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one hundred and ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four year', 'DATE'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antiq', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('astrologiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('geometriam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ijs ampliora viuendi spatia condonauit', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi', 'NORP'): 1; ('impletur', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('six hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the great year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Roger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('secreta quibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('nam deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Methusalath', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('age threescore year', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year of the world', 'DATE'): 1; ('2434', 'DATE'): 1; ('thereabouts', 'TIME'): 1; ('three thousand year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('three score year', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aben Ezra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deuter', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('S.', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('six hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('only two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caleb', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herodotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thalia', 'GPE'): 1; ('four score year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Solon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laertius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Censorinus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Laert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the age of eighty one year', 'DATE'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Barzillai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 32', 'DATE'): 1; ('35.', 'DATE'): 1; ('year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sam 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judah 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('only four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('those year', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12 and 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pliny', 'PERSON'): 1; ('48 49', 'DATE'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred and two and', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Berosus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred and seventeen', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Sibylla Erithraea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phlegon Trallianus', 'FAC'): 1; ('viginti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('longissima tempora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trebellius Pollio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('neque amplius cuiquam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mosen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('familiarem viginti quinque', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quereretur', 'GPE'): 1; ('neminem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('the age of one hundred twenty five year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pollio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred and', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Sem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eber', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peleg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Terah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Terentius Varro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egyptians', 'NORP'): 1; ('every year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Varro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Varro', 'NORP'): 1; ('Syrach', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marcus Valerius Corvinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Metellus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one hundred and fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one hundred and two', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('twenty five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seventy seven', 'DATE'): 1; ('one hundred and eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one hundred and four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Asinius Pollio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Terentia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one hundred and three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clodia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ofilius', 'NORP'): 1; ('one hundred and fifteen year', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fifteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Galeria Copiola', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Q. Sulpitius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustus Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('the hundred and four year', 'DATE'): 1; ('ninety one year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pomponius', 'ORG'): 1; ('C. Marius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Carbo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iaacob', 'NORP'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one hundred and twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phineas Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Beiamin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phineas be Iud', 'ORG'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('42.', 'DATE'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one hundred fifty and eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('twenty seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fourteen', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iunius', 'ORG'): 1; ('erat', 'NORP'): 1; ('four year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('five hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('five hundred year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Irenaeus', 'GPE'): 1; ('the 2 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Traian', 'NORP'): 1; ('101', 'FAC'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('90', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Comp', 'LOC'): 1; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('51', 'DATE'): 1; ('100', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•', 'NORP'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vespasian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Parma', 'ORG'): 1; ('one hundred twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Parma', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Faventia', 'ORG'): 1; ('one hundred thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bononia L. Taurentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marcus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ariminium m. Aponius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Velleiacum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred and twenty year', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred and forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('fifty four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fifty seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one hundred and thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred thirty five', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('one hundred thirty seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('plyny', 'ORG'): 1; ('Latines', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cri•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Roger bacon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui magnifico medicamine sumpto vixerat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('multis alijs annis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('huius rei', 'ORG'): 1; ('nine hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Johannes Buttadeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about six year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antwerp', 'GPE'): 1; ('Guido Bonatus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about 400 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('141', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year 1604', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iohannis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry Savill', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1228', 'DATE'): 1; ('Armenia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul of Eitsen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sleswing', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year 1542', 'DATE'): 1"
A02484,32,CAP. More reason year stature ancient time sect reason take,measure: 0.45; foot: 0.45; cubit: 0.45; stature: 0.45; man: 0.45; body: 0.45; proportion: 0.45; part: 0.45; inch: 0.45; reason: 0.25; lib: 0.05; heighth: 0.05; middle: 0.05; phalanx: 0.05; phya: 0.05; persian: 0.05; persians: 0.05; persiens: 0.05; patronos: 0.05; pharaohs: 0.05; pisistratus: 0.05; pillar: 0.05; passage: 0.05; cap: 0.05,"('four', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('six foot', 'QUANTITY'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('this day', 'DATE'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Suetonius', 'ORG'): 4; ('Tiberius', 'ORG'): 3; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Vitruvius', 'ORG'): 2; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('grecian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Causabon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('half a inch', 'QUANTITY'): 2; ('five foot and nine inch', 'QUANTITY'): 2; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 2; ('seven foot', 'QUANTITY'): 2; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Thalia', 'LOC'): 2; ('two foot', 'QUANTITY'): 2; ('CAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Protagoras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'ORG'): 1; ('mensura', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vitruvius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gellius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sicily', 'GPE'): 1; ('Trallianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Amphora Capitolina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Capitol', 'FAC'): 1; ('Iulius Capitolinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maximinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Congius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Farnese', 'NORP'): 1; ('Vyllalpandus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezekiel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('mediocris staturae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('grecian foot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve inch', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Lucas Gauricus', 'ORG'): 1; ('membris dimensionu•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('certo', 'NORP'): 1; ('partibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Geometrae', 'ORG'): 1; ('latitudinem positum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Grownsell', 'ORG'): 1; ('Columella', 'NORP'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Ezek', 'ORG'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Persiens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iunius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deuteronomy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ribera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'MONEY'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Augnstine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('three hundred cubit', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('fifty cubit', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('four hundred and fifty thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Buteo', 'ORG'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ribera', 'ORG'): 1; ('6. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iachin and Boaz', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('eighteen cubit', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('thirty five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirty six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eighteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixty foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('one hundred cubit', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fifteen foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Herod', 'NORP'): 1; ('twenty five cubit', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Goliath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tiberio', 'GPE'): 1; ('Georgius Agricola', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vatican', 'FAC'): 1; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 1; ('thereof', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('nine foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Herodotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Regius Cubitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('twenty seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phya', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pisistratus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Persians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Xerxes', 'GPE'): 1; ('statura inter persas procerissima', 'ORG'): 1; ('persian', 'NORP'): 1; ('about eight foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry Savill', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Agricola', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mensur', 'GPE'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('dvobus', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Angelo Colocci', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Goropius Becanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gigantomachiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Appian', 'NORP'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Augustus', 'ORG'): 1; ('79', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iulius Marathus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('heighth', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('more than two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Italians', 'NORP'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('justam excederet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Valentinian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Valens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('five foot and', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('seven inch', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Vegetius Theodo•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marius', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten inch', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('inter Alares', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sidonius Apollinaris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('four hundred and forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Carmine', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Catuli•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Patronos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('espy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gigantes', 'GPE'): 1; ('quot vix Alcinoi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nicephorus', 'ORG'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lentulus', 'NORP'): 1; ('senate', 'ORG'): 1; ('4. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zaccheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('three inch', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1"
A02484,35,CAP. principal profession divinity law physic divinity gentile Jew Christ,body: 0.5; man: 0.5; age: 0.5; god: 0.5; part: 0.5; art: 0.5; time: 0.45; church: 0.4; law: 0.3; year: 0.25; use: 0.15; knowledge: 0.15; thing: 0.1; truth: 0.1; burn: 0.05; word: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 6; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('greek', 'NORP'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('France', 'GPE'): 4; ('french', 'NORP'): 4; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 4; ('Laurentius', 'PERSON'): 4; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('latin', 'NORP'): 3; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Hippocrates', 'GPE'): 3; ('Sylla', 'NORP'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 2; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Haereticum', 'ORG'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Boniface', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Herodotus', 'ORG'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('Molossos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Pelagius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Massonius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Romani', 'ORG'): 2; ('Bononia', 'GPE'): 2; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 2; ('Galen', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Democritus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Sylla', 'PERSON'): 2; ('cornelian', 'NORP'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Galen', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 2; ('Dioscorides', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paracelsus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('CAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('sec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lodovicus Vives', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christianae', 'ORG'): 1; ('scitu digna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('necessaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Minutius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Octavius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sva vitia facundi', 'FAC'): 1; ('habitu sapientiam sed mente praeferimus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nostri temporis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Talmudists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pharises', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Josephus de bello Jud', 'ORG'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mat 14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'NORP'): 1; ('Euphorbus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Callidas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hermotimus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pyrrhus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cyrill', 'ORG'): 1; ('Graeca Ca•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prophetas', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mira profecto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod tam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam si', 'PERSON'): 1; ('unquam verbum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quot verba', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('the three first century', 'DATE'): 1; ('habuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('unquam alia plurimos praestante', 'ORG'): 1; ('illustre doctore', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Magdeburgians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Arnobius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Centur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hilarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Victorinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Basilius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nazianzenus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Prudentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hieronymus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Faustinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Optatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the same century', 'DATE'): 1; ('heresy saint Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vincentius', 'NORP'): 1; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('haerese', 'NORP'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('illis temporibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christianum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae de optimis', 'ORG'): 1; ('nam', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quondam vel doctissimis viris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('obscura', 'ORG'): 1; ('aut etiam incognita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mediocriter', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Andradius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tridentine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dominicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('2a', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2ae', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('58', 'DATE'): 1; ('Roffensis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Confut', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caietan', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Gene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Espencaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sorbon', 'LOC'): 1; ('Greeke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rhemigius', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ludovicus Vives', 'ORG'): 1; ('principibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Latinè', 'GPE'): 1; ('dei l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zacharie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('d•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Filia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spiritua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry Stevens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Du Prat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Henry', 'GPE'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve mastiff', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Muletos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Artois', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Parker', 'ORG'): 1; ('Britannicae', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('Metropoliticae', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Priscian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('coelestibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Donati', 'GPE'): 1; ('Donatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('about 200 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pelagium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Annales', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. Hierome', 'ORG'): 1; ('Suidas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Photius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gennadius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abbas Tritemius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Illyricus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('the eight age', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philosophiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('artium obliuio per', 'FAC'): 1; ('quidem vllis siue', 'PERSON'): 1; ('principibus quicquam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hominibus doctrina', 'ORG'): 1; ('ingenio claris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sine etiam claris principibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baldus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jason', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Accursius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alciatus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ottomannus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jacobus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pithaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('conditoribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Themis', 'GPE'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arias Montanus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romanum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Turba', 'GPE'): 1; ('sva iura', 'ORG'): 1; ('nitori', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gouianus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Gouianum Bibliot', 'ORG'): 1; ('99', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iustinianaei', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('quotquot', 'NORP'): 1; ('quaeratur', 'GPE'): 1; ('palma deferenda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Justinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Naples', 'GPE'): 1; ('Florence', 'ORG'): 1; ('Genoa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mantua', 'GPE'): 1; ('Perusium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aix', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bordeaux', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seruin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Herbary', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('medicina videatur', 'FAC'): 1; ('Homer', 'FAC'): 1; ('Thucydides', 'ORG'): 1; ('Damogetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('proptereà seco', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('the very day', 'DATE'): 1; ('wer•', 'LOC'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vrnae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Marius', 'ORG'): 1; ('54', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tully 2 de legibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Remus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romulus', 'GPE'): 1; ('arsarosque artus vnxit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pythagorean', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tullus Hostilius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sepelito', 'LOC'): 1; ('Gellius 20', 'LAW'): 1; ('the 300 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('almost 400 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Blasius Vigenerus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the first Decade of Livy', 'DATE'): 1; ('Livy lib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Manlius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('above 270 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('humana', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pliny', 'ORG'): 1; ('proem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dion', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tiberius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antonins', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Macrobius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pertinax', 'GPE'): 1; ('fifty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('herodian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Riolan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Neotericks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herophilus', 'NORP'): 1; ('qui hominem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine de Civit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('harp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonnulla crudelis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('anatomicos appellant lani•', 'ORG'): 1; ('gobbet', 'GPE'): 1; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etiam humanae considerationis', 'ORG'): 1; ('seculis incognita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vassaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Varolius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Silvius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fallopius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Piceolhominaeus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Columbus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Riolanus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('perfectionis', 'NORP'): 1; ('attigisse', 'NORP'): 1; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 1; ('Danbie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arabic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Vienna', 'GPE'): 1; ('Salamanca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chalde', 'GPE'): 1; ('Clementinarum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theophraestus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plynie', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plynie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ruellius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rouillius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fuchsius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ioachimus marquis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Brandenburg', 'GPE'): 1; ('Herbaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Monaedus', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('helvetian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Philippus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theophrastus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bombastus', 'ORG'): 1; ('about the year 1494', 'DATE'): 1; ('Salisburge', 'GPE'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year 1541', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bullinger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gesner', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some year', 'DATE'): 1; ('carter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('all night', 'TIME'): 1; ('a penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('magician', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arabia', 'GPE'): 1; ('ten year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bickerus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Galen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Methodists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paracelsiaus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Roseae Crusis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristotle 3', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 1; ('homunculo', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('some thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nova medicina', 'LOC'): 1; ('Galeni•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phrarmac•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Quercitan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hiprocrates', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aristoteles', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Galenus', 'ORG'): 1; ('mirificis', 'GPE'): 1; ('operationibus', 'GPE'): 1; ('quidam', 'PERSON'): 1"
A02484,40 | 939,virgin mean Iphigenia sacrifice sight father Agamemnon occasion Lucretius potuit,god: 0.5; son: 0.5; worship: 0.5; king: 0.5; sacrifice: 0.5; man: 0.45; idol: 0.45; lib: 0.4; child: 0.4; mother: 0.35; religion: 0.2; blood: 0.15; daughter: 0.05; priapus: 0.05,"('Lib', 'PERSON'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Priapus', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 4; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Saturn', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tophet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Berecynthia', 'PERSON'): 2; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Maacha', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('S. Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Iphigenia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Agamemnon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucretius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Silius Italicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('ac flagrantibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('infandum dictu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pescenius Festus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Agathocles king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sicill', 'GPE'): 1; ('two hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Agathocles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gaules', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucan', 'NORP'): 1; ('diro T•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Haesus et', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dianae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Taranis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Diana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Moabite', 'NORP'): 1; ('Moab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('Deut 12 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('senate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cornelius Lentulus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Licinius Crassus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneas', 'GPE'): 1; ('tua qui cum ess eruditus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod nefariè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod detestabiliter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tophet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hinnon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezekiell', 'ORG'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39 the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('36 37', 'DATE'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('16.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Selden de Dis Syris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gehinnon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gehenna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chalde', 'LOC'): 1; ('Lev•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wolphius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam occidant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Moloch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gyraldus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('morbus', 'ORG'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('professionem quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('moribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jove Coleis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Hierome', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isidore', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iouinianum', 'ORG'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Moabite', 'EVENT'): 1; ('Israelites', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hosea', 'GPE'): 1; ('Maacham matrem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pryapi', 'ORG'): 1; ('dei lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('solenni la• … ationis eius', 'ORG'): 1; ('scenicis qualia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non dico matrem deorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed matrem qualiumcun', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quorumlibet', 'GPE'): 1; ('nec matrem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the solemn day', 'DATE'): 1; ('quae', 'ORG'): 1; ('sacri legia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae inquinatio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lyndians', 'NORP'): 1; ('violaris', 'GPE'): 1; ('si quando inter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cato', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augurem Cicero de divination', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cato', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christiana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander ab Alexandro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Die•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christo domino regi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('doctori nostro', 'ORG'): 1; ('doctrina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Prisci', 'GPE'): 1; ('Coloss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Talmud', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Buxdorsius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Synagoga Iudaica', 'LOC'): 1; ('Philastrius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Castro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1"
A02484,50 | 1430,c• point thing man wonder deviser devise self workman fabric,man: 0.5; roman: 0.5; world: 0.5; war: 0.5; fortitude: 0.45; god: 0.45; hand: 0.4; king: 0.3; nation: 0.25; fortune: 0.25; people: 0.25; death: 0.2; romans: 0.15; empire: 0.05; town: 0.05; heaven: 0.05; enemy: 0.05; peace: 0.05; kingdom: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 8; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Mamertins', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Sardinia', 'GPE'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Mithridates', 'GPE'): 2; ('Galgacus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 2; ('Amilcar', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('poena', 'ORG'): 2; ('Decci', 'ORG'): 2; ('Diogenes', 'ORG'): 2; ('Calais', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cannae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quisquis ab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('notanda', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Ammianus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Florus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romanum', 'ORG'): 1; ('fortunam contendisse videri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustus Caesar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bethleem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Easie 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('shall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustin', 'ORG'): 1; ('potestatē nisi deo vero qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('faelicitatē', 'PERSON'): 1; ('regno coelorū solis piis', 'ORG'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('nihil injustè placet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. second', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('non martyrem poena', 'ORG'): 1; ('Remota', 'GPE'): 1; ('nisi magna latrocinia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S.', 'NORP'): 1; ('singuli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('publicè', 'GPE'): 1; ('geritur', 'GPE'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nonius Marcellus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cicero•', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Percuteret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('iniquum gentibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nat', 'ORG'): 1; ('praes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam invndatio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam conflagratio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae nunquam laudantur', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi peracta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sallust', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romani Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arsocen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arma', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eos acerrima quibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('maxima', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Romanis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cupid', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tacitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iulij Agricola', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'GPE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('gloriam computant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam lacessierint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('socijs defendendis terrarum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cicero', 'FAC'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('carthaginians', 'NORP'): 1; ('syracusian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Messana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sicily', 'GPE'): 1; ('Decius Campanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('4000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rhegium', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pyrrhus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rhegium', 'ORG'): 1; ('1200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hannibal', 'GPE'): 1; ('7. third', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fort appellantur quòd', 'FAC'): 1; ('3. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('shatpe brunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui miser', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Machiavelli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dis', 'ORG'): 1; ('1. 11. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13 14', 'DATE'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mutio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('alter ab hostibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cum videret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam meruerat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mutius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laurent Valla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Graecos', 'GPE'): 1; ('magnitudinem illustre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nullus Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nostri temporis martyribus dorotheo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sodalibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('ministris comparari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('grecian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dorotheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui Scaevolas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inferendo de Ciu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5 14', 'DATE'): 1; ('illatas', 'NORP'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Apolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('apud vos ad tolerantiam doloris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mortis hortantur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cicero', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tusculanis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Fortuitis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pyrrhon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christiani', 'NORP'): 1; ('Philip de Valois', 'ORG'): 1; ('John lord', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vienna', 'GPE'): 1; ('eleven month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Stephen S. Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Daire', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Horatij', 'PERSON'): 1"
A02484,51,doubt man scripture place time end passage iniquity love cold,time: 0.5; day: 0.5; antichrist: 0.5; come: 0.5; man: 0.5; world: 0.4; christ: 0.35; empire: 0.35; apostle: 0.35; emperor: 0.35; saint: 0.3; end: 0.2; kingdom: 0.1; word: 0.1,"('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 20; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 12; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('the day', 'DATE'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('greek', 'NORP'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('last day', 'DATE'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('S. John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 2; ('many year', 'DATE'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cyneas', 'ORG'): 2; ('3 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jude', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isayah', 'FAC'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42.', 'DATE'): 1; ('one hundred and', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hesichius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('extremis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Iud•', 'ORG'): 1; ('3. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christianae Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Shiloh', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the latter day or', 'DATE'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('63 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Daniels', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iunius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tremelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('sequentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('consequentibus temporibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('sec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eustathius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tatians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Marcionists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cathari', 'ORG'): 1; ('less than two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('comparat', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('potius qualis futura', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aretius', 'GPE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Disertè', 'NORP'): 1; ('hominibus qui', 'ORG'): 1; ('sed etiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hominibus cuiuslibet temporis', 'ORG'): 1; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('temporum malitiam de Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('suspicati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tempora antichristi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. cyprian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam ducentorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Hierome', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichristum', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('omnia quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rex superbiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('lib 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Serm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('Iudaeus Apella', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 6. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Latins', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Primasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sedulius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the thirty second chapter', 'TIME'): 1; ('Apologie', 'ORG'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Algasia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gaudentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gerontia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Daniell', 'ORG'): 1; ('saint John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustulus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Charlemagne', 'GPE'): 1; ('stat magni', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('erat', 'NORP'): 1; ('Romano Imperio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anselme', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('diu gentes recesserunt', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romano', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichristus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lyra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romanum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pauli', 'GPE'): 1; ('negantia', 'GPE'): 1; ('redditionem tributi jam à multis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('quampridem Romanum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iustinianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Salmeron', 'ORG'): 1; ('Imperium Romanum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romanus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('imperij antiqui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romani', 'NORP'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Machiavelli Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sigonius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Guicciardin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lypsius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Admiranda', 'ORG'): 1; ('Legum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cum armis', 'ORG'): 1; ('sacris indulsit :', 'PERSON'): 1; ('moribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('prudentia', 'GPE'): 1; ('annis', 'NORP'): 1; ('nihil ambigat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel cum regibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel cum heroibus comparare', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magis innoxia', 'GPE'): 1; ('vltronea sunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('jura ac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sacror•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ipsi Reges', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('obnoxia capita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Capiti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('senate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1"
A02484,52,CAP. world end fire consume sect world end point christian,heaven: 0.5; world: 0.5; earth: 0.5; thing: 0.5; saint: 0.5; creature: 0.5; god: 0.45; fire: 0.4; end: 0.3; man: 0.25; place: 0.2; time: 0.15; restitution: 0.1; part: 0.05; change: 0.05; day: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 14; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 8; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('the day', 'DATE'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 6; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 5; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 4; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('John', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Iunius', 'ORG'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Lucretius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('syderibus', 'ORG'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 3; ('102', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('one day', 'DATE'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lucan', 'NORP'): 2; ('Astra', 'NORP'): 2; ('Ludovicus Vives', 'ORG'): 2; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 2; ('Sibylla', 'ORG'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('S. Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('S. John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('eundem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 2; ('CAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Christianity', 'GPE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('qualis futura', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('quidenim', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mutationis', 'NORP'): 1; ('non Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('71', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('illumex', 'ORG'): 1; ('temporibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quaecun { que', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil constat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('loco stabili', 'PERSON'): 1; ('montes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maria sorbebit ▪', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('terris homo', 'ORG'): 1; ('melioribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('illis', 'NORP'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aetna', 'ORG'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Parnassus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Olympus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heraclitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petri Anaxagoras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Democritus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maria ▪ ac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('terris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hor•', 'ORG'): 1; ('tria corpora memmi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tres species tam', 'ORG'): 1; ('tria talia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Una', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sustentata', 'GPE'): 1; ('behold', 'GPE'): 1; ('so many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Carmina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucreti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eleg', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucrece', 'GPE'): 1; ('littora nolet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phoebe', 'GPE'): 1; ('Indignata', 'NORP'): 1; ('Machina', 'NORP'): 1; ('foedera mundi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the last hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('exustionis huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidam etiam ad gentes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('philosophorum', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae An•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zeno , Cleanthes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chrysippus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('disposito lucet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cicero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mundus ignesceret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ludou', 'GPE'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lib.', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pharsalia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hos Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vret cum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Communis', 'NORP'): 1; ('ossibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Misturus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Metamorph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('laborat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sybillinis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Arden', 'GPE'): 1; ('manabit ab alto igneus atque', 'ORG'): 1; ('locos consum•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lib 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('acul•', 'ORG'): 1; ('terramque', 'NORP'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Magius de', 'ORG'): 1; ('only two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Job', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('fig', 'ORG'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Job', 'ORG'): 1; ('8. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sobria Philosoph .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Superius', 'ORG'): 1; ('beati incolunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bl•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clements', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 24', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Catharinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Salmeron', 'ORG'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'FAC'): 1; ('Iosuah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('babylonian', 'NORP'): 1; ('nec lu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15. 44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. John Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('quoniam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nova', 'LOC'): 1; ('nec ijs', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui hanc dissolutionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tremelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('five 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('nunc sequitur historiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('7. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('creatura hoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoniam habebit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1"
A02484,53,CAP. use consummation world day judgement sect day world end,god: 0.5; day: 0.5; man: 0.5; world: 0.5; soul: 0.5; judge: 0.5; judgement: 0.5; body: 0.5; sin: 0.4; justice: 0.25; life: 0.15; death: 0.1; reason: 0.05; angel: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('the day', 'DATE'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('that day', 'DATE'): 5; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('Sibylla', 'ORG'): 2; ('a day', 'DATE'): 2; ('gore', 'PERSON'): 2; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('CAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('Raimundus Sebundus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Raymundus Lullius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('outward peace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('confid•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('58', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('last', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hydaspes , Hermes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eusebius de p•', 'ORG'): 1; ('aeparati ne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last age', 'DATE'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae deus faciet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lactan', 'GPE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hermes', 'GPE'): 1; ('notwithstan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'GPE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('luci finem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('judicium aethereus pater', 'ORG'): 1; ('humano generi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aetherij sistentur judicis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('coelum ego convolven penetralia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('recludam Telluris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fati', 'NORP'): 1; ('mortis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peru', 'GPE'): 1; ('America', 'GPE'): 1; ('Surius', 'ORG'): 1; ('1558', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('holy Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Serm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sepulchre', 'GPE'): 1; ('Felix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('will|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('IESVS', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('so many million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Act•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Creat•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Saviour', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anselme', 'GPE'): 1; ('the great day', 'DATE'): 1"
A02484,53 | 1544,sect consideration day admonition thing dossolve manner person conversation godliness,day: 0.5; man: 0.5; account: 0.5; god: 0.5; judge: 0.5; judgement: 0.5; lord: 0.5; self: 0.4; world: 0.4; truth: 0.2; thing: 0.2; end: 0.15; shame: 0.05; evil: 0.05; mind: 0.05,"('this day', 'DATE'): 9; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('7. third', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Chrysostome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('mortui', 'GPE'): 1; ('venite ad judicium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apologie', 'ORG'): 1; ('Enoch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antiq', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mahometans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Andrew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Achaia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('India', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Indies', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gaudia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pelle timorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1"
A01053,5,corollary view argument progress man life fate be trace course,church: 0.5; man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; white: 0.5; use: 0.5; garment: 0.5; service: 0.5; feast: 0.35; england: 0.35; custom: 0.3; time: 0.3; communion: 0.1; egyptian: 0.05; gesture: 0.05,"('England', 'GPE'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('grave year', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Brutus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dion', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('ΈΙΡΗΝΟΙΝΩνΊΑ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pri', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gordon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('T. S.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nathaniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1612', 'DATE'): 1; ('ad angliam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('donis ditata supernis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clara viris claris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sceptra', 'NORP'): 1; ('gentibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Legum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('humanis nil', 'ORG'): 1; ('nam proli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Parua', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('angligenas jungunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam foelice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Authorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pacis', 'GPE'): 1; ('anglia', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Agape', 'NORP'): 1; ('many hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1"
A01974,217,peace end war benefit note war enjoy peace attribute war,peace: 0.5; god: 0.4; creature: 0.4; providence: 0.4; war: 0.4; ground: 0.35; sparrow: 0.35; say: 0.25; man: 0.25; psal: 0.2; blackfriar: 0.2; blessing: 0.15; people: 0.1; pearl: 0.1; praise: 0.1; posterity: 0.1; point: 0.1; place: 0.1; preach: 0.1; path: 0.1; preserve: 0.1; earth: 0.1; nov: 0.1; farthing: 0.05,"('12', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Blackfriar', 'GPE'): 4; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Aug. Enar', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 3; ('Nov. 1623', 'DATE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('147', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 2; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1623', 'DATE'): 2; ('Oct. 27', 'DATE'): 2; ('stilo vet', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Nov. 5', 'DATE'): 2; ('stilo novo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('148', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Mat 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('hominibus sunt necessariae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bern de modo', 'ORG'): 1; ('benè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('prophet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('122. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('saint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('15.', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa 9 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ , Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('3. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('527', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Differamus', 'ORG'): 1; ('patriam pacis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('shall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten day before', 'DATE'): 1; ('William GOVGE', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('George miller', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward Brewster', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pauls', 'GPE'): 1; ('1631', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('§', 'NORP'): 1; ('10. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('culicis ut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph.', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1"
A01974,243,matter inducement encouragement observation double honour due arm enducement man,man: 0.4; honour: 0.4; war: 0.4; artillery: 0.4; god: 0.4; say: 0.35; israel: 0.35; exercise: 0.35; mind: 0.3; profession: 0.2; lord: 0.2; observe: 0.1; number: 0.1; patron: 0.1; pat: 0.1; part: 0.1; offer: 0.1; perfection: 0.1; observation: 0.1; nature: 0.1; neglect: 0.1; encouragement: 0.1; double: 0.1; valour: 0.05,"('Israel', 'GPE'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('§', 'NORP'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('Iudg', 'PERSON'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('those many hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Joab', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sint', 'ORG'): 1; ('l. 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epigr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('56', 'DATE'): 1; ('Virgil', 'ORG'): 1; ('Achilles', 'GPE'): 1; ('Diomedes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Themistocles', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pericles', 'ORG'): 1; ('Horatij', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fabius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pompey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amasiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('two hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iehosaphat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoniam sibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mercedem ab homine', 'ORG'): 1; ('non quaesrvit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ambr de Abr Pat. l. 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vacant hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('strenuus industrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gideon', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('20. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epaminondas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Israelitarum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. de mirab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet 2 Chron', 'ORG'): 1; ('four hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Benjamin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gibeah', 'GPE'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ammon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17. 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ziklag', 'GPE'): 1; ('1 Chron', 'PERCENT'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1"
A02170,4 | 6864,David God joy gladness doe son Salomon gold silver men-singer,god: 0.5; heart: 0.5; sin: 0.5; bone: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; face: 0.5; right: 0.5; joy: 0.5; presence: 0.45; break: 0.45; make: 0.1,"('thou', 'GPE'): 29; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('David', 'PERSON'): 5; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Bathsheba', 'GPE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Hiericho', 'GPE'): 2; ('Achilleo', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four day', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thy day', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cain', 'ORG'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Urias', 'ORG'): 1; ('i•l', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicodemus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anriga', 'GPE'): 1; ('•reneth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('summ•r', 'ORG'): 1; ('s•t', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nebo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1"
A09900,81,oath attovrney ancient admission disuse stead oath allegiance minister falsehood,june: 0.5; may: 0.5; october: 0.5; cross: 0.5; man: 0.5; nouemb: 0.5; term: 0.5; febru: 0.45; thing: 0.35; contemplation: 0.3; court: 0.2; quind: 0.15; christ: 0.05,"('Nouem', 'PERSON'): 4; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Mich.', 'GPE'): 3; ('Hillary', 'PERSON'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ian', 'PERSON'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('July 2', 'DATE'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('January 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('February 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('essoin day', 'DATE'): 1; ('hill Ian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hill Ianu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Purif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Octab Purif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Febru', 'ORG'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('April 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('may 26', 'DATE'): 1; ('Apr. 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('May 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('May 2', 'DATE'): 1; ('May 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('may 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('May 6 may 7 may 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('may 13 may 14', 'DATE'): 1; ('May 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pasch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('may 19 May 20 may 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('May 2•', 'DATE'): 1; ('May 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('May 24', 'DATE'): 1; ('may 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('May 26', 'DATE'): 1; ('June 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cra•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('June 9 June 10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('June 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('June 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('June 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('June 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('June 18.', 'DATE'): 1; ('June 19', 'DATE'): 1; ('June 23.', 'DATE'): 1; ('June 24', 'DATE'): 1; ('June 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('June 26', 'DATE'): 1; ('June 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('July 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('July 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('October 9 and end', 'DATE'): 1; ('November 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Octab', 'GPE'): 1; ('October 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('October 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('October 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('October 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('October 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('October 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('October 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tres', 'GPE'): 1; ('October 2• … October 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('October 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('October 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mense Mich. Octo', 'ORG'): 1; ('27.', 'DATE'): 1; ('October 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('October 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('October 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('Crast', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('novemb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Octab', 'ORG'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nouemb', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Hillary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13 January', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Wolston', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 January', 'DATE'): 1; ('Conuersio S. Pauli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25 January', 'DATE'): 1; ('10 February', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Valentine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14 February', 'DATE'): 1; ('Easter', 'LOC'): 1; ('28 April', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Gordian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('12 June', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Buttolph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17 June', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24 June', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30 June', 'DATE'): 1; ('Michaelmas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6 October', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13 October', 'DATE'): 1; ('2 November', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Martin 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('November', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Edmund', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20 November', 'DATE'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('ilex ▪', 'LOC'): 1; ('quam tu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('T. P. Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Io', 'LOC'): 1; ('HAYVVARD', 'ORG'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('John bill', 'PERSON'): 1; ('m.dc.xxiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ANNE Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ssr Julius Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('casta', 'ORG'): 1; ('matrona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Imperat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('this present year', 'DATE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet tam', 'ORG'): 1; ('nigri quam limb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui fert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Golgotha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('71', 'DATE'): 1"
A07807,84,CHAP. Xvii argument logician mayor doctrine doctrine pagan Christians doctrine,oath: 0.5; faith: 0.5; thing: 0.5; god: 0.5; priest: 0.5; equivocation: 0.45; man: 0.35; pagan: 0.35; answer: 0.3; matter: 0.25; oracle: 0.25; christ: 0.25; lib: 0.1; truth: 0.05; sacrament: 0.05; arius: 0.05; doctrine: 0.05,"('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Arius', 'ORG'): 4; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Pyrrhus', 'ORG'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('§', 'NORP'): 2; ('Tully', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cic', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Poeni', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Bellar', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Xvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ergo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iurans', 'NORP'): 1; ('nisi esset', 'ORG'): 1; ('quidam etiam ad iniustum carcerem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•iunt', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi', 'NORP'): 1; ('t•t', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tully', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cicero Offic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Senatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('anni', 'NORP'): 1; ('duceretur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('cozen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hannibal', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui verò dcunt nullam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sidem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Infideli', 'ORG'): 1; ('quaeratur', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam', 'NORP'): 1; ('Punica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•ucata', 'GPE'): 1; ('charta habebat', 'GPE'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 1; ('vero', 'ORG'): 1; ('nihil verius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Prapar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euang', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Delphos', 'GPE'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sacram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('charactêrem indelebilem', 'PERSON'): 1; (""praestat caeteris omnib '"", 'ORG'): 1; ('Christiani', 'ORG'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tooffer', 'GPE'): 1; ('Offic', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. August', 'ORG'): 1; ('Infidelem', 'GPE'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A08806,5 | 15011,word teach meaning word thing gloss time papist year majesty,god: 0.5; father: 0.5; angel: 0.5; man: 0.5; saint: 0.5; name: 0.5; lord: 0.5; prayer: 0.45; christ: 0.35; thing: 0.3; invocation: 0.25; earth: 0.05; creature: 0.05; church: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Manifesto', 'GPE'): 2; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('60. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('48.16', 'MONEY'): 1; ('deliverer', 'ORG'): 1; ('47.4', 'DATE'): 1; ('28.15', 'MONEY'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laban', 'ORG'): 1; ('31.11.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bethel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Osea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bethel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lyranus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peniel', 'ORG'): 1; ('148', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Spaletto', 'GPE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chemni', 'ORG'): 1; ('174', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Job', 'ORG'): 1; ('Montanus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('quem de sanctis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('Reinold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.7.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fredericus Staphilus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mardoche', 'ORG'): 1; ('5 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('63.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.9', 'DATE'): 1; ('the Mammon of unrighteousness', 'ORG'): 1; ('Stella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil aliud', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi ut bona nostra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('26.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tu qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('Zephan', 'GPE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of hell', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Absalon', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iubal', 'ORG'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('11.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('148.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abba', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Spoleto', 'GPE'): 1; ('saint depart', 'PERSON'): 1"
A08806,5 | 15149,mediator God church saint Augustine purpose point show necessity mediator,god: 0.5; father: 0.5; saint: 0.5; name: 0.5; son: 0.5; church: 0.5; christ: 0.45; man: 0.35; prayer: 0.35; work: 0.3; faith: 0.2; call: 0.15; interest: 0.1; gregory: 0.1,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 9; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('Oure', 'ORG'): 3; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 3; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 3; ('England', 'GPE'): 3; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('angeli', 'NORP'): 1; ('orationibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apostoli Serm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('justi', 'GPE'): 1; ('63.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('22.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iosiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Epistolam', 'ORG'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abba', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('honorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iehouah', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.17.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Primogenitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.1', 'MONEY'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1551', 'DATE'): 1; ('Andrew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fiat', 'ORG'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Andrew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Io', 'LOC'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 22', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pappa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fifteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eulogius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of Chalcedon', 'ORG'): 1; ('sed tamē nullus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amsterdam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sibi', 'GPE'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('singuli pro omnibus', 'PERSON'): 1"
A08806,7,beast food raven man thing God title obedience part favour,bread: 0.5; god: 0.5; life: 0.5; thing: 0.5; day: 0.5; man: 0.5; use: 0.5; petition: 0.5; lord: 0.35; earth: 0.25; gift: 0.15; father: 0.15; word: 0.1,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('this day', 'DATE'): 9; ('David', 'PERSON'): 5; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('every day', 'DATE'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('daily', 'DATE'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('the year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Bacchus', 'ORG'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('fiat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vulcan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tubalcaine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nobis panem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('our year', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui accipitur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cum ab', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet substantia', 'ORG'): 1; ('panem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cambden', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hlaf', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wirtlic', 'NORP'): 1; ('some 200 year young', 'DATE'): 1; ('700 year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Henry the', 'FAC'): 1; ('160 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Adrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Englishman', 'GPE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Henry', 'GPE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wicliffe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scaliger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iakeh', 'GPE'): 1; ('panem dimensi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iun', 'GPE'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('panem necessitatis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('panem', 'ORG'): 1; ('paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('5 this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezekiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('38.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('119 175', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('10.14 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Melchisedech', 'NORP'): 1; ('14.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob answer Rahel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30.2', 'MONEY'): 1; ('da mihi panem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('6.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.21.22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Neptune', 'ORG'): 1; ('orco poena', 'ORG'): 1; ('polo gloria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('casta', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucina', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sebastian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Raphael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apollonia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 1"
A08806,7 | 16225,reason God thing honour due right Christ saviour bread heaven,god: 0.5; bread: 0.5; prayer: 0.5; care: 0.5; church: 0.5; man: 0.5; christ: 0.35; gift: 0.35; thing: 0.3; father: 0.25; blessing: 0.25; sac: 0.2; peace: 0.1; charity: 0.1; meat: 0.05; apostle: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Sacerd', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('this day', 'DATE'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('daily', 'DATE'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('gloria', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 2; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 7.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Salomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mar. 6.23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('145', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quoniam tu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('benedictus', 'ORG'): 1; ('domine deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui misereris nostri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('laetitia corda nostra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Conv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tu das escam', 'ORG'): 1; ('aperis tu manum tu•m', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Conv', 'GPE'): 1; ('Conv', 'ORG'): 1; ('erat', 'NORP'): 1; ('Benedic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tua dona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mensae coelestibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Con', 'ORG'): 1; ('sicut erat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui vivis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('domine', 'GPE'): 1; ('anima mea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mansueti', 'ORG'): 1; ('the greek church', 'ORG'): 1; ('gloria tibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gloria tibi rex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoniam dedisti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('laetitiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quando', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salvator', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('ita veni etiam ad nos', 'ORG'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('sibi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('4 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('30.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam acquirere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('31.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'NORP'): 1; ('this spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('13.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('late day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('6.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('William Rufus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('aperis tu manum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
