tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A77079,13,reverend preacher combine lecture New-Windsor honour man preach profess word,thing: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; people: 0.5; mind: 0.5; mr: 0.45; self: 0.45; brotherhood: 0.4; place: 0.35; truth: 0.35; discourse: 0.3; word: 0.05; apostle: 0.05; church: 0.05; owen: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Owen', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('New-Windsor', 'FAC'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('W.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('holland', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Whitlock', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('the afternoon', 'TIME'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('late in the evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('next morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Horace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('integer vitae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Babel', 'GPE'): 1"
A77079,20,sabbath send letter burgess place mayor town copy sir disturbance,people: 0.45; place: 0.4; god: 0.35; man: 0.35; mr: 0.35; parliament: 0.35; day: 0.3; mayor: 0.25; truth: 0.25; power: 0.2; sir: 0.2; soldier: 0.2; peace: 0.15; part: 0.15; permit: 0.15; performance: 0.15; oppose: 0.15; order: 0.15; preacher: 0.15; time: 0.1; town: 0.05; castle: 0.05; thing: 0.05; authority: 0.05,"('kind', 'PERSON'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Windsor', 'GPE'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Eaton', 'GPE'): 2; ('bacon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Kinsington', 'PERSON'): 1; ('may 1. 1652', 'DATE'): 1; ('the evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('the next morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the afternoon', 'TIME'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the follow week', 'DATE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('-late', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Richard Bream', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Westminster-hall', 'GPE'): 1; ('some nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('at least one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('about a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Corah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abiram', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cokayn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Croesus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae tua sunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae functio una requirit comittas soli', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1"
A76080,1,engrave portrait John Bastwick right 164• man day flower man,god: 0.5; opinion: 0.5; brethren: 0.5; government: 0.5; reason: 0.5; truth: 0.45; man: 0.4; self: 0.35; church: 0.35; difference: 0.25; word: 0.25; another: 0.25; world: 0.1; faith: 0.1,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 18; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('John Bastwick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('164•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John BASTVVICK', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('John macock', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1645', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Galathian', 'NORP'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jan. 2.8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judas 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('one hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Roman Caesar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Walter Montague', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elenchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('papisticis', 'DATE'): 1; ('Apologie', 'ORG'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1"
A71250,11 | 1023,saint God merit Christ saint memory saviour blood covenant grace,saint: 0.5; bless: 0.5; virgin: 0.5; god: 0.5; day: 0.45; name: 0.45; devotion: 0.4; society: 0.35; saviour: 0.35; heaven: 0.3; church: 0.25; honour: 0.2; piety: 0.1; superstition: 0.1; man: 0.05,"('it|be', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('this day', 'DATE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ben', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ida', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Luxembourg', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('Flora', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Pomona', 'PERSON'): 2; ('145', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('146.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('147.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('148', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaia Xxiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Germain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anselme', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antonine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernardine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Card', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Bona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Crasset', 'ORG'): 1; ('149', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('maris stella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Herman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Regina', 'FAC'): 1; ('Alma Redemptoris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jul. 19', 'DATE'): 1; ('Herman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jul. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('151', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gerard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sept. 24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chappel', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Hungarians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Stephen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('152', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sept. 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joscio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('153', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('154', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('IV', 'GPE'): 1; ('Maii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('320', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hildersheim', 'GPE'): 1; ('scito imperatorem meo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('JƲSSƲ', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('155', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paula , Cal', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jan. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aldegundis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Francisca', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tom IV.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('590', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dec. xi', 'DATE'): 1; ('156', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Venus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Cupid', 'ORG'): 1; ('157', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bienfaisante dans la France', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dans', 'NORP'): 1; ('may 20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('mar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vulcan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cyclops', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nayades , Ceres', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Mars', 'LOC'): 1; ('procul item profani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ceres', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1"
A76092,5,desire soul nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet work mind fountain desire mint coin,christ: 0.5; word: 0.5; desire: 0.5; man: 0.5; heaven: 0.5; soul: 0.5; life: 0.5; time: 0.35; paul: 0.35; day: 0.25; apostle: 0.2; death: 0.1; thing: 0.1; self: 0.1; peril: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 15; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 10; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 9; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the day of the year', 'DATE'): 3; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english Bibles', 'FAC'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Scaliger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Syriack', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('exposito mari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nullus portus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi mortis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('salutis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 1; ('12.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('verbum ab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tremelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tuesday-night', 'TIME'): 1; ('how many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty eight hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Thursday', 'DATE'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Friday', 'DATE'): 1; ('the same week', 'DATE'): 1; ('21.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Seneca', 'FAC'): 1; ('the 35th', 'DATE'): 1; ('qui gravi sarcina pressus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('explicari', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi accessit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('m. T. Cicero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cato', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pilgrim', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('47.9', 'MONEY'): 1; ('a hundred and', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cupio recipi jam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Angles', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Christo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23-29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('a night and', 'TIME'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Penelope', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ulysses', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nil mihi rescribas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ipse veni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('persian', 'NORP'): 1; ('tu mihi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apostle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('mihi proximus ipsi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('kinsman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A76358,1,confession obstinacy ignorance father bell priest declare manner trial condemnation,bell: 0.5; god: 0.5; priest: 0.5; death: 0.45; law: 0.45; mr: 0.45; religion: 0.4; church: 0.35; man: 0.3; execution: 0.25; faith: 0.25; kingdom: 0.2; roman: 0.1; people: 0.1; place: 0.1; bring: 0.05; christ: 0.05,"('bell', 'PERSON'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 4; ('Newgate', 'ORG'): 3; ('Monday', 'DATE'): 2; ('11. 1643', 'DATE'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('english', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('bridge', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John Pym', 'PERSON'): 2; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1643', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tyburn Decemb', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Henry', 'GPE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('a hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last week', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('t•t', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cajetan', 'GPE'): 1; ('mirabilis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('harden', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nottinghams house', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tillet', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('6000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gray inn .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tavistocke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Decemb', 'ORG'): 1; ('8. 1643', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A71096,62,conclusion Christians contemplation Christ delectation knowledge thing life mean thing,god: 0.4; man: 0.4; thing: 0.4; contemplation: 0.4; delight: 0.4; love: 0.4; light: 0.35; scripture: 0.35; world: 0.3; christians: 0.3; christ: 0.2; persecution: 0.1; people: 0.1; philosopher: 0.1; person: 0.1; perseverance: 0.1; piece: 0.1; perfection: 0.1; pain: 0.1; part: 0.1; pitch: 0.1; divine: 0.1,"('Christians', 'NORP'): 7; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('one day', 'DATE'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('xv', 'ORG'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Xvi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Tully', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hortensius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cicero', 'FAC'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1"
A71096,88,CHAP. Xviii conclusion way exhortation reason discourse way care self,thing: 0.5; man: 0.5; body: 0.5; evil: 0.5; life: 0.5; church: 0.5; saint: 0.5; make: 0.5; place: 0.35; god: 0.3; decease: 0.2; mind: 0.05; catholic: 0.05; manner: 0.05,"('catholic', 'NORP'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Xviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('persian', 'NORP'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('saint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mortuis', 'GPE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paulin', 'GPE'): 1; ('CHAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paulinus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Flora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cynegius', 'NORP'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('Enchiridion ad Laurentium', 'ORG'): 1; ('110', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phlegeton', 'PERSON'): 1"
A71096,108,guide heaven man duty interest heaven lose undo whole world,god: 0.5; heart: 0.5; man: 0.5; self: 0.5; heaven: 0.5; christ: 0.5; soul: 0.45; line: 0.4; way: 0.35; world: 0.3; people: 0.3; thing: 0.1; precept: 0.1,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('saint H.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egomet', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('9.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('A. Churchill', 'PERSON'): 1; ('W. Churchill', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dorset', 'ORG'): 1; ('1687', 'DATE'): 1; ('brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('quaesiveris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the great day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('28.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A70327,16,CHAP. Xiii conclusion whole certainty happiness care work child espouse,soul: 0.5; god: 0.5; world: 0.5; man: 0.5; day: 0.5; work: 0.45; time: 0.45; self: 0.4; lord: 0.35; sin: 0.35; heart: 0.3; christ: 0.15; child: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 10; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 9; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 3; ('tender year', 'DATE'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('their young year', 'DATE'): 2; ('night', 'TIME'): 2; ('Jam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 2; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('a week', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Xiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ethiopian', 'NORP'): 1; ('all the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('these year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fifty year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('ibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('grey hair', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('2.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('si caetera discis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('100', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('100 mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('their season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Feri', 'ORG'): 1; ('feri', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quando', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('all day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('that little short hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 17', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.1', 'DATE'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A78222,5 | 2989,doctrine viz. subjection subjection creature creature father name Christ think,name: 0.5; jesus: 0.5; text: 0.5; god: 0.45; divine: 0.45; man: 0.45; church: 0.45; honour: 0.45; canon: 0.35; duty: 0.25; command: 0.2; knee: 0.1; power: 0.05; prerogative: 0.05; prefer: 0.05; preach: 0.05; pre: 0.05; prayer: 0.05; practise: 0.05,"('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 40; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Antiteichisma', 'GPE'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('38', 'DATE'): 2; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 2; ('William', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Iehovah', 'ORG'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Babington', 'GPE'): 2; ('Willet', 'PERSON'): 2; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the late crazy day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lewes in', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Sussex', 'GPE'): 1; ('July 1635', 'DATE'): 1; ('the loose day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the late the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 1; ('54', 'DATE'): 1; ('107', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('poteris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eve•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41.45', 'MONEY'): 1; ('33.3', 'MONEY'): 1; ('18.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 17.6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('1. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ponere fulmina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eccl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greedy wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('1603', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antiteich', 'ORG'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hooker', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aug. Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('110', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ianu', 'GPE'): 1; ('section Xviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Andrew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iustifi', 'GPE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sup', 'ORG'): 1; ('beati immacul .', 'ORG'): 1"
A78222,5 | 3035,business prove Text. peruse prelate bishop Andrew word opinion duty,name: 0.35; text: 0.35; jesus: 0.35; knee: 0.35; god: 0.35; subjection: 0.3; man: 0.3; thing: 0.25; king: 0.25; place: 0.2; reason: 0.2; authority: 0.15; quiet: 0.15; prelate: 0.15; proof: 0.15; prove: 0.15; psal: 0.15; psalmist: 0.15; put: 0.15; question: 0.15; preach: 0.15; church: 0.1; ground: 0.1; time: 0.05,"('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 11; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Iustifi', 'GPE'): 2; ('18.21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Andrew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Babington', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pa. 22', 'GPE'): 1; ('Catho', 'ORG'): 1; ('197', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ha•e do', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zanch', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. Scrip', 'ORG'): 1; ('423', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam etiam verbales', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anabaptist', 'NORP'): 1; ('Horat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quicunque', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sacrilega', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Perniciem', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Pagi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.9.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('63.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('n•t', 'PERSON'): 1"
A78222,6,answer pretend answer pretence name Jesus name Jesus get deal,name: 0.5; jesus: 0.5; christ: 0.5; god: 0.5; king: 0.5; reason: 0.5; title: 0.5; jew: 0.5; honour: 0.4; lord: 0.4; man: 0.1; time: 0.1,"('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 46; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 19; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 10; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Antiteichisma', 'GPE'): 3; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Pilate', 'ORG'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('possess•d', 'ORG'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vain•', 'ORG'): 1; ('63.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hesiod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zanchius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.9', 'DATE'): 1; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('13.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('encounter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nazareth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Atqui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('beleev•d', 'ORG'): 1; ('Andrew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioh', 'GPE'): 1; ('19 v. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iehovah', 'ORG'): 1; ('sai•h', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 1; ('245', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('65', 'DATE'): 1; ('m•n', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•eproach', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elohim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Messiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 9.22', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('n•me', 'ORG'): 1; ('sixthly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A78222,7,break force viper head way mother side crush foot respect,part: 0.5; sect: 0.4; god: 0.4; son: 0.4; father: 0.4; name: 0.4; honour: 0.4; christ: 0.4; jesus: 0.4; glory: 0.2; trinity: 0.1; performance: 0.1; permit: 0.1; ode: 0.1; opinion: 0.1; order: 0.1; page: 0.1; par: 0.1; pay: 0.1; obates: 0.1; man: 0.1,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 19; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 19; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 9; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 6; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('angel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a few minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('one day of the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iehovah', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('•orat', 'NORP'): 1; ('Diespiter', 'GPE'): 1; ('poena', 'ORG'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mascall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('avow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('opposita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('justice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('y•u', 'ORG'): 1; ('l. 25', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Egidius', 'ORG'): 1; ('90', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('divisa', 'ORG'): 1"
A75725,7,ʋse Iii trade trade man pursuit trade interest prejudice hindrance,heart: 0.5; world: 0.5; god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; man: 0.5; thought: 0.5; soul: 0.5; christ: 0.5; interest: 0.45; lord: 0.3; desire: 0.2; sin: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 28; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 7; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 5; ('this day', 'DATE'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 2; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 2; ('one day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Agrippa', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jehu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lucellum expergisci', 'PERSON'): 1; ('127', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rabbi Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('62.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jethro', 'GPE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('from morning to night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Shechem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dinah', 'GPE'): 1; ('34.', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rachel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('fourteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six year', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gen. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('41', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('trap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Naaman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rimmon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('incurvavit', 'GPE'): 1; ('erueret aurum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam possidendum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cordis vita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alsted', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theol', 'GPE'): 1; ('613', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jonathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jonathan saul son', 'PERSON'): 1; ('delight much', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod appetitui satisfacit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Reynolds', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 1; ('197', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa. 63. 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lebanon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Assyria', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bethshemesh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Benjamin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nabal', 'ORG'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 33', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('49.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'NORP'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernice', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('20. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ezek', 'ORG'): 1; ('33. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('grace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('horret caro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nimirum crucem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jonah 4. 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Petrarch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Goliath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('another day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Euphrates', 'ORG'): 1; ('57 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('miserius misero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('miserante seipsum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 1; ('7. 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('grey hair', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israelem', 'GPE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A78461,1,material case conscience kingdom perplex clear pain assembly London I.,parliament: 0.5; king: 0.5; oath: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; conscience: 0.5; kingdom: 0.45; power: 0.45; word: 0.4; time: 0.3; way: 0.2; sword: 0.05; thing: 0.05; contrary: 0.05; religion: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('christian', 'NORP'): 9; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('England', 'GPE'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('London', 'GPE'): 3; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Jonathan', 'PERSON'): 3; ('so many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Scot', 'PERSON'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('scottish', 'NORP'): 2; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jonathan 1 Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tailor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('554', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('presbyterians', 'NORP'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('xi', 'ORG'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lecturers', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('article 35', 'LAW'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eccles 5.4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deaconty', 'ORG'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('some 30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('some 40. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xvi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Henry 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Manifesto', 'GPE'): 1; ('9.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ananias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saphira', 'ORG'): 1; ('rob Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 1; ('2.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty-one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xxii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1500', 'DATE'): 1; ('Genevae', 'NORP'): 1; ('shine light', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('73.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty-five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Davids', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vriah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rebuke Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xxvii', 'GPE'): 1; ('the bless day', 'DATE'): 1; ('those golden day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elizabeth day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xxviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Job', 'ORG'): 1; ('twenty-nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('24.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 1; ('10.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xxxi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('quam semper', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1645', 'DATE'): 1"
A78099,21,explication office god grace perform part preface work other talon,god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; hymn: 0.5; glory: 0.5; sheep: 0.5; word: 0.5; father: 0.5; office: 0.3; son: 0.3; man: 0.3; heart: 0.2; people: 0.2; day: 0.1; divine: 0.05; praise: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Alleluia', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('li', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Septuagesima', 'GPE'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Durandus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Nicene', 'ORG'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('S. Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('94', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S.', 'ORG'): 1; ('Berachoth', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Benedict', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rationa', 'GPE'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('loco cit', 'ORG'): 1; ('num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Colla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 3.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cassian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Surius', 'ORG'): 1; ('144', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Ierome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Damasus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three hundred and eighteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Sp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sancto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Basill', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tom 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('A. D. 382', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Confes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Suarez', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('146', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('99', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Stephen Durantus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alleluia', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Consecr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint John damascene li 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine week', 'DATE'): 1; ('the ten week', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hymn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('137', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ierome', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marcelia', 'ORG'): 1; ('each day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peter Damian Tom 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('invito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('only two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hebr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hebrews', 'PERSON'): 1; ('so many year before', 'DATE'): 1; ('another day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1"
A78099,64,morning night• Israel lord begin day end night man people,god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; self: 0.5; israel: 0.5; people: 0.45; christ: 0.45; eye: 0.4; heart: 0.4; mother: 0.35; word: 0.2; man: 0.2; glory: 0.2; soul: 0.15; thing: 0.1; night: 0.05; mercy: 0.05,"('Israel', 'GPE'): 6; ('thou', 'GPE'): 6; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 2; ('night', 'TIME'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Symeon', 'ORG'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('day or night', 'TIME'): 1; ('130', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('precep•t', 'ORG'): 1; ('Prouer', 'ORG'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pseudo Apostles', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•o', 'NORP'): 1; ('•uill', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('conuen•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('adie be institute', 'ORG'): 1; ('ordain', 'GPE'): 1"
A78099,66,antiquity reformation observation Turk triangle rest world roundhead show difference,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; policy: 0.5; light: 0.5; law: 0.5; king: 0.45; religion: 0.35; reformation: 0.35; turk: 0.3; father: 0.3; church: 0.2; world: 0.2; heaven: 0.15; rest: 0.1; day: 0.05; opinion: 0.05,"('Turk', 'PERSON'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 3; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1609', 'DATE'): 2; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 2; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 2; ('3 day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('B. Alsop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('R. Harper', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Smithfield', 'GPE'): 1; ('1647', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dyonisius the Areopagite', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babel', 'GPE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('360', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('about 15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sergius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Maximus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Astia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cairo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Arabia', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sibbs', 'GPE'): 1; ('Andrew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('lucis mundi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod cum facis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ille momendo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laudat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('acta suo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mercantall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Normans', 'NORP'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Orpheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Daniell', 'ORG'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Philip de Comines', 'ORG'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Par', 'ORG'): 1; ('3 month', 'DATE'): 1; ('shun murder', 'PERSON'): 1; ('imprimatur', 'NORP'): 1; ('John downame', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward Bagshaw', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Coronae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vinculo Juramenti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Regist', 'NORP'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antiqua Maneria Coronae', 'ORG'): 1; ('regi non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rex Coronae', 'ORG'): 1; ('tenetur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Fleta', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul Church-yard', 'ORG'): 1; ('1660', 'DATE'): 1; ('June the 29th 1644', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A77186,4 | 5191,law consent right justice ground man poet place reason reason,king: 0.45; lord: 0.45; law: 0.45; power: 0.45; people: 0.45; house: 0.45; commons: 0.4; hen: 0.4; man: 0.35; parliament: 0.3; god: 0.25; plague: 0.05; pleasure: 0.05; piscator: 0.05; pl: 0.05; place: 0.05; piece: 0.05; plea: 0.05; plutarch: 0.05; plot: 0.05; person: 0.05; distinction: 0.05; prince: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 17; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('England', 'GPE'): 9; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 2; ('Richard 2', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('above 2000 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.40 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ket', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('parens patriae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two second', 'TIME'): 1; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trussell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('W. Raul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Capitalis Justiciarius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('totius angliae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five and fifty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Fitz', 'ORG'): 1; ('nat', 'ORG'): 1; ('brev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cummonitis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bracton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('part f .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('64', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Killingworth', 'GPE'): 1; ('almost two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('last first', 'DATE'): 1; ('almost threescore year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tacitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('dictum de Killingworth', 'ORG'): 1; ('1556', 'DATE'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Par', 'ORG'): 1; ('R.', 'NORP'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Comines', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hooker Eccl', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sparta', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hammond', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bracton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bracton Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvins', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the 10th year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cobham', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cok', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Walter Raleigh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twofold', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('magi', 'NORP'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Briareus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('more than a three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the house of commons shall', 'ORG'): 1; ('Edw', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the first year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the king commission', 'ORG'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('Parl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mag', 'GPE'): 1; ('Charta', 'GPE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sciatis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('emendationem Regni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; (""fitz l'"", 'ORG'): 1; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 1; ('York', 'GPE'): 1"
A79498,1,protector parliament fear God Zion sin high-place Jah blast lightning,place: 0.5; god: 0.5; steeple: 0.5; temple: 0.5; idol: 0.5; man: 0.5; people: 0.5; lord: 0.4; parliament: 0.3; thing: 0.2; time: 0.1; worship: 0.1; year: 0.05; cross: 0.05; high: 0.05; name: 0.05; top: 0.05; house: 0.05; deut: 0.05; day: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Gloucester', 'GPE'): 3; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('17', 'DATE'): 2; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Devon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('valiant swordman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('NAaman', 'ORG'): 1; ('syrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.10', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('28.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these 1600 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mount Zion', 'GPE'): 1; ('15 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('idol temple', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Botolphs', 'ORG'): 1; ('Boston', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lincolnsh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Babylonish', 'NORP'): 1; ('i diverse year', 'DATE'): 1; ('24 day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the 11 month , 1652', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chidley', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('the last first day', 'DATE'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('sexton', 'ORG'): 1; ('Parker', 'ORG'): 1"
A73571,31,Isaac Abraham flesh Ishmael spirit Machmad nation poison world Isaac,christ: 0.5; heaven: 0.5; god: 0.5; isaac: 0.5; son: 0.5; jacob: 0.5; soul: 0.45; joseph: 0.4; egypt: 0.25; death: 0.2; abraham: 0.15; hope: 0.15; patriarch: 0.15; year: 0.1; name: 0.1; father: 0.05,"('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 7; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 7; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 7; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 6; ('215', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 5; ('Aram', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Thamar', 'GPE'): 4; ('Aminadab', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Isaac', 'ORG'): 2; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 2; ('Bethel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ezron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Plato', 'ORG'): 2; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Machmad', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isaac', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abrahams', 'ORG'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('53', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('70', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaac ben Arama', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Siphri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaak', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gehennia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Symeon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Levy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 1; ('Benjamin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bicrj', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iosep', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mathusala', 'GPE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('70', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Mathevv', 'ORG'): 1; ('Messiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zara', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Pascha', 'ORG'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six year', 'DATE'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('60', 'DATE'): 1; ('130', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chanaā', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fgypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('430', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Genebrard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('430 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('moo•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maurice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Chanaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iosephs', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ammi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noe', 'GPE'): 1; ('Diodorus Siculus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Homer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lerned', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clemens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Eusebuis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theodoret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('300 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Symbolon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vveael', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ireneus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lerned Caius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zorobabel', 'GPE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1"
A73571,90,D. infirmity l. l. Lev. l. mourning E. a. whetstone,part: 0.5; man: 0.5; book: 0.5; government: 0.5; say: 0.5; lord: 0.5; england: 0.45; general: 0.4; god: 0.3; honour: 0.3; name: 0.2; cause: 0.15; ireland: 0.05; person: 0.05; parliament: 0.05; army: 0.05,"('lin', 'PERSON'): 11; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('a. lin', 'PERSON'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('30', 'DATE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('free-quarter', 'DATE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('whetstone', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11 i .', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. 10', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinacria', 'ORG'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. H. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('rodanim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('I. 1.', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('caari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Matthew Simmons', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1649', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lilburne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Walwins', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pasquil', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scarerow', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fairfax', 'GPE'): 1; ('CROMWEL', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cato Major', 'ORG'): 1; ('odijs exercitus est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quadragy enim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('causam dixit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sabel l. 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam domi cum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui contempti habentur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pralium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('375', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('superat', 'ORG'): 1; ('conscientia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Tiberius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rh•scuporis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fider•', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('mutetque virorem', 'PERSON'): 1"
A79828,4,accusation ground lie England p. officer soldier slight discountenance vote,man: 0.5; thing: 0.5; officer: 0.5; truth: 0.5; scandal: 0.5; way: 0.5; people: 0.45; word: 0.3; england: 0.25; reason: 0.25; slander: 0.2; army: 0.15; report: 0.15; book: 0.15; relation: 0.05; place: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('England', 'GPE'): 8; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Lilburne', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the council of war', 'ORG'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Tacit', 'ORG'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Walwyn', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the council of state', 'ORG'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('William Thomson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('twenty pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 1; ('council of state', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniels', 'ORG'): 1; ('Haman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sixthly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('walwin wile', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Answ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('viris quam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cont', 'GPE'): 1; ('16.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ziba', 'ORG'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mephibosheth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nulli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('sannigerratoris qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quum', 'GPE'): 1; ('infert mala', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nazianzen', 'LOC'): 1; ('•nsuetudin•m', 'PERSON'): 1; ('assidua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('natu•a•', 'GPE'): 1; ('s••eribus a•t••ctus', 'ORG'): 1; ('•i••ll•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('supera•omne', 'ORG'): 1; ('L. si confessus de c•st', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('340', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('paena claudo', 'ORG'): 1; ('ill forego', 'GPE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('l. 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('342', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pomfret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('shall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Perinnis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Henry Lilburn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tinmouth', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Machiavelli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesuite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Blaesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('potius', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam a', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Reipub', 'GPE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Newcastle', 'GPE'): 1; ('12 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Je•', 'GPE'): 1; ('9.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A79828,4 | 7069,Answ. encage pretense thing mean general largeness love affection land,man: 0.5; soldier: 0.5; army: 0.5; officer: 0.5; thing: 0.5; general: 0.5; council: 0.4; word: 0.4; people: 0.4; liberty: 0.25; cause: 0.1; report: 0.1; way: 0.1; book: 0.05; england: 0.05; page: 0.05; mutiny: 0.05; captain: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('England', 'GPE'): 6; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('John', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the grand year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Lilburne', 'GPE'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Arnold', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('m•n', 'PERSON'): 2; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Strafford', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('dona', 'ORG'): 1; ('Danaum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ʋlisses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aeneld', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 12', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pellicalam', 'ORG'): 1; ('v••id•', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alcoran', 'PERSON'): 1; ('musul manem servati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thomson', 'ORG'): 1; ('nam', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Legato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pannony', 'GPE'): 1; ('ducis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Valerius Max', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Skott', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bray', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Windsor', 'GPE'): 1; ('74', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Vibulenus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tacit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hartford', 'GPE'): 1; ('Newcastle', 'GPE'): 1; ('Albanes', 'GPE'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('jussus erat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('liv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hockley', 'ORG'): 1; ('the same night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Olney', 'LOC'): 1; ('Northamptonshire', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dunstable', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam mihi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('no•••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tyburn', 'ORG'): 1; ('twelve month', 'DATE'): 1; ('Walwyns', 'ORG'): 1; ('thievish', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lapis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('o•••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fairfax', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hasletig', 'ORG'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Libellus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('decay parson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Latins', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesuite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Musculus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('H. B.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hortano l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('verba au•••m', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tus', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('council of state', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Lilburne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Magestrates', 'GPE'): 1; ('74.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•5', 'ORG'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('Corah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abiram', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leyden', 'GPE'): 1; ('doctori cum culpa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jack straw', 'PERSON'): 1; ('w•t Tiler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trapp', 'ORG'): 1; ('s•i', 'ORG'): 1; ('Astnus Asino', 'ORG'): 1; ('equis simile', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of war', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Colchester', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alban', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Reynalds', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Holland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rigby', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arnolds', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cornelius Fuscus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vitellium', 'GPE'): 1; ('nihil spei', 'ORG'): 1; ('sibi inter adversa reliquerat', 'ORG'): 1; ('423', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jack', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plautus', 'ORG'): 1; ('captivis', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sollomons', 'ORG'): 1; ('10 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lilburnes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Reinolds', 'PERSON'): 1"
A77250,3,CHAP. founder name institution name constitution society Sect. elate church,name: 0.5; jesuit: 0.5; jesus: 0.5; sect: 0.5; ignatius: 0.5; society: 0.5; pope: 0.45; rule: 0.4; obedience: 0.4; paul: 0.25; hist: 0.2; institution: 0.2; constitution: 0.05; king: 0.05,"('§', 'NORP'): 14; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 13; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 10; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('§', 'PERSON'): 5; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Paul Iii', 'PERSON'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ignat', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ignatian', 'NORP'): 3; ('1549', 'DATE'): 3; ('Jo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('neiremb', 'PERSON'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Castille', 'GPE'): 2; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('L. Luc', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sleidan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ignat', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Hosp', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1580', 'DATE'): 2; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 2; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesuitism', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Polydor Virg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1366', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hetruria', 'GPE'): 1; ('ʋrban Vii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solanna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bareta', 'ORG'): 1; ('R. Hosp Lud', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucii Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 1491', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aspatheia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Biscay', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cantabria', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Vargas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Relat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Innicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Inighistus', 'ORG'): 1; ('1630', 'DATE'): 1; ('conveniunt rebus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nomina saepe', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maphaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Loyolae l. 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sociis Salmanassar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ferdinand court', 'ORG'): 1; ('austrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Spaniards', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pampelona', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pompeiolis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Navarre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pyrenaean', 'NORP'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ignatius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the catholic King', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacob Crusius Rect', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maritimi belli munia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Armado', 'DATE'): 1; ('Madrid Alph', 'FAC'): 1; ('annual', 'DATE'): 1; ('1000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de Cannonizit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Valderama', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aetna', 'ORG'): 1; ('Impetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('26 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the holy sepulchre', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salamanca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Complutum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alcala de Hevares', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('ten year', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('1. 1537', 'DATE'): 1; ('Henry Viii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luthers', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calvins Genebrard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('grandeiur', 'ORG'): 1; ('mdxl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1540', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thuan', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tom 1. l.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('novo ac ut pleris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nomine appellati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bez.', 'ORG'): 1; ('Linwood Constitut', 'ORG'): 1; ('vindicet ipse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sibi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apostolorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('contubernalis jactant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('apostle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('1.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mi deus', 'ORG'): 1; ('tuum', 'GPE'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daemonum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vergerius Baldus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bezae Epig', 'LOC'): 1; ('quas erebo emittens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('procul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam pater', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ignatius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Accipio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('procul ab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Digna Patre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('procul item', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Ignatius le grand', 'LAW'): 1; ('Valderama', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Digitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('120 year proof', 'DATE'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eumenidum thalami', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Viperium', 'GPE'): 1; ('horrendum stridens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chimaera , Gorgones', 'ORG'): 1; ('Harpyae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gorgon', 'ORG'): 1; ('L. Lucii Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Regul', 'GPE'): 1; ('1588', 'DATE'): 1; ('Turks', 'NORP'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('l. 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('totius mundi dominos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lugd', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1607', 'DATE'): 1; ('254', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caeca', 'ORG'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Regul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dutch', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maphaeus de vita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve month', 'DATE'): 1; ('L. Luc.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ignat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Reg Jesuit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quakers', 'ORG'): 1; ('Regulae Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('76', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Balaus Vergerus', 'ORG'): 1; ('epicuraean', 'NORP'): 1; ('Iulius Iii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Innocentius de monte', 'ORG'): 1; ('1546', 'DATE'): 1; ('1551', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul IV.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('suavis l. 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pius IV.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1561', 'DATE'): 1; ('1565', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sess', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 1568', 'DATE'): 1; ('1571 73.', 'DATE'): 1; ('76', 'DATE'): 1; ('Trent', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Paul V.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eliz', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thuan', 'LOC'): 1; ('heresy', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be observe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('no less than 36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('W. C. Jesuit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bull 1549', 'DATE'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Spaniards', 'PERSON'): 1; ('their first century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1543', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lewis Owen Jesuit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1629', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lud', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1550', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lucius Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('141', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('142', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Delegate', 'ORG'): 1; ('1568', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesu•t', 'PERSON'): 1"
A77250,3 | 9329,Holland •ngland ignatians dress merchant trade company knack confession secret,jesuit: 0.5; faith: 0.5; god: 0.5; college: 0.5; king: 0.45; year: 0.4; christ: 0.35; society: 0.35; pope: 0.35; mouth: 0.25; blood: 0.2; book: 0.2; fire: 0.2; man: 0.1; hand: 0.05; saint: 0.05; hist: 0.05,"('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 12; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('§', 'NORP'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Hosp', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('156', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('France', 'GPE'): 3; ('L. Lucii', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 3; ('Ignatian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('italian', 'NORP'): 2; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('§', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Bavaria', 'GPE'): 2; ('Id.', 'GPE'): 2; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 2; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Portugal', 'GPE'): 2; ('Poland', 'GPE'): 2; ('3d', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('venetian', 'NORP'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1608', 'DATE'): 2; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Antwerp', 'GPE'): 2; ('french', 'NORP'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Holland', 'GPE'): 1; ('•ngland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pius V.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Spaniards', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ignat', 'ORG'): 1; ('1556', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ja', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laynez', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1565', 'DATE'): 1; ('Borgia', 'GPE'): 1; ('1572', 'DATE'): 1; ('1581', 'DATE'): 1; ('1615', 'DATE'): 1; ('they|will', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christi Vicarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul IV', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1558', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul Iii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1550', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('L. Lucii Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Monachium Id.', 'FAC'): 1; ('Ingolstad', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thuan', 'ORG'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregory Xiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ireland Ciracella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('145', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1611', 'DATE'): 1; ('4000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lud', 'ORG'): 1; ('L. Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('171', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prague', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bohemia', 'GPE'): 1; ('500', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('some hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Magazeen', 'DATE'): 1; ('Posnania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lublin', 'GPE'): 1; ('polish', 'NORP'): 1; ('proximâ quan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Borgia Schot', 'ORG'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Borgiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quot collegia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Castilia', 'GPE'): 1; ('157', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul V.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('swan', 'GPE'): 1; ('50 year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hasen', 'NORP'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2000000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60 year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Barrisonius the Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bononia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apr. 21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('163', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Transylvania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peter Cotton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sicily', 'GPE'): 1; ('Belgia', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('earl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ib', 'NORP'): 1; ('marquis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('cum spirituali', 'ORG'): 1; ('169', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the holy Jesus', 'ORG'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('5.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mercure Jesuite', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('1622', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cracow', 'GPE'): 1; ('40 year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('John Baptista', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fransciscus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salamanca', 'ORG'): 1; ('333', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1641', 'DATE'): 1; ('Xii', 'LOC'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('1658', 'DATE'): 1; ('x.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('less than 40 year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('W. crashaw', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Turselinus Greg', 'FAC'): 1; ('Gretzerus C. Sribanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bonarscius Ant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Possevin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lipsius', 'ORG'): 1; ('1605', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ignat', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scribannius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Palaeopoli', 'GPE'): 1; ('1606', 'DATE'): 1; ('Apparat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tom 1. light', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('356', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('crashaw', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haereo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lateris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Matris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non possem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lac', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sanguinem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Loyolan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Chemnitius Theolog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Doctrinae Jes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rupellae 1589', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1598', 'DATE'): 1; ('Genev', 'GPE'): 1; ('1653', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elias Hausenmullerus Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ordin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1595', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('pool', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oxon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tillotson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('the french Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('1643', 'DATE'): 1; (""mouns d'st"", 'PERSON'): 1; ('Contin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the english Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mathias Wilson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Floyd', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward Knott', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel of Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pestifera', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apostolorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Regula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('mounsieur de saint', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sorbonne', 'GPE'): 1; ('gallican', 'NORP'): 1; ('donna Olimpia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prudential', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('120', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Oct. 1651', 'DATE'): 1; ('about a quarter of a year', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1651', 'DATE'): 1; ('78', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('June 9 1653', 'DATE'): 1; ('431', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cathedrâ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Provinc Let', 'PERSON'): 1; ('343', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mar. 24.', 'DATE'): 1; ('1657', 'DATE'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five proposition', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Jansenius Gazet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prefat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1627', 'DATE'): 1; ('40. year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Naetetians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Anthropomorphites', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Carpocratians', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Manichees', 'GPE'): 1; ('massilians', 'NORP'): 1; ('pelagians', 'NORP'): 1; ('mahometans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Priscillianists', 'NORP'): 1"
A77250,3 | 9367,mouse do will puss pate heart sincerity decree April order,jesuit: 0.5; king: 0.5; man: 0.5; practise: 0.5; jes: 0.5; fire: 0.5; hosp: 0.45; paris: 0.25; father: 0.25; proph: 0.2; god: 0.2; son: 0.15; bishop: 0.15; word: 0.1; luc: 0.05; ignatian: 0.05; year: 0.05; sect: 0.05; order: 0.05,"('§', 'NORP'): 14; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 13; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 8; ('Jo', 'PERSON'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Hosp', 'PERSON'): 5; ('France', 'GPE'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 4; ('Ignatian', 'NORP'): 4; ('§', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Myst', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Proph', 'GPE'): 3; ('Mariana', 'PERSON'): 2; ('128', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1000', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Loyolan', 'GPE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Vulcan', 'NORP'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Proph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ignatius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Luc', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Prague', 'GPE'): 2; ('fulf', 'PERSON'): 2; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hildegard', 'ORG'): 2; ('Antwerp', 'GPE'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Spec', 'PERSON'): 2; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('Portugal', 'GPE'): 2; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 2; ('italian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('154', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John Chastle', 'PERSON'): 2; ('April 9 1612', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aquaviva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Suarez', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1626', 'DATE'): 1; ('Swarez', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mutius Vitelescus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paris D. Du', 'FAC'): 1; ('Moulin Vindic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('P. Cotton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ignatians', 'NORP'): 1; ('••ey', 'NORP'): 1; ('thoug• ◊ general assembly', 'ORG'): 1; ('gallican', 'NORP'): 1; ('1642', 'DATE'): 1; ('remonstrance Add', 'PERSON'): 1; ('125', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('130', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('135', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('138', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bonasus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ignigeni', 'NORP'): 1; ('W.P.', 'ORG'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vargas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam ille', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vulcani', 'NORP'): 1; ('Quaqua', 'GPE'): 1; ('calefacit', 'ORG'): 1; ('forlese', 'NORP'): 1; ('Burn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('mar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter Jacridge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Coynings', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jams Beauf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('1658', 'DATE'): 1; ('Thes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('2.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 7.23', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hildeg', 'GPE'): 1; ('fulfil p.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('W.P. Pref', 'ORG'): 1; ('4 hundred 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ignatius Loyola', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xaverius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Taylor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('225 249', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('F. Doza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('these last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ignatius Hosp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aldermanbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cacodaemon', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('432', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('F. Cotton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('L. Luc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('172', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae filo inserti', 'ORG'): 1; ('numerat', 'NORP'): 1; ('murmura baccis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50. 51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thievish', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1640', 'DATE'): 1; ('Scaliger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Causabon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jurata lingua est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 10. 52', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luther , Calvin , Beza', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Pistol', 'ORG'): 1; ('Landsperg', 'GPE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 37', 'DATE'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Th', 'ORG'): 1; ('accipe dum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('trojan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('they|will', 'ORG'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('201', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lupanaria Romae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gennese', 'NORP'): 1; ('Venetians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Summerman the Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Switzerland', 'GPE'): 1; ('199', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('228', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Padua', 'GPE'): 1; ('Friburg', 'GPE'): 1; ('Corduba', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heidelberg', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesuitism l. 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('132', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('Merc', 'ORG'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Horace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mox daturo', 'ORG'): 1; ('vitiosiorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('crimine ab uno disce omnes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Poland Hosp', 'ORG'): 1; ('195', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jubet .', 'GPE'): 1; ('Crucigerorum Spurii', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antonio Barberino', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scarl', 'ORG'): 1; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nella Marca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bordeaux', 'FAC'): 1; ('at least 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('respect pseud-apostoli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('48', 'DATE'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christianismi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Onan', 'GPE'): 1; ('60.', 'DATE'): 1; ('year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('1603', 'DATE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1632', 'DATE'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Princ', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lemma of Loyolas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Turkey', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('the Ignatian Rooks', 'ORG'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('1. L.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('221', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Toledo', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Prato', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clermont', 'GPE'): 1; ('1550', 'DATE'): 1; ('60000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('crown', 'ORG'): 1; ('1554', 'DATE'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Francis iid .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Guise', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Card', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('225', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1561', 'DATE'): 1; ('Charles Moulin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the university of Paris', 'ORG'): 1; ('226', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('227', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pasquerius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter Tersorius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('229', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Renat', 'NORP'): 1; ('1672', 'DATE'): 1; ('Belg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('52.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Joan Albreta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Navarre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Conde', 'ORG'): 1; ('Grosse', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bartholomew day the same year', 'DATE'): 1; ('70000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Legate', 'ORG'): 1; ('three month', 'DATE'): 1; ('100000', 'DATE'): 1; ('50', 'DATE'): 1; ('1577', 'DATE'): 1; ('Henry Iii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('151', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Franc', 'ORG'): 1; ('James Clement', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dominican', 'NORP'): 1; ('1589', 'DATE'): 1; ('P. Sixtus V.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('152', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sept. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('same year', 'DATE'): 1; ('four year', 'DATE'): 1; ('F. Camolet', 'GPE'): 1; ('J. Clement', 'ORG'): 1; ('153', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1593', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ehud', 'ORG'): 1; ('P. Barier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('the 29th', 'DATE'): 1; ('F. Cammolet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Picardy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the age of 19', 'DATE'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('F. Gneret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Guignard Jesuit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('156', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bratholomew', 'FAC'): 1; ('Jan. 7. 1595', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gneret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Guignard', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luc', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('382', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('385', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('C. Scribanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander hay', 'PERSON'): 1"
A77250,3 | 9401,sect V. loyolan be year burn sea conflagration city solemnity,fire: 0.5; house: 0.5; jesuit: 0.5; papist: 0.5; london: 0.5; another: 0.5; hand: 0.45; man: 0.4; thing: 0.35; place: 0.3; take: 0.2; burn: 0.1; god: 0.1; flame: 0.05; way: 0.05,"('London', 'GPE'): 18; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 17; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 10; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 9; ('§', 'NORP'): 7; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Hubert', 'PERSON'): 4; ('french', 'NORP'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('Cracow', 'GPE'): 2; ('Poland', 'GPE'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Thursday', 'DATE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tuesday', 'DATE'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Troy', 'GPE'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('these late year', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jamblicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('146', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the late fire 1666', 'DATE'): 1; ('Amos 3.6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Digitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Londinum', 'GPE'): 1; ('annual', 'DATE'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('§', 'PERSON'): 1; ('C. s. §', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 3. 4. 3. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Madrid', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thonon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('magna charta burn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Posnania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Briga', 'GPE'): 1; ('Silesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('86', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('87', 'DATE'): 1; ('92', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dublin', 'GPE'): 1; ('August 1666', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('about 1666', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that year', 'DATE'): 1; ('1500', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1652', 'DATE'): 1; ('the succeed year', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('wiseman civil law l.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Par', 'ORG'): 1; ('quid quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Menochius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Stat Capitolini', 'ORG'): 1; ('Postulata', 'EVENT'): 1; ('a half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six day of', 'DATE'): 1; ('September 1666', 'DATE'): 1; ('373.', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('89', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('parish church', 'ORG'): 1; ('thirteen thousand too hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Idonei', 'ORG'): 1; ('pro se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('Reos', 'ORG'): 1; ('Holborn', 'GPE'): 1; ('Kingsstreet', 'GPE'): 1; ('three hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wiseman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('F. Cotton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scribanius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Huguenot', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apologie', 'ORG'): 1; ('Answ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four year of age', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peidlow', 'ORG'): 1; ('about 1595', 'DATE'): 1; ('D. W. D. Horae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('53', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ramford', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hicks', 'ORG'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. p.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry 3d.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Langhorn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six month', 'DATE'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('April', 'DATE'): 1; ('between June and October', 'DATE'): 1; ('Temple-bar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fitz-Harris', 'ORG'): 1; ('irish', 'NORP'): 1; ('July', 'DATE'): 1; ('September', 'DATE'): 1; ('Yazley', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ilford', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aug. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Aleuson', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aug. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Belk', 'GPE'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aug. 30th', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Saint-George', 'PERSON'): 1; ('George', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two day', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one week', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Holcroft Septemb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('the evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('Troja', 'GPE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Frenchman Septemb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('West-smithfield', 'GPE'): 1; ('Frenchman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Monday', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Septemb', 'GPE'): 1; ('the same day one', 'DATE'): 1; ('King-street', 'GPE'): 1; ('300', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bridewell', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laurence Poultneys', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bayley', 'ORG'): 1; ('saint antholins church', 'FAC'): 1; ('9 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('several hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('leaden-hall-street', 'FAC'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A78308,1,glass time scripture minister Christ teacher collection error time author,error: 0.45; god: 0.45; christ: 0.45; rom: 0.45; matth: 0.45; john: 0.45; man: 0.45; encage: 0.35; tim: 0.2; scripture: 0.2; minister: 0.15; london: 0.15; soul: 0.15; heb: 0.1; nature: 0.05; name: 0.05; overseer: 0.05; original: 0.05; ordinance: 0.05; opinion: 0.05; oath: 0.05; part: 0.05; mortal: 0.05; pet: 0.05; word: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 17; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 10; ('London', 'GPE'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Confut', 'PERSON'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 3; ('4', 'DATE'): 3; ('Confu', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4.1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'DATE'): 2; ('Lond', 'ORG'): 2; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('3.11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19.4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('T. C.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Robert Ibbitson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1648', 'DATE'): 1; ('gift', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 21.16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.41', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.79', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('16.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('55.10.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.54', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 6.27 it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119.130', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('false prophet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('railer', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.8 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph 4.14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Laurence Clarkson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 5.39', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('J. G. 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5 46', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('18.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Bidle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('45.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.3 . 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 1.14.3.16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul Best', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 4.42 .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Timoth', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('L.S. 1', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('9.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('R. O. Cit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27.50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.4 . 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('P. Hobson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cit', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lond', 'LOC'): 1; ('1.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('H. Hammond', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London Test', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philip 2.8', 'ORG'): 1; ('J. S.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.19.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 1.33', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Johns Baptisine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Confutat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Johnh 1.33', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.4 . 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('10.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gorton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('R. Williams', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A79834,15,Corinthians holiness God man time bless Sivillians sect Pharisee garb,god: 0.5; truth: 0.5; aegidio: 0.5; day: 0.5; soul: 0.5; man: 0.45; lord: 0.4; death: 0.4; time: 0.35; doctor: 0.35; bless: 0.25; thing: 0.15; grace: 0.05; christ: 0.05; church: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('Seville', 'GPE'): 7; ('Arias', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Aria', 'GPE'): 5; ('Aegidio', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Constantino', 'ORG'): 4; ('Asoto', 'ORG'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two year', 'DATE'): 3; ('outward garb', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Varquio', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Aria', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ruizio', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 2; ('Granata', 'ORG'): 2; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Roderigo Valerio', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Nebrissa', 'GPE'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('Valerio', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('three year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sivillians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregorio Ruizio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isidore', 'ORG'): 1; ('whole day', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('yearly one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('grey hair', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Truly', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Aegidio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seville', 'ORG'): 1; ('irish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Danube', 'PERSON'): 1; ('st Lucar', 'GPE'): 1; ('the 50th year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Constantio Fontio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('varquia magno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Valerio de Nebrissa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Corrano', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dominico Asoto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the university of salamank', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten year', 'DATE'): 1; ('two or three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantio Fontie', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constantio Fontie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four in the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Toledo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Utica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fifteen day', 'DATE'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('no few than thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jane', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cacalla', 'ORG'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1"
A79834,17,instruction give king Spain inquisitor inquisition proceed proceed inquisition correction,god: 0.5; world: 0.5; inquisition: 0.5; book: 0.5; majesty: 0.35; sentence: 0.3; thing: 0.3; netherlands: 0.25; answer: 0.25; house: 0.2; day: 0.2; king: 0.15; print: 0.15; self: 0.15; mercy: 0.15; author: 0.1; apostate: 0.1; subject: 0.1; city: 0.1; heretic: 0.05; faith: 0.05; catholic: 0.05,"('Netherlands', 'GPE'): 5; ('England', 'GPE'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('this 30 day of January , 1642', 'DATE'): 2; ('the committee of the house of commons in parliament', 'ORG'): 2; ('Printing', 'ORG'): 2; ('John white', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Fidentine', 'GPE'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('one day', 'DATE'): 2; ('the 11th of may 1565', 'DATE'): 1; ('only some one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the king council', 'ORG'): 1; ('the catholic king', 'ORG'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Madrill', 'ORG'): 1; ('William bridge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Benjamin Allen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1642', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20. 10 , 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('1618', 'DATE'): 1; ('Herlicius Stargardensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('between twenty and thirty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cermany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1"
A79838,2 | 14481,kingdom king child pride pomp riot expect curse plague nation,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; state: 0.5; king: 0.5; people: 0.5; victory: 0.5; thing: 0.5; commonwealth: 0.45; hand: 0.25; lord: 0.25; blood: 0.2; nation: 0.15; country: 0.05; papist: 0.05; place: 0.05; enemy: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Scot', 'PERSON'): 3; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 3; ('irish', 'NORP'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Scots', 'ORG'): 3; ('Jones', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('don', 'PERSON'): 2; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ormond', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 2; ('Cato', 'ORG'): 2; ('liv', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hannibal', 'GPE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('more than one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bodin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Avidius Cassius', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seleucia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('22.3', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('poena', 'ORG'): 1; ('ill forego', 'GPE'): 1; ('Egyptians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Munster', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Connaught', 'ORG'): 1; ('derry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dublin', 'GPE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('19000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iireh', 'NORP'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Haman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abasuerus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('persian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('zicrono libraca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Orat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sicul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('C. Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sueton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lucan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('Valerius Corvinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rupert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Inchiqueen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leonidas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simonides', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tully', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spartae', 'ORG'): 1; ('sanctis', 'NORP'): 1; ('legibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('helvetian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Vereingetorix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vanquish Pompey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
