tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A27294,11,song page Erminias chamber door Amintas heart swain river bank,antichrist: 0.45; pope: 0.45; babylon: 0.45; god: 0.45; prince: 0.45; christian: 0.45; popery: 0.35; church: 0.35; apoc: 0.3; papist: 0.25; king: 0.25; people: 0.15; apo: 0.1; gospel: 0.1; papistry: 0.05; peace: 0.05; paul: 0.05; patron: 0.05; partaker: 0.05; persuader: 0.05; opposition: 0.05; opportunity: 0.05; christ: 0.05,"('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 21; ('christian', 'NORP'): 6; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 5; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Silvia', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 3; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Apo', 'PERSON'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 3; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14.', 'DATE'): 2; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Erminias', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sylvia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sylvia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Robert Bellarmine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('George dovvname', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cuthbert Burbie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1603', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('this seventeenth century', 'DATE'): 1; ('this age or century', 'DATE'): 1; ('the golden cup', 'FAC'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iericho', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('lord mouth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dagon 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sam 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('opugn Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these few year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Goliath', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antichristianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deu', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('18. 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('Apo', 'ORG'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('quod iam facis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laudat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('acta su•', 'PERSON'): 1"
A20740,8,assumption Rome Babylon argument description Babylon whore Babylon set ghost,room: 0.5; antichrist: 0.5; babylon: 0.5; beast: 0.5; rome: 0.5; empire: 0.5; hill: 0.45; city: 0.45; head: 0.4; king: 0.35; christ: 0.15; whore: 0.05; seat: 0.05; time: 0.05; pope: 0.05,"('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 32; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 31; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 25; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 23; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 11; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 11; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('hill', 'PERSON'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('John', 'PERSON'): 8; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 7; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 6; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 5; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('R.', 'NORP'): 3; ('17. 8', 'DATE'): 2; ('Septem', 'ORG'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 2; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 2; ('Apoc', 'GPE'): 2; ('Apocalypse', 'ORG'): 2; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 2; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 2; ('17. 13', 'DATE'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Mat 24', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('finem', 'GPE'): 2; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Julian', 'NORP'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('toti quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('praesidet orbi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Georgic', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('una sibi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Varro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a festival day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lib 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Septimontium', 'ORG'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Blondus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Montes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Qutrinalis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Coelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Viminalis', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Apo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romae', 'LOC'): 1; ('capita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('decemuir', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('candlestick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ad algasiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paulin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apocalypsi Ioannis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epistola Petri', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Primasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sibylla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 6. third', 'DATE'): 1; ('17. 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chapt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sodom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Romain', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('seventeenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('eighteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Apocalypse', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Pantheon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Boniface', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phocas Marcellin', 'FAC'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('rosin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bethel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bethauen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mantuan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('iam tota lupanar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petrarch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sentina', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('17. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Strabo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Augustulus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Charlemagne', 'GPE'): 1; ('325', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year 475', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year 800', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ap', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('ten province 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('17. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('the same hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Johannes', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui sibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('magnā Germaniae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gothiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noruegiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daniā vniuersam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bonā Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('angliae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heluetiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Boemiae ac pānoniae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sueuia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gothland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Norway', 'GPE'): 1; ('Denmark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Helvetia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Polonia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Boemia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pannonie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Babylon Apo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marcelia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Titus Vespasian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('templo', 'GPE'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('21. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('roman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Socrat', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sozom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theodoret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cyrill', 'ORG'): 1; ('Marcell', 'ORG'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1"
A20740,10,Chap. condition Antichrist opposition Christ note place time rest pope,christ: 0.5; god: 0.5; antichrist: 0.5; pope: 0.5; church: 0.5; man: 0.5; word: 0.45; apostasy: 0.4; jesus: 0.35; doctrine: 0.25; truth: 0.2; name: 0.1; body: 0.1; devil: 0.05; father: 0.05; john: 0.05,"('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 47; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 35; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 19; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 13; ('John', 'PERSON'): 11; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 8; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 4; ('thou', 'GPE'): 4; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 3; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Iehouah', 'GPE'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Theodoret', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Bellar', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Tim. 4. 3', 'DATE'): 2; ('Antichristianisme', 'ORG'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Apocalypse', 'ORG'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2. 22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('jure matris impera', 'ORG'): 2; ('Bembus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 2; ('Boniface', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter Gen.', 'LAW'): 1; ('9 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antichrist , Hilary', 'ORG'): 1; ('T•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antichrist Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('R.', 'NORP'): 1; ('dei lib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cyrill', 'ORG'): 1; ('Catech', 'NORP'): 1; ('2. 10. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antiehrist', 'GPE'): 1; ('nota', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lent', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Edward day', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. second', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Magdeburg', 'GPE'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Apo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mat •', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tim. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('13. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Faber', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antoninus', 'ORG'): 1; ('John the Euangelist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pauli', 'GPE'): 1; ('heuheu', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alas', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('se•', 'ORG'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nicolas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aventine', 'GPE'): 1; ('862', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Bellarm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('twofold', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ecce', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Auentin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hierome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Marte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many century', 'DATE'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the catholic apostasy', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('outward 2', 'DATE'): 1; ('quisquis autem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tully', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7 second', 'TIME'): 1; ('Jesus be Immanuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Messiah', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Rc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Deus', 'DATE'): 1; ('discip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('111', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('apud iuellum .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('creare se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Vid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('infinite power', 'ORG'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus be Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sixtus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iulius 2', 'ORG'): 1; ('more than twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Silvester 2', 'LAW'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iulius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 10', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 14', 'LAW'): 1; ('10. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('cum beati possimus', 'ORG'): 1; (""Thomas Becket th'archbishop"", 'ORG'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henry the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christe', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('un', 'ORG'): 1; ('aeternitatis gloriam consequamur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Breuiar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mary the bless virgin', 'ORG'): 1; ('vnica', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mariae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Innoc', 'GPE'): 1; ('300', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vnb•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Spe•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi tu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('virgo puerpera', 'ORG'): 1; ('patris parens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('filia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nostra pian scelera Ibid', 'ORG'): 1; ('laudem virginis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ reserve justice', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bernardinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mar•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylon', 'ORG'): 1; ('ita facis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('iur .', 'GPE'): 1; ('ca•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mentz', 'GPE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elizeus', 'ORG'): 1; ('fidelity', 'ORG'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1"
A20740,11,Chap. pride ambition Antichrist call God Antichrist enemy Christ adversary,god: 0.5; pope: 0.5; emperor: 0.5; king: 0.5; christ: 0.5; man: 0.5; antichrist: 0.45; worship: 0.45; earth: 0.4; call: 0.3; power: 0.2; angel: 0.2,"('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 20; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('terris', 'GPE'): 5; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 4; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('caerem', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Antonin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('§', 'NORP'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Bald', 'PERSON'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('R.', 'NORP'): 2; ('251', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hadrian', 'NORP'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3. light', 'QUANTITY'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gregor', 'GPE'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('praese', 'NORP'): 2; ('Joan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('2. 4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.', 'DATE'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Wisd', 'ORG'): 1; ('15.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antiochus Epiphanes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11. 36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antiochus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aemulus Christi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clemeatin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pastoralis de re Iudic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Floret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Papa', 'ORG'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antonius de Rosellis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Carem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clem 5', 'ORG'): 1; ('council', 'GPE'): 1; ('vienn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('64', 'DATE'): 1; ('tibi domino', 'PERSON'): 1; ('solitae de maior', 'ORG'): 1; ('G•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sta•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('regi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('regé', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('apud iuellum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mantuan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ense', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Helmoldus Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('81', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frederick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('caesaris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('papae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Auent•', 'NORP'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Frederick Naucler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aspidem', 'GPE'): 1; ('draconem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petro', 'GPE'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Celestin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Laterane', 'GPE'): 1; ('iurans prid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('potestas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lateranēs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('leo', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Bal', 'NORP'): 1; ('Haimburg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('apud jewel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Papa Angelis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('angelis praecipit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('angelis paradisi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('penitus absolutam', 'ORG'): 1; ('pope quoad canonizationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Troilus Maluil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hildebrand', 'GPE'): 1; ('Johannes Monlucius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Valence', 'ORG'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lib de religion', 'PERSON'): 1; ('reginam matr•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three or', 'DATE'): 1; ('Stapleton', 'ORG'): 1; ('ante p• … incip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('do•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ca•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('supreme nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('ecclesiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lateran', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l.', 'NORP'): 1; ('ecclesiam ut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Beza', 'ORG'): 1; ('facrens se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Decius c', 'ORG'): 1; ('ca•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Felin', 'GPE'): 1; ('ego', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of Laterane', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christoph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. Lateran', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arca triumph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1555', 'DATE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sixtus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('vocis', 'GPE'): 1; ('crederis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canonists', 'NORP'): 1; ('conditorem dictae decretalis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frederic', 'ORG'): 1; ('dominationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Othon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Franciscus Zabarella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('episc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quanto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('v•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nos•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('un', 'ORG'): 1; ('Capistran', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bonifac', 'GPE'): 1; ('C. Fundamenta', 'LOC'): 1; ('n•', 'ORG'): 1; ('nee', 'ORG'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('satis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantino', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec posse', 'ORG'): 1; ('ab hominibus iudicari manifestū est', 'ORG'): 1; ('god', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Auentinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Extrau', 'ORG'): 1; ('aequè ac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('intentionis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Erasm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ps', 'ORG'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('finem tit de censib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clement', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Auentin', 'PERSON'): 1"
A20740,12,lechery hollow father marriage clergy self speak rule Nicol pope,pope: 0.5; sin: 0.5; man: 0.5; saint: 0.5; call: 0.4; god: 0.4; part: 0.35; john: 0.35; idolatry: 0.25; church: 0.25; incest: 0.25; adultery: 0.15; time: 0.15; world: 0.1; whole: 0.1; covetousness: 0.1; marriage: 0.1; word: 0.05,"('3', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('John', 'PERSON'): 4; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('France', 'GPE'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 3; ('§', 'NORP'): 3; ('England', 'GPE'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 3; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Alexander 6', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Constantia', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul 3', 'PERSON'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Antonin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Fulm', 'ORG'): 2; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Nicol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Honestius', 'ORG'): 1; ('implicari :', 'PERSON'): 1; ('conscientia cum una ligari', 'FAC'): 1; ('John the 8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marozia', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 12', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zando', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 13', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laterane', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 14.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Benedict', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cade', 'GPE'): 1; ('Benedict 12', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Francis Petrarch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gerhard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calixtus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hildebrand', 'LOC'): 1; ('Innocentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicolas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vrsine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Martin 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sixtus 5', 'LAW'): 1; ('John the 13', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Stephana', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bastard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucretia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pius 5', 'LAW'): 1; ('Lucy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the three hot month of the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('Casa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Beneuentum', 'GPE'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leo 10', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petrus Aloysius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cosmus Cherius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sixtus 4', 'LAW'): 1; ('600', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sylvester', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('this thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Onuphr', 'NORP'): 1; ('heresy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Babylon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('virgin marry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Papa', 'ORG'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de judaic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tolle', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('llibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('gonorrhaean', 'GPE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Vid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('svi de acti•', 'ORG'): 1; ('30000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45000', 'DATE'): 1; ('courtesan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('monthly', 'DATE'): 1; ('eius avaritiae totus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eius luxuriae meretrix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('m•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•', 'NORP'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ludouic', 'ORG'): 1; ('1228', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hadrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('1538', 'DATE'): 1; ('two million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ludo•', 'ORG'): 1; ('three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('nine hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Blondus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dum singulae civitate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romano', 'ORG'): 1; ('boneficia sacerdotalia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1301', 'DATE'): 1; ('an . 1246', 'DATE'): 1; ('lib', 'GPE'): 1; ('Steph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gardiner', 'PERSON'): 1; ('v•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Muscull', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ministr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nundinati•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Io• … Mon•', 'ORG'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Martin 5', 'LAW'): 1; ('9 million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bonner', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vult marcas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Papas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('si de deris •', 'ORG'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Petr', 'ORG'): 1; ('indesin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed ad quēcunque', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abbas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('321', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('monastery', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ferrariens•', 'ORG'): 1; ('§', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ex suo corpore', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('halfpenny', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ieroboam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1"
A20740,33,Chap. conclusion whole treatise argument prove pope Antichrist evidence truth,god: 0.5; church: 0.5; antichrist: 0.5; pope: 0.5; christ: 0.5; apoc: 0.5; truth: 0.5; prince: 0.3; self: 0.25; beast: 0.2; city: 0.2; papist: 0.15; doctrine: 0.1; mark: 0.1; prove: 0.1; part: 0.05; christian: 0.05,"('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 17; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 5; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Antonin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('14.', 'DATE'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('§', 'NORP'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('Tim. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('18. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 10. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ierome', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichristianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antichristians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Seminary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('20. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pius 5', 'LAW'): 1; ('182', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('idol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Asserted', 'GPE'): 1; ('xxxv', 'GPE'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Joan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alstedius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the university of Herborne', 'ORG'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('••••ltus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year of the', 'DATE'): 1; ('John Cordwell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lybbe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas Chambrelan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('George', 'PERSON'): 1; ('these many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Io', 'LOC'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paulinum', 'EVENT'): 1; ('verb•', 'ORG'): 1; ('se•lednesse', 'NORP'): 1; ('deal•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marcell', 'ORG'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Themi•t', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xenophon', 'DATE'): 1; ('•', 'GPE'): 1"
A25221,26,object take Cor. apostle end world come other time end,year: 0.5; christ: 0.5; resurrection: 0.5; time: 0.5; world: 0.45; satan: 0.4; place: 0.4; object: 0.4; answ: 0.35; martyr: 0.3; opinion: 0.2; chiliast: 0.15; judgement: 0.15; soul: 0.1; antichrist: 0.1,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 20; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 13; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 11; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('the thousand year', 'DATE'): 10; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('these thousand year', 'DATE'): 6; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 6; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('those thousand year', 'DATE'): 5; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 4; ('1000 year', 'DATE'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Magog', 'LOC'): 4; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('these 1000 year', 'DATE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Cerinthus', 'NORP'): 3; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19.20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Magog', 'ORG'): 2; ('the year', 'DATE'): 2; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 2; ('20.6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the year of Christ 1073', 'DATE'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Alfonsus Conradus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Alcoran', 'PERSON'): 2; ('28', 'DATE'): 2; ('31', 'DATE'): 2; ('1000 a•nis nihil', 'QUANTITY'): 2; ('cibus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Trem', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2 Thes', 'PERSON'): 2; ('10.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Enallagen', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter 11', 'LAW'): 1; ('2.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'GPE'): 1; ('20.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Viii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('2.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 20', 'LAW'): 1; ('8.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the 70 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('pagan idol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epocha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('70', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Turks', 'NORP'): 1; ('20.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johnh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('grae•es', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustus Caesar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ebraeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Codere', 'ORG'): 1; ('Obsopaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orcum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tacitus discedito', 'ORG'): 1; ('Child', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27.50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('51', 'DATE'): 1; ('52', 'DATE'): 1; ('thirteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. third', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the end of', 'DATE'): 1; ('Benedict 9', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Hildebrand', 'GPE'): 1; ('D. Prideaux', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orat de gog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('b•nisa•t 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('about the year 1300', 'DATE'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'NORP'): 1; ('the year of Christ', 'DATE'): 1; ('1073', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousadd year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de haeresiou', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vide epithanium and ▪ Philastrium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cerinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mille', 'ORG'): 1; ('agmine magno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rursus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('corpora', 'NORP'): 1; ('velle reverti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Camerarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alcinoum Flitonis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Carpentarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('322', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'LOC'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alfonsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the end of the', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heaben', 'GPE'): 1; ('twenty-one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Magog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christoph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('some year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Papa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('yesterday', 'DATE'): 1; ('500 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1"
A27015,1,religion disputation reform religion popery popery scripture unity church consent,popery: 0.5; pope: 0.5; church: 0.35; scripture: 0.35; man: 0.35; papist: 0.35; sense: 0.35; wine: 0.3; people: 0.25; bread: 0.15; work: 0.15; plot: 0.15; prepare: 0.15; powder: 0.15; pretence: 0.15; point: 0.15; perniciu: 0.15; pestilence: 0.15; principal: 0.15; doctor: 0.1; council: 0.05; religion: 0.05,"('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('contra', 'NORP'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Richard Baxter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra rationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemo Christianus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemo Pacificus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abraham miller', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas Ʋnderhill', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul Church-yard', 'ORG'): 1; ('Francis Tyton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fleetstreet', 'GPE'): 1; ('1657', 'DATE'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('monthly', 'DATE'): 1; ('so many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quakers', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Disput', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sanchez', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 1"
A26880,21,postscript reader write occasion matter manner sheet reason communion print,church: 0.5; man: 0.5; communion: 0.5; god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; sin: 0.5; love: 0.4; dr: 0.4; worship: 0.35; another: 0.3; truth: 0.2; error: 0.2; mr: 0.1; mistake: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Nonconformists', 'ORG'): 5; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Warner', 'ORG'): 3; ('1660', 'DATE'): 3; ('this day', 'DATE'): 3; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('D. O.', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1200.', 'DATE'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Scots', 'ORG'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Owen', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christ', 'NORP'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('August be twelvemonth', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Basilides', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Martin Ithacius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Idacius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('1200', 'DATE'): 1; ('1300 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Saint•', 'ORG'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iames 3', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('•hil', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1661', 'DATE'): 1; ('•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('this three and twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Universa•', 'ORG'): 1; ('20 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iii', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ralphson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ralphs•n', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('more than one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('his late year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('late year', 'DATE'): 1; ('commu•i•n •f Saint•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Modes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('g•d', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('n•t', 'PERSON'): 1; ('anoth•r', 'ORG'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Drs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('locis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('so many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tear east', 'LOC'): 1; ('14.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Booksellers', 'ORG'): 1; ('the fit season', 'DATE'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('almost two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Barnabas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('overboard long ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('three and twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Commissioned', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tuckney', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spurstow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Calamy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arthur Iackson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('case', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clerke', 'ORG'): 1; ('ma•th', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Horton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cooper', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rawlinson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dr lightfoot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Collins', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Drake', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Woodbridge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ri', 'GPE'): 1; ('the king commission', 'ORG'): 1; ('lightfoot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Reignolds', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('only two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iackson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Crofton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prelacy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('other hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Satan', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('1000 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bonner', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gardiner', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bradford', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ridley', 'GPE'): 1; ('I|will', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the 3 penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Waldenses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1"
A20731,4,enemy chastity chief provoker lust excess meat fullness meat seminary,god: 0.5; lust: 0.5; prayer: 0.5; occasion: 0.5; time: 0.5; exercise: 0.5; fast: 0.5; lord: 0.5; sabbath: 0.4; day: 0.3; humiliation: 0.25; bind: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Esth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 3; ('Ierome', 'ORG'): 3; ('three day', 'DATE'): 3; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ezra', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Prou', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 2; ('Leuit', 'ORG'): 2; ('58.5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Leuit', 'NORP'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8.21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13.3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Barnabas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('every day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rusticum Monach', 'GPE'): 1; ('de viuendi formae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hieronym', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eustoch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ad furiam de vid•itate servant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('irrigata corporis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('terraspinas libidinum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sine cerere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Venus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('animos veneri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('19.32', 'MONEY'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Proximus', 'NORP'): 1; ('inconcessam venerem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Valerius Max', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('16.49', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('haec quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Basill', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fac', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ovid', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('13.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.2 9 man', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('the ten day of the seven month', 'DATE'): 1; ('16.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.27.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the seventy year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the four month', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sam 12.20', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('weekly', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nehem', 'GPE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nehe', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('Purim', 'NORP'): 1; ('9.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Easie 58', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('58.5.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mar. 2.18', 'DATE'): 1; ('chapter 9', 'LAW'): 1; ('Mar. 2', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('17.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anna', 'GPE'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('fourteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('electioni•n', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mat 9.15', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phil 4.4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 9.16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.4.11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Esther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('416', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Haman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mordecay', 'GPE'): 1; ('the ministry of the', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.16 .', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.21', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John the Euangelist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ebion and Cerinthus', 'ORG'): 1; ('9.9.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samuell', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sam 7.6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Neh', 'PERSON'): 1"
A26892,15 | 6684,humble Christ saviour clothe flesh meanness reputation despise sinner use,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; pride: 0.5; sin: 0.5; flesh: 0.5; self: 0.5; soul: 0.5; christ: 0.45; body: 0.4; devil: 0.2; lord: 0.2; world: 0.1; dust: 0.05; glory: 0.05; wisdom: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 16; ('§', 'NORP'): 9; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('14', 'DATE'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('13', 'DATE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('88', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jo••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('2 •', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('89', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('44 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('24.', 'DATE'): 1; ('90', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('6. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elders', 'PERSON'): 1; ('91', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('carnal•y', 'NORP'): 1; ('this hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('92', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten thousand fold', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('93', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('94', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fictilibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Agathoclea', 'NORP'): 1; ('Samio', 'LOC'): 1; ('Fercula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('poker•t', 'NORP'): 1; ('rex ego qui', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sicaniae', 'GPE'): 1; ('loco', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Auson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('••prosi•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the next year', 'DATE'): 1; ('§', 'PERSON'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Usefulness', 'ORG'): 1; ('Read Iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('12. 19', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elihu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Read Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('49.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('sepulchre', 'GPE'): 1; ('14. 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('31 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('childi•h', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Achitophel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1"
A26892,63 | 9778,man danger scruple Christianity part viz. God father son ghost,god: 0.5; perjury: 0.5; oath: 0.5; man: 0.5; sin: 0.5; duty: 0.5; thing: 0.5; self: 0.5; case: 0.35; perfidiousness: 0.2; vow: 0.2; conscience: 0.2; perjure: 0.05,"('§', 'NORP'): 13; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('202', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 2; ('seven day', 'DATE'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('yearly', 'DATE'): 1; ('the next year', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sanderson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. Sect', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('74', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('75', 'DATE'): 1; ('haec tempora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesiasticum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('publicis sacris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('legibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('ingeniculationem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Quaeritur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pro Resp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dico', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra conscientiam peccat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Voluntas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tritum', 'ORG'): 1; ('contra conscientiam aedificat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sententiam ferente', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apostolo', 'GPE'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dir', 'PERSON'): 1; ('125', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14. 14', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nemini debetur commodum ex sva culpa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('how many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Nat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Carbo', 'ORG'): 1; ('•u', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('12. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canute', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bilson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plutarch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lysa•d', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cicer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de leg l. 3.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Q. Curtius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cicero de Offic', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Agesilaus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cleomenes', 'GPE'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('seven night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Achitophel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Princ', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gabao•itarum', 'ORG'): 1; ('licet extortum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('exit•um', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('prolog', 'NORP'): 1; ('haud', 'GPE'): 1; ('justitiae est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('Graeca', 'GPE'): 1; ('Silius', 'ORG'): 1; ('non illi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aut conjux aut vita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('Despecta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('poenam merito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tibull', 'ORG'): 1; ('poena', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pausanias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('regibus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Appian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Valerius Max', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be fruit', 'ORG'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('deceit', 'GPE'): 1"
A26892,253,Romans thief fraud plea judgement gain deprive other right Lampridius,physician: 0.5; man: 0.3; god: 0.3; life: 0.3; gain: 0.3; cause: 0.3; self: 0.3; money: 0.3; profession: 0.25; plut: 0.2; plea: 0.2; posset: 0.2; poet: 0.2; plutarch: 0.2; prefer: 0.2; place: 0.2; pretence: 0.2; plautus: 0.2; mean: 0.2; health: 0.1; thing: 0.05,"('§', 'NORP'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('eos', 'ORG'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alexander Severus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('damnati', 'GPE'): 1; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('appellan eosdem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Turinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('ego vero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('justitiam homini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('justissimo defendere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tenacem propositi virum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Horat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plautus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iusta', 'NORP'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ri•h', 'NORP'): 1; ('qui novit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('quem doctrina', 'ORG'): 1; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17. 33', 'DATE'): 1; ('P. Rutilius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sibi', 'NORP'): 1; ('tota vita', 'FAC'): 1; ('moveri', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('quod cum semel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('amicos illi judicandum esset', 'PERSON'): 1; ('amico judicium', 'ORG'): 1; ('se provocaret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('quidem est justitia', 'ORG'): 1; ('justitiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ita illustrem reddidit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lycurg', 'GPE'): 1; ('Numa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('potest poena dilata', 'ORG'): 1; ('cum non', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A20674,1,abstrvsenesse divine mystery knowledge another church schism unanimity orthodox professor,god: 0.5; mystery: 0.5; reason: 0.5; thing: 0.5; divine: 0.5; man: 0.45; knowledge: 0.45; self: 0.45; mind: 0.4; understanding: 0.2; essence: 0.2; grace: 0.15; conceit: 0.1; eye: 0.1,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Merton', 'GPE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 2; ('may 1. 1627', 'DATE'): 1; ('17. 1628', 'DATE'): 1; ('Oxford', 'GPE'): 1; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Lichfield Printer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dom', 'ORG'): 1; ('1628', 'DATE'): 1; ('John dovghty', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quaerit se natura', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eleven 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Iustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec quaeri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1a', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneas', 'GPE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('dum aestimari non', 'PERSON'): 1"
A20674,3,come attribute power will man dulness understanding object equal strength,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; knowledge: 0.5; word: 0.5; point: 0.5; divine: 0.45; mystery: 0.45; self: 0.45; thing: 0.35; reason: 0.25; wisdom: 0.2; science: 0.1; heresy: 0.1; hand: 0.1; lord: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 4; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 2; ('Iraeneus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Esdras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('somn', 'GPE'): 1; ('S• L. 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Macrobius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Durando', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 17', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tacitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicetas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leviathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 1; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gelasius Cucycenu•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nice', 'GPE'): 1; ('19 v. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('21. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arminius', 'ORG'): 1; ('David Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Astro', 'GPE'): 1; ('mazelesse', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pentheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bacchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Medea', 'ORG'): 1; ('ingenio suo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quintil', 'LOC'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Salvian', 'NORP'): 1; ('quam sinaris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('novatians', 'NORP'): 1; ('eunomians', 'NORP'): 1; ('valentinians', 'NORP'): 1; ('qui semetipsos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('L. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vniversorum agnitionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Exercit', 'ORG'): 1; ('vbi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scaliger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aesop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Festus de v•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lu•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nae•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petrarch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('add marcellin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('St Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tragedian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aliena', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('L. de artibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Capella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ja', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Homer', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 5', 'ORG'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samaritan', 'FAC'): 1; ('the 10th', 'DATE'): 1; ('two penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Optatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('46.', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('these late day', 'DATE'): 1; ('1 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam rabie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('st John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 10', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rhenanus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('saint cyprian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epictetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('syrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three whole week', 'DATE'): 1; ('L. de . mysterijs Aegyptiorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pythagorean', 'NORP'): 1; ('Minerva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Saviour', 'NORP'): 1; ('Colos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1"
A29229,8 | 16291,say doubt sleep desire hour transmutation hour approach Aurora burnish,god: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; church: 0.5; author: 0.5; doctrine: 0.5; government: 0.4; self: 0.4; majesty: 0.35; life: 0.35; christ: 0.25; discipline: 0.2; king: 0.2; husband: 0.2; joy: 0.1; persuade: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('meek', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Chaucer', 'GPE'): 2; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('presbyterian', 'NORP'): 2; ('this happy hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Aurora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Survivors', 'ORG'): 1; ('king|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('outward grace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('his bloom year', 'DATE'): 1; ('his hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('VVelles', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('George', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thomas Creed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('William hall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas Snodham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1611', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4 Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1"
A20733,25,CHAP. Iii argument sermon church Asia diocese testimony proof produce,church: 0.45; city: 0.45; bishop: 0.45; country: 0.45; diocese: 0.45; proposition: 0.45; parish: 0.45; consequence: 0.45; presbytery: 0.35; circuit: 0.25; divide: 0.15; asia: 0.1; omit: 0.05; office: 0.05; pag: 0.05; origen: 0.05; order: 0.05; ordain: 0.05; opposite: 0.05; oppose: 0.05; opponent: 0.05; opinion: 0.05; power: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 16; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 12; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 8; ('§', 'NORP'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Cenchreae', 'ORG'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cenchrea', 'GPE'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Caes', 'PERSON'): 2; ('baron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Serm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Smyrna', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sardes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laoidcea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pergamus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thyatira', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philadelphia', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eighteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('seventeenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('54', 'DATE'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('presuppo•ed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the church of Corinth', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phoebe', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bullinger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ditissima foemina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioanna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chusa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Susanna', 'ORG'): 1; ('16.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('the apostle day', 'DATE'): 1; ('three or four hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bez. de grad', 'ORG'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('542', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rainolds', 'ORG'): 1; ('39.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lib', 'GPE'): 1; ('Not•t', 'GPE'): 1; ('the council of Constantinople Const', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trullo', 'GPE'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('19.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('restifi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'GPE'): 1; ('three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('20.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('16.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epiphanius , Chrysost', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nazianz', 'ORG'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('44.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('ordain bishop', 'GPE'): 1; ('the ministry of the apostle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Colossae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phrygia', 'ORG'): 1; ('the ministry of Epaphra• Coloss', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.7 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the ministry of Archippus', 'ORG'): 1; ('more than one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty five year', 'DATE'): 1; ('cathedra episcopi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('M.D.', 'GPE'): 1"
A29201,6 | 19476,protestant confess schism side luxu•i• member catholic church member catholic,law: 0.5; queen: 0.5; subject: 0.5; man: 0.5; pope: 0.5; prince: 0.5; england: 0.5; time: 0.35; treason: 0.35; make: 0.2; religion: 0.2; protestant: 0.15; catholic: 0.1; roman: 0.1; necessity: 0.05,"('England', 'GPE'): 16; ('english', 'NORP'): 7; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Roman catholic', 'NORP'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 4; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 3; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 2; ('Henry', 'GPE'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rheims', 'NORP'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Nero', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Nicholas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Puritan', 'GPE'): 2; ('fond de schism p', 'ORG'): 1; ('103', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nisi libidinis', 'ORG'): 1; ('luxu•i•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Livy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tully', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aen Gaz', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Demosthenes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timocratem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heraclitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('a•e', 'PERSON'): 1; ('suff•rs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Crumabo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Butlerabo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Imbargues', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sand de Schis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Annal', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eliz', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hieronimo Catena', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexandrino', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sixtus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Allen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Desmond', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('145', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('164', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Douai', 'FAC'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('supreme authority', 'ORG'): 1; ('Doleman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sanders', 'ORG'): 1; ('Parre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('74', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Allens', 'NORP'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bruce , Creiton', 'ORG'): 1; ('132', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Nicholas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eliot', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('329', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Campian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Respublica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bowtifeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apr. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('El', 'GPE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apol', 'ORG'): 1; ('the Lateran council', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Edm.', 'GPE'): 1; ('Conc', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the six year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the fourteenth year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Agnus', 'FAC'): 1; ('six year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the twenty three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the twenty four year', 'DATE'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Maryes', 'ORG'): 1; ('juvenius orta parentibus infecit', 'ORG'): 1; ('aequor', 'NORP'): 1; ('R. C. say', 'PERSON'): 1; ('infl•ct', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Enthymeme', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Ithacus', 'ORG'): 1; ('magno', 'PERSON'): 1"
A29201,9 | 19594,faith due moderation parliament fear proceed parliament force show force,pope: 0.5; king: 0.5; church: 0.5; power: 0.5; obedience: 0.5; god: 0.5; authority: 0.45; man: 0.4; fault: 0.3; bishop: 0.3; time: 0.2; prince: 0.15; papacy: 0.1; self: 0.1,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 9; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('England', 'GPE'): 5; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('english', 'NORP'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 3; ('Pius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 3; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 3; ('1530', 'DATE'): 2; ('Gardiner', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Stephen Gardiner', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Nicholas Sanders', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cherb', 'NORP'): 2; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('the council of tower', 'ORG'): 2; ('Britannick', 'PERSON'): 2; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('334', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nineteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('potius orbirationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nedde•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('ib•dem', 'ORG'): 1; ('719', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul and Uzziah', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ld', 'GPE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('305', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('last', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hora mortis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the very hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Sand', 'GPE'): 1; ('102', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('398', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the come two day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year 1533', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rota', 'LOC'): 1; ('Katherine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('128', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Vrban', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sextus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rusticus', 'GPE'): 1; ('defluat amnis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry the', 'FAC'): 1; ('Henry', 'GPE'): 1; ('seventeen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the four year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('huic operi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nehushtan', 'GPE'): 1; ('about the year 1120', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Conc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('R•sp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('13.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Kings', 'ORG'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregory', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mauritius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Patriarchates', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Laity', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('quam Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam non', 'PERSON'): 1"
A26785,6 | 19923,proof Jesus Christ send God know counsel salvation man consequence,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; love: 0.5; divine: 0.5; gospel: 0.5; son: 0.5; life: 0.45; word: 0.3; world: 0.3; thing: 0.2; heaven: 0.05; truth: 0.05; person: 0.05; saviour: 0.05; glory: 0.05,"('it|be', 'PERSON'): 10; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('qui verbum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('significationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nescivit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('erravit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Porphiry', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judea', 'GPE'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Enquirer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lusts', 'ORG'): 1; ('Messiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paulin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rhet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae cum ita sint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magna videlicet praerogativa de nomine', 'ORG'): 1; ('ac vivimus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christianus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aestimari de cultoribus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tam malos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('discipulos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('blaspheme', 'PERSON'): 1"
A26200,3,Jesuit scrap ear Quakers fault bind pare scrap sever freehold,truth: 0.45; matter: 0.45; heart: 0.45; effect: 0.45; brethren: 0.4; doctrine: 0.4; work: 0.4; church: 0.35; prophet: 0.2; disorder: 0.15; cause: 0.15; book: 0.15; order: 0.1; master: 0.1; course: 0.1; cor: 0.05; christ: 0.05; peace: 0.05; pauli: 0.05; pharaohs: 0.05; persuade: 0.05; person: 0.05; permission: 0.05; people: 0.05; philosoph: 0.05; pare: 0.05; papist: 0.05; religion: 0.05; rod: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 2; ('Quakers', 'ORG'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 2; ('D.', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('700', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iames Nayler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quaker', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('160', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nonconformists', 'ORG'): 1; ('Prynne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Deacon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Walker .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vtilius permittitur', 'ORG'): 1; ('nasci scandalum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('erroris', 'GPE'): 1; ('etiam nullo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etiam multis impugnantibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrys', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('LONDINI Impensis Geor. bishop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1601', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('I. W.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.32.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jude 22.23', 'LAW'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Darell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('88', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('blush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.10.11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.13.14 .', 'DATE'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1"
A20001,11 | 20343,Orthodoxus bee point Iam. Pet. Pet. Brentius Luc. man faith,faith: 0.5; christ: 0.5; disciple: 0.5; time: 0.5; prayer: 0.5; apostle: 0.5; page: 0.5; doctrine: 0.45; self: 0.45; god: 0.3; increase: 0.15; word: 0.1; orthodoxus: 0.05,"('D.', 'NORP'): 17; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Orthodoxus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Darell', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Orthodoxus', 'ORG'): 2; ('17.5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('46', 'DATE'): 2; ('17.1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tabitha', 'GPE'): 2; ('9.40', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('a whole day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Iam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.18.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luc', 'DATE'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.13.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('17.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.29.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('13.9.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('re••lation•', 'NORP'): 1; ('28.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Publius', 'GPE'): 1; ('14.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iosh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('acknowledge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('mark', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('one minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elijah', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41.42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('48.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('23.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('4 10.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Wright', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pleno laudat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('about nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('between three and four', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A23710,7,man interest God benefactor equal favour argument spirit benefactor requite,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; love: 0.5; law: 0.5; rule: 0.5; christian: 0.35; vice: 0.35; self: 0.35; virtue: 0.3; heart: 0.2; duty: 0.2; argument: 0.05; christians: 0.05; divine: 0.05; precept: 0.05; person: 0.05,"('christian', 'NORP'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 3; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 3; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 2; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 2; ('Jam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('every morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('our few day', 'DATE'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi dignus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Celsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccl', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('13.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('64.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epaminondas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lacedaemon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristides', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Numa Pompilius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marcus Antonius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A23710,15,nature peace trouble vexation blessing place mercy other fruition pity,man: 0.45; wisdom: 0.45; peace: 0.45; holiness: 0.45; fool: 0.45; thing: 0.35; fear: 0.35; account: 0.35; conscience: 0.25; courage: 0.2; soul: 0.2; war: 0.15; spirit: 0.15; cause: 0.1; word: 0.05; principle: 0.05; prince: 0.05; psal: 0.05; prov: 0.05; prophecy: 0.05; prohibit: 0.05; puddle: 0.05; principal: 0.05; pity: 0.05; precept: 0.05; religion: 0.05; nature: 0.05,"('kingdom', 'GPE'): 2; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ceditius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rhadamanthus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Spira', 'GPE'): 1; ('mar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sibi', 'GPE'): 1; ('nulla palescere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119.165', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Burlesque', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('73.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A27009,33,direction Having settle peace direction caution contrary extreme viz. heed,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; soul: 0.5; church: 0.5; devil: 0.5; scruple: 0.45; body: 0.4; religion: 0.35; self: 0.25; duty: 0.15; way: 0.1; world: 0.1; day: 0.1; christians: 0.05; work: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 16; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 10; ('christian', 'NORP'): 9; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Herbert', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('that day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomons', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccl', 'GPE'): 1; ('7.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the middle between two', 'DATE'): 1; ('Amesius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prop. 2', 'LAW'): 1; ('Prop. 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prop. 4', 'LAW'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('Systeme', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('three hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eve', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.1', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('8.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Epiphamus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Belial', 'GPE'): 1; ('Calvinism', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cathedrals', 'ORG'): 1; ('many a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pater', 'PERSON'): 1; ('midnight', 'TIME'): 1; ('altar', 'ORG'): 1; ('188', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('189', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('190', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luthers day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magistra•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('antinomian', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('6. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('garb', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28.47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Friday', 'DATE'): 1; ('40 day every year', 'DATE'): 1; ('7.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ethiopia', 'GPE'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Meeter', 'NORP'): 1; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a solemn day', 'DATE'): 1; ('what hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('f••th', 'PERSON'): 1"
A27214,6,CHAP. IV. objection chapter mystery resurrection drift scope chapter Sect.,body: 0.5; resurrection: 0.5; soul: 0.5; doctor: 0.5; sense: 0.5; word: 0.5; school: 0.5; article: 0.4; creed: 0.35; chapter: 0.25; point: 0.25; self: 0.2; objection: 0.05,"('Resurrectio', 'ORG'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 3; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 3; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 3; ('Apologie', 'ORG'): 2; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('Kenelm Digby', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('quibus', 'ORG'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('CHAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('Creed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('America', 'GPE'): 1; ('Durandus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Avicenna', 'GPE'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Troja', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('resurrectionis vocabulum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non aliam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aelia', 'FAC'): 1; ('Hadrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('soul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pythagorean', 'NORP'): 1; ('Trojani', 'NORP'): 1; ('Euphorbus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 7', 'LAW'): 1; ('S. Iren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('iisdem scilicet', 'ORG'): 1; ('mortui fuerant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('iisdem ipsis', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec iidem', 'ORG'): 1; ('ipsi qui mortui erant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoniam corpus quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cst caro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod illi negabant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('amittendo', 'ORG'): 1; ('ita mortui vocabulum corpori', 'ORG'): 1; ('mortui est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('corporis erit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cum potius timendum qui corpus', 'ORG'): 1; ('non qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('animae autem', 'ORG'): 1; ('hominibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('ita resurrectionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gehennam nisi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theodoret Heret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ancorat', 'LOC'): 1; ('92', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('64', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet S. Chrys', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Resur', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. Jerom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pamach', 'GPE'): 1; ('quoniam spiritus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('carnem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eadem habebimus membra quibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sanguinem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('chapter 4', 'LAW'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the 1 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A27214,7,passage episcopacy join presbytery presbytery objection episcopacy faction episcopacy presbytery,episcopacy: 0.5; government: 0.5; church: 0.5; faction: 0.5; christ: 0.5; right: 0.5; discipline: 0.5; doctor: 0.45; end: 0.35; precept: 0.3; power: 0.3; thing: 0.05; objection: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('christian', 'NORP'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Calvinism', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19th', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Paragraph', 'GPE'): 2; ('1647', 'DATE'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvinism', 'GPE'): 1; ('Calvinism', 'ORG'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('millenian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paragraph', 'NORP'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('indicio suo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('1. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('corinth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Apollo , Cephas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cephas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Spencer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chappel', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Stanza 58', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Stanza 59', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Stanza 60', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1660', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18•h', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Logi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Visier', 'PRODUCT'): 1"
A20795,2,element creature sun moon star plant bird fowl fish groan,god: 0.5; judgement: 0.5; world: 0.5; day: 0.5; christ: 0.5; earth: 0.5; heaven: 0.5; judge: 0.5; glory: 0.4; argument: 0.35; end: 0.1; word: 0.05; creature: 0.05; sign: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('20.11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('last', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('the set hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Douercourt', 'ORG'): 1; ('Harewich', 'GPE'): 1; ('June 12. 1615', 'DATE'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('IESVS', 'ORG'): 1; ('19.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 5.28.29', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 12.44', 'LAW'): 1; ('17.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.16 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 5.2', 'LAW'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.27.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sublatis', 'NORP'): 1; ('finem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gomorrah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Armado', 'GPE'): 1; ('1588', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('outward afflict', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome 8.18', 'ORG'): 1; ('4 17 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('8.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26.64', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sibylla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.35 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('7.31 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('omnia orta intereunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A20202,5 | 25660,Theol. apostle S. Peter foretell Pet. day mocker lust writer,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; oath: 0.5; theol: 0.5; word: 0.5; thing: 0.5; sin: 0.5; time: 0.45; day: 0.35; lord: 0.35; prophet: 0.35,"('Theol', 'GPE'): 20; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Phila', 'PERSON'): 6; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('theo', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the year', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('S. Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Caluin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Infernus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Micha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'NORP'): 1; ('8. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ashamed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elishah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deut', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Halcion Amos', 'ORG'): 1; ('8. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phila', 'GPE'): 1; ('a week', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('neither morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('3. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elihu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('58', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jehova', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Malachi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zachary', 'EVENT'): 1; ('harden', 'GPE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('so many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the great day', 'DATE'): 1; ('leaden foot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Job', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('their day', 'DATE'): 1; ('saint marry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mouse-foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('S.', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zephany', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Malcham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Molech', 'ORG'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anabaptist', 'NORP'): 1; ('LordIere', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('10. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isocra', 'GPE'): 1; ('Demon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A20202,5 | 25816,Theol. oppression usury oppression bribery kind oppression oppression rent oppression,oppression: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; lord: 0.5; heart: 0.5; theol: 0.5; widow: 0.4; day: 0.35; blood: 0.3; phila: 0.3; soul: 0.25; oppressor: 0.2; house: 0.05; hand: 0.05; child: 0.05; good: 0.05,"('Theol', 'GPE'): 10; ('Phila', 'PERSON'): 8; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 5; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 2; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14.', 'DATE'): 2; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Achab', 'PERSON'): 2; ('21', 'DATE'): 2; ('one day', 'DATE'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('orphan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eccl', 'GPE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('needy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('defraud1', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('4. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zeph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 3. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zion', 'ORG'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Esa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the pooreIob', 'DATE'): 1; ('a week', 'DATE'): 1; ('twelve month', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year long', 'DATE'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('EnterPro', 'ORG'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('21. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('24. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cain', 'ORG'): 1; ('Reg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Naboth', 'ORG'): 1; ('Malachi', 'GPE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Neh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abacuch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('behold deceit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pater', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('66.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('9 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1"
A20202,5 | 26028,Theol. man prayer join other exercise handmaid director whetstone prayer,god: 0.5; theol: 0.5; man: 0.5; cause: 0.5; thing: 0.5; decree: 0.5; self: 0.5; motion: 0.35; election: 0.3; mercy: 0.2; scripture: 0.15; word: 0.15; life: 0.1; world: 0.1; antil: 0.05; time: 0.05; evil: 0.05,"('Theol', 'GPE'): 26; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('Phila', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('theo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('God', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three hour', 'TIME'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ishmaelite', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('every night', 'TIME'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Electra', 'ORG'): 1; ('herein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 1; ('16.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('the ocean sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Beza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4 antile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('FatherEphes', 'ORG'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 1; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six and', 'DATE'): 1"
A26947,38,CHAP. Xxxi another deceit translation bible people corrupt word God,part: 0.5; papist: 0.5; people: 0.5; clergy: 0.5; another: 0.5; man: 0.45; prince: 0.45; god: 0.35; minister: 0.35; priest: 0.3; church: 0.2; ministry: 0.1; land: 0.1; translation: 0.05; write: 0.05; kingdom: 0.05; teacher: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Xxxi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Edw', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Europae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('Venice', 'GPE'): 1; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Puritan', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quakers', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Quakers', 'ORG'): 1; ('Wolverhampton', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mammon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mammon', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred have two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prelacy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('91.', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('general council', 'ORG'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bodin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heylin Geograph', 'ORG'): 1; ('148', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one million and', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('heylin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Edwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred and four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five hundred and forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve thousand three hundred and twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five hundred sixty seven', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('seven hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two hundred fifty nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Malta', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('a hundred thirty thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about fifteen million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three million', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A26947,41,CHAP. another deceit holiness church ministry unholiness matter fact mind,man: 0.5; pope: 0.5; church: 0.5; saint: 0.5; papist: 0.5; christ: 0.5; life: 0.5; god: 0.5; world: 0.45; faith: 0.4; age: 0.05; christian: 0.05; communion: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 18; ('christian', 'NORP'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 4; ('France', 'GPE'): 4; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 3; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christopher', 'PERSON'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 2; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('xxxiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('inter haeretico', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus de converse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('531', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mass.', 'GPE'): 1; ('Friday', 'DATE'): 1; ('inn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pater', 'PERSON'): 1; ('observe day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a few minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('H. T.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dominick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Patrick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lancashire', 'GPE'): 1; ('Albaspinaeus Observat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('siquis unquam hoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eucharistiae', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('partibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam ante excommunicationem habuit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eandem cum caeteris', 'ORG'): 1; ('fidelibus consuetudinem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Albaspinaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tiber', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sergius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Boniface', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('897', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Stephen the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tuscia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('912', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred and fifty year', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Genebrard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pelagius de planctu', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mantuan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petrarch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui cupitis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('platina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marcellini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Claudius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epicurus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('V. Quadr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Guicciardine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tit', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sixtus', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('paenitentia vivit', 'FAC'): 1; ('Watson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quodl', 'LOC'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('57', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Papa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Barthol', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Morisot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Perron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Legationes', 'NORP'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ville', 'GPE'): 1; ('87', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clement', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Francisc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mariae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Urbine', 'ORG'): 1; ('how many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mariana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Espensaeus lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1"
A26947,41 | 27081,gain pope prelate market benefice labour Nicol Clemangis Archidiaconus Baiosensis,church: 0.5; pope: 0.5; man: 0.5; sin: 0.5; holiness: 0.5; life: 0.5; saint: 0.45; god: 0.4; clergy: 0.25; word: 0.25; lib: 0.2; thing: 0.2; minister: 0.15; concubine: 0.1,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('England', 'GPE'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('italian', 'NORP'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('Nicol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clemangis Archidiaconus Baiosensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('annatibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alvarus Pelagius de planctu', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eccles.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'GPE'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cardinel', 'ORG'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marc Ant. de Dom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Budaeum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Duarenum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Maphaeus , Alvarus Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hoffmeister', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Grotius Discussio Apol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('72', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quidam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sacramenti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vox significet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cum ipsos pudent', 'ORG'): 1; ('sint venalia', 'LOC'): 1; ('quae vocant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sacramentis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Parachos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ecclesiastas quod', 'GPE'): 1; ('Episcopis', 'GPE'): 1; ('nostris', 'GPE'): 1; ('numerantur potius', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam examinantur :', 'PERSON'): 1; ('favoris habet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('apud quosdam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nolim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcopos , Decanos', 'ORG'): 1; ('Canonicos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('intrudat potiùs quam ordinet romana curia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('juxta jocum cujusdam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('satiari', 'NORP'): 1; ('sacris — ab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sacerdotia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sacerdos', 'GPE'): 1; ('quidem cogitarunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sixtus Quintus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregor', 'GPE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orichovius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Onuphrius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thuanus', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alvarus Pelagius', 'ORG'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('241', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pelagius Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('ecclesiast', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Henr', 'ORG'): 1; ('819', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hugo', 'EVENT'): 1; ('Lons', 'ORG'): 1; ('the east gate', 'LOC'): 1; ('Costerus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesuite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Enchirid', 'ORG'): 1; ('de Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Roma', 'ORG'): 1; ('vidisse', 'GPE'): 1; ('cum leno aut meretrix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Franciscans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Guil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theodora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sergius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Luitprandus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('octo', 'GPE'): 1; ('hunc merito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aloisus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Parma', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dominicus Soto de Instit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Timothy and', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('the Jansenist Montaltus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicolas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caranza', 'ORG'): 1; ('395', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quakers', 'ORG'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five , sixth', 'DATE'): 1; ('Basil , Gregory Nazianz', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nyssen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysostom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('british', 'NORP'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Salvian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gregory Mag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('venia suo ingenio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('si sit assidua', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Gratian', 'NORP'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cit c', 'ORG'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('697', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('195', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alured', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of the clergy', 'ORG'): 1; ('Spelm', 'GPE'): 1; ('362', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('saint Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Serm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('224', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bononia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Austin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aufer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('altar', 'ORG'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 1"
