tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A33241,3 | 967,imposer affect oath advise take be give press man allow,oath: 0.5; covenant: 0.5; thing: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; mr: 0.5; church: 0.45; time: 0.35; conscience: 0.25; take: 0.25; faith: 0.25; reason: 0.15; government: 0.1; mean: 0.1; truth: 0.05; party: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Aberdene', 'NORP'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('contra', 'NORP'): 2; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Scots', 'ORG'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('ley', 'PERSON'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Com', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Elton', 'PERSON'): 2; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 2; ('Confut', 'PERSON'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('288', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('plausitum l. 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Confut', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('perfectissima', 'GPE'): 1; ('seilicet quando obeditur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('domino suo :', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bellar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nullo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Divinitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('bozius l. 18', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bozius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('synod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Covenanters', 'PERSON'): 1; ('li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Forsitan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Covenanters', 'ORG'): 1; ('Forsitan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Taylor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jenkins', 'PERSON'): 1; ('doub•s ▪ p ▪', 'ORG'): 1; ('100', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vega', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Soto', 'ORG'): 1; ('Catherinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('heresi•', 'NORP'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Oedipus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Exo', 'LOC'): 1; ('295', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wheth•r', 'ORG'): 1; ('juravit David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ser', 'GPE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ames', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hamilton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('L.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. iubemus nulli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pr•••biti', 'GPE'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Conditio', 'ORG'): 1; ('•el impossibilis vitiat', 'FAC'): 1; ('Contractus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('instit l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Absurdum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('adigi', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('suscepta', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de a•te Amand', 'PERSON'): 1; ('heathens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pieta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('foedera servet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('untigbte•us', 'ORG'): 1; ('discourse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Owen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('89', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('222', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sivero boni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tuno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('juramento deest justitia', 'ORG'): 1; ('controversiae f•niantur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('6. 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heraclea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pontus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amycus', 'ORG'): 1; ('bebrycians', 'NORP'): 1; ('mad laurel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('presbyterians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Surrey', 'GPE'): 1; ('Kent', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Essex', 'GPE'): 1; ('Wales', 'GPE'): 1; ('14.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aberdene', 'GPE'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alsted', 'ORG'): 1; ('Syntag', 'ORG'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('amico juret se ipsi bona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam ipse baberet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'MONEY'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zedekiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Subscribers', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('defensive', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('79', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alsted', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alstedius', 'GPE'): 1; ('conscientia', 'GPE'): 1; ('obligari non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bakewell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aberdine', 'ORG'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Deanes', 'ORG'): 1; ('dr.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcop', 'ORG'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('par', 'ORG'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Episcopcaie', 'ORG'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('child', 'PERSON'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A33241,3 | 1018,covenant Asa Josiah mention reason ground example ground covenant covenant,man: 0.5; oath: 0.5; god: 0.5; covenant: 0.5; thing: 0.5; reason: 0.5; law: 0.5; magistrate: 0.4; people: 0.35; nation: 0.15; take: 0.15; time: 0.1; word: 0.1; scripture: 0.05; put: 0.05; lord: 0.05; heart: 0.05; conscience: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 17; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Suarez', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('C.', 'NORP'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Josiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the great deceit', 'FAC'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Deut.', 'DATE'): 1; ('17. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('arminians', 'NORP'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gregorius de Valentia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Tripl', 'GPE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tom 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8 c', 'DATE'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Becan', 'NORP'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Turrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('101.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('tandem l. 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edicto Praet ris rescinditur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam dei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('133', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Juramenta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non eru•t', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isidor', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('decret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('157', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ecclesiasticum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frederick', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Auth', 'ORG'): 1; ('etiam à majoribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('maximè ne quaerimoniam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Commissorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('hoc alteri fac', 'ORG'): 1; ('alteri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('449', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('560', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lambert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1021', 'DATE'): 1; ('1022', 'DATE'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4 Selnec', 'PERSON'): 1; ('paedag', 'ORG'): 1; ('75. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('Loc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('240', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the Psal 5 •', 'LAW'): 1; ('Bakewell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bakewel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anabaptist', 'NORP'): 1; ('192', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apollodorus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scots', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kirk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('irish', 'NORP'): 1; ('doli tes•em', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Exod', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('quam non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fox', 'ORG'): 1; ('vipido gestan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ille qui', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui hominem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('adjurationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tu periisti qui de illius morte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('satiari voluisti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('swearech', 'NORP'): 1; ('suo perjurio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•0', 'ORG'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('34. 18 , 19', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17 16. 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 ▪ mal 2', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5 33', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zedekiab', 'GPE'): 1; ('Puritan', 'GPE'): 1; ('nova', 'LOC'): 1; ('quae christus non docuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tech', 'ORG'): 1; ('par', 'ORG'): 1; ('655', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('juramentu•n', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ʋrsinus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14. 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('54', 'DATE'): 1; ('Downam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evang', 'GPE'): 1; ('74', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1071', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mar.', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philo de leg .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('one half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('harden', 'GPE'): 1"
A30399,11,contrary scripture Gal. contrary saint Augustin Unit. Eccles. contr Epist.,id: 0.5; church: 0.5; council: 0.5; contrary: 0.5; tom: 0.5; christ: 0.5; sacrament: 0.4; epist: 0.35; year: 0.3; article: 0.25; saviour: 0.2; communion: 0.2; sect: 0.15; father: 0.1; number: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 15; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Apol', 'PERSON'): 4; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('20', 'DATE'): 3; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('27', 'DATE'): 3; ('28', 'DATE'): 3; ('Iustin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('22', 'DATE'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'DATE'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Sess', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sacram', 'PERSON'): 2; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Id.', 'GPE'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tom 2', 'PERSON'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cassander', 'PERSON'): 2; ('22.', 'DATE'): 2; ('Dionysius Areopagita', 'PERSON'): 2; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Gregor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('inn', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tom 1', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Dial', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Homil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ioh', 'GPE'): 2; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustin de Unit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bellar', 'FAC'): 1; ('de Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Secunda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Id. de council', 'ORG'): 1; ('consult dr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('article 25', 'LAW'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('article 30', 'LAW'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Constantiense anno Dom', 'ORG'): 1; ('1414', 'DATE'): 1; ('fourteen hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chytrae', 'ORG'): 1; ('de Statu Eccl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('149', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1576', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('venio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cyril of Jerusalem', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Sacramentis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustin de Doctr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Catech', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('118', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ianuar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peter Lombard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1144', 'DATE'): 1; ('the council of Florence', 'ORG'): 1; ('1438', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bellarmin', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Sacram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccl', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apollinaris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the four century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cress', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('§', 'NORP'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('133', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('74', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ignatius Ep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philadelph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('162', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('94', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paedagog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ad uxorem c', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hom', 'GPE'): 1; ('inn Num. cyprian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('54', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tom 1. l. 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nazianzen Orat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gorgon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Orat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ambros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orat', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theodos', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theodoret Hist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hieronymus Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('646', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levit', 'GPE'): 1; ('leo Ser', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Comperimus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hincmar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rheims', 'NORP'): 1; ('Clovis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hauriat', 'ORG'): 1; ('vitam de sanguine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Injecto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Remigius', 'NORP'): 1; ('sva vota', 'ORG'): 1; ('Liturg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Liturgic', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('618', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. encage', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('58', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paschae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paschasius Radbertus de corp .', 'ORG'): 1; ('domini c', 'ORG'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Laity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salmeron', 'ORG'): 1; ('tertiam', 'NORP'): 1; ('s. Thome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('80', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('216', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vasquez', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('above 1200 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('1400 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('leo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gelasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constance', 'GPE'): 1; ('Birkbeck', 'PERSON'): 1; ('article 4', 'LAW'): 1; ('jewel be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Harding', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Taylor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('article 28', 'LAW'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('Irenaeus l. 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eusebius de Demonst', 'ORG'): 1; ('Evangel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Macarius Homil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nazianz', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pasch', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Bened', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anchorat', 'LOC'): 1; ('Chrysostome Homil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa', 'GPE'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ierem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Doctr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dei l. 21', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tractat', 'ORG'): 1; ('nat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ephrem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('229', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 c', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gaudentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leviticum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cheyney', 'ORG'): 1; ('Q.', 'GPE'): 1"
A37049,13 | 3534,way sanctification strictness call Jew tie ceremonial whole service sabbath-service,day: 0.45; sabbath: 0.45; duty: 0.45; god: 0.45; work: 0.45; worship: 0.45; command: 0.35; secret: 0.3; heart: 0.3; sanctification: 0.15; word: 0.15; prayer: 0.15; thing: 0.15; frame: 0.1; time: 0.1; permission: 0.05; people: 0.05; practice: 0.05; place: 0.05; piety: 0.05; piece: 0.05; pharisee: 0.05; petition: 0.05; person: 0.05; rest: 0.05; man: 0.05,"('that day', 'DATE'): 14; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('the day', 'DATE'): 12; ('this day', 'DATE'): 11; ('other day', 'DATE'): 11; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 4; ('the week', 'DATE'): 4; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('six day', 'DATE'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the six day', 'DATE'): 3; ('every day', 'DATE'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('16.23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('all the week', 'DATE'): 2; ('all day', 'DATE'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('92', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('twenty four hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('mar holy duty', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the sabbath day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the seven day', 'DATE'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a fast day', 'DATE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the very day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a solemn day', 'DATE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('God that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('58', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be come', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Saturnsdays night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Mondays', 'DATE'): 1; ('the week past', 'DATE'): 1; ('prey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seventh-day', 'DATE'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•y', 'GPE'): 1; ('boreans', 'NORP'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A37049,15,life soul sin man respect other matter soul sin occasion,man: 0.5; sin: 0.5; murder: 0.5; command: 0.5; life: 0.5; lord: 0.45; anger: 0.45; person: 0.4; justice: 0.25; brother: 0.2; evil: 0.15; neighbour: 0.15; word: 0.1; provocation: 0.1; breach: 0.1; soul: 0.1; revenge: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Eli', 'ORG'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Josephs', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Abner', 'ORG'): 2; ('Amasa', 'ORG'): 2; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cain', 'ORG'): 2; ('3.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David do Joab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vriah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jonadab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amnon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thamar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tamar do Juda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephen', 'GPE'): 1; ('2 Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 10', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.18 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lev 19.6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam 2.22', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 Sam 3.13', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 1; ('45.27', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('13.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cains', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sauls', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David of Vriah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Naboth', 'ORG'): 1; ('Joab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('kinsman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15 19', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 3.15 .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saevitia', 'GPE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.54', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.5', 'DATE'): 1"
A37049,16 | 3739,end God give use creature excess self other rule give,man: 0.5; drunkenness: 0.5; sin: 0.5; excess: 0.5; use: 0.5; god: 0.5; drink: 0.5; time: 0.45; meat: 0.35; respect: 0.25; self: 0.15; end: 0.15; consider: 0.1; reason: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 6; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5.11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('1 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 2; ('10.16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'DATE'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6.25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('mar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.17 .', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('5.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Josephs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tarry long', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('145.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('supreme', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8 9 Rom', 'DATE'): 1; ('14.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('5.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('21.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('outward appear .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hosea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('early in the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.11 , 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.8 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A37049,16 | 3762,ill look drunkenness God ill consequence condemn rule liberty take,health: 0.5; drink: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; time: 0.5; self: 0.45; way: 0.45; use: 0.45; thing: 0.45; drunkenness: 0.25; end: 0.15; occasion: 0.15; give: 0.15,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('season', 'DATE'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10.16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'DATE'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('•l', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('23.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('grace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four-hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•n or season', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ahasuerus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Esther 1.8', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bolton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phiala Jovis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ambros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de alea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jejunio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('231', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('232', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A39199,4,Tim. clergy meeting encage Tim. self godliness count word apostle,man: 0.5; godliness: 0.5; self: 0.5; god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; religion: 0.5; holiness: 0.45; christian: 0.35; time: 0.3; piety: 0.25; church: 0.25; whole: 0.2; life: 0.05; care: 0.05; master: 0.05; way: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 15; ('christian', 'NORP'): 9; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 8; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 4; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('4. 7', 'DATE'): 2; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 2; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 2; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ireneus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Valentinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chifletius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athenian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Philo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Stagyrite', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cabbala', 'GPE'): 1; ('liquorish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gymnasia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Laodicean', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mensura', 'ORG'): 1; ('the minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('their hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('the week after', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Syriack', 'ORG'): 1; ('justitiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('sidem puram', 'ORG'): 1; ('1. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('godliness hallow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•', 'ORG'): 1; ('he|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hercules', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Evangelium', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christiani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non magna loquimur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('saint Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scotish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Origines', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apelles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('last 420.', 'DATE'): 1; ('300', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('eighteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('half a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('thou daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae agenda docebat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1"
A39573,184 | 5747,man mr. Blake seed Gentiles seed other man world seed,seed: 0.5; birth: 0.5; heir: 0.5; god: 0.5; name: 0.45; privilege: 0.35; parent: 0.35; christ: 0.35; mr: 0.3; promise: 0.3; believer: 0.25; people: 0.1; holiness: 0.1; infant: 0.1; christians: 0.1; infidel: 0.05; faith: 0.05; jew: 0.05; blake: 0.05; gospel: 0.05,"('Christians', 'NORP'): 11; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 10; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 6; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 5; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 4; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('year', 'DATE'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Canaan', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('jam jam tacturo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 10', 'ORG'): 1; ('2. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('30. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('all my day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('no less than 16 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('about seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('notwithstan', 'GPE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('infideli', 'ORG'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('indian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ephesian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('2. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ashdod', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tartar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cana•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('actu•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('2. 3. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ashford', 'ORG'): 1"
A39573,235,babist neck teacher put yoke circumcision call disciple put yoke,infant: 0.35; disciple: 0.35; baptize: 0.35; mr: 0.35; yoke: 0.35; command: 0.35; circumcision: 0.3; put: 0.3; neck: 0.2; provision: 0.15; reason: 0.15; piece: 0.15; place: 0.15; position: 0.15; precept: 0.15; print: 0.15; proof: 0.15; proposition: 0.15; prosecution: 0.15; christ: 0.15; day: 0.15; viz: 0.1; call: 0.1; man: 0.05; word: 0.05,"('tomb', 'PERSON'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Judaea', 'ORG'): 2; ('Jordan', 'GPE'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the eight day', 'DATE'): 2; ('ergo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baptist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 1; ('pell mell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('martial', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('217', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('1000•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tombe•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('120', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about 3000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cozen', 'GPE'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peter do •', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Testamen•', 'ORG'): 1; ('marshal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35.', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('37.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•', 'ORG'): 1; ('197', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('202', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('203', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A39573,286,Christ rule person baptize make disciple delay convert disciple person,disciple: 0.35; baptize: 0.35; baptism: 0.35; christ: 0.35; person: 0.35; child: 0.35; convert: 0.35; delay: 0.3; mr: 0.25; example: 0.15; time: 0.15; period: 0.15; peter: 0.15; order: 0.15; parent: 0.15; part: 0.15; paul: 0.15; pen: 0.15; people: 0.15; perform: 0.15; night: 0.15; commission: 0.05; viz: 0.05; baxter: 0.05; infant: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 26; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Baxter', 'PERSON'): 4; ('38', 'DATE'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('baxte', 'PERSON'): 2; ('127', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3000', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('126', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('John 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 1; ('Samiaria', 'ORG'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Ananias', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('9 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lydia', 'GPE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the same hour of the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('18. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tarry thou', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephanus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 3. 26', 'DATE'): 1; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 1; ('7. year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('howbeit', 'GPE'): 1; ('128', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ecclosiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('three thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Baxter assert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1"
A39573,310,infant baptism question wit oppose hear century be withstand conflict,baptism: 0.45; church: 0.45; infant: 0.45; error: 0.45; christ: 0.45; promise: 0.4; pope: 0.4; thing: 0.4; truth: 0.25; case: 0.2; matter: 0.2; spirit: 0.2; man: 0.15; time: 0.15; priest: 0.05; presence: 0.05; professor: 0.05; profess: 0.05; proceed: 0.05; priesthood: 0.05; protestant: 0.05; possibility: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the first century', 'DATE'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('600', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lateran', 'GPE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luth', 'GPE'): 1; ('Featley', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Protestanism', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('lit•', 'ORG'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('g .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('amici', 'NORP'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('alias pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1"
A39573,343,Review work spirit faith soul equal creation subject spirit God,infant: 0.45; faith: 0.45; spirit: 0.45; manner: 0.45; thing: 0.45; baptize: 0.45; soul: 0.4; baptism: 0.4; man: 0.3; equal: 0.15; god: 0.15; christ: 0.15; woman: 0.1; scripture: 0.1; plea: 0.05; power: 0.05; pagan: 0.05; parent: 0.05; passage: 0.05; person: 0.05; petworth: 0.05; piece: 0.05; place: 0.05; nation: 0.05; viz: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 2; ('Turks', 'NORP'): 2; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Petworth dispute Ian', 'FAC'): 1; ('5. 1651', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('outward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('1000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•', 'ORG'): 1; ('1 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15. 35', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A39573,476,man ceremony substance Baptist receive letter friend word suit word,baptism: 0.4; ceremony: 0.4; ordinance: 0.4; thing: 0.4; water: 0.4; mr: 0.4; truth: 0.4; viz: 0.4; another: 0.25; rite: 0.25; circumcision: 0.15; rag: 0.1; purpose: 0.1; reason: 0.1; rantize: 0.1; rantism: 0.1; recovery: 0.1; privation: 0.1; prophet: 0.1; resemblance: 0.1; proportion: 0.1; self: 0.05; matter: 0.05; god: 0.05,"('cook', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('218', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Baptist', 'ORG'): 1; ('baxte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wash', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('adesse', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tilenus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('219', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baxter', 'PERSON'): 1"
A39573,515 | 8326,parish pppastor self dispensation Christ selfs sake flock flock Christ,god: 0.5; truth: 0.5; man: 0.5; way: 0.5; thing: 0.5; self: 0.5; word: 0.5; time: 0.5; people: 0.45; king: 0.15; faith: 0.15; reformation: 0.1; priest: 0.1; authority: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 3; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('scottish', 'NORP'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Holland', 'GPE'): 2; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 2; ('100d', 'DATE'): 2; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('his quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('five and ten pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Kirk', 'ORG'): 1; ('presbyterian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ahab 1 kin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Micaiah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tempora mutantur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('illis', 'GPE'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Q.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Q. Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('synodian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Festraw', 'ORG'): 1; ('Prelacy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('6. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Babylon to Zion', 'ORG'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judaea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Corinth', 'GPE'): 1; ('Galatia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plilippi', 'GPE'): 1; ('colosse', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thessalonica', 'GPE'): 1; ('gape', 'ORG'): 1; ('singulis', 'GPE'): 1; ('singuli', 'GPE'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Denmark', 'GPE'): 1; ('Swethland', 'GPE'): 1; ('•', 'GPE'): 1; ('Baxt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('151', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('long•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Fonts', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('a penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Papal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Presbyte•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Presb•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('100d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('more than one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Featley', 'PERSON'): 1; ('167', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('they|will', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('PPPriest', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('nec per se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euphoniae', 'NORP'): 1; ('two hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('two day', 'DATE'): 1; ('two week', 'DATE'): 1; ('two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tyrannus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pilate', 'ORG'): 1; ('the half quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('irish', 'NORP'): 1"
A39573,515 | 8396,shift invention clergy religion protestant abomination protestant ccclergy Prelacy Presbytery,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; church: 0.5; christ: 0.5; truth: 0.5; minister: 0.5; people: 0.5; ccclergy: 0.35; clergy: 0.35; reason: 0.25; gospel: 0.2; dr: 0.15; viz: 0.1; anabaptists: 0.05; thing: 0.05,"('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 9; ('England', 'GPE'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Featley', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Helin', 'ORG'): 2; ('161', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('164', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ashford', 'ORG'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Prelacy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levites', 'GPE'): 1; ('Classis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('189', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adul•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 2', 'LAW'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('anthropo', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nicolas', 'ORG'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('163', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('118', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hos suo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('1099', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christndome', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty to 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('P•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Artium', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('100', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nescis nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('noscis', 'DATE'): 1; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('mar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the university of Athens', 'ORG'): 1; ('the ccchristian ministry', 'ORG'): 1; ('Baptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('former day', 'DATE'): 1; ('•', 'NORP'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christndom', 'GPE'): 1; ('BBBabilon', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('All•', 'ORG'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('nihil consequeris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi vilem de blasphematione', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('periculi veterem fidem quasi novellam otiosa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('truth•', 'NORP'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Thes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('g•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Roger', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pos•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1500 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('martial', 'PERSON'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('bakewel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('barber', 'PERSON'): 1; ('otiosam disputationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Henry Wotton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pruritus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pruritus', 'ORG'): 1; ('smith', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cice•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('na•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sch•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sor•', 'PRODUCT'): 1"
A35416,28,child return PROV son heart be spirit people God be,heart: 0.45; god: 0.45; son: 0.45; give: 0.45; man: 0.45; soul: 0.45; religion: 0.45; thing: 0.4; love: 0.35; way: 0.2; lord: 0.15; word: 0.1; enemy: 0.05; principle: 0.05; priority: 0.05; pride: 0.05; primitia: 0.05; principal: 0.05; press: 0.05; privilege: 0.05; privation: 0.05; presence: 0.05; prison: 0.05; due: 0.05; self: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 20; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('PROV', 'ORG'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Idiom', 'ORG'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('indian', 'NORP'): 1; ('American', 'NORP'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Saul', 'ORG'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bathsh•ba', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magn•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ʋdum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dam primitia• Cordis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alpha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dam •lorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Donum Hamatum', 'ORG'): 1; ('prosperous day', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Posse', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pythagorean', 'ORG'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Dalilah', 'GPE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('truth|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('ceremouy', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jezabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('scinderis hamo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fluxus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cordis', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1"
A35416,28 | 10269,lord heart nonlatinalphabet throne heart man dominion sovereignty usurpation popery,heart: 0.5; god: 0.5; love: 0.5; give: 0.5; performance: 0.5; man: 0.5; self: 0.5; thing: 0.45; religion: 0.4; intention: 0.25; apostle: 0.25; christ: 0.1; soul: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 42; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jonah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('persian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Davids', 'GPE'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tota', 'PERSON'): 1; ('outward expression', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacobs', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bacchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Venus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Neptune', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('Danaos', 'NORP'): 1; ('dona', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dalilah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samson', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou lov-st', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('cor suum', 'ORG'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be fibula animarum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('knit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israelite', 'NORP'): 1; ('Evangelicall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lukewarm Laodicea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('cor tuum mi•i', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'GPE'): 1; ('ethiopian', 'NORP'): 1; ('hypocrisy it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('take heed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Basan', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lebanon', 'GPE'): 1; ('outward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1"
A35416,29,soul PSAL. hart water-brook soul God! strain David harp expression,god: 0.5; soul: 0.5; water: 0.5; glory: 0.5; sweetness: 0.45; brook: 0.4; face: 0.35; hart: 0.3; word: 0.25; joy: 0.25; self: 0.2; double: 0.2; creature: 0.15; christian: 0.15; man: 0.15; heaven: 0.1; place: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 48; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 19; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 12; ('thou', 'GPE'): 9; ('David', 'PERSON'): 9; ('christian', 'NORP'): 9; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 6; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('hart', 'LAW'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 2; ('he|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('he|be', 'TIME'): 2; ('Bethlehem', 'GPE'): 2; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('polish', 'NORP'): 1; ('139', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sharon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Agamemnon', 'GPE'): 1; ('autumn', 'DATE'): 1; ('Historistia Animalium', 'ORG'): 1; ('three hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('fifty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Haeret', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seraphim', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('marty•um exercitu•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Antipater', 'GPE'): 1; ('Laodicean', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirsty hart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('modestia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lucian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Isis', 'GPE'): 1; ('fig', 'ORG'): 1; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('water|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eunapius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Longinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nilum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bonum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be svi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('diffusi•um', 'NORP'): 1; ('Canaan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inviscerari', 'GPE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Job', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nimrod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Meribah', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet ▪', 'ORG'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gilead', 'ORG'): 1; ('comfort fail', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Imperatoria', 'NORP'): 1; ('a night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Anacreon', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Themistocles', 'ORG'): 1; ('Kedar', 'ORG'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('look|it', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Davids', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bethlehem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eustathius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bethesda', 'GPE'): 1; ('Carnea Encheiridia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('flumina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Trismegistus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calix', 'ORG'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('flagon', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('domus orationis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('matutina laetitia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Beza', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heinsius', 'NORP'): 1"
A35416,35,worth soul man profit whole world soul man exchange soul,soul: 0.45; man: 0.45; god: 0.45; body: 0.45; world: 0.45; worth: 0.45; thing: 0.45; spirit: 0.45; self: 0.35; excellency: 0.35; christ: 0.1; working: 0.05; word: 0.05; preservation: 0.05; price: 0.05; preciousness: 0.05; preparation: 0.05; prerogative: 0.05; prescribe: 0.05; presence: 0.05; presentness: 0.05; pour: 0.05; prison: 0.05,"('it|be', 'PERSON'): 22; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 5; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 3; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Acupictus', 'ORG'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('benè', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('Amminadab', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plotinus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('suiipsi•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('•enestrata', 'ORG'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('st John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gaius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nestor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('body|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Angles', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('he|will', 'NORP'): 1; ('they|will', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leviathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('polish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gilead', 'ORG'): 1; ('the present season', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('victuri', 'GPE'): 1; ('Animula', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae tandem abitura', 'ORG'): 1; ('nay', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jezabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylonish', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be double', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ambrosia', 'GPE'): 1"
A39896,12,lutheran saviour eucharist cross roman catholic reality part saint Paul,god: 0.5; church: 0.5; conception: 0.5; truth: 0.5; christ: 0.5; time: 0.5; saint: 0.4; religion: 0.4; define: 0.3; body: 0.3; reveal: 0.25; place: 0.15; spirit: 0.05; faith: 0.05; scripture: 0.05; man: 0.05,"('B.', 'NORP'): 5; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paschal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Roman catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('extirpat', 'GPE'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('500', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Taylor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Machievillians', 'NORP'): 1; ('prudentia', 'NORP'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('quae se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('meliora transire', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ambros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('B.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Momus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('de arcanis cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Andrew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abdias', 'ORG'): 1; ('historiarum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it• secundus Adam for•••• ex •erra virginea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nunquam maledicta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('qui ita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sanzez', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baptista de Lezana Carmel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sedulius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('430', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lib', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('PP', 'GPE'): 1; ('rosa mollis surgit acutis nil quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evae de stirpe', 'ORG'): 1; ('maria virginis antiquae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nova virgo', 'LOC'): 1; ('natura gratiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('natunam cum qua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('• Paral', 'ORG'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sexta Sinodus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('veneratur liturgiam D. Jacobi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('matrem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('synod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('inn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('summi pontificis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernard in Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('174', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ad canonicos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laus Deo', 'ORG'): 1"
A30537,11,confusion kingdom Babylon divide form presbyterians imdependant Anabaptists other worship,christ: 0.5; word: 0.5; heart: 0.5; lord: 0.5; god: 0.5; light: 0.45; scripture: 0.4; kingdom: 0.35; day: 0.35; power: 0.3; man: 0.25; people: 0.2; jesus: 0.15; observation: 0.05,"('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 6; ('the day', 'DATE'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('David', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('the year', 'DATE'): 3; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 2; ('Lo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('day', 'DATE'): 2; ('presbyterians', 'NORP'): 1; ('the golden cup', 'FAC'): 1; ('so many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Balaa•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gosp•', 'ORG'): 1; ('the acceptable year', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('sigh shall', 'ORG'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('blasphemer', 'GPE'): 1; ('forth•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'PERSON'): 1; ('janne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the latter day', 'DATE'): 1; ('ge', 'ORG'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('W. D.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sodom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('new Jer•', 'GPE'): 1"
A38689,12,epilogue widow sir Frederick revenge frolic wit cozen make wealth,church: 0.45; god: 0.45; catholic: 0.45; man: 0.45; lord: 0.45; roman: 0.45; christ: 0.4; protestant: 0.4; father: 0.35; faith: 0.2; cure: 0.15; promise: 0.1; sin: 0.05; glory: 0.05; parliament: 0.05; pain: 0.05; please: 0.05; play: 0.05; place: 0.05; pay: 0.05; particular: 0.05; preacher: 0.05; offend: 0.05; objection: 0.05; vow: 0.05; make: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 6; ('Roman catholic', 'NORP'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Alleluia', 'PERSON'): 2; ('John 5', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('the holy catholic church', 'ORG'): 2; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Frederick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wheadle', 'GPE'): 1; ('Wheadle', 'ORG'): 1; ('we|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('former day', 'DATE'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('George duke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Buckingham', 'GPE'): 1; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 1; ('the month of June and July 1663', 'DATE'): 1; ('A. S.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('misericordiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('confiteri honorificum', 'LOC'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the first of August , 1663', 'DATE'): 1; ('Clama', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tubam exalia', 'ORG'): 1; ('vocem tuam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('annuntia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isaiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('58', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('gaudeamn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('demus gloriam ei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gnace George Buckingham', 'FAC'): 1; ('domino misericordiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('heresy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('luke 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tha•', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sectarian Bible', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('false prophet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bailiff', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('435', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Whitaker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epist', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('heresy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('18. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mat 18. 17', 'PERSON'): 1"
A35963,8,cure faith cure glory God soul cure cure cure God,god: 0.45; cure: 0.45; king: 0.45; voyage: 0.45; work: 0.45; drake: 0.45; man: 0.4; francis: 0.35; faith: 0.3; john: 0.25; west: 0.2; soul: 0.15; glory: 0.05; hand: 0.05; peter: 0.05; paul: 0.05; preparation: 0.05; practice: 0.05; place: 0.05; print: 0.05; peace: 0.05; parentage: 0.05; parliament: 0.05; protestant: 0.05; ship: 0.05,"('Francis Drake', 'PERSON'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Alleluia', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 9 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('merit de congruo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('domini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thrice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('JehoVa jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('CHAP', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('operibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('exurgat deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Urim', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thummim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jachin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('IESVS', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('maria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mater dei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Samuel Clark', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bennet Fink', 'ORG'): 1; ('Simon miller', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1671', 'DATE'): 1; ('1595', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tavistock', 'GPE'): 1; ('Devonshire', 'GPE'): 1; ('Francis Russel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('earl of', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bedford', 'GPE'): 1; ('Francis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('navy', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deacon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Medway', 'ORG'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zealand', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Hawkins', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1567', 'DATE'): 1; ('John de Vllva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Drake', 'ORG'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('the year 1572', 'DATE'): 1; ('Whitsunday Eve', 'DATE'): 1; ('may 24th', 'DATE'): 1; ('John Drake', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twenty five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seventy three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('forty seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty six', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A36385,2,urge resistance command person duty bind saviour Io. another doctrine,king: 0.5; man: 0.5; law: 0.5; prince: 0.5; subject: 0.5; peace: 0.45; self: 0.25; god: 0.25; right: 0.2; people: 0.2; resistance: 0.2; time: 0.2; term: 0.2; act: 0.15; take: 0.1; ground: 0.1; majesty: 0.05; kind: 0.05; sovereign: 0.05; word: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 2; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Io', 'LOC'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iezabel', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phaedria', 'GPE'): 1; ('natus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Topick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Agamemnon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vulcan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pelops', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Quaeris', 'GPE'): 1; ('parem', 'GPE'): 1; ('nisi ipse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zenophen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Synesius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('fortunati nimium bona', 'FAC'): 1; ('sva !', 'ORG'): 1; ('thrice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('st Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Homer', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('110 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('viâ lacteâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pacificus', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('propulsare injuriam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fort', 'GPE'): 1; ('Civilia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Una', 'LOC'): 1; ('Lynceus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oedipu•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Publicis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Samson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Machiavelli', 'GPE'): 1; ('amplianda', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Canonists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Kings', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the supreme magistrate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jehues', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joram', 'ORG'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeroboam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Enthusiastis', 'NORP'): 1; ('perplex mystery', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui regem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rehoboam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1"
A36385,2 | 22493,resistance foremention resistance undertake way resistance other resistance see write,king: 0.45; god: 0.45; way: 0.45; time: 0.45; resistance: 0.45; prince: 0.45; person: 0.4; blood: 0.4; reason: 0.35; law: 0.2; defence: 0.15; point: 0.15; premise: 0.1; religion: 0.05; sin: 0.05; right: 0.05; people: 0.05; prayer: 0.05; power: 0.05; ponder: 0.05; plant: 0.05; prediction: 0.05; performance: 0.05; parliament: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('quod restat probandum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('defensoribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dioclesian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('notwithstand•ng', 'GPE'): 1; ('last two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('st John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zacharias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 15', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Corah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Moses', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cives', 'ORG'): 1; ('Moabite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anglica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('24. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('the disaffect party', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1"
A34097,8 | 25522,supremacy pope Boniface An. title bishop thing conduce honour government,church: 0.5; emperor: 0.5; pope: 0.5; empire: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; power: 0.5; king: 0.5; italy: 0.4; supremacy: 0.3; prince: 0.25; god: 0.2; world: 0.1; clergy: 0.1; thing: 0.05; right: 0.05; head: 0.05,"('Italy', 'GPE'): 15; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 5; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Pepin', 'ORG'): 4; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 4; ('Boniface', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 3; ('Mauritius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 3; ('France', 'GPE'): 3; ('Hildebrand', 'LOC'): 3; ('Hildebrand', 'GPE'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Boniface', 'ORG'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 2; ('french', 'NORP'): 2; ('Caroline', 'NORP'): 2; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ralph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Petra', 'ORG'): 2; ('606', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Chalcedon', 'ORG'): 1; ('fourteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the church accord institute', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phocas', 'GPE'): 1; ('about 606', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lucifer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('about the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('410', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Carthage', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mantuan', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be prelate', 'ORG'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year 710', 'DATE'): 1; ('about 726', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('712', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Charles Martel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saracens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pepin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pepin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('temple , abbey', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caroline', 'ORG'): 1; ('884', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about the year 900', 'DATE'): 1; ('German', 'NORP'): 1; ('about the year 1000', 'DATE'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about 1047', 'DATE'): 1; ('about 1050', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nicholas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about 1060', 'DATE'): 1; ('the next year', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1073', 'DATE'): 1; ('Henry 4', 'LAW'): 1; ('Rodolph', 'ORG'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mathilda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4 th .', 'DATE'): 1; ('supreme iversal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Canonists', 'NORP'): 1; ('supreme', 'ORG'): 1; ('Religionists', 'NORP'): 1; ('christianity', 'NORP'): 1"
A34097,9 | 25821,Alexander name word speech God soul book edition christian people,god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; king: 0.5; book: 0.5; people: 0.5; world: 0.5; christian: 0.5; man: 0.5; lord: 0.35; name: 0.35; church: 0.1; prophet: 0.1; christ: 0.05; self: 0.05,"('christian', 'NORP'): 18; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 6; ('thou', 'GPE'): 6; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 6; ('France', 'GPE'): 6; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 4; ('John', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Micheas', 'ORG'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 2; ('french', 'NORP'): 2; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 2; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('325', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pasquin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anonymus', 'ORG'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20 , 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nineveh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caiphas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Waldus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wickliff', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Serena', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lewis Xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Drabricius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some ten year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cyrus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('44.', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cyrus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Augustus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Cain', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jezebel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antiochus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Caiphas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Deodat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylonish', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eli', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('machiavellian politician', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezek', 'ORG'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1714', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tartar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bartimeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Moab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Damascus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Babylonish', 'NORP'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mich. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 and a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eliah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dabricius', 'ORG'): 1; ('416', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('259', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Drabr', 'ORG'): 1; ('559', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'ORG'): 1; ('569', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A34097,9 | 25966,God father lord Jesus Christ leave consolation protection demonstration verity,god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; lord: 0.5; earth: 0.5; day: 0.5; man: 0.5; nation: 0.5; world: 0.35; name: 0.35; spirit: 0.3; end: 0.1; faith: 0.1; glory: 0.1; christ: 0.05; prophecy: 0.05; make: 0.05; speech: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 28; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 4; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('these last day', 'DATE'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Hildegard', 'ORG'): 2; ('Effron', 'ORG'): 1; ('211', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('250', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('257', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nicholas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('Alpha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Omega', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa. 49.', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a day', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('July', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('1664', 'DATE'): 1; ('my age the 76th', 'DATE'): 1; ('48th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('36th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('26th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('the year 1653', 'DATE'): 1; ('April 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year 1664', 'DATE'): 1; ('June 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('Seraphim', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou day', 'DATE'): 1; ('acknowledge', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou alone', 'GPE'): 1; ('twenty six whole year', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten month', 'DATE'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('this year 1664', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Josias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul Laurine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Drabricius', 'ORG'): 1; ('the end of September', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augurium', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eugenius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Kotter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A33236,35,survey chapter leave discourse Trinity censure considerer mystery matter chapter,man: 0.5; martyr: 0.5; christ: 0.5; christian: 0.5; witness: 0.5; god: 0.5; sovereign: 0.45; saviour: 0.35; mr: 0.35; faith: 0.15; heart: 0.15; thing: 0.15; hobbes: 0.1; command: 0.1; scripture: 0.05; life: 0.05; king: 0.05; church: 0.05,"('christian', 'NORP'): 18; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('John', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 3; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 3; ('Rimmon', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('272', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Naaman', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('273', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('274', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('chapter 42', 'LAW'): 1; ('Arius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Macedonius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('267', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('those hundred of year', 'DATE'): 1; ('hobb•s', 'PERSON'): 1; ('261', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('n•w', 'ORG'): 1; ('•urmise', 'PERSON'): 1; ('271', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('syrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('dr lightfoot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ehuds', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eglon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Naaman', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 2. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('101', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('19 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Venus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('d•nieth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Mahometan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mahomet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mahometan', 'NORP'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cromwell', 'ORG'): 1; ('Euripides english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hudibras', 'LOC'): 1; ('half a dozen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus be Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fath•r', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mahometans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hobbes', 'PERSON'): 1"
A38506,3,opportunity digression notice sense passage write soul mention right interpret,soul: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; nature: 0.5; law: 0.45; life: 0.45; self: 0.4; thing: 0.35; divine: 0.35; world: 0.25; death: 0.25; body: 0.2; epicurus: 0.2; immortality: 0.05; lib: 0.05,"('Lib', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Epicurus', 'ORG'): 4; ('Epicurus', 'PRODUCT'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 3; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 2; ('aurae particulam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cato Major', 'ORG'): 1; ('Divina', 'GPE'): 1; ('referri omnia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sideris', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Empedocles', 'GPE'): 1; ('tandem', 'ORG'): 1; ('pristinam sedem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clem Alexandrinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Animos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deos fieri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Lethe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pythagoras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Stobaeus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Eccl', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Jove', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Classis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Greeks , Dicaearchus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Andraeas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Asclepiades', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phaed', 'GPE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Galen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theodoret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the Tenent of Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexander Rosse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Demonax', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lucian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Marcus Antoninus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Animas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aer : and', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magno', 'ORG'): 1; ('extriti permeare non posse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('statim dispergi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Democritus', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('the supreme essence (', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bacchus', 'ORG'): 1; ('his day', 'DATE'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('grecian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('only two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hominibus', 'GPE'): 1; ('ipsi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('omnino nihil curent', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pietas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('debetur', 'GPE'): 1; ('nihil acceperis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deberi potest', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('coactus', 'ORG'): 1; ('graecorum conviviis', 'ORG'): 1; ('aut bibat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoniam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pariter cum aliis voluptate potandi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diogenes Laertius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mirâ', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui incolumis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('integer', 'ORG'): 1; ('sine morbo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vivis excessit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Demosthenes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Democles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cleanthes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysippus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Empedocles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Cleombrotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nullam aliam ob causam nisi quod Platoni', 'PERSON'): 1; ('W. Charleton', 'PERSON'): 1"
A37244,2,thing abstract kind lodge mind act accident observation abstract divine,soul: 0.5; body: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; power: 0.5; thing: 0.5; sin: 0.45; nature: 0.4; sense: 0.4; world: 0.35; life: 0.2; light: 0.1; part: 0.1,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 18; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 8; ('China', 'GPE'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zach', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zachariah 12.1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erroneus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('every hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Matthew 19', 'PERSON'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul 2 mile', 'PERSON'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('autumn', 'DATE'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('grey winter', 'ORG'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('noon', 'TIME'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('european', 'NORP'): 1; ('african', 'NORP'): 1; ('American', 'NORP'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cookery', 'ORG'): 1; ('a thousand light', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Janus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Poll', 'PRODUCT'): 1"
A38774,1,time king Charles war holland issue emperor war Turk event,king: 0.5; charles: 0.5; god: 0.5; messiah: 0.5; israel: 0.5; book: 0.45; ben: 0.45; war: 0.4; france: 0.35; people: 0.25; hand: 0.2; man: 0.15; england: 0.05; print: 0.05; world: 0.05; throne: 0.05; enemy: 0.05,"('Charles', 'PERSON'): 14; ('Ben-Israel', 'PERSON'): 7; ('France', 'GPE'): 6; ('french', 'NORP'): 6; ('England', 'GPE'): 5; ('Messiah', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('Messiah', 'GPE'): 3; ('holland', 'GPE'): 2; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Esai .', 'DATE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('Swedland', 'ORG'): 2; ('english', 'NORP'): 2; ('eight year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1664', 'DATE'): 1; ('1650', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ephe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('this 1650', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Messiah', 'LOC'): 1; ('Oliver', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three hundred year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Edward 3 d .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('white', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five year', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('deliverer', 'ORG'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lorain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lorain', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('this five year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Holland', 'GPE'): 1"
A38774,4,Ben-Israel Evans wish grace truth God saviour sir difference language,king: 0.5; god: 0.5; charles: 0.5; messiah: 0.5; jesus: 0.5; call: 0.5; jew: 0.5; son: 0.5; christ: 0.3; say: 0.2; scripture: 0.15; ephraim: 0.15; england: 0.1; man: 0.05; land: 0.05,"('Charles', 'PERSON'): 41; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 24; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 19; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 18; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 17; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 16; ('England', 'GPE'): 15; ('Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 13; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 13; ('Messiah', 'PERSON'): 11; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 9; ('David', 'PERSON'): 9; ('Ephratah', 'ORG'): 9; ('Ieroboam', 'PERSON'): 9; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 8; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Juda', 'PERSON'): 7; ('english', 'NORP'): 6; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('Messiah', 'PRODUCT'): 6; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 6; ('Shem', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('morning', 'TIME'): 5; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 5; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 4; ('Iaphet', 'GPE'): 4; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 4; ('27', 'DATE'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('London', 'GPE'): 4; ('28', 'DATE'): 4; ('8', 'DATE'): 4; ('14', 'DATE'): 4; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Magog', 'ORG'): 3; ('26', 'DATE'): 3; ('Pharaoh', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Gogmagog', 'GPE'): 3; ('Messiah', 'GPE'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 3; ('this day', 'DATE'): 3; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('11', 'DATE'): 3; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'DATE'): 3; ('4', 'DATE'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('ruth', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Abel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('18', 'DATE'): 2; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 2; ('132', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('mount Ephraim', 'LOC'): 2; ('Ephrathites', 'NORP'): 2; ('2. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ephrah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('35.', 'DATE'): 2; ('Melchizedek', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('1. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Scota', 'NORP'): 2; ('Scots', 'ORG'): 2; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'DATE'): 2; ('John 16', 'PERSON'): 2; ('9', 'DATE'): 2; ('10', 'DATE'): 2; ('12', 'DATE'): 2; ('13', 'DATE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'DATE'): 2; ('6', 'DATE'): 2; ('7', 'DATE'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'DATE'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17. 12', 'DATE'): 2; ('Boaz', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Malhon', 'GPE'): 2; ('24', 'MONEY'): 2; ('Rebeckah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ben-Israel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evans', 'ORG'): 1; ('Charles of England', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deliverer', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this twenty four year', 'DATE'): 1; ('above twenty two year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('as thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('56', 'DATE'): 1; ('two messiahs', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Jesus of Shem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('13.', 'DATE'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('39', 'MONEY'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('Egyptians', 'NORP'): 1; ('41', 'MONEY'): 1; ('11. 45', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hosea', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hosea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Holland', 'GPE'): 1; ('mount Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Micah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Messiah', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sam 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('50', 'DATE'): 1; ('Epratah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chorn', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('4. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abram', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('16.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephrata', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bethelem Ephratah', 'LOC'): 1; ('Matthew 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bethelem', 'GPE'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Constantine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus , Revelat', 'ORG'): 1; ('2. 27.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Selah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psalm 97', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('5. 10. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Esdras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('three hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gathelus Fergus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Scota', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sodam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gathelus Fergus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bethel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Portugal', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Knockfergus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bethel in Canaan', 'ORG'): 1; ('some hundred year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('Westminster Abby', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iames', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('10. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the 30 of January , 1648', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('6. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Ian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iudgson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that day morning', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('John 14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('11. 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('1 Corin', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baptist', 'NORP'): 1; ('48. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zecha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a thousand year 2 Pet', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('53.', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('110', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('63. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('5. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Charles', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joshua 16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zereda', 'GPE'): 1; ('Caleb', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('2. 50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('53', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zeruah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epbratah', 'GPE'): 1; ('1. 50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eprathites', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('obed•esse', 'ORG'): 1; ('jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 26', 'DATE'): 1; ('•y', 'GPE'): 1; ('Damascus', 'GPE'): 1; ('15', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Rebeckah', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('thirty year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('this eight year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jang', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arise Evans', 'PERSON'): 1; ('march', 'DATE'): 1; ('16••', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A35787,10,CHAP. IV. reason IV. write father be place corrupt time,council: 0.5; book: 0.5; church: 0.5; man: 0.5; thing: 0.5; time: 0.5; canon: 0.45; saint: 0.3; father: 0.3; write: 0.3; bishop: 0.1; body: 0.1; word: 0.1; christ: 0.1; act: 0.05; find: 0.05; author: 0.05; whole: 0.05; pope: 0.05,"('greek', 'NORP'): 16; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('latin', 'NORP'): 12; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 11; ('this day', 'DATE'): 9; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 9; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Cypr', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Hier', 'PERSON'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 6; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 5; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('Adrian', 'NORP'): 5; ('Anastasius', 'ORG'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 5; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 4; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 4; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 4; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Apol', 'PERSON'): 3; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Viii', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Latines', 'ORG'): 3; ('Tom 3', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Conc', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Tarasius', 'ORG'): 3; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Athanasius', 'ORG'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1537', 'DATE'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Par', 'ORG'): 3; ('1564', 'DATE'): 3; ('pamel', 'PERSON'): 3; ('quae', 'GPE'): 3; ('S. Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('August', 'DATE'): 3; ('Bertram', 'PERSON'): 3; ('nec', 'ORG'): 3; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Latins', 'PERSON'): 2; ('S. Hierome', 'PERSON'): 2; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 2; ('S. Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Tom 4', 'PERSON'): 2; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Praef', 'PERSON'): 2; ('James', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the council of Chalcedon', 'ORG'): 2; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Dionysius Exiguus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Dionysius Exiguus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Tobit', 'ORG'): 2; ('Judith', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Laodicea', 'ORG'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the greek Code', 'EVENT'): 2; ('Balsamon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Zonaras', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Cyprus', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Vii', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Anastas', 'ORG'): 2; ('Chalcedon', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ib', 'NORP'): 2; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the council of Florence', 'ORG'): 2; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Latins', 'ORG'): 2; ('saint cyprian', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Pamel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Gryph', 'GPE'): 2; ('Cathedra', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Morel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('254', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Morel', 'ORG'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sirmond', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ms.', 'ORG'): 2; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('869', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Simon Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Photius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 2; ('Id.', 'GPE'): 2; ('paris', 'GPE'): 2; ('Tom 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten or twelve century of year', 'DATE'): 1; ('ethiopian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pyrrhonians', 'NORP'): 1; ('this last age', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Hier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tom 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daemonum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('saint luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Expos', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tom 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ruff', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hypothesis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cyril', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antioch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Conc', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('S. Cyril', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Praefat', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tom 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('Trustee', 'ORG'): 1; ('these eight hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('S.', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Irenaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ruffinus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ruffin', 'GPE'): 1; ('93', 'DATE'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gennald', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Catal', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Hierome', 'ORG'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theoph', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Verceil', 'ORG'): 1; ('a quarter of a hour', 'DATE'): 1; ('211', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('assuisse', 'GPE'): 1; ('nugas suas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vives', 'ORG'): 1; ('twenty-one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine de civitate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lud', 'ORG'): 1; ('lib', 'GPE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('antiquis libris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui sequuntur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten or', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bruges', 'GPE'): 1; ('Collen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1531', 'DATE'): 1; ('Holstein', 'GPE'): 1; ('praef', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tomb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Procli', 'ORG'): 1; ('iisdem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dutchman', 'GPE'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Andreas Masius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Syriac', 'LOC'): 1; ('Andr', 'GPE'): 1; ('litur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Masius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Liturg', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cassander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2148', 'DATE'): 1; ('2158', 'DATE'): 1; ('Scalig', 'ORG'): 1; ('198', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('201 a.', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Telesphorus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Card', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('perron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Observ', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year 451', 'DATE'): 1; ('600', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tom 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zozimus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about fifty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('about seventy four year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the council of Chalcedon , Dionysius Exiguus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Regi•', 'DATE'): 1; ('the council of La•dicea', 'ORG'): 1; ('163', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the greek Code of the church iversal', 'EVENT'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('162', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xxii', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apocalypse', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('the council of the french church', 'ORG'): 1; ('scriptur•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('the african church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Perron Repl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Perron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('the greek Cud•', 'ORG'): 1; ('the i ▪ council of Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Balsamon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zonaras', 'LOC'): 1; ('the council of Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dionysius', 'ORG'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the general council of Eph•sus', 'ORG'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('178', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Ephesus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the least seven hundred and fifty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('gen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('A•astasius Bibliothecarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('eight hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the general council of Chalcedon', 'ORG'): 1; ('senate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chalc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('206', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Metropolitans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pontus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Thrace', 'ORG'): 1; ('eleven hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('the six century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about seven hundred and', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('557', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Photia', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('synod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('625', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('616', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Panarium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ancyranus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. Conc', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ancoratus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eunomius', 'ORG'): 1; ('latin•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cyrill', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epictetus', 'ORG'): 1; ('eastern', 'NORP'): 1; ('Zozimus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gregorius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Florence , Apol', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('protosyn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marc Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John damascene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petavi••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epiphan', 'GPE'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saturdays', 'DATE'): 1; ('Viii', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Anastasius Bibliothecarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('the Nicene Creed', 'ORG'): 1; ('Julian', 'NORP'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Conc Vii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('videnda annot', 'ORG'): 1; ('late year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Laurentius Bochellus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesiae Gallicanae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bochel Praefat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ab is•i•', 'ORG'): 1; ('regibus parcero non assuetis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nedum s. Ludovico', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonrull•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('maximè ad rei Gallicae', 'ORG'): 1; ('ab Bibliotheca', 'ORG'): 1; ('PP', 'ORG'): 1; ('constitutionibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lutetiae', 'NORP'): 1; ('vae', 'ORG'): 1; ('nebulonibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Musarum', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('musas ipsa', 'ORG'): 1; ('religionis zelo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inter pias', 'ORG'): 1; ('Kings', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lewis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sanctio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Regiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Muse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Extr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('domini doctrinam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Confessorum praesentiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Martyrum', 'GPE'): 1; ('148', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aliae Editiones', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Manutii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Morellii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1568', 'DATE'): 1; ('158', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('124', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Petram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cathedram Constituit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gryphii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Primatus Petro', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apostolis', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae verba omnia', 'ORG'): 1; ('illis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Morel •ti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Qui Cathedram Petri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam sundata', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nunquam editam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Epistolam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Firmilianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Caesarea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cappadocia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Manutius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Morellius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Opusc', 'GPE'): 1; ('216', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nicolas Faber', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('215', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1603', 'DATE'): 1; ('Damasus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('B.', 'NORP'): 1; ('episcopum consecravit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel ecclesiam omnem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('disponendam commisit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tu minimè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('habentur haec ex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1621', 'DATE'): 1; ('664', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Stephano V.', 'GPE'): 1; ('219', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Papa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Papa Urbis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euchar', 'GPE'): 1; ('464', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Papa Ʋrbis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Papa Orbis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fulbert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Villersio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1608', 'DATE'): 1; ('168', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Figura', 'GPE'): 1; ('dicet Haereticus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fulbertus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gregor', 'GPE'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sacer•o•um •i praepatatur exercitus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vindic', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gregor loc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('666', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('pari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aimon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Gest', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5 c', 'DATE'): 1; ('quam synodo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Universalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Orthodoxi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Orthodoxi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom x.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Viii general council', 'ORG'): 1; ('Doct', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Card', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phrygia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Archangel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David H•eschelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origen against Celsus', 'ORG'): 1; ('483', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bellarm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jussu recognitis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('937', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui B. Petro Apostolo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('clavibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('coelestibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('animas ligandi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'ORG'): 1; ('Animas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tuesday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Clem Viii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('reco•n', 'ORG'): 1; ('369', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dixit Jesus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Brev', 'GPE'): 1; ('1492', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jo. de Prato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('discipulos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simoni Petro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Valencia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pontif', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod nonnunquam ignoratur à pluribus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('soavez', 'PERSON'): 1; ('trident l. 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nestorian', 'GPE'): 1; ('the catholic party', 'ORG'): 1; ('V. Col', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theodorus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ibas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mopsuestia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edissa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Id. Col', 'ORG'): 1; ('about three hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('five hundred year before', 'DATE'): 1; ('hea•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the seven council , council', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.', 'TIME'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nicaea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constantia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ep', 'NORP'): 1; ('Adriani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leone x. Sess', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Leo x.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lateran', 'GPE'): 1; ('1518', 'DATE'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a whole year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Malfi', 'GPE'): 1; ('R. P. D. Alexio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcopo Malfitano', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui dixit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('operibus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Decreto de edit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sess', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('peregrinas doctrinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zizania', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christianae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sess', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pius IV.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sixtus V.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight or nine hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('Madrid', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ind.', 'GPE'): 1; ('Athanas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ind. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('adorari', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athanas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Frag', 'GPE'): 1; ('Fest', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesi•sticus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Esther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('w•rds', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Adimantus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Infr', 'ORG'): 1; ('Maxim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Angelo excellentissimo de lignis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ab Ecclesia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about some seven hundred and fifty year', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deiphobus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('auribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('truncas inbonesto vulnere naris', 'ORG'): 1; ('twenty eight', 'DATE'): 1; ('lib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Corp.', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sangu', 'ORG'): 1; ('verùm etiam corpus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('multis', 'NORP'): 1; ('fidelibus', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mysterio membra populi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui sanguis christi dicitur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('misceri jubetur', 'GPE'): 1; ('nec christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('vel corpus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pariter admixta est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sanguinem populi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('accipitur spiritualiter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('I•em', 'ORG'): 1; ('se', 'GPE'): 1; ('negari non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dentibus commolitum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Expurg', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bertram', 'GPE'): 1; ('geritur', 'GPE'): 1; ('cad', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae idem sunt', 'ORG'): 1; ('viâ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sacramentarians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Charles the Bald', 'PERSON'): 1"
