tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A82508,24,elder lord God heritage leader guide shepherd ruler overseer bishop,power: 0.5; elder: 0.5; preeminence: 0.5; church: 0.5; diotrephes: 0.5; christ: 0.5; thing: 0.4; brethren: 0.4; presbytery: 0.35; say: 0.25; apostle: 0.25; bishop: 0.2; text: 0.1; england: 0.05,"('Diotrephes', 'ORG'): 11; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('New-England', 'LOC'): 8; ('John', 'PERSON'): 6; ('D.', 'NORP'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('fourteen', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Mat 23.6', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'GPE'): 1; ('the quarter', 'DATE'): 1; ('74', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zebedee', 'ORG'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zebedee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('12.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prel', 'ORG'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('down', 'PERSON'): 1; ('81.', 'DATE'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prelacy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('juvtual', 'GPE'): 1; ('Patriam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gloria paucorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fifteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('aequè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the church of Corinth', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('digito', 'DATE'): 1; ('tractari debet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Classis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Classis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Classis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aemilius', 'ORG'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Corah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abiram', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1"
A84129,37 | 1005,Jesus call son equal father John father epithet appropriate father,god: 0.45; father: 0.45; son: 0.45; nature: 0.45; divine: 0.45; power: 0.45; christ: 0.45; person: 0.45; man: 0.45; call: 0.25; equal: 0.2; object: 0.05; number: 0.05; opposition: 0.05; opposite: 0.05; oppose: 0.05; opinion: 0.05; operation: 0.05; office: 0.05; observe: 0.05; original: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('John', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Divina', 'GPE'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 2; ('socinians', 'NORP'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Biddle', 'PERSON'): 2; ('luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('as v. 35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('97.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('57.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('83.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baptist', 'NORP'): 1; ('76', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 10.28', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nyss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the Athanasian Creed', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('Bisterfield', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Theodoret Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('143', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('eunom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('damascen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregory Nazianzene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de Theolog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysost', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('natu•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('syllogi•me', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psalm 45.7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('omnis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ʋniversalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.6.7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('139.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine de Doctrina Christiana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('1 kin', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('8.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Senten', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Distin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vorstius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sabellius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('servus', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('last', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('more than one', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A84129,42 | 2045,answer sanctification gift grace confer nature mean grant saviour regard,god: 0.5; father: 0.5; christ: 0.5; son: 0.5; man: 0.5; word: 0.5; thing: 0.5; lord: 0.45; place: 0.3; lib: 0.3; bidle: 0.25; origen: 0.1; command: 0.1,"('Trinity', 'ORG'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 8; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 4; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('about the year', 'DATE'): 3; ('Tom 2', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Homil', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Novat', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Paraclete', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('Ruffin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Patre', 'ORG'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Arnobius', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Arnobius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('resurrectionem immortalitatis corpora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('misceri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Divina', 'GPE'): 1; ('sociari', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('natura hominem credendum', 'ORG'): 1; ('deum credendum', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter 12', 'LAW'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de conscientia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('180', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antolycus', 'GPE'): 1; ('arians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Centuriat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this second century', 'DATE'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('Virgil .', 'DATE'): 1; ('Platonists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lunae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Astra', 'ORG'): 1; ('mens agitat molem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plato', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theophilus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Justin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'ORG'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joshuah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the first three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Origen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epiphanius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('230', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ammonius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Justinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Constantinople', 'ORG'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gelasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('265', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Melchior Canus', 'FAC'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('origenians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Arius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nestorius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scultetus Modul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pamphilus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eusebius Cesariensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bellarmine de Viris', 'ORG'): 1; ('hireom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Genebrardus , de Origenis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apologist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Origens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leci', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Praefat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrinus and Gregory Thaumaturgus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nicene', 'ORG'): 1; ('Didymus Alexandrinus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierom', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ruffinam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Exod', 'GPE'): 1; ('Prooemio', 'GPE'): 1; ('Natus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('these last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Celsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the end of the', 'DATE'): 1; ('Levit', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('march', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the three first century', 'DATE'): 1; ('african', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dioclesian', 'ORG'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('three hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the four century', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Principalis', 'GPE'): 1; ('14.45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('45.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anobius', 'ORG'): 1; ('socinians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the supreme king', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sibylla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Helenus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Martius', 'PERSON'): 1"
A84129,42 | 2089,answer moment quotation gentile object Christ counterfeit man Gentiles think,man: 0.5; word: 0.5; flesh: 0.5; make: 0.5; christ: 0.5; god: 0.5; nature: 0.5; thing: 0.5; person: 0.5; assume: 0.15; son: 0.15; spirit: 0.1; bidle: 0.1,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Arnobius', 'ORG'): 3; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 3; ('fourteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Marcionists', 'NORP'): 2; ('Justin', 'ORG'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Arnobius', 'GPE'): 2; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 2; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11.6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John 1.1', 'PERSON'): 2; ('socinians', 'NORP'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gentiles', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Sibyl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Clemens Alexandrinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bellar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de christo cap 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('great comfort herein', 'FAC'): 1; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Causam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arnobius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('syne•d•che', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('totius secundùm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 1.14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('6 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('65.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaiah 45', 'DATE'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('145 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thu•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Grotius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Irenaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('tertul•ian', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('John 1.6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('almost of', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Orthodoxal', 'NORP'): 1; ('saint John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nesterius', 'ORG'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'FAC'): 1; ('forty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 2.9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Chalcedon', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet come original', 'ORG'): 1; ('Schecina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1"
A84129,42 | 2137,answer Christ nature incarnation nonlatinalphabet thing adversary cause lose nature,god: 0.5; son: 0.5; father: 0.5; christ: 0.5; man: 0.5; thing: 0.45; word: 0.45; lactantius: 0.35; answer: 0.3; nature: 0.25; cap: 0.25; place: 0.15; faith: 0.1; world: 0.1; author: 0.05; bidle: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 17; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('Lactantius', 'GPE'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Histor', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Arian', 'NORP'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Chrysostom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Lactan', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thirteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('arians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Evangelicae', 'ORG'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Socrates Eccles', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 2; ('2.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 4.2 .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 1.14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eutiches', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dioscorus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chalcedon', 'GPE'): 1; ('six hundred and thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Arnobius', 'LOC'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nullam substantiam corporalem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aliquod tegman materiae solidioris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('similitudine potentiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('videri', 'NORP'): 1; ('Arnobius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Bidle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lactantius Divinar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lactantius Firmianus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arnobius', 'ORG'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Firmianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Firminus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dioclesion and Constantine', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Magedburgians', 'ORG'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('issu•th', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('relata•se', 'ORG'): 1; ('s•n', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hosea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lactan de ira cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('novatians', 'NORP'): 1; ('valentinians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Marcionists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de Beneficiis', 'ORG'): 1; ('mox', 'ORG'): 1; ('tuo pro crimine passum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ingressus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Funcra', 'GPE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theologia', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('smith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marcellum de ecelesiastica Theologia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Eusebius contra Marcellum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eusebius Pamphilas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Constantine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Faith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Histor lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theodoret lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 1.1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Justin', 'ORG'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('12.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be the voice of', 'ORG'): 1; ('28.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hebr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('culverwel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sydonians', 'NORP'): 1"
A84129,54,ARGƲM knowledge thing apprehension nature consideration work action scripture open,god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; thing: 0.5; miracle: 0.5; creature: 0.5; power: 0.45; world: 0.45; make: 0.45; creation: 0.4; man: 0.3; work: 0.25; father: 0.15; heaven: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 14; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 7; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 7; ('John', 'PERSON'): 6; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 2; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 2; ('Homil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('socinians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Hebr', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('John 5.17', 'PERSON'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('48.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jerem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 1.3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysostom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('66', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antioch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Colos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levite', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nehem', 'GPE'): 1; ('9.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Natura', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rada', 'PERSON'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Durandus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lodovicus', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.3 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Colos', 'GPE'): 1; ('1.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the first six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Heinsius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Suarez', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de scientia', 'ORG'): 1; ('a Water-Milne', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('joshuahs day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('139', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bradwardine', 'ORG'): 1; ('351', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam 2.3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('147.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Halens', 'GPE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('360', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('145', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('22.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 24.25', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian Apologet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 9.8', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('78.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jehoram king', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sarepthah', 'GPE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Naaman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('syrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('4.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('115.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 9.32', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 15.24', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 5.19', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 10.25', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon Magus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 5.18', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('4.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('antiochen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. Tractat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johan', 'GPE'): 1"
A85500,64,lord confusion righteousness lord ear haste lord soul •ledge• God,page: 0.5; god: 0.35; soul: 0.35; psalm: 0.35; lord: 0.35; mr: 0.35; ledge: 0.35; distress: 0.35; death: 0.25; child: 0.2; penny: 0.15; paul: 0.15; person: 0.15; perplexity: 0.15; perkins: 0.15; pleasure: 0.15; part: 0.15; pollute: 0.15; party: 0.15; life: 0.15; redge: 0.05; end: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8. 28', 'DATE'): 2; ('BB', 'GPE'): 2; ('492', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('•ledge•nd', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•ledge•ee', 'GPE'): 1; ('•ledge•or', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jam. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('boltons', 'PERSON'): 1; ('284', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•ledge•eene', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•ledge•ather', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•ledge•ould', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Meter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('thirteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eighty sixth', 'DATE'): 1; ('the hundred and second', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the hundred forty one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Kilby', 'PERSON'): 1; ('EPHES', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirty four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the hundred and three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the hundred and sixteenth', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the hundred and •ledge•ighteenth', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the hundred and thirty eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the hundred forty five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Richard kilbie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Richard Royston', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles', 'GPE'): 1; ('9 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 38', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Greenhams', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Boltons Instruct', 'PERSON'): 1; ('230', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bolton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('458', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('denison monument', 'PERSON'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Hieron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('617', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. a.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('378', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('acta', 'GPE'): 1; ('358', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A89733,2,care parent expectation encourage first-fruit son proficiency hope whole time,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; word: 0.5; mr: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; time: 0.45; heart: 0.4; youth: 0.4; boston: 0.3; christ: 0.3; whole: 0.1; day: 0.1; learning: 0.1; cotton: 0.05; father: 0.05; scholar: 0.05; cambridge: 0.05; year: 0.05; lord: 0.05; place: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('Boston', 'GPE'): 8; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 7; ('cotton', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Sibbs', 'GPE'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Dionysius', 'ORG'): 3; ('Preston', 'PERSON'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 2; ('Juel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('misso', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('William', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Lincolnshire', 'GPE'): 2; ('Lincoln', 'ORG'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('aristorle require', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nostrisunt agri animati', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clem Alex', 'PERSON'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Mephibosheth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('julian apostasy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Libanius and Jamblicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('polish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 1; ('Xenophon', 'TIME'): 1; ('Lacedaem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('about thirteen year of age', 'DATE'): 1; ('Trinity - college', 'ORG'): 1; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 1; ('Parkhurst', 'PERSON'): 1; ('juelle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nunc ero discipulus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Philostratus', 'ORG'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the university of France', 'ORG'): 1; ('Junii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('the winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Winchester', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucilius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seni utenduan est', 'ORG'): 1; ('Emanuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trinity to Emanuel', 'ORG'): 1; ('Seminary', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Themistocles', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cato that Helus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eve', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 10', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Numinous', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Democritus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plinius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nazianzen', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scaliger', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mellific', 'LOC'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Historia Alcibidis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alcibiades', 'ORG'): 1; ('the ministry of mr', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peter-house', 'ORG'): 1; ('Musa Attica', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('st Maries', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pericles', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quintilian', 'NORP'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Achilles', 'GPE'): 1; ('Plato', 'ORG'): 1; ('Concio', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('about half a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Barloe', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cotton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Simon Biby', 'PERSON'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Heman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theologum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the first year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ ministry', 'ORG'): 1; ('the acceptable year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter be gird', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three or four year', 'DATE'): 1; ('leveret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('New-England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jacob be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Benner', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the end of twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zechariah', 'GPE'): 1; ('every month', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('First', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Matthews', 'GPE'): 1; ('chapter 16', 'LAW'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('the 5 day of the week', 'DATE'): 1; ('the week day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the four and five day early in the morning', 'DATE'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('only these three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('some few year', 'DATE'): 1; ('five or six hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dorcester', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Old-Boston', 'ORG'): 1"
A89733,2 | 3614,time wife mistress Sarah story widow bless marriage wife matron,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; time: 0.5; day: 0.5; lord: 0.5; duty: 0.45; life: 0.35; thing: 0.25; ministry: 0.25; prayer: 0.2; church: 0.2; study: 0.2; people: 0.2; divine: 0.1; father: 0.1; way: 0.05; house: 0.05; heart: 0.05; respect: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('the day', 'DATE'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('New-England', 'LOC'): 2; ('cotton', 'PERSON'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('that day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Cotton', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Boston', 'GPE'): 2; ('Sarah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Euodias and Syntyche', 'ORG'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('America', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Patmos', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jotham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeshimon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many thousand mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('jubet mihi dulce videri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Beza Eleg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anodine', 'GPE'): 1; ('Dod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paraeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anvilla', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bethlehem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pliny', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('Obadiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athanasius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Haggai 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zerubbabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Menenius Agrippa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib 2. cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('N. E.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('New-Boston', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Haggai', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ezra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. de bono', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('gratefulnese', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sturmius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Miraculi', 'GPE'): 1; ('Marian', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samuels', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non necessaria discendo', 'ORG'): 1; ('necessaria ignoramus', 'ORG'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('ciceronian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hierom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('sit night', 'TIME'): 1; ('tribuuntur agendis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Summus', 'FAC'): 1; ('exactissima', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('his latter year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Solon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Quintilian', 'NORP'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Heterogeneus', 'NORP'): 1; ('equidem', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('aut scriberc legenda', 'ORG'): 1; ('C. Pli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Whitaker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('189', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('herein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bradford', 'GPE'): 1; ('Synesius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('sin ep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the ministry of the word', 'ORG'): 1; ('exemplary ministry of grace', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mde', 'GPE'): 1; ('twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Askelon', 'ORG'): 1"
A89733,2 | 3645,time word ancient opinion soul divine dissolution look motion nature,god: 0.5; word: 0.5; day: 0.5; christ: 0.5; time: 0.5; man: 0.5; death: 0.45; heart: 0.4; father: 0.35; church: 0.3; hand: 0.3; son: 0.1; comet: 0.1,"('David', 'PERSON'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Boston', 'GPE'): 2; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('cotton', 'PERSON'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Vespasian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Parthia', 'ORG'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Xen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cyrus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('decet imperatorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('November 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prisca', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Aquila', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Octoginta', 'GPE'): 1; ('illi servio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six year', 'DATE'): 1; ('God forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('disce puer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('verúmque laborem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paraeis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vivit gnatus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wilson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('December 23. 1652', 'DATE'): 1; ('between eleven and twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the sixty and eight year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29. day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Brick', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ilium', 'ORG'): 1; ('New-England', 'NORP'): 1; ('New-England', 'LOC'): 1; ('isaiah day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iosiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hippo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vandal', 'LOC'): 1; ('Heidelbergh', 'FAC'): 1; ('about fourteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('militat Aether', 'PERSON'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lodowick', 'GPE'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('timeamus conditorem', 'ORG'): 1; ('huius Cometae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('1533', 'DATE'): 1; ('Quakers', 'GPE'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heu Pietas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('nimis de ea quasi jam transacta securitas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Albigenses', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Simon Montfort', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romanists', 'NORP'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three day and a half', 'DATE'): 1; ('julian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vita lutheri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Stephen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniels', 'ORG'): 1; ('the end of day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Babylon', 'GPE'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('John Davenport', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel Whiting', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Novemb', 'GPE'): 1; ('6. 1657', 'DATE'): 1"
A85131,4,whole priest send God enemy fruit make persecutor wisdom deceiver,priest: 0.5; lord: 0.45; isai: 0.45; man: 0.45; love: 0.45; people: 0.45; vine: 0.45; king: 0.4; spirit: 0.35; thing: 0.2; christ: 0.15; book: 0.15; seal: 0.1; precept: 0.05; power: 0.05; profit: 0.05; pretend: 0.05; preserv: 0.05; prophet: 0.05; praise: 0.05; place: 0.05; portrait: 0.05,"('Isai', 'ORG'): 10; ('thou', 'GPE'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 3; ('31', 'DATE'): 2; ('3.11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'DATE'): 2; ('13', 'DATE'): 2; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 2; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('•ll', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hosca 6.9 .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ier', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•aith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hosea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('peopl•', 'NORP'): 1; ('15.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2• 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas 11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 1; ('hat•', 'EVENT'): 1; ('29.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19•10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thei• heart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('••ese', 'NORP'): 1; ('29.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('29.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•itfull', 'LOC'): 1; ('◊ day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('29.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('20.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Preserv•', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('merc•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salem', 'GPE'): 1; ('flagon', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('j•r', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the ministry of Antichrist , Mal', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 19 , 20 ,', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('R. F. 1 John 1 10', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.21 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('R. F.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('January 27. 1648', 'DATE'): 1; ('Calvarie', 'GPE'): 1"
A86112,9 | 5210,Vectigal patrimoniale custom beginning right patrimony Caesar emperor call vectigalia,king: 0.5; law: 0.5; sea: 0.5; case: 0.5; river: 0.5; custom: 0.45; england: 0.4; grant: 0.3; right: 0.25; prerogative: 0.2; land: 0.2; commodity: 0.15; time: 0.15; war: 0.15; nation: 0.1; tribute: 0.1; subject: 0.05,"('England', 'GPE'): 12; ('Davis', 'PERSON'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 5; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 3; ('Tac', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Baldus', 'ORG'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('year', 'DATE'): 2; ('ibidem plura', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Fitz', 'ORG'): 2; ('Stanf', 'PERSON'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('swan', 'GPE'): 2; ('french', 'NORP'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('France', 'GPE'): 2; ('mercibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('regibus jus imponendi vectigalia', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Dier', 'ORG'): 1; ('165', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Primaria', 'ORG'): 1; ('ac ratio fuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('plana', 'GPE'): 1; ('praetereunti itinera praestarentur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 c .', 'DATE'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 Mar.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quanta', 'GPE'): 1; ('nihil magis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vide ibidem plura', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cato', 'ORG'): 1; ('coke l. 3. f .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry Finch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('234', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33 H. 8', 'PERCENT'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Coke', 'ORG'): 1; ('quando jus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('domini regis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('coke l. 9 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('262', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('be selo de se', 'PERSON'): 1; ('263', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nisi sit', 'ORG'): 1; ('281', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('436', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adrianus Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Justinian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('322', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('stanfords', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lip de Mag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quod est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caesari', 'GPE'): 1; ('Moneta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Northumberland', 'ORG'): 1; ('Omnium', 'GPE'): 1; ('333', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('335', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('226', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('Coke l. 7.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('coke l. 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('107', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hen•y constable', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae sunt ostia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Janua', 'ORG'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('F. N. B. 113', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('alto mari', 'PERSON'): 1; ('flumina', 'GPE'): 1; ('portas publica sunt', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bracton', 'GPE'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('annual', 'DATE'): 1; ('totam illam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abboesbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('315', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bann', 'ORG'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bann', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ibidem plura', 'ORG'): 1; ('poenabelli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('William', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fulbeck', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fulb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('99', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('maxim conservanda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jura belli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Justinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('imperatoriam majestatem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etiam armis decoratam', 'ORG'): 1; ('gubernari', 'ORG'): 1; ('Buchan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tullys Offi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lentulus', 'NORP'): 1; ('quoniam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam stipendiario bellicis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('casibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Wales', 'GPE'): 1; ('Galba', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam conducere alienos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Machavell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('state', 'ORG'): 1; ('many year ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Epominondas', 'GPE'): 1; ('consensu quodum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('theagiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tacitus', 'ORG'): 1"
A81624,2,chawcers folk Britain England wall Scotland religion pope F. crown,day: 0.5; god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; saint: 0.5; thing: 0.5; way: 0.5; kingdom: 0.5; time: 0.45; prophecy: 0.4; england: 0.25; take: 0.1; misery: 0.1; year: 0.1; counsel: 0.05; trouble: 0.05,"('England', 'GPE'): 5; ('the day', 'DATE'): 5; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 2; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('that day', 'DATE'): 2; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Geoffrey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Strafford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year 1640', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year 1644', 'DATE'): 1; ('Britanny', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this present year 1647', 'DATE'): 1; ('Wales', 'GPE'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 13.32', 'PERSON'): 1; ('such a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•••••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a week', 'DATE'): 1; ('a thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('each day', 'DATE'): 1; ('HAGIOMASTIX', 'ORG'): 1; ('some month', 'DATE'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('56', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('120. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Goodwin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matthew Simmons', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry Overton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1646', 'DATE'): 1; ('reader', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sect', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('15. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1"
A85394,6 | 5616,Querie abomination soul recover self fog Sect. mist ignorance ill,law: 0.5; god: 0.5; force: 0.5; man: 0.5; death: 0.5; sect: 0.5; word: 0.45; church: 0.45; doctrine: 0.3; commandment: 0.25; testament: 0.25; thing: 0.15; reason: 0.1; religion: 0.05,"('Sect', 'PERSON'): 11; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 7; ('Querie', 'PERSON'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('blasphemer', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('36', 'DATE'): 3; ('37', 'DATE'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 2; ('32', 'DATE'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('35', 'DATE'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rabbi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sect', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('thousand thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('N. B.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Querie', 'GPE'): 1; ('classiq•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('13. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15. 38', 'DATE'): 1; ('39', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be ••ue', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('10. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('1. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ainsworth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tremellius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'GPE'): 1; ('midnight', 'TIME'): 1; ('noonday', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the sword Vers', 'LOC'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ibid', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Galatians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('altera pars vivit', 'ORG'): 1; ('par•', 'NORP'): 1; ('part|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A85394,6 | 5655,Query opinion Sect. consubstantiation particulariz•d ordinance gentleman Luther• error consubstantiation,man: 0.5; ordinance: 0.5; error: 0.5; truth: 0.5; practice: 0.5; sin: 0.5; christ: 0.5; sect: 0.45; god: 0.4; evil: 0.2; kind: 0.1; death: 0.1; judgement: 0.1; opinion: 0.05; doctrine: 0.05; profession: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 13; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 9; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('54', 'DATE'): 3; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lebanon', 'GPE'): 2; ('presbyterians', 'NORP'): 2; ('55', 'DATE'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('56', 'DATE'): 2; ('Gangraena', 'GPE'): 2; ('58', 'DATE'): 2; ('Query', 'ORG'): 1; ('particulariz•d', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zuinglius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bucer', 'ORG'): 1; ('Occolampadius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward Gang', 'PERSON'): 1; ('par', 'PERSON'): 1; ('77', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('Socinianisme , Arminianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antinomianisme', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('114', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ashamed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rutherford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('several month', 'DATE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sect', 'LOC'): 1; ('eleven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sect', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nicholas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('brutu•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caesarea', 'NORP'): 1; ('Amphitheatro', 'LOC'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('as many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('animos demissa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Horat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'ORG'): 1; ('fidelibus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('59', 'DATE'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('degr•e', 'ORG'): 1"
A85394,6 | 5672,sequel answer expression query imprisonment death ordinance opinion ordinance imprisonment,man: 0.5; death: 0.5; sect: 0.5; god: 0.5; ordinance: 0.5; opinion: 0.5; church: 0.45; error: 0.45; truth: 0.3; imprisonment: 0.3; answer: 0.2; judgement: 0.15; contrary: 0.1; thing: 0.05,"('Sect', 'PERSON'): 7; ('Querie', 'PERSON'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Gangrena', 'ORG'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('••', 'ORG'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Sect', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('63', 'DATE'): 2; ('Corinth', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('64', 'DATE'): 2; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Gang', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('par', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lucis tam dira', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('un', 'ORG'): 1; ('fourteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixteen foot', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quer•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('61.', 'DATE'): 1; ('62', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paulus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('quae sunt', 'ORG'): 1; ('ex•i•dantur', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Doctrinam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luther and Gal', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Sect', 'ORG'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('fifteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Galatia', 'GPE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sxteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Harrow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Do•a•i•tae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('•aetibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('o•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Loc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('••ct', 'ORG'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sect.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eunomius', 'GPE'): 1; (""n'est sectatoribus"", 'ORG'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Querie', 'GPE'): 1; ('seventeenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('apagè calumniarum quisquilia', 'PERSON'): 1"
A85394,6 | 5737,man hand faith determination decretal synod council assembly person capacity,answer: 0.5; ordinance: 0.5; man: 0.5; reason: 0.5; thing: 0.5; word: 0.5; god: 0.5; sect: 0.45; admonition: 0.4; parliament: 0.25; querie: 0.2; persecution: 0.2,"('second', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 10; ('Querie', 'PERSON'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 3; ('91', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 2; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Query', 'ORG'): 2; ('synod , council', 'ORG'): 1; ('magnific', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('t•••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Socinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('thirty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sect', 'LOC'): 1; ('93', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven degree', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('midnight', 'TIME'): 1; ('94', 'DATE'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Querie', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('n•h', 'ORG'): 1; ('6. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gangrena', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sibi', 'GPE'): 1; ('suppo•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('•ittle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nunquam sera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('99', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A85123,1,heaven heaven minister reverend pastor God word assemble synod England,law: 0.5; oppression: 0.5; prisoner: 0.5; debt: 0.5; god: 0.45; justice: 0.4; jailer: 0.4; psal: 0.4; prison: 0.35; man: 0.3; reason: 0.3; isa: 0.25; contrary: 0.05; make: 0.05; release: 0.05,"('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('4', 'DATE'): 4; ('7', 'DATE'): 4; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 4; ('3', 'DATE'): 3; ('6', 'DATE'): 3; ('8', 'DATE'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 2; ('5', 'DATE'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('the year of England', 'DATE'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('forty four', 'DATE'): 1; ('J. m. F. humble show', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('52.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Turks', 'NORP'): 1; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('magna charta', 'ORG'): 1; ('14.4 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('53.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('94.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('58.5', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezech', 'ORG'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matthew 23.23', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('23.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('no penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('35.', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 19', 'LAW'): 1; ('Regis', 'ORG'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('6. 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('chapter 15', 'LAW'): 1; ('5.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 4', 'LAW'): 1; ('of many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the 42 Ed', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter 1', 'LAW'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('18.19', 'MONEY'): 1; ('three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hosea 4.1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('24.14.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('58', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eliz', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('21.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•', 'ORG'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23 yea', 'TIME'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42.22', 'DATE'): 1; ('24.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A88693,19,CHAP. note number antagonist excommunicate ordinance church person speak question,church: 0.5; mr: 0.5; degree: 0.5; reason: 0.5; excommunication: 0.5; thing: 0.5; man: 0.5; government: 0.45; suspension: 0.35; right: 0.35; word: 0.3; aretius: 0.05,"('W.', 'PERSON'): 17; ('Aretius', 'GPE'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('§', 'NORP'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jus Divinum', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('§', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('Aug. 29.', 'DATE'): 1; ('1648', 'DATE'): 1; ('10.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('ill mar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hackwell', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johannes Picus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tagus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ganges', 'ORG'): 1; ('435', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('their day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Grotius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('potest circa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Blake', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('Whitaker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dureus', 'GPE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('1583', 'DATE'): 1; ('807', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ignoramus', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('820', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luther , Zuinglius , Bucer ,', 'ORG'): 1; ('Oecolampadius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Presbyteri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui Episcopi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('alio etiam ecclesiis presbytero', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nolim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vocationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('recubans', 'NORP'): 1; ('tegmine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('137', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lusannae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1578', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('B. v. 9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('heed holy write', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A88693,20 | 6004,conceit excommunication notion refell section inference consideration gradual excommunication communion,excommunication: 0.5; communion: 0.5; church: 0.5; word: 0.5; offender: 0.5; member: 0.45; sacrament: 0.4; minister: 0.4; people: 0.4; god: 0.2; thing: 0.15; scripture: 0.1; prayer: 0.1; officer: 0.1; heathen: 0.05; christian: 0.05; person: 0.05; law: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('§', 'NORP'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Ames', 'PERSON'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('W.', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3.10', 'MONEY'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 2; ('cyprian', 'NORP'): 2; ('3.6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 20.23', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Camero', 'ORG'): 1; ('532', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('peecatori impenitentiam profitenti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel reipsâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel etiam verbo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sigilla sunt remissionis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calvia', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('278', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('nihil senioribus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi ut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('durius', 'NORP'): 1; ('ultima', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antiochenum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('divina', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui communieati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam ad vos qui ministratis dicta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dico', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui', 'ORG'): 1; ('sordibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paulus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('sanguinem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Demoniaco', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui petccati sibi conscius accedit', 'ORG'): 1; ('54', 'DATE'): 1; ('Liberalis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caldonius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cornelio', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('2 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('10.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('15.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aretius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theol', 'GPE'): 1; ('religionem nostam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('peccati ecclesiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epislola', 'ORG'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cornelin', 'GPE'): 1; ('ratio domino', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ponderantibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('aminantibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('qui recipi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('admitli', 'ORG'): 1; ('Quibusdam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sana', 'PERSON'): 1; ('suntvulnerentur', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui ita morbidas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('contactas', 'ORG'): 1; ('gregi admiscet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ita contrà', 'ORG'): 1; ('vel adusteriis vel sacrificiis contaminati', 'PERSON'): 1; ('imo extorqueo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epistola 68 Cyprianus , Caecilius , Primus', 'LAW'): 1; ('praeceptis dominicis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sacriledgi sacerdotis sacrificia miscere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quando ipsa maximè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel indignos recusandi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('delegantur', 'GPE'): 1; ('malorum crimina', 'GPE'): 1; ('bonorum merita praedicentur', 'FAC'): 1; ('quae omnium', 'ORG'): 1; ('suffragio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('judicio fuerit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('publican', 'NORP'): 1; ('Maccovius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Loc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('familiarem consuetudinem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('humsrey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vindic', 'NORP'): 1; ('149', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Drake', 'PERSON'): 1; ('§', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Classis', 'NORP'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10 , 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('William Morice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Estius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('147', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Caena quas•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tornesius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A88693,21,CHAP. IV. syllogism copy saint p. conclusion respect exception phrase,church: 0.5; person: 0.5; minister: 0.5; order: 0.5; suspend: 0.5; england: 0.45; canon: 0.45; suspension: 0.4; communion: 0.3; book: 0.25; mr: 0.2; lord: 0.2; excommunication: 0.15; ordinance: 0.1,"('England', 'GPE'): 10; ('W.', 'PERSON'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('§', 'NORP'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('year', 'DATE'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('§', 'PERSON'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten to one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('May', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'DATE'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('the first year', 'DATE'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Egregiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('laudem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1"
A88693,22,CHAP. v. confirmation proposition syllogism saint mr. W. p. jejune,christ: 0.5; unbeliever: 0.5; word: 0.5; lord: 0.5; sense: 0.5; person: 0.5; believer: 0.5; church: 0.45; god: 0.35; faith: 0.3; supper: 0.15; sacrament: 0.15; way: 0.05; respect: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 18; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('W.', 'PERSON'): 9; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 9; ('§', 'NORP'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 6; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 5; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 4; ('§', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Passeover', 'GPE'): 3; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('twofold', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12.46', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('4.3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('18', 'DATE'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4', 'DATE'): 2; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('19', 'DATE'): 2; ('13', 'DATE'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20', 'DATE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('morbid-christians', 'GPE'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52', 'DATE'): 1; ('53', 'DATE'): 1; ('W. assert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 20.27', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Titus 1.15', 'LAW'): 1; ('dr Hammond', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('saint luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Messiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.21', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.19 . 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 3.15', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ling', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Graec', 'PERSON'): 1; ('verbo suo .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scapula', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui fidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('item infidus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('61', 'DATE'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('justisy', 'ORG'): 1; ('6. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Electra', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 8.54', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'DATE'): 1; ('42.47', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('57', 'DATE'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29.10', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Passeover', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet veaz', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ainsworth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.12', 'MONEY'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.24.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet vecol', 'GPE'): 1; ('Schindler', 'PERSON'): 1; ('60.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('64.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ainsworth', 'GPE'): 1; ('43.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cotton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('131', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119.115', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 13.33', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('judicio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('animo sibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('10. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Camero', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amyraldus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ephesian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('chapter 5.8', 'LAW'): 1; ('abundance', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A88693,23,CHAP. chief argument management light scripture frame lord supper administer,baptism: 0.5; faith: 0.5; heart: 0.5; lord: 0.5; baptize: 0.5; eunuch: 0.5; supper: 0.5; condition: 0.4; adult: 0.3; whole: 0.3; require: 0.15; admission: 0.1; admit: 0.05; person: 0.05; use: 0.05; profession: 0.05; philip: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 13; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 7; ('§', 'NORP'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('§', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('2.38', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('36', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15.12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Mt. Humphreys', 'ORG'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Humphreys', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eunach', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philip', 'GPE'): 1; ('Exc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('13.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('arabic', 'NORP'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('amici', 'NORP'): 1; ('svi sinceri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cordibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('26.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('86.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jocl', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('10.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Commissioned', 'ORG'): 1; ('soro', 'GPE'): 1; ('6.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Richard Baxter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psalm 119', 'GPE'): 1; ('6th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A88693,24,CHAP. Vii caution faith conformity obedience gospel habit faith exercise,faith: 0.5; sin: 0.5; god: 0.5; pardon: 0.5; church: 0.5; repentance: 0.5; minister: 0.5; person: 0.45; sacrament: 0.3; way: 0.25; judgement: 0.25; man: 0.2; grace: 0.05,"('§', 'NORP'): 9; ('David', 'PERSON'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('§', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('18.3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('6.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('loc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('remissio peccatorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('ita obtenta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('constanti illius custodiâ', 'ORG'): 1; ('remissionem iteratur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('51.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('18.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 1.6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 10.28', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('22.32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Corinthian', 'NORP'): 1; ('4. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mallcus', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ames', 'GPE'): 1; ('Medul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('applicationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sutura autem virtuailter', 'ORG'): 1; ('praeterita', 'ORG'): 1; ('se', 'GPE'): 1; ('Baxter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('266', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ames', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 1.7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('soro', 'GPE'): 1; ('juridicali', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quakers', 'ORG'): 1; ('our day', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hooker', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('§', 'GPE'): 1; ('9 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeanes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('54', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cornelio', 'ORG'): 1; ('avertat à', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fratribus nostris', 'ORG'): 1; ('seipsum fallit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cord occultat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cor scrutari', 'ORG'): 1; ('fiat Eucharistia', 'ORG'): 1; ('sanguinem fundere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sanguinem denegamus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ecclesiâ', 'GPE'): 1; ('domini jure', 'ORG'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cyrian answer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nee majestati divinae', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chrysoslom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('divina', 'GPE'): 1; ('nullus ita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Justin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antonium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Johanne Lang', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eucharistia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quoth nulli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('quam veram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('doctrinam', 'NORP'): 1; ('remissionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Classis', 'NORP'): 1; ('10. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Worcestershire', 'PERSON'): 1; ('shine light', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Maurice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('53', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('54', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A88693,25,CHAP. Viii chapter due weigh reader compare mr. W. discourse,person: 0.5; believer: 0.4; church: 0.4; unbeliever: 0.4; saint: 0.4; mr: 0.4; sinner: 0.35; faith: 0.35; christian: 0.3; christ: 0.2; sacrament: 0.15; baptise: 0.15; pearl: 0.1; path: 0.1; persuade: 0.1; people: 0.1; pen: 0.1; peccato: 0.1; portion: 0.1; page: 0.1; pagan: 0.1; profess: 0.05; faction: 0.05,"('W.', 'PERSON'): 9; ('christian', 'NORP'): 7; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('§', 'NORP'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('proselyte', 'PERSON'): 2; ('§', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('53', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cresconius', 'GPE'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('Grammaticum', 'GPE'): 1; ('interpretari', 'NORP'): 1; ('auribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('cordibus tuam', 'ORG'): 1; ('2. P. 50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sinner quoad', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('meek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Passeover', 'GPE'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Passeover', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jacobi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('34.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezra 10.3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8.11', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('58', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('midnight', 'TIME'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('64', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A88693,26,CHAP. passage mr. W. please argument suspension people Israelites solemnity,passeover: 0.5; lord: 0.5; argument: 0.5; sacrifice: 0.5; sacrament: 0.5; supper: 0.4; day: 0.4; god: 0.4; reason: 0.35; testament: 0.3; jew: 0.25; people: 0.2; offering: 0.1; ground: 0.05; admit: 0.05,"('Passeover', 'ORG'): 7; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Passeover', 'GPE'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 3; ('16.2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('§', 'PERSON'): 2; ('W.', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'DATE'): 2; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 2; ('§', 'NORP'): 2; ('Baxter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('3. 1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the first day', 'DATE'): 1; ('quando pascha immolabant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ralph Cudworth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the university of Cambridge', 'ORG'): 1; ('38.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Onkelos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oxen', 'GPE'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Josiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30000', 'DATE'): 1; ('3000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sacrifi•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levite', 'NORP'): 1; ('30.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezra 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levit', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 12.5', 'LAW'): 1; ('9.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29.42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('34.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Aegypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Transitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('13.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('10.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('404', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('303', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('notioribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paschal', 'ORG'): 1; ('16.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('( many hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('a few hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('the fourteenth day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the end of one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tolet', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Cloppenburgius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Scaliger', 'ORG'): 1; ('Causabon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('johannem Cloppenburgium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paschate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cudworth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Talmud', 'ORG'): 1; ('the christian Aera', 'ORG'): 1; ('the right day', 'DATE'): 1; ('diverse day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hugo Grotius', 'FAC'): 1; ('Annot', 'GPE'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Capellus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou dwell', 'ORG'): 1; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('70', 'DATE'): 1; ('71', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('72', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A88693,27,CHAP. chapter consequence argument viz. people Jew circumcise admit Passeover,passeover: 0.5; god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; people: 0.5; heart: 0.5; israel: 0.5; chap: 0.5; covenant: 0.45; king: 0.35; exod: 0.2; time: 0.2; text: 0.1; sin: 0.05; word: 0.05; thing: 0.05; viz: 0.05,"('Passeover', 'GPE'): 10; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 9; ('Passeover', 'ORG'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 5; ('§', 'NORP'): 5; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 4; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 4; ('17', 'DATE'): 4; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 4; ('Josiah', 'PERSON'): 4; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'DATE'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('20', 'DATE'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('16', 'DATE'): 3; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('arabic', 'NORP'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('45', 'DATE'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('12.48', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('27', 'DATE'): 2; ('31.14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'DATE'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Syriack', 'ORG'): 2; ('seven day', 'DATE'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 2; ('x. §', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gillespy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('accessary', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fifteen mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('8.2 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a solemn day', 'DATE'): 1; ('a holy day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gelaspy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30.38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'DATE'): 1; ('19.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.14', 'MONEY'): 1; ('17.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('32.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('35.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('20.9 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isralitish', 'NORP'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chron', 'ORG'): 1; ('35.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Manasseh', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Amon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('the twelve year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the 18th year', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('this same 18th year', 'DATE'): 1; ('23.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezra 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cyrus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Ezra 1.5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('69', 'DATE'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5-11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.44', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('53', 'DATE'): 1; ('61', 'DATE'): 1; ('63', 'DATE'): 1; ('65', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezra 6.14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israelite', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('49', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ainsworth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gen. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Transitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Davids', 'ORG'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('74', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('76', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('77', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('78', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('79', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('80', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A88693,28,CHAP. quarrel examination cast way p. intruder other matter resolve,faith: 0.45; mr: 0.45; church: 0.45; believer: 0.45; man: 0.45; certainty: 0.4; minister: 0.4; sacrament: 0.4; christian: 0.35; word: 0.25; person: 0.2; communion: 0.2; lord: 0.05; ordinance: 0.05; opposite: 0.05; pastor: 0.05; party: 0.05; part: 0.05; parish: 0.05; parenthesis: 0.05; order: 0.05; offender: 0.05; viz: 0.05,"('W.', 'PERSON'): 10; ('christian', 'NORP'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('58', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('§', 'NORP'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('§', 'PERSON'): 1; ('54', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('59', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('5.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abundans', 'NORP'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('a hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('a few mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('pecuniam negate', 'PERSON'): 1; ('coelestibus fidem commodat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salvian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccl', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.17 , 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('predominat', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('W. viz.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('81', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('85', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('86', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bee', 'ORG'): 1; ('87', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('88', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A88693,29,CHAP. Xii clear confirm way wickedness exercise faith account unbeliever,seal: 0.5; faith: 0.5; christianity: 0.5; sacrament: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; lord: 0.45; mr: 0.45; supper: 0.25; abraham: 0.25; believer: 0.05; doctrine: 0.05,"('Christianity', 'NORP'): 23; ('W.', 'PERSON'): 20; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 15; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('§', 'NORP'): 11; ('christian', 'NORP'): 11; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('pagan', 'GPE'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.11', 'DATE'): 2; ('8', 'DATE'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Abrahams', 'ORG'): 2; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Xii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.22', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Josephs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42.9', 'MONEY'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Math', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.21', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('64', 'DATE'): 1; ('65', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('infidel•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('4. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('16.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 3.16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('Wotton', 'GPE'): 1; ('John 1.12', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.3 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Episcopal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baxter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sixty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('only two or three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Maximo Florentino Interp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nullam aliam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam ut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pro signo ac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ipsam circumserret circumcisionem justitiae illius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('ipsi Abrahae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sigilli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('accepit circumcisionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil ipsi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('justitiam prosuit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed hâc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod cum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet autem', 'ORG'): 1; ('proprie fuit respectu electorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('justitiam eis collatam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('justitiae fidei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cartwright', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('St Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Whitaker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fulk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('John 8.39', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('17.1', 'MONEY'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('nisi jam eos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nam de illis', 'ORG'): 1; ('gratiam habeant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Justificatio', 'GPE'): 1; ('luditur opera', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui baptismi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('promissionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('praeterea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('67', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('89', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('90', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('91', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('92', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('93', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('94', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A88693,31,case consideration time admit communion ask Christ other resolve command,person: 0.5; christ: 0.45; mr: 0.45; exception: 0.45; answer: 0.45; time: 0.45; man: 0.45; say: 0.35; consequence: 0.3; contradiction: 0.2; case: 0.2; communion: 0.1; lord: 0.1; word: 0.1; peeper: 0.05; place: 0.05; petilianus: 0.05; petiliani: 0.05; perusal: 0.05; practice: 0.05; periphrasis: 0.05; paratragoediat: 0.05; partaker: 0.05,"('W.', 'PERSON'): 13; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 4; ('§', 'NORP'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('over night', 'TIME'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Arian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Socinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('80', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('81', 'DATE'): 1; ('82', 'DATE'): 1; ('83', 'DATE'): 1; ('Query', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Query', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('didicit ille', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tacitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Petilianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('contra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petiliani', 'LOC'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Arrianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('105', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('107', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('108', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('109', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('110', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('111', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A88693,32,CHAP. reader please question qualify debar sacrament case word Christianity,case: 0.35; supposition: 0.35; reason: 0.35; suppose: 0.35; exception: 0.35; part: 0.35; christianity: 0.35; person: 0.35; argument: 0.3; word: 0.3; thing: 0.2; principle: 0.15; profectò: 0.15; permittam: 0.15; please: 0.15; pluck: 0.15; point: 0.15; precept: 0.15; preserve: 0.15; pretend: 0.15; debar: 0.05,"('Christianity', 'NORP'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('W.', 'PERSON'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 4; ('§', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Idolis', 'ORG'): 3; ('§', 'NORP'): 2; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui se mutuò', 'PERSON'): 1; ('yesterday', 'DATE'): 1; ('sensu composito', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amyraldus', 'ORG'): 1; ('specim', 'GPE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paulus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('justitiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('justificationem non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('mendaxero', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 8.39', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('operibus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dicturi sunt homini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('acceperis .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('acceperis baptismum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('membra meretricis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('malis', 'NORP'): 1; ('haec quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sanctificati', 'ORG'): 1; ('domini Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('illis', 'GPE'): 1; ('haec quidem suistis sed abluti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caecilianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('4. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('114', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('115', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('116', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('117', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('118', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('120', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('86', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('87', 'DATE'): 1"
A88693,33,case say respect respect incest parricide instance respect rule case,case: 0.5; rule: 0.5; god: 0.5; mr: 0.5; word: 0.5; remedy: 0.45; christ: 0.45; principle: 0.45; man: 0.35; evil: 0.35; person: 0.25; argument: 0.05; sense: 0.05; offence: 0.05; power: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('W.', 'PERSON'): 10; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('§', 'NORP'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('daily', 'DATE'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('twofold', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be humble', 'ORG'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Randal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('89', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('90', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('94', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Canaan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gerrard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evang', 'GPE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('183', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tandem', 'ORG'): 1; ('christum medintorem', 'GPE'): 1; ('quando Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('generalem justificationis formam', 'ORG'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod ergo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Latronis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Purgatorii', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('generale', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Davids', 'ORG'): 1; ('Uriah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('publican', 'NORP'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('etiam ficta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('P. Ramus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('103', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam 8.7 .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 12.48', 'PERSON'): 1; ('97', 'DATE'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('121', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('122', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quash', 'PERSON'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('124', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('125', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('126', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('127', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('128', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A88693,34,CHAP. Xvii consequence argumentation word rejecter Christianity baptize adult debar,mr: 0.45; christ: 0.45; church: 0.45; word: 0.45; suspension: 0.45; consequence: 0.45; man: 0.45; reason: 0.35; offender: 0.25; discipline: 0.25; deed: 0.25; timson: 0.2; answer: 0.05; precept: 0.05; power: 0.05; proceed: 0.05; print: 0.05; priest: 0.05; prevail: 0.05; pretend: 0.05; presumption: 0.05; presume: 0.05; product: 0.05,"('W.', 'PERSON'): 19; ('Timson', 'PERSON'): 6; ('§', 'NORP'): 5; ('Humphreys', 'PERSON'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 3; ('Titus 1.16', 'LAW'): 3; ('103', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('99', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('18.15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'DATE'): 2; ('2.2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('cyprian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Xvii .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('99', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Math', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elders', 'PERSON'): 1; ('100 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('101', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('102', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('105', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('107', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17.4', 'DATE'): 1; ('wonderful', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('108', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quaker', 'ORG'): 1; ('Quakers', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Timson', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('90', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the christian magistrate', 'ORG'): 1; ('march 29 , 1648', 'DATE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cornelium', 'GPE'): 1; ('ita res est', 'ORG'): 1; ('de Episcopatus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sublimi ac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('divinâ potestate', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christiani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('circo', 'ORG'): 1; ('relinquenda', 'ORG'): 1; ('disciplina', 'GPE'): 1; ('quoniam convitijs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('89', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marsilius Ficinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('Platonis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidam familiaris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eidem de eo platonem consulenti', 'ORG'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('129', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('130', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('131', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('132', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('133', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('134', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('135', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('136', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A88693,35,CHAP. Xviii answer mr. W. reason reader argumentation Christ suspension,word: 0.45; profession: 0.45; deed: 0.45; contrary: 0.45; mind: 0.45; lord: 0.45; god: 0.4; testimony: 0.4; sign: 0.35; thing: 0.25; take: 0.15; truth: 0.1; john: 0.1; psalmist: 0.05; psalm: 0.05; pythonisse: 0.05; purse: 0.05; purpose: 0.05; reason: 0.05; promise: 0.05; prophet: 0.05; reject: 0.05; psal: 0.05; man: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 3; ('§', 'PERSON'): 2; ('W.', 'PERSON'): 2; ('§', 'NORP'): 2; ('Sauls', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Xviii .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cyprian de unitate', 'ORG'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nisi restituatur ablatum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('St John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezra 4.2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 2.4', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 1.6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sylas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de mendacio ad consentium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ille mentitur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('animo', 'GPE'): 1; ('vel quibuslibet significationibus ennnciat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('36.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Baxter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('277', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salvian', 'NORP'): 1; ('dei l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('143', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('utique nisi ob eos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christiani', 'NORP'): 1; ('religionis', 'NORP'): 1; ('factis autem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('137', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('138', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('139', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('140', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('141', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('142', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('143 surprise', 'MONEY'): 1; ('144', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('truth|be', 'GPE'): 1"
A88693,36,CHAP. Xix another reason paper add mr. W. p. Christ,child: 0.5; right: 0.5; church: 0.5; parent: 0.5; god: 0.5; baptism: 0.5; lord: 0.5; debar: 0.45; member: 0.3; mr: 0.3; man: 0.2; supper: 0.2; word: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('§', 'NORP'): 7; ('W.', 'PERSON'): 6; ('christian', 'NORP'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('England', 'GPE'): 3; ('109', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 2; ('Humphreys', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('108', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('48', 'DATE'): 1; ('110', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('111', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('112', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('114', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('115', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('116', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Quakers', 'ORG'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('3. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antioch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de sumentibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•••ou', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('§', 'PERSON'): 1; ('drake', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 3', 'LAW'): 1; ('7.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('a month', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('the eight day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Passeover', 'ORG'): 1; ('ergo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ezek', 'ORG'): 1; ('16.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'DATE'): 1; ('23.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('264', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('265', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ames', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. Resp', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('excommunicatorum contumacium liberi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('baptizari nisi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('idonco•um', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('146', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('147', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('148 the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('149', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('151', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('152', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
