tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A42758,12,controversy Jesuit doctor Sarbon meaning place expound C. Sect. Jesuit,apostle: 0.5; honour: 0.5; word: 0.5; elder: 0.5; labour: 0.5; doctrine: 0.5; double: 0.5; place: 0.4; duty: 0.4; church: 0.25; paul: 0.25; text: 0.15; man: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 12; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 7; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 2; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 2; ('5.17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Elders', 'PERSON'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Sarbon', 'GPE'): 1; ('50', 'DATE'): 1; ('Spongia', 'GPE'): 1; ('the university of Paris', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sorbon', 'NORP'): 1; ('Vindicia Censura', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aurelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('378.380', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('362', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Barnabas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Barnabas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('one half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam quaerere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tueri', 'NORP'): 1; ('14.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sutcliffe', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('grad', 'PERSON'): 1; ('minis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evang', 'GPE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Episcop', 'ORG'): 1; ('219', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saravia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Answ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('13.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cartwright', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('16.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sutcliffe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ignoramus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apoc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•', 'GPE'): 1; ('•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('4.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A42758,13,man need exposition apostle other elder minister word advantage elder,bishop: 0.45; elder: 0.45; ambrose: 0.45; word: 0.45; church: 0.45; presbyter: 0.45; apostle: 0.45; commentary: 0.45; minister: 0.35; doctrine: 0.2; teacher: 0.15; testimony: 0.1; answ: 0.05; time: 0.05; perfidiousness: 0.05; pastor: 0.05; person: 0.05; perpet: 0.05; permission: 0.05; perkins: 0.05; policy: 0.05; papist: 0.05; parker: 0.05; polit: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Bilson', 'PERSON'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Elders', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 2; ('Parker', 'ORG'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 2; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Sutliffe', 'NORP'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Damasc', 'ORG'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('heresy', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. third', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Viii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Glossa', 'GPE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('tempora', 'NORP'): 1; ('226', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scultingius', 'LOC'): 1; ('Milan', 'GPE'): 1; ('the catholic authority', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Collen , 1532', 'DATE'): 1; ('1551', 'DATE'): 1; ('Costerius at Basile', 'ORG'): 1; ('1555', 'DATE'): 1; ('Collen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1616', 'DATE'): 1; ('1632', 'DATE'): 1; ('372', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('373', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('3 c', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hilarius Diaconus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Remigius Lugdunensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Louvain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Censura', 'ORG'): 1; ('134', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('210', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sutcliffe', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ambrose', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evag', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1"
A41614,12,Iii moor supplication virgin Christ virgin heaven Christ reason son,virgin: 0.45; god: 0.45; christ: 0.45; mother: 0.45; church: 0.45; bless: 0.45; book: 0.45; thing: 0.3; son: 0.3; jesus: 0.25; devotion: 0.25; kingdom: 0.1; power: 0.1; say: 0.1; pian: 0.05; petition: 0.05; praise: 0.05; pope: 0.05; place: 0.05; pity: 0.05; prerogative: 0.05; people: 0.05; peer: 0.05,"('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 2; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('§', 'NORP'): 2; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 2; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('there|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Gabriel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('136', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Bonavent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Opusc', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tom 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vatican', 'FAC'): 1; ('S. Bernardin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('apud Bernadin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bustis', 'NORP'): 1; ('nostra pian scelera', 'ORG'): 1; ('jure Matris', 'ORG'): 1; ('Balinghem a Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Balinghem Parnass', 'ORG'): 1; ('208', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tournay', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amiens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Roman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saint Bernardin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mendoza , Mendoza', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Virid', 'GPE'): 1; ('virgin|be kingdom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salazar , Salazar', 'ORG'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mexico', 'GPE'): 1; ('nuero', 'GPE'): 1; ('148', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('matrem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mendoza', 'NORP'): 1; ('Viridar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('about ten year', 'DATE'): 1; ('la saint verge', 'FAC'): 1; ('1679', 'DATE'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Monita Salutaria B. V. Mariae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('56', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Latria', 'GPE'): 1; ('1685', 'DATE'): 1; ('Superiorum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Seraphim', 'ORG'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bellarm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Culiu Sanct', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Basilicae', 'ORG'): 1; ('outward tribulation', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A49123,6,sum scripture school doctrine Trinity comprise line God man unity,church: 0.5; mr: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; person: 0.5; notion: 0.45; thing: 0.45; schism: 0.35; communion: 0.35; reason: 0.2; error: 0.2; judgement: 0.15; authority: 0.15; case: 0.1; author: 0.05; chillingworth: 0.05,"('hale', 'PERSON'): 9; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Chillingworth', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Hooker', 'ORG'): 5; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('218', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('144', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('120', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('210', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('207', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('260', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('186', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('239', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the holy catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('779', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Volkelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Socinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('potter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Donatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laud', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baxter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('464', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Relig', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('100', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('145', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('108', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('212', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('121', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Irenicum', 'ORG'): 1; ('215', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('394', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('223', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('225', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('hooker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eaton', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sepulchre', 'GPE'): 1; ('nisi quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('terris semota suisque temporibus defuncta videt', 'ORG'): 1; ('Parergon', 'GPE'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('216', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('217', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Parker', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred and', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the supreme authority on earth', 'ORG'): 1"
A49123,7 | 23261,author page advice liturgy liturgy form service frame fancy thing,thing: 0.5; liturgy: 0.5; god: 0.5; person: 0.5; scruple: 0.5; author: 0.5; man: 0.5; church: 0.5; superior: 0.4; worship: 0.3; opinion: 0.15; governor: 0.1; practice: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('218', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('presbyterians', 'NORP'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('194', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Owen', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Nonconformists', 'ORG'): 3; ('Nicene', 'ORG'): 2; ('Athanasian', 'NORP'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('arrian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Socinian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 2; ('215', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Devonshire', 'GPE'): 1; ('216', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('172', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('183', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the first 600 year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Arrianism', 'ORG'): 1; ('Calvinists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Heylin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hickman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Harry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Charles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('226', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('196', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Papias S. Johns', 'PERSON'): 1; ('201', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Oedipus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nonconformists', 'NORP'): 1; ('408', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('149', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('unitas', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec vel', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dissert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('77', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quis erit schismatum modus', 'ORG'): 1; ('91', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Owen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cartwright', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('262', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('propterea ita rejicienda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sacramento', 'GPE'): 1; ('forlese', 'NORP'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('at least three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Baxter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sabbatarians', 'NORP'): 1"
A45496,12,Origenes Adamantius §5 know name Origenes Adamantius call adamant stone,cap: 0.5; origen: 0.5; lib: 0.5; euseb: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; alexandria: 0.5; time: 0.45; man: 0.35; father: 0.35; scripture: 0.3; catalog: 0.2; hieronym: 0.2; cent: 0.1; year: 0.05,"('lib', 'PERSON'): 28; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 27; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Euseb', 'PERSON'): 9; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Erasm', 'ORG'): 6; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 6; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 6; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 5; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Euseb', 'GPE'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Arabia', 'GPE'): 4; ('Caesarea', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Palestine', 'GPE'): 4; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 3; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 3; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Suidas', 'GPE'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paulus', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('Antioch', 'ORG'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Heraclas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Alex', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('220', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('§', 'NORP'): 2; ('Hist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Demetrius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Theodorus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Origenes Adamantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origenes Adamantius', 'ORG'): 1; ('scriptoribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('tolerantiam Admantini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('adag', 'ORG'): 1; ('Didymus', 'ORG'): 1; ('mille', 'ORG'): 1; ('Origeni Theologo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chalcenterus', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Adamantinus', 'FAC'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('quas colligaret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('adamantinis quibusdam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Biblioth', 'GPE'): 1; ('118', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leonides', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Severus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('outward appearance', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ammonius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seven year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the age of seventeen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('God , Cent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gabriel Powel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samosatenus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('about the eighteenth year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Granmar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eos', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zonaras', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tom 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Severo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christianae', 'ORG'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('demetri•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('continu•d', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexandri•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Demetrius the', 'ORG'): 1; ('diverse year', 'DATE'): 1; ('from morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Heraclas', 'ORG'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('•rasm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Servius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec ulla', 'ORG'): 1; ('cura remanebat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Virgil .', 'GPE'): 1; ('aeneld', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('herbis etiam quibusdam emasculabantur', 'ORG'): 1; ('etiam coire', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierophantae', 'ORG'): 1; ('mysteriorum praese', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierophantas', 'ORG'): 1; ('dier', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hierodidascalos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonnullos Hieronomos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jovinian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ageruchiam viduam de monogamiâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Graeci', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alexander ab Alexandro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierophantas Atheniensium', 'ORG'): 1; ('surrecti fuerint', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lect', 'PERSON'): 1; ('antiq', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rhodiginus', 'LOC'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('testibus circa', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('De•eirius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zephyrinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('un•• Alexandria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('64', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Valentinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Marcionist', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sabellian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Schol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('Palestina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Episcopi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dissereret de sacris literis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nicephorus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Laranda Euelpis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Neon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Icouium Paulinus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Celsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Synada Theodorus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Atticus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mammaea', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Alexander Severus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trithemius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non abhor••it', 'PERSON'): 1; ('zonoras', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('no less than', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Notarii', 'ORG'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Baronius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('erat', 'NORP'): 1; ('Librariorum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hyppolyto', 'DATE'): 1; ('Miraeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Librarii', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adversar', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('non tantùm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hym', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('magister literarum sederat', 'ORG'): 1; ('brevibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('praepetibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('literis scribere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Manilius', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('erit felix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quique notis linguam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ep•gr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('176', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Helio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•0', 'ORG'): 1; ('Achaia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eras•', 'DATE'): 1; ('about forty and three year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('230', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 1; ('this year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nicopolis', 'ORG'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexander and Theoctistus', 'ORG'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Osiand', 'LOC'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cesares', 'ORG'): 1; ('Niceph', 'ORG'): 1; ('7.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mo••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Piam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('approbaverat', 'NORP'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('firmilian bishop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cappadocia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gregorius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Neocaesarea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pontus', 'ORG'): 1; ('266', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thaumaturgus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Athenodorus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five year', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bostra', 'ORG'): 1; ('heresy', 'GPE'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arabiei', 'ORG'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('damaseen nonlatinalphabet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('animimortales', 'GPE'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('Epiphanius Sampsaei', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Per••', 'ORG'): 1; ('Elxaeus', 'GPE'): 1; ('h•r', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1"
A45496,13 | 24059,humility grace Christianity beauty rest baptism donatist lib Augustinus account,epistle: 0.5; epist: 0.5; word: 0.5; lib: 0.5; church: 0.5; pamelius: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; write: 0.45; erasmus: 0.35; cypr: 0.3; work: 0.15; pamel: 0.1; edition: 0.05; rest: 0.05; martyrdom: 0.05,"('Epist', 'PERSON'): 10; ('Pamelius', 'ORG'): 10; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Cypr', 'PERSON'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Pontius', 'NORP'): 5; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Goulart', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Pamel', 'GPE'): 3; ('76', 'DATE'): 3; ('Erasmus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Augustinus', 'GPE'): 2; ('Cent', 'ORG'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 2; ('Orat', 'GPE'): 2; ('Lyrinens', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Scultetus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Prudentius', 'ORG'): 2; ('Cyprian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Schol', 'GPE'): 2; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Margaret', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nisi vos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('tanto', 'GPE'): 1; ('erat', 'NORP'): 1; ('quanto humilior', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Epist', 'GPE'): 1; ('Scythians', 'NORP'): 1; ('a hundred thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ecclesiâ', 'GPE'): 1; ('de domini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cleri', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Brerewood de pretiis vet .', 'ORG'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('etiam quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non pleno', 'ORG'): 1; ('judicio religionis examino', 'PERSON'): 1; ('delictis plusquam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('promp•â', 'ORG'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('contrà', 'ORG'): 1; ('Stephen bishop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Carthage', 'ORG'): 1; ('Collegae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('singuli sentiamus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('neminem judicantes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nazianz', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laud', 'GPE'): 1; ('fidelity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nazianzen', 'LOC'): 1; ('Martyrum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cyprianum', 'ORG'): 1; ('fortissimus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Crescon', 'ORG'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('coeli', 'GPE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('terris', 'GPE'): 1; ('nec ab', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec lybiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solis', 'ORG'): 1; ('gallos fovet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('praesidet hesperiae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hiberis', 'ORG'): 1; ('catal', 'ORG'): 1; ('sole clariora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Strigel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Melancthon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Laeta', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cypriani', 'NORP'): 1; ('Laetam Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chronolog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paulinum', 'FAC'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Quirinus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Epistolae Cypriani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chemnitius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Arden', 'GPE'): 1; ('Crit', 'ORG'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day eighty', 'DATE'): 1; ('thirty and eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('eighteen', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Stephen', 'GPE'): 1; ('the particular year', 'DATE'): 1; ('•oulart', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cypria', 'GPE'): 1; ('cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tridentine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Simon Goulart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Coci', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bilson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epist', 'LOC'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('annotatiuncul', 'GPE'): 1; ('secundâ epistolâ', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sermonis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Doctr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trithemius', 'ORG'): 1; ('an .', 'DATE'): 1; ('263', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antoninus', 'GPE'): 1; ('250', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cypriaeno', 'GPE'): 1; ('quod ad ostentationem inge•• videri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daille', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cypriano Papae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Presbyteri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Diaconi Romae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('vigorem suum tam profanâ facilitate', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nervos', 'GPE'): 1; ('Vincent', 'GPE'): 1; ('Costerus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Epistolam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romae', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('6. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('52', 'DATE'): 1; ('54', 'DATE'): 1; ('64', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('65', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eucratium Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nec majestati divinae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Notis', 'GPE'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('seventy seven', 'DATE'): 1; ('debilitari posse', 'ORG'): 1; ('beneficia divina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sumenlis accipitur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod de divinis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('muneribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four .', 'DATE'): 1; ('Fortunatianus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('64', 'DATE'): 1; ('heretic truth', 'ORG'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('h•e', 'GPE'): 1; ('6. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('81', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('77', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christiani', 'ORG'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('novissimos cygnaeos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tom 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Demetriad', 'ORG'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trithemius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the first year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rhenanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tertulliano', 'ORG'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('virginitatem magno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cyprianus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('tom .', 'DATE'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pamol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('herein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertulian', 'NORP'): 1"
A45496,13 | 24129,exposition apostle creed insert work Ruffinus presbyter Aquileia Bellarm. script,epist: 0.5; thing: 0.5; church: 0.5; god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; word: 0.5; christ: 0.45; bishop: 0.45; people: 0.4; father: 0.3; time: 0.15; author: 0.1; erasmus: 0.1; faith: 0.05,"('Epist', 'PERSON'): 11; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('thou', 'GPE'): 7; ('christian', 'NORP'): 6; ('cyprian', 'NORP'): 5; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 4; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Pamelius', 'ORG'): 3; ('Bellar', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Erasmus', 'PRODUCT'): 3; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Augustin', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('§', 'NORP'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Cyprian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Judith', 'PERSON'): 2; ('pamel', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('Goulart', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('medulla', 'GPE'): 2; ('crit', 'ORG'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cypr', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Erasmus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Vives', 'ORG'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 2; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('74', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Pompeio', 'GPE'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Aquileia', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bellarm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gennadius', 'ORG'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samosatenus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eunomius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tobit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Celsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jason', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tuum celsum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Helvic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('Charles mar•ell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('750', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ri•t', 'PERSON'): 1; ('crit', 'GPE'): 1; ('some hundred of year', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twofold', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fortunatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dioclesian', 'ORG'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Neoterick', 'ORG'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rivet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trithem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Laick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ebrardus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Climacus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Coena', 'PERSON'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('Africum Cyprianus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Eras•', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hilarii', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tertulliano', 'ORG'): 1; ('ipse nonnunquam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('herein cyprian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('demosthe••s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('Erasm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chrysostom', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Africa', 'LOC'): 1; ('tertul•ian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pa•linum', 'LOC'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prudentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('saporem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sedem animae penetrate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sixtus Senensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('ciceronian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alsted', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Latines', 'ORG'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ascham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('255', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Donatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caecilius', 'ORG'): 1; ('de stud', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theolog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hyperius', 'ORG'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Froben', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Prophetas', 'ORG'): 1; ('retrò illuminator', 'PERSON'): 1; ('induitur', 'GPE'): 1; ('deus cum homine', 'GPE'): 1; ('christus esse voluit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prophetis', 'ORG'): 1; ('vocis imperio daemonia de hominibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('illuminaret caecos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sibi', 'GPE'): 1; ('famulari', 'ORG'): 1; ('maria obedire', 'PERSON'): 1; ('magum de licentiâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hunc magistri eorum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('doctrina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pontio Pilato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('procura•at', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac pertinacibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('crucifix•s', 'GPE'): 1; ('videntibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('d• vel ab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('coelum', 'ORG'): 1; ('hominem quem dilexit', 'ORG'): 1; ('jam venturo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('poenam diaboli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ultoris vigore', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Toby', 'ORG'): 1; ('53', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jubaianum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('God .', 'DATE'): 1; ('Stephen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Beatus Cyprianus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('firmis•imam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nativitatis', 'NORP'): 1; ('non carnem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('baptizari posse', 'ORG'): 1; ('cum suis', 'ORG'): 1; ('idol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Demetrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('55', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'ORG'): 1; ('68 § 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'GPE'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('§', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidam vim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed ipse vim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('urbe', 'GPE'): 1; ('svae praedicationis illustre', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('judicio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'ORG'): 1; ('suffragio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bonorum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Presbyteros', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ep', 'PERSON'): 1; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Episcopatus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antonianum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'GPE'): 1"
A45496,16,Hilarius Pictaviensis bear France Gallus Antonin part cap answer Leo,book: 0.5; bishop: 0.5; hilary: 0.5; arian: 0.5; time: 0.5; lib: 0.5; epist: 0.45; cent: 0.4; hilar: 0.35; man: 0.2; erasm: 0.15; faith: 0.15; synod: 0.1; emperor: 0.05; ibid: 0.05; heresy: 0.05; ant: 0.05,"('10', 'CARDINAL'): 19; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 15; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 14; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('France', 'GPE'): 10; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Jerome', 'PERSON'): 10; ('Cent', 'ORG'): 8; ('Hilary', 'PERSON'): 8; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Constantius', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Hilary', 'GPE'): 6; ('Erasm', 'ORG'): 6; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 6; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Arian', 'NORP'): 5; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 5; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 5; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 5; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 5; ('Galli', 'PERSON'): 4; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Bellar', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Seleucia', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Ruff', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Erasmus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Hieron', 'PERSON'): 4; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Gallus', 'GPE'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('gallican', 'NORP'): 3; ('Arles', 'GPE'): 3; ('Sulp', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Sulp', 'GPE'): 3; ('the council of Ariminum', 'ORG'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Sixtus Senensis', 'ORG'): 3; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 3; ('this day', 'DATE'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('nec', 'ORG'): 3; ('Antonin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Leo', 'PERSON'): 2; ('erat', 'NORP'): 2; ('Celtae', 'PERSON'): 2; ('year', 'DATE'): 2; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 2; ('Poitiers', 'ORG'): 2; ('Hil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Anton', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Italy', 'GPE'): 2; ('latin', 'NORP'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('Biblioth', 'GPE'): 2; ('Hierouym', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Apol', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Fortunatus', 'ORG'): 2; ('Victorius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Schol', 'GPE'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('crit', 'ORG'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('senens', 'GPE'): 2; ('fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Riv', 'ORG'): 2; ('crit .', 'ORG'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('l. •', 'PERSON'): 2; ('nihil nisi', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Trin', 'GPE'): 2; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('Hilarius Pictaviensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hilarius Gallus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Galliâ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aquitanicus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gallis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Po•ctiers', 'ORG'): 1; ('Geograph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Guienne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caesar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('s•rab', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mela', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('geog l. 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sulpitius Severus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Strabo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 1; ('Moses , Hilar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Poictou', 'GPE'): 1; ('tomb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saturninus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Valens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Vrsatius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('arians', 'NORP'): 1; ('l. 2.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vir sanè pessimus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ingenio malo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('infamiam multis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesia', 'GPE'): 1; ('byterris', 'GPE'): 1; ('three whole year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the four year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tom 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isauria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ariminum', 'ORG'): 1; ('the gallican church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sabellius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of nice', 'ORG'): 1; ('half - arian', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Ariminum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantium', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Vercellis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sozom', 'GPE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iuyricum', 'GPE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('proem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Galat', 'GPE'): 1; ('Latines', 'ORG'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de Synod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Hieronymus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Marcellam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('141', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hiliodorio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Origene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysostom', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ludovic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Imperat', 'ORG'): 1; ('de Judaie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('superstitionibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quâ cantela', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidem', 'GPE'): 1; ('extiterit', 'GPE'): 1; ('Venantius', 'NORP'): 1; ('about the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('575', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('auctario', 'GPE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Martin', 'ORG'): 1; ('amoris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hilarius', 'ORG'): 1; ('buccina terribilis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tubam legis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('praeco', 'ORG'): 1; ('auro', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vberior Nilo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apostolicus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Po', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rhone', 'ORG'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nile', 'LOC'): 1; ('Ister', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ruffin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('almost forty thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fermè millia versuum Origenis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Septenary', 'LOC'): 1; ('pro l•bris .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jovinlan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Apol', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hilar', 'GPE'): 1; ('Valens and', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Trithem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('heresy', 'GPE'): 1; ('Trith', 'ORG'): 1; ('Berg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hilariani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('incerti authoris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sulpitius Severus', 'GPE'): 1; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Osius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Corduba', 'GPE'): 1; ('a hundred year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rivet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hilarius quidam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pictaviensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Romanus', 'ORG'): 1; ('denuo hanc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Camarinam movit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pamel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cypriani', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Luciferian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phrygia', 'FAC'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Socrat', 'GPE'): 1; ('l. 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theodor', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ariaus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ierome', 'ORG'): 1; ('Milan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Auxentius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ante loc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chemnitius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Greeks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('doctrin•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thirty and', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sixt', 'ORG'): 1; ('Evangelist', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'NORP'): 1; ('sixty and nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the hundred and nineteenth', 'DATE'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Fl•rentium', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Abram', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Eras•', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gyraldus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bellat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ecclef', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eighty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Riv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aquitain', 'ORG'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('Semipelagians', 'NORP'): 1; ('352', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ann', 'PERSON'): 1; ('440', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('339', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sulpitius Severus Eucherius', 'FAC'): 1; ('Budaeus', 'GPE'): 1; ('adeò faeliciter', 'ORG'): 1; ('eruditum', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nunquam satiet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pauli•um', 'PERSON'): 1; ('trivialiter literatos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('procul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Greece', 'GPE'): 1; ('Quintilian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Matthew , Sixt', 'ORG'): 1; ('Constan', 'GPE'): 1; ('imperatorem Constantium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('qnem omnia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tempora aeterna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deus verbum', 'GPE'): 1; ('qui cum in forma', 'PERSON'): 1; ('salutis', 'NORP'): 1; ('factus obedience', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus christus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('132', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non continentur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil necesse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ita omnipotentiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('anteriusve cougrueret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil deest', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ipse est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui nihil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mosen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('manens', 'GPE'): 1; ('Prophetis', 'GPE'): 1; ('perimens', 'GPE'): 1; ('spei nostrae fidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('corruptionem carnis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gloriâ corporis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('unigenito soli', 'ORG'): 1; ('poena', 'ORG'): 1; ('decreti', 'GPE'): 1; ('se sentiat', 'GPE'): 1; ('quae non per dem•tationem naturae', 'ORG'): 1; ('commota', 'GPE'): 1; ('7.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('confiteri', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae vr•ò insania est', 'ORG'): 1; ('qualis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•um', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec multiplici', 'ORG'): 1; ('solicitat', 'NORP'): 1; ('confiteri', 'NORP'): 1; ('nova', 'LOC'): 1; ('confessionem baptismi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quot voluntate', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quot vitia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae sola est', 'FAC'): 1; ('Doctrinae', 'ORG'): 1; ('aut quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•esideratis coac•rvare doctrinam', 'ORG'): 1; ('religionis', 'NORP'): 1; ('sequitur', 'GPE'): 1; ('defectionem hypoerisis m•ndax', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam amiserat conscienti•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('svae misericordiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('remissionem largitur deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('remissio non probitatis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sed spontaneae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('operibus ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('neminem adjuvandum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Melchior Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gobelini', 'NORP'): 1; ('1420', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gobelinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isenach', 'ORG'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('Frederick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christiana', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('alia', 'GPE'): 1; ('exorari', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('gratiam impetremus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about four day', 'DATE'): 1; ('morum sunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etiam haec quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('scientiam necessaria', 'PERSON'): 1; ('inter reliqna', 'ORG'): 1; ('tant•m', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nisi doctus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('doctrinae sit autoritare nisi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'NORP'): 1; ('doctrina', 'GPE'): 1; ('140', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Differt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('125', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('animae captivitas', 'ORG'): 1; ('tristis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('humanitatis fugax', 'PERSON'): 1; ('religionem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dedecoris volutatur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('svae fervorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mortem quandam naturae incolumi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Quanta', 'ORG'): 1; ('memoratis', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('malis serviunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de trinitat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aeternitatem adsignat', 'ORG'): 1; ('imaginem filio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('spiritui sancto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nullis obnoxiam molestis affectionibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('similitudinem', 'NORP'): 1; ('quidem haec impeturae passionis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non tamen dolorem passionis', 'ORG'): 1; ('aut aera', 'ORG'): 1; ('quidem corpus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('parùm benè ab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mariam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil addidisse de suo :', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Mariae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sanguinem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('simul', 'GPE'): 1; ('de libero arbitrio non satis videtur cauté', 'PERSON'): 1; ('118', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cum ait', 'ORG'): 1; ('Psal', 'LOC'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('prius ( inquit', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae à deo sunt cum honore praeposuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('se cum confession subjecit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('exquiratur', 'GPE'): 1; ('est quidem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('§', 'NORP'): 1; ('Osiand', 'GPE'): 1; ('Julian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('grant liberty', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sulpit', 'GPE'): 1; ('Valentinian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Valens', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('baron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three hundred sixty six', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('three hundred sixty nine', 'QUANTITY'): 1"
A42822,24,page line philophy philosophy p. l. elipsis ellipsis Id. l.,chap: 0.5; god: 0.5; advantage: 0.5; life: 0.5; knowledge: 0.5; man: 0.45; death: 0.45; improvement: 0.45; mr: 0.25; age: 0.25; reason: 0.25; discourse: 0.2; society: 0.2,"('4o', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('London', 'GPE'): 3; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('CHAP', 'ORG'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Aristotle', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 2; ('8o', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12o', 'DATE'): 2; ('James Janeway', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Id.', 'GPE'): 1; ('133', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Vieta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Wallis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Geography', 'ORG'): 1; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('59', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aristotle', 'ORG'): 1; ('x.', 'ORG'): 1; ('71', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xi', 'ORG'): 1; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('83', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Boyle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('92', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('102', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('110', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xvi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('115', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('122', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Xviii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('128', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('137', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James Collins', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Mompesson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Corbet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('October 10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Seth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Exon', 'ORG'): 1; ('John Janeway', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cheapside', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Chappel', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('1674', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Joseph Alleine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('thirty three year', 'DATE'): 1; ('almost sixty year of age', 'DATE'): 1; ('twenty three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1"
A40084,5 | 37764,Philalethes time advantage get reasonableness precept gospel demonstrate viz. confirmation,god: 0.5; gospel: 0.5; duty: 0.5; man: 0.5; love: 0.5; philal: 0.5; precept: 0.5; religion: 0.5; theoph: 0.35; thing: 0.3; self: 0.2; reason: 0.15,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Philal', 'GPE'): 8; ('christian', 'NORP'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Philalethes', 'ORG'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('xxiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cybele', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bacchus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Flora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Venus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Priapus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Xxv', 'LOC'): 1; ('xxvii', 'GPE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gregory Nyssen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xxix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xxx', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Severus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('heathens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('some one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Socrates', 'LOC'): 1; ('Cato :', 'ORG'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Celsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lycurgus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lycurgus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zeno', 'GPE'): 1; ('Platonists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hierocles', 'GPE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apollo', 'ORG'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Brutus', 'GPE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xxxiv', 'PERSON'): 1"
A40084,5 | 37849,Philal. difference Theoph. righteousness regulation man law righteousness call righteousness,righteousness: 0.5; theoph: 0.5; christ: 0.5; god: 0.5; faith: 0.5; man: 0.5; sense: 0.5; philal: 0.5; impute: 0.5; sin: 0.3; saint: 0.2,"('Philal', 'GPE'): 15; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 8; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 6; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Theophilus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 3; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 3; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Antinomian', 'NORP'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 1; ('noonday', 'DATE'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lix', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lx', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antinomianism', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iames 2', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('S. James 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15. 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lxiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Philalethes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zacheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('antinomian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A40084,5 | 37950,Philal. please paraphrase give context Theoph. interpretation place nonconditionality covenant,place: 0.5; philal: 0.5; man: 0.45; god: 0.45; faith: 0.45; work: 0.45; justification: 0.45; grace: 0.45; doctrine: 0.45; theoph: 0.45; paul: 0.05; particular: 0.05; persuade: 0.05; person: 0.05; perform: 0.05; people: 0.05; paraphrase: 0.05; papist: 0.05,"('Philal', 'GPE'): 7; ('Philalethes', 'ORG'): 4; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('S. Iames', 'ORG'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Galatians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hebrves', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Theophilus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fault', 'PERSON'): 1; ('about one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('heathens', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Antinomian', 'NORP'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Galatian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. James', 'PERSON'): 1"
A40084,6,Par. manner account opinion refer matter doctrine discipline account opinion,philal: 0.5; god: 0.45; man: 0.45; theoph: 0.45; doctrine: 0.45; sin: 0.45; philalethes: 0.45; opinion: 0.4; notion: 0.35; thing: 0.15; scripture: 0.15; nature: 0.1; church: 0.1; goodness: 0.05; soul: 0.05; world: 0.05; perception: 0.05; peace: 0.05; pity: 0.05; phrase: 0.05; philosopher: 0.05; person: 0.05; permit: 0.05; perfection: 0.05,"('Philal', 'GPE'): 15; ('Philalethes', 'ORG'): 5; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Par', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iii', 'NORP'): 1; ('Armagh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ireland', 'GPE'): 1; ('396', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('some day', 'DATE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Vii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theophilus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Voluntas', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Vatablus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nineveh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('forty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ninevites', 'GPE'): 1; ('Xii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the late day', 'DATE'): 1; ('xiv .', 'GPE'): 1"
A40084,6 | 38033,Philal. doubt say scripture doctrine number comparison Theoph. sense notion,god: 0.5; way: 0.5; man: 0.5; theoph: 0.5; sense: 0.5; philal: 0.5; grace: 0.5; scripture: 0.5; doctrine: 0.4; self: 0.35; thing: 0.15; time: 0.05; mean: 0.05,"('Philal', 'GPE'): 11; ('Theophilus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Calvinists', 'NORP'): 2; ('Arminius', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Catharinus', 'GPE'): 2; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Philalethes', 'ORG'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('hearty comfort', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xvii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('608', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Decretum', 'ORG'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Brutus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Calvinism', 'GPE'): 1; ('Calvinist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dominicans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Franciscans', 'NORP'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Xxi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('diverse year', 'DATE'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Goodnight', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Arminianism', 'NORP'): 1"
A47788,21,CHAP. Iii order morning evening prayer use say prayer B.,lord: 0.5; priest: 0.5; prayer: 0.5; god: 0.5; father: 0.5; edw: 0.5; sin: 0.45; mercy: 0.35; time: 0.3; day: 0.2; people: 0.2; minister: 0.15; heaven: 0.1; glory: 0.1; place: 0.05; psalm: 0.05; church: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 13; ('Scot', 'PERSON'): 9; ('daily', 'DATE'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 6; ('evening', 'TIME'): 5; ('morning', 'TIME'): 5; ('the year', 'DATE'): 5; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('this day', 'DATE'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1. B.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('that day', 'DATE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('domini domino', 'PERSON'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 2; ('Benedictus', 'ORG'): 2; ('100', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('where morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('common prayer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chappel', 'LOC'): 1; ('Chappel', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Deans', 'NORP'): 1; ('2. year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Edw', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Deacon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alb', 'ORG'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psalm 51', 'PERSON'): 1; ('prayer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jocl 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('142', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('o• Ed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•ame', 'GPE'): 1; ('scotch liturgy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Easter to Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Renedictus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nun•', 'ORG'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matthew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the whole year', 'DATE'): 1; ('•ent', 'ORG'): 1; ('66.', 'DATE'): 1; ('thou cherubin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seraphin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('125', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vouchsafe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('123', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('moon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('•lesse', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('ble•e', 'GPE'): 1; ('Azarias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Misael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 1; ('6. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ponce Pilate', 'ORG'): 1; ('three day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the holy catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Versicles', 'GPE'): 1; ('Edward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Clarks', 'PERSON'): 1; ('all the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('that morning', 'TIME'): 1"
A46823,135,CHAP. Vers. people lord word original translate render margin complainer,god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; vers: 0.5; people: 0.5; moses: 0.5; flesh: 0.5; man: 0.45; day: 0.4; spirit: 0.4; quail: 0.3; fire: 0.15; camp: 0.15; exod: 0.05; gift: 0.05; place: 0.05,"('two', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('Hattaavah', 'PERSON'): 4; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 3; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 3; ('78.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three day', 'DATE'): 2; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('God', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paran', 'GPE'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 2; ('32', 'DATE'): 2; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('a month', 'DATE'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('78. 19 , 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Taberah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Deut', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Taberah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('15. 39', 'DATE'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Porrum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a• frangere morsu', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('sanctas gentes quibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nascuntur', 'GPE'): 1; ('numina', 'GPE'): 1; ('lanatis animalibus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('omnis mensa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('he day after day', 'DATE'): 1; ('their year', 'DATE'): 1; ('18. 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sanhedrin', 'NORP'): 1; ('Herod day', 'LOC'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the next day', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six hundred thousand footman', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('chapter 2', 'LAW'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 10', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. Exod', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20. 7.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 10.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Moses', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('the second month', 'DATE'): 1; ('about a year', 'DATE'): 1; ('two cubit', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('a hundred', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Ezek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('45. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A46823,195,CHAP. Vers. Moses plain Moab mountai• N•bo labourer night chamber,place: 0.5; moses: 0.45; plate: 0.45; manner: 0.45; land: 0.45; lord: 0.45; art: 0.4; way: 0.4; god: 0.35; honour: 0.2; body: 0.15; country: 0.15; christ: 0.1; paper: 0.05; page: 0.05; perform: 0.05; people: 0.05; peake: 0.05; particular: 0.05; part: 0.05; pain: 0.05; ordinance: 0.05; canaan: 0.05,"('Canaan', 'GPE'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Israelite', 'NORP'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Moab', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('xxxiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('N•bo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gilead', 'ORG'): 1; ('jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Reuben', 'NORP'): 1; ('Manasseh', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leshem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Josh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 47', 'DATE'): 1; ('Laish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Judg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Naphtali', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Judah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the midland sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('the utmost sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Coloss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('unt•', 'ORG'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('forty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('sepulchre', 'GPE'): 1; ('Michael', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Archangel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('CALLOT', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bosse', 'ORG'): 1; ('FAITHORNE', 'ORG'): 1; ('Barr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1662', 'DATE'): 1; ('Robert Peake', 'PERSON'): 1; ('William Faithorne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mellan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Natalis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pontius', 'NORP'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('W. F.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Spaniard', 'NORP'): 1; ('Faithorne', 'NORP'): 1; ('T. Flatman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('polish', 'NORP'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Graver', 'GPE'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1"
A48824,6,epigramma G.B. Roma Papa Romulea miror pastor urbe Sceptra pastor,god: 0.5; minister: 0.5; friend: 0.45; time: 0.45; ladyship: 0.4; cause: 0.4; family: 0.4; christ: 0.35; pastor: 0.3; self: 0.25; ministry: 0.2; love: 0.2; servant: 0.15; child: 0.15; sir: 0.15; honour: 0.05; name: 0.05; thing: 0.05,"('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 3; ('non ego Romulea', 'PERSON'): 2; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 2; ('epigramma G.B. de Roma', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sceptra', 'ORG'): 1; ('Quum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quomodo', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('ill .', 'GPE'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('socinians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Familist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quakers', 'GPE'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Kingsnorton', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('A. W.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph Cranford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul Church-yard', 'ORG'): 1; ('1660', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lucy Grantham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ratcliff', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nottingham', 'ORG'): 1; ('scho•ars', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('weekly', 'DATE'): 1; ('constant morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('evening', 'TIME'): 1; ('the lord day', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dorcas', 'GPE'): 1; ('9 39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nottingham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two hundred pound', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Kings-Norton', 'ORG'): 1; ('Novemb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 1659', 'DATE'): 1; ('Richard GREVIS', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Moseley', 'NORP'): 1; ('Worcester', 'GPE'): 1; ('Esq', 'GPE'): 1; ('Impolite', 'NORP'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam Shaw', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Long-Whatton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('July 2. 1659', 'DATE'): 1"
A45328,6,CHAP. title dignity utility necessity efficacy gi••n mi••sters Christ ghost,god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; minister: 0.5; call: 0.5; man: 0.5; word: 0.5; gospel: 0.45; church: 0.3; cor: 0.3; lord: 0.2; light: 0.2; master: 0.2; world: 0.15; people: 0.1; ox: 0.1,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 41; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 31; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 15; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 12; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 9; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 5; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 4; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('14.', 'DATE'): 4; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('14', 'DATE'): 4; ('3. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('20.', 'DATE'): 3; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('England', 'GPE'): 3; ('1. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3. 17', 'DATE'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('3. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Ezech', 'ORG'): 2; ('12', 'DATE'): 2; ('38', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Starrs', 'ORG'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'DATE'): 2; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the mi••sters of Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('14.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('the ministry of the word', 'ORG'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sam 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ti•othy', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Belial', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Levites', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('1. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('52. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('10. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('vine dresser', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 37', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three and thirty year of age', 'DATE'): 1; ('fifty year of age', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('57', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fifty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.', 'DATE'): 1; ('16.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zach', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•ade', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharoab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('62.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 8.', 'DATE'): 1; ('13. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('63.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('diligence', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sta••e', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('39', 'DATE'): 1; ('40', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eph.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('91.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('2. kin', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('2•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.', 'DATE'): 1; ('2• 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('20. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('12. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezech', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phil 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('philem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hebrews', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•4', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10 ▪ god', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Elijah', 'PRODUCT'): 1; (', than thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. kin ▪', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('19 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('kin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elders', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph. 4. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jude 12', 'LAW'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•lattereth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('necessi•yes', 'GPE'): 1; ('6 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('glorio•sly', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hanun', 'ORG'): 1; ('15. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('outward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('•acob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('144', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('summer', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cor 6. 4', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 34', 'DATE'): 1; ('Zeph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Num• .', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 16', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 35.', 'DATE'): 1; ('•hat', 'LOC'): 1; ('36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('glori•yes', 'ORG'): 1; ('49.', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('60.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A45328,10,CHAP. use instruction doctrine necessity gospel-ministry salt world sin whole,god: 0.5; ministry: 0.5; man: 0.5; minister: 0.5; christ: 0.5; salt: 0.5; world: 0.45; church: 0.4; thing: 0.35; earth: 0.25; apostle: 0.15; word: 0.15; king: 0.1; honour: 0.1; lord: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 20; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 17; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 9; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('Egyptians', 'NORP'): 4; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 3; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('14', 'DATE'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 2; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 2; ('10. 15', 'DATE'): 2; ('17', 'DATE'): 2; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('ark', 'GPE'): 2; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('18', 'DATE'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nourish', 'NORP'): 2; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8', 'DATE'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('16', 'DATE'): 2; ('Ezech', 'ORG'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hos', 'PERSON'): 2; ('70', 'DATE'): 2; ('14.', 'DATE'): 2; ('23. 21', 'DATE'): 2; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 2; ('32', 'DATE'): 2; ('5. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Constantinopolitans', 'NORP'): 1; ('our atheistical day', 'DATE'): 1; ('arrian', 'GPE'): 1; ('arminians', 'NORP'): 1; ('socinians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Familist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antisabbatarians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Antitrinitarians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mortalists', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('four year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lerna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('23. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('the kingdom of', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 16', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('20. 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 3. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ps. 74. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('30. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('8. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('16.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('52.', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('30. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Baptist', 'NORP'): 1; ('6. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Galattan', 'NORP'): 1; ('Corn•lius', 'ORG'): 1; ('10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Roman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iaddus', 'GPE'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antiquit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aqutla', 'GPE'): 1; ('Priscilla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16. 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Obadiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Elisah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the ministry of the law', 'ORG'): 1; ('3. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('54', 'DATE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('28. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the ministry of the church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Levite', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ierusal•m', 'GPE'): 1; ('10. 45', 'DATE'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iehorah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Andrew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('asian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Indians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('2. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('16. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Galatians', 'NORP'): 1; ('3. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13. 10 , 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gracchi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Catiline Cethegus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Mercury', 'ORG'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nicol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de cleman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('75', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('223', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('Charles', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('71', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mall 2', 'LAW'): 1; ('62. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ecebolius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vilenes•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sam 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('counterfe•t', 'ORG'): 1; ('11. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('gift brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('these day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hercules', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iereboam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caligula', 'GPE'): 1; ('Balaam', 'GPE'): 1; ('ambrosia', 'GPE'): 1; ('nectar', 'ORG'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23. 32', 'DATE'): 1; ('call|it', 'ORG'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('9 37', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ieremiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('babylonish', 'NORP'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thyatira', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iezabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Uzzah', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Korah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dathan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abiram', 'ORG'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('10. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Familist ▪ Anabaptists', 'ORG'): 1; ('vveigelians', 'NORP'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gamaliel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•4', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amaziah Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A45328,12,CHAP. Viii assert maintenance minister use reprehension correction Anabaptists leveller,minister: 0.5; god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; maintenance: 0.5; man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; gospel: 0.5; law: 0.5; apostle: 0.4; church: 0.25; people: 0.1; give: 0.05; right: 0.05; word: 0.05; ministry: 0.05; care: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 17; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 12; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('thou', 'GPE'): 6; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 6; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 4; ('Levites', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 4; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('14.', 'DATE'): 4; ('22', 'DATE'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 3; ('12', 'DATE'): 3; ('11', 'DATE'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('14', 'DATE'): 3; ('15', 'DATE'): 3; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 2; ('Pharaoh', 'PERSON'): 2; ('31', 'DATE'): 2; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nay', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Levi', 'PERSON'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('44', 'DATE'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Levite', 'FAC'): 2; ('13', 'DATE'): 2; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20. 25', 'DATE'): 2; ('Ierem', 'PERSON'): 2; ('20.', 'DATE'): 2; ('assert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aegypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('47', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phoenicia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Neh 13', 'LAW'): 1; ('Euseb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21. 36', 'DATE'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccl', 'GPE'): 1; ('4. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the Anabaptistical party', 'ORG'): 1; ('Vince', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('6. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Musculus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eliah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'DATE'): 1; ('necessi•yes', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chaldee', 'NORP'): 1; ('Ezra 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•ythes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('18. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•lipt', 'NORP'): 1; ('•0', 'ORG'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('Theologicall', 'ORG'): 1; ('li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('500 l. some 600 l.', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('2 Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian magistrat•s', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('100 200', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('300', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('laboure•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('•plendor', 'ORG'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'DATE'): 1; ('Neh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ieremiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Julian', 'GPE'): 1; ('9 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pro•u•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apostle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prolepsis', 'GPE'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wret•h', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('Barnabas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 5', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'DATE'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('27. 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 35', 'DATE'): 1; ('22.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iosh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10. 32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ezek', 'ORG'): 1; ('30.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Levites', 'ORG'): 1; ('48', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Levite', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Answ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the ministry of the law be', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 10 , 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('prove•b', 'ORG'): 1; ('Iudg', 'GPE'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('rob God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Austine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Serm', 'PERSON'): 1; ('219', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24. 14', 'DATE'): 1; ('22. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45. 9 , 10 , 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35. 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Philem', 'GPE'): 1; ('19 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('secul•r', 'FAC'): 1; ('Baal priest', 'GPE'): 1; ('Iezabel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('18. 19', 'DATE'): 1; ('a hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('several year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('28. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('20.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Oreb', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zeb', 'ORG'): 1; ('Zebah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zalmunna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tollant nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('•iunt', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('A. Gellius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dolabella', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cassius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antonius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caepio', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tholossane', 'PERSON'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('thievish', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Belshazzar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antiochus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Julianus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Claudius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Fulvius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lactant', 'GPE'): 1; ('4. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 22', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A45328,14,CHAP. corollary doctrine place Christ minister heed salt Christ put,god: 0.5; word: 0.5; man: 0.5; life: 0.5; christ: 0.5; minister: 0.5; thing: 0.45; lord: 0.4; tim: 0.35; work: 0.35; cor: 0.25; doctrine: 0.1; people: 0.05; preacher: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 25; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 23; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 8; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 7; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 4; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 4; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Ier', 'PERSON'): 4; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Austine', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('14', 'DATE'): 3; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 3; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14.', 'DATE'): 2; ('Zachary', 'PERSON'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('24', 'DATE'): 2; ('35', 'DATE'): 2; ('season', 'DATE'): 2; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'DATE'): 2; ('11. 23', 'DATE'): 2; ('yesterday', 'DATE'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('cha••e', 'ORG'): 2; ('Ezek', 'ORG'): 2; ('x.', 'ORG'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('take heed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('•each', 'PERSON'): 1; ('more than a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bernard to Eugenius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Staughton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('saeculi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('91', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('92', 'DATE'): 1; ('93', 'DATE'): 1; ('24.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ezra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ezra 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mat 5', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nazianzen', 'FAC'): 1; ('Lam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Absalon', 'ORG'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Samuel , Ieremiah , Daniel', 'ORG'): 1; ('15.', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bradford', 'GPE'): 1; ('Latimer', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hooper', 'ORG'): 1; ('2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ministerialy', 'GPE'): 1; ('audito•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Urim', 'ORG'): 1; ('2 Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of Trent', 'ORG'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('10.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hero•ck', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8. 36', 'DATE'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Latimer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rath•r', 'ORG'): 1; ('3. 1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph. 4. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('1. 22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 8. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('synagog•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('55', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 47', 'DATE'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Illyricum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Damascus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Arabia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cyprus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pamphylia', 'GPE'): 1; ('P•sidia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lycaonia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Syria', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cilicia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phrygia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Galatia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Mysia', 'GPE'): 1; ('•roas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Achaia , Epyrus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Farellus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lonsannenses', 'ORG'): 1; ('No•ocomenses', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('a hundred eighty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chrysostome', 'GPE'): 1; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('8. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John 21', 'PERSON'): 1; ('minist•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('•ear', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('•oon', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('c•n', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•o', 'ORG'): 1; ('a•henian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Alexander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fig•t', 'GPE'): 1; ('Trojane', 'ORG'): 1; ('tyri•n', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ierobo•m', 'ORG'): 1; ('Herod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrysostome Eudoxus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 1; ('6. 50', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 8. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('13. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('19 41', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samaritane', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('La•renti••', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John , Ioh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elisha Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('390', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Iesus•', 'ORG'): 1; ('4 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.', 'DATE'): 1; ('the ministry of God', 'ORG'): 1; ('five thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('mixtu•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('Micajah', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phil 4 17', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('3. 30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'NORP'): 1; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa 56. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tha•', 'GPE'): 1; ('procu•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('scottish', 'NORP'): 1; ('one penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('three hundred crown', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('last', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1"
A45336,15,argument absurdity grant man Topick man swallow man read swallow,gift: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; call: 0.5; error: 0.5; learning: 0.5; devil: 0.4; preacher: 0.3; scripture: 0.25; word: 0.2; spirit: 0.15; king: 0.15; christ: 0.1; thing: 0.1; original: 0.1; language: 0.1; worm: 0.1; tribe: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ab absurdo', 'ORG'): 1; ('Topick', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ruther•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('275', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mille', 'ORG'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phelps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeroboam', 'GPE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('52', 'DATE'): 1; ('24', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Naylor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Taylor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dulcius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Workman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('dr ▪ hall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. Dec. 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('351', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('371', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('melchizedecke offer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rex Salem', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Lack-Latines', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Caryl on Job 1', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('A. here|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('11. 25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('subj', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('D. Prid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('237', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Geneva', 'GPE'): 1; ('the season', 'DATE'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('h•c', 'ORG'): 1; ('socinians', 'NORP'): 1; ('11. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Spanheim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('d•b', 'PERSON'): 1; ('74', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('piscatorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Probl', 'ORG'): 1; ('62', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Titus 1', 'LAW'): 1; ('Aratus', 'ORG'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('15. 33', 'DATE'): 1; ('Syriack', 'ORG'): 1; ('Abba', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 19', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bethel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1"
A45336,16,man truth purity V. Davenant heretic learning man phrase scripture,man: 0.45; call: 0.45; scripture: 0.45; church: 0.45; encage: 0.45; place: 0.45; person: 0.4; god: 0.3; read: 0.25; argument: 0.2; gift: 0.15; ordain: 0.15; art: 0.15; minister: 0.1; ministry: 0.1; apostle: 0.05; pium: 0.05; piety: 0.05; pref: 0.05; preacher: 0.05; prayer: 0.05; plough: 0.05; presbyterio: 0.05; pet: 0.05; ordination: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('14', 'DATE'): 3; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('V. Davenant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pastor Eya•', 'ORG'): 1; ('71', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prid', 'GPE'): 1; ('de Sap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('709', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Relig', 'GPE'): 1; ('424', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Dithmar Ethic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non necessitate absolutâ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theologia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('superioribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('ancilli', 'GPE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ruthers', 'ORG'): 1; ('Presbyt', 'ORG'): 1; ('491', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('par', 'ORG'): 1; ('1 sewan diatrib', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elders', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Crete', 'GPE'): 1; ('Barnabas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('15. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Presbyterio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Timothy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hieron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paulinum', 'EVENT'): 1; ('hanc garr•l•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hanc sophista verbosus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•aici', 'PERSON'): 1; ('abundanter verbum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrys', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epist', 'GPE'): 1; ('Coloss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pium', 'ORG'): 1; ('requirit s. Scriptur•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Thess', 'NORP'): 1; ('4. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('B•za', 'PERSON'): 1; ('meek', 'GPE'): 1; ('Basil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tuum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Caesari', 'GPE'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fabrilia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Naylor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Milner', 'ORG'): 1; ('Parry pref .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ursin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Catech', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 13', 'DATE'): 1"
A45336,26,kind gift brethren precept precedent word God tolerate church God,church: 0.4; lord: 0.4; man: 0.4; god: 0.4; reform: 0.4; practice: 0.4; office: 0.35; call: 0.35; ch: 0.3; government: 0.25; way: 0.2; ovid: 0.1; orthodox: 0.1; person: 0.1; peace: 0.1; pastor: 0.1; parliament: 0.1; parable: 0.1; phrase: 0.1; ordinance: 0.1; order: 0.1; prisoner: 0.1; engl: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Engl', 'PERSON'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the holy ministry', 'ORG'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('gift brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('V. Synops', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theolog', 'PERSON'): 1; ('564', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seventeenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Forsitan', 'GPE'): 1; ('parva', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae non presunt singul•', 'ORG'): 1; ('juncta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ovid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 32', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('W. Burton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('m. B•rnard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nathan catch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amsterdam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Babel', 'GPE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('arrian ▪', 'ORG'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mortalists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Familist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quakers', 'GPE'): 1; ('J.', 'ORG'): 1; ('J. Alas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('suo lata', 'PERSON'): 1; ('iuriscon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vous avez reform church', 'ORG'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('353', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cons', 'ORG'): 1; ('25•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Novemb', 'GPE'): 1; ('2. 1649', 'DATE'): 1; ('Presb', 'NORP'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ecclesiae Scoticanae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('multis', 'NORP'): 1; ('54', 'DATE'): 1; ('sine schismate', 'ORG'): 1; ('Haeresi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('doctrinae retinuerit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Confes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Helvetia , Bohemia', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Ausperg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('Edinburgh', 'GPE'): 1; ('Glascow', 'GPE'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('236', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('246', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('258', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26•', 'DATE'): 1; ('267', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('255', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('April 26. 1645', 'DATE'): 1; ('Tho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Fairfax', 'GPE'): 1; ('ordin-•or', 'GPE'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•', 'PRODUCT'): 1"
A42351,3,argument allegation ornature kind beauty beauty Plotia En. kind flourish,temple: 0.5; place: 0.5; kind: 0.5; god: 0.5; beauty: 0.5; house: 0.5; thing: 0.5; time: 0.5; image: 0.4; delight: 0.3; eye: 0.25; scripture: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Easie', 'PERSON'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('•', 'PRODUCT'): 5; ('•hich', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Tom 2', 'PERSON'): 3; ('three degree', 'QUANTITY'): 3; ('Templ•', 'ORG'): 3; ('•o', 'GPE'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 2; ('contra', 'NORP'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('this day', 'DATE'): 2; ('woul•', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Templum', 'ORG'): 2; ('2.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. •', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ornatiora templa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('haebe•e', 'GPE'): 1; ('10 10', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Samaria', 'GPE'): 1; ('•ermeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•lihy', 'ORG'): 1; ('•aturall', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('•arle', 'GPE'): 1; ('4 four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Inhonestum', 'ORG'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•loud', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•o', 'NORP'): 1; ('syrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Gehezi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('season', 'DATE'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Nauta', 'ORG'): 1; ('Flacc', 'GPE'): 1; ('•hem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hesperus and Vesperus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('for•s•us', 'ORG'): 1; ('nihil amabilius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil •chrius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('concern••g', 'ORG'): 1; ('quam munita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('edita doctrina', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pers', 'ORG'): 1; ('Puppae', 'ORG'): 1; ('divine•y', 'ORG'): 1; ('•hey', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•he', 'PERSON'): 1; ('52', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('96', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13•', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('49.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•', 'NORP'): 1; ('•ceans', 'NORP'): 1; ('•uropians', 'NORP'): 1; ('•ould', 'ORG'): 1; ('Europa', 'LOC'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('veluti dubia', 'GPE'): 1; ('intendi animos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('putab•nt', 'GPE'): 1; ('••me', 'ORG'): 1; ('••ild', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•hild', 'ORG'): 1; ('49', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Darnell', 'ORG'): 1; ('••e', 'ORG'): 1; ('••eld', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('kin•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hosea', 'GPE'): 1; ('2.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28.17', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cav•', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hilarius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the ministry of ••e word', 'ORG'): 1; ('20.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('new bui•• house', 'ORG'): 1; ('Nehemiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Nehem', 'GPE'): 1; ('12.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•ossessions', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•ing', 'ORG'): 1; ('•actum', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('on• dwell house', 'ORG'): 1; ('•n •uk', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('14.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eliz', 'ORG'): 1; ('23.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the ••id sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('••n', 'ORG'): 1; ('36.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Asia', 'LOC'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Belus', 'GPE'): 1; ('70', 'DATE'): 1; ('Singulae ◊ singulis lapidibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('de', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Seneca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28.22', 'MONEY'): 1; ('11.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the week day', 'DATE'): 1; ('31.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•hing', 'GPE'): 1; ('whereunto', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('outward eyesore', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•elight', 'GPE'): 1; ('the 1 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12 23', 'DATE'): 1; ('may spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('outward eye', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('the season', 'DATE'): 1; ('21.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Mat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•d', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('say••g', 'GPE'): 1; ('Easie 1.12', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•ho', 'ORG'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('year', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('al•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 Chron', 'PERCENT'): 1; ('17.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa•', 'ORG'): 1; ('•m', 'NORP'): 1; ('13.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('8 7', 'DATE'): 1; ('7.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezech', 'GPE'): 1; ('24.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Steven', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apologie', 'ORG'): 1; ('7 51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('uncircumcis•', 'ORG'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•ace', 'ORG'): 1; ('•ch', 'NORP'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sam 6.7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('those day', 'DATE'): 1; ('••rd', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('•w', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•ods', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('•egree', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•ommon', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('•t', 'ORG'): 1; ('21 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('ca•', 'ORG'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1"
