tcpID,curr_div_idx,beginning,topic,entities
A73323,2,end further furnish bless sacrament doctrine practice other rock be,man: 0.5; god: 0.5; self: 0.5; examination: 0.5; lord: 0.5; sin: 0.5; grace: 0.5; christ: 0.45; time: 0.4; line: 0.3; work: 0.15; duty: 0.05; another: 0.05; table: 0.05; danger: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 2; ('will|be', 'GPE'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('N. T. nonlatinalphabet H. graij ad Authorem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('edatur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cambus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod edatur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('habet', 'GPE'): 1; ('eiusdem nonlatinalphabet', 'ORG'): 1; ('qualis conuiua prob•tur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vobis', 'ORG'): 1; ('finxerit iste libre', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('etlaetus edas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lauta parantur', 'ORG'): 1; ('Georgius Taylerus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('91', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('136', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fourthly', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('7. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('shall|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cain', 'ORG'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('keeper', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salomons 1', 'LAW'): 1; ('3 24', 'DATE'): 1; ('sword', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A73323,26,sense Christ body place other accident subject whiteness snow snow,body: 0.45; bread: 0.45; christ: 0.45; thing: 0.45; sign: 0.45; god: 0.4; nature: 0.4; lord: 0.4; sacrament: 0.35; accident: 0.25; word: 0.25; substance: 0.1; element: 0.05; heaven: 0.05; potters: 0.05; possession: 0.05; presence: 0.05; practice: 0.05; power: 0.05; powe: 0.05; promise: 0.05; perceive: 0.05; place: 0.05; property: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 2; ('paris', 'GPE'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('s•a', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ioh', 'LOC'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two or three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Adimant', 'GPE'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cyprian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('102', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('outward mean', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('albeit', 'GPE'): 1; ('Subblato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('h•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iames', 'ORG'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1636', 'DATE'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1"
A79485,2,be ground build parliament justice caunse parliament dissolution payment faith,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; time: 0.5; lord: 0.5; papist: 0.45; general: 0.45; moses: 0.4; parliament: 0.4; self: 0.4; people: 0.25; isa: 0.15; place: 0.1; faith: 0.1; law: 0.1; justice: 0.05; work: 0.05; death: 0.05; thing: 0.05,"('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('April last', 'DATE'): 3; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 3; ('the last of April', 'DATE'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 2; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 2; ('Joab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('100', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40 day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the supreme trust', 'ORG'): 1; ('the 22th', 'DATE'): 1; ('25.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Shemey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 kin', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('18.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 7.2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('more than 100', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('more than 100000', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eccles 3.7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Psal 62', 'LAW'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('29.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.31', 'DATE'): 1; ('22.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.3', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12,6-8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('22.21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('i long ago', 'DATE'): 1; ('9.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nimsby', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ahab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jezebel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baal', 'LOC'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('141.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Marah', 'GPE'): 1; ('sheep kin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('3d', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('58.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa 1.15', 'DATE'): 1; ('21.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('66.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('the 32th', 'DATE'): 1; ('the same day', 'DATE'): 1; ('22th', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1"
A79944,4,champ prayer David brevvers plea vindication strong-beere ale declare bounty,creature: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; beer: 0.5; wine: 0.5; sin: 0.5; abuse: 0.5; blessing: 0.5; house: 0.4; zeal: 0.35; heart: 0.1; people: 0.05; drunkard: 0.05; part: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('21', 'DATE'): 3; ('Canaan', 'PERSON'): 3; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('veniam corvis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1647', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lectori candido', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. P. D.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Volusi', 'ORG'): 1; ('nec', 'ORG'): 1; ('crea•ures', 'ORG'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('John 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.9 14', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Balak', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Balaam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 17.11', 'PERSON'): 1; ('their latter day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cheapside', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('•o• inquam', 'ORG'): 1; ('Primetheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('iaph•t', 'ORG'): 1; ('Janus', 'FAC'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cairo', 'GPE'): 1; ('iudians', 'NORP'): 1; ('•oules', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('21.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('23.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('••', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('•hem', 'ORG'): 1; ('becau•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('callin•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('this cit•e of London', 'ORG'): 1; ('•2 verse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('sise•a', 'ORG'): 1; ('••e', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('a•mighty', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A72513,60,Q. example A. poet kind artificialnes people viz. beast head,person: 0.5; sacrament: 0.45; page: 0.45; lord: 0.45; mr: 0.45; man: 0.45; principle: 0.4; reader: 0.4; practice: 0.35; rejoinder: 0.35; suspension: 0.15; christ: 0.15; humphrey: 0.05; peter: 0.05; pity: 0.05; piece: 0.05; philip: 0.05; poet: 0.05; pet: 0.05; passion: 0.05; pen: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Humphrey', 'PERSON'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('London', 'GPE'): 2; ('21', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Horace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iliad', 'GPE'): 1; ('Troy war', 'ORG'): 1; ('Virgil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aeneas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sicilia', 'GPE'): 1; ('Roger Drake', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Justin', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christianis', 'ORG'): 1; ('10. 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1656', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('H. grant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('246', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('171', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('82', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('83', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('92.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('198', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 1; ('209', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1"
A74671,24,sect Viii objection damnation page m. H. answer church part,mr: 0.5; man: 0.5; christ: 0.5; duty: 0.5; grace: 0.5; answ: 0.5; faith: 0.5; person: 0.5; sacrament: 0.4; sin: 0.35; page: 0.15; word: 0.05; act: 0.05,"('D.', 'NORP'): 14; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('m. H.', 'PERSON'): 9; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('H.', 'PERSON'): 8; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 5; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('243', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Answ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('247', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('248', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Query', 'ORG'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('251', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 2; ('14.', 'DATE'): 2; ('256', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('257', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('John 2', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('178', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('11. 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Micha 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('3. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('D. it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('H. p. 244', 'PERSON'): 1; ('M.H.', 'GPE'): 1; ('dr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('m. Bradford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('245', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('70', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('13. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('122', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('H. p. 246', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10 21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('retort m. H.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('absurd', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('H. ib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('H. p. 244.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('250', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Passeover', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ʋzziah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Passeover', 'ORG'): 1; ('252', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('moon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('m. H. ib .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fieri', 'GPE'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('188', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('225', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('255', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('259', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvinists', 'NORP'): 1; ('malis', 'GPE'): 1; ('sumsionis quam sit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dispar exitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('vita pit erit', 'ORG'): 1; ('cerebro', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amaracus', 'ORG'): 1; ('immundas illius aura sue', 'ORG'): 1"
A76988,7 | 8062,discriminate characterize name badge faction bellows strife mark division fuel,difference: 0.5; truth: 0.5; agreement: 0.5; name: 0.5; thing: 0.5; man: 0.5; god: 0.5; division: 0.5; church: 0.4; way: 0.35; strife: 0.2; self: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 15; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 6; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Calvinists', 'NORP'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Bucer', 'PERSON'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hussites', 'GPE'): 1; ('80', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('70', 'DATE'): 1; ('heresy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nazianzen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Petrians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Paulians', 'NORP'): 1; ('nisi', 'ORG'): 1; ('the polonian church seek union', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eutychianisme', 'ORG'): 1; ('conscientia spectare qui', 'FAC'): 1; ('Davē', 'GPE'): 1; ('adhort', 'GPE'): 1; ('ad frat con inter e•an e•cl', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('meek', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('noluit hāc laudem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('versae parti concedere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod pacis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam ipse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Marperg', 'ORG'): 1; ('outstrip', 'GPE'): 1; ('Netherlands', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('239', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Casaub', 'ORG'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('hitherto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('innumeris', 'GPE'): 1; ('publi•h', 'ORG'): 1; ('Europae', 'NORP'): 1; ('173', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1"
A72333,1,tainen Issa ground weeper eye cunning heaven word grant suit,woman: 0.5; saint: 0.5; sinner: 0.5; book: 0.5; self: 0.5; gospel: 0.5; magdalene: 0.5; marie: 0.4; paul: 0.35; man: 0.35; censure: 0.1; thing: 0.1; cap: 0.1; act: 0.05; lib: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Magdalene', 'PERSON'): 3; ('saint luke', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('marie Magdalene', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Luc', 'DATE'): 2; ('Martha', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Issa', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'PERSON'): 1; ('W. H.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Andrew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('1639', 'DATE'): 1; ('proem', 'GPE'): 1; ('captu lectoris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('W. H. sancta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('I. saint luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('8.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pauls', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theol', 'GPE'): 1; ('66', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Evangelii', 'ORG'): 1; ('Alstedius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Coloss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Theologus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eusebius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Theodotus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Laodicea', 'ORG'): 1; ('Euseb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Apostolorum', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bois', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lorinus', 'GPE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ambros', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rehoboam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Barlaeus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mens assueta operi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mille volumina soler ambulat', 'ORG'): 1; ('Natur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('propè', 'PERSON'): 1; ('incomparabile quiddam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pliny', 'ORG'): 1; ('Arachne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mihi soli', 'ORG'): 1; ('Danaides', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('4.13', 'MONEY'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('pallados aula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deliciae', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bibliotheca', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae', 'ORG'): 1; ('clausa angustiis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latitudine coeli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae plus habent subtilitatis quàm utilitatis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('athenian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Orig', 'GPE'): 1; ('35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Origen', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Magdalen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stapulensis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Amb', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('only one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Albertus', 'NORP'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Lazarus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bethanie', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ecce mulier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Janus', 'LOC'): 1"
A72333,7,sect Iii sinner be sinner be nonlatinalphabet admiration man sinner,sin: 0.4; man: 0.4; sinner: 0.4; woman: 0.4; thing: 0.35; father: 0.35; saint: 0.3; aliud: 0.3; god: 0.3; adam: 0.3; lust: 0.2; custom: 0.2; please: 0.1; pillar: 0.1; prolapsion: 0.1; practice: 0.1; pollution: 0.1; poison: 0.1; poet: 0.1; publican: 0.1; place: 0.1; philosopher: 0.1; motion: 0.05; king: 0.05,"('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paulinus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('dam mihi aliquem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Quintilian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Amsterdam', 'GPE'): 1; ('multis', 'GPE'): 1; ('James 3.2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Solomons', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ʋriah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('15.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sin hourly', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.46', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sam 15.18', 'PERSON'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 3.9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James 1.14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('hospitibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('a thousand ton', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Gerson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet habet', 'ORG'): 1; ('admirationis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Chemnitius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sinon', 'FAC'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('qualis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Conzen', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aug. de civit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Epirus', 'ORG'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('Narcissus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ipse sibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mediis qui', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A72333,11,penitent cunning aftergame sinner recovery part God saint bed sin,ointment: 0.5; woman: 0.5; god: 0.5; saviour: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; repentance: 0.5; time: 0.35; jesus: 0.35; christ: 0.3; heaven: 0.25; house: 0.2; soul: 0.15; sin: 0.1; length: 0.1; sinner: 0.05; way: 0.05; pharisee: 0.05; deep: 0.05,"('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hezekiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('peteret regem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mutius Scevola', 'ORG'): 1; ('Porsenna', 'GPE'): 1; ('Magdalene', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Miriam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Buchan', 'GPE'): 1; ('42', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the cool spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('Infixa', 'GPE'): 1; ('sagitta', 'GPE'): 1; ('Salmeron', 'ORG'): 1; ('Turbata erat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('piscina', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'ORG'): 1; ('publican', 'NORP'): 1; ('Zaccheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Episcop', 'ORG'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Simon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisees', 'GPE'): 1; ('espy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the greek church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Luc', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 2.23', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('John 7.46', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the golden cymbal', 'LOC'): 1; ('non nisi', 'GPE'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 1; ('marie mourn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nardus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three hundred penny', 'MONEY'): 1"
A72333,13,story order step Evangelist part story thing repentance sweetness comfort,shame: 0.45; fear: 0.45; tear: 0.45; sin: 0.45; god: 0.45; sorrow: 0.45; foot: 0.45; eye: 0.45; repentance: 0.4; hand: 0.2; self: 0.15; head: 0.1; poet: 0.05; plato: 0.05; presence: 0.05; pompey: 0.05; pomp: 0.05; poison: 0.05; price: 0.05; plut: 0.05; physician: 0.05; pity: 0.05; face: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Evangelist', 'ORG'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('3.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pompey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Plut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('31.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Absalon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jewish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('Philo', 'GPE'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Philo', 'NORP'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laban', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 1; ('Esau', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('stetit retrò', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('51.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('avert faciem tuam', 'ORG'): 1; ('domine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('affectus perfectivus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('56.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('Siloam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bethesda', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zevecotius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Magdala', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vincta', 'GPE'): 1; ('solvendam domini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jacis ante', 'PERSON'): 1; ('unda tagi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('illi etenim solum volvunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gemma tuis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Interdum', 'NORP'): 1; ('pondera vocis habent', 'ORG'): 1"
A76549,3,premise church God age bath make David psalter part devotion,devotion: 0.5; psalm: 0.5; prayer: 0.5; church: 0.5; god: 0.5; psalter: 0.5; david: 0.45; christendom: 0.45; charity: 0.35; communion: 0.25; saint: 0.2; collect: 0.1; christ: 0.1; form: 0.05; man: 0.05,"('David', 'PERSON'): 11; ('Christendom', 'ORG'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Nicene', 'ORG'): 2; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Antwerp', 'GPE'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every week', 'DATE'): 1; ('Suidas', 'GPE'): 1; ('Alexandria', 'GPE'): 1; ('sai•h Philo', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Ignatius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Flavianus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Diodorus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rusticus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gregory', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ancona', 'GPE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ravenna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Hierome', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Athanasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('some eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernardine', 'ORG'): 1; ('western church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Salvatoris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hymno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('119', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('psalm ad verbum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tertullian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('B. Hippolytus', 'ORG'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Paul and Silas', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prudentius', 'ORG'): 1; ('p•o', 'GPE'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Flendo', 'ORG'): 1; ('S. Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quas sudi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ecclesiae', 'ORG'): 1; ('meae', 'ORG'): 1; ('instituti huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 1; ('minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('Socinian', 'NORP'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('George Cassander', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1545', 'DATE'): 1; ('litany', 'GPE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A76549,52,O God father child spouse church saviour redeemer mankind mercy,mercy: 0.5; jesus: 0.5; soul: 0.5; god: 0.5; lord: 0.5; bless: 0.45; grace: 0.45; servant: 0.35; father: 0.3; christ: 0.2; bishop: 0.2; life: 0.15; spirit: 0.1; end: 0.1; power: 0.05; church: 0.05; blessing: 0.05; cup: 0.05,"('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 7; ('thou', 'GPE'): 7; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 3; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Hester', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Rebeccah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sarah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('x.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('xi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Xii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Xiii', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tobias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('night', 'TIME'): 1; ('xiv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xv', 'PERSON'): 1; ('xvi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('the ministry of thy word', 'ORG'): 1; ('the ministry of thy kingdom', 'ORG'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sanctus Immortalis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('John Brinsley', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('E. C.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joseph Cranford', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1660', 'DATE'): 1; ('Brinsley', 'PERSON'): 1"
A77498,4 | 11493,way reprehension Applic. exhortation reprehension affliction way reprehension eye bless,father: 0.4; god: 0.4; hand: 0.4; people: 0.4; affliction: 0.4; lord: 0.35; child: 0.35; spirit: 0.35; heart: 0.35; time: 0.3; relation: 0.15; plunder: 0.1; pledge: 0.1; prodigal: 0.1; principal: 0.1; priest: 0.1; prescribe: 0.1; prayer: 0.1; potter: 0.1; potion: 0.1; prophet: 0.1; affection: 0.1; suffering: 0.05,"('David', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Jer', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Luk', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 2; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 2; ('64.7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'DATE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8.15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Abba', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Applic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('spring', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('39.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.3 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('53.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etiam quum', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ferus Annot', 'ORG'): 1; ('63.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chapt', 'LOC'): 1; ('32.40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 1; ('2.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thy arrow', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32.4 .', 'DATE'): 1; ('Lam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sit licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Parentum', 'GPE'): 1; ('89.31', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('54.7', 'DATE'): 1; ('Josephs bowel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Simeon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('42.24', 'MONEY'): 1; ('31.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('63.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3.6 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8.35', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('31.9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('89.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('3.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Romans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Galathian , Gal', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('6.6 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('24.11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('26.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('63.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('46.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('27.34', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A70635,12,water Richmond Windsor journey Woodstock servant other side man word,god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; page: 0.5; vol: 0.5; fox: 0.5; lord: 0.5; foot: 0.5; word: 0.35; death: 0.3; man: 0.3; sin: 0.2; world: 0.1; bishop: 0.1; ask: 0.05; burn: 0.05; farewell: 0.05,"('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Eulalia', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Richmond', 'GPE'): 1; ('Windsor', 'GPE'): 1; ('Woodstock', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Woodstock', 'GPE'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Esch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry Voes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Brussels', 'GPE'): 1; ('1523', 'DATE'): 1; ('101', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('102', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Emerita', 'FAC'): 1; ('Portugal', 'GPE'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('120', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('thou hangman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve year of age', 'DATE'): 1; ('160', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christopher Fabrianus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('155', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tha•', 'GPE'): 1; ('•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Clark', 'PERSON'): 1; ('674', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('William Farellus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('fox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('216', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Richard Jones', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Robert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Richard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julian Leville', 'PERSON'): 1; ('France', 'GPE'): 1; ('595', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('144', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fillula', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Fillula', 'PERSON'): 1; ('153', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Henry Filmer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Testwood', 'PERSON'): 1; ('555', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('William', 'PERSON'): 1; ('242', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bonner', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('832', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A70635,14 | 13312,provost Monsieur Brez notice day God goodness provost news bring,god: 0.5; christ: 0.5; man: 0.5; lord: 0.5; life: 0.5; mr: 0.4; love: 0.35; blood: 0.3; self: 0.3; world: 0.25; death: 0.25; faith: 0.2; father: 0.15; body: 0.15; heaven: 0.1; paul: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 22; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 10; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('christian', 'NORP'): 6; ('Pa.', 'GPE'): 4; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Pag', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hussey', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jane', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Mary', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Fecknam', 'GPE'): 2; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 2; ('daily', 'DATE'): 2; ('Monsieur de Brez', 'ORG'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Monsieur la Grange', 'PERSON'): 1; ('43', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('monsieur la Grange', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Brez', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephen Gratwick', 'PERSON'): 1; ('790', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('therein triumph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pa. 792', 'GPE'): 1; ('Sunday', 'DATE'): 1; ('arrian', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sacramentarians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Winchester', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('fox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('622', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Glutrony', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vale', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mei memineris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bartram', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Newgate Jan. 20', 'EVENT'): 1; ('1556', 'DATE'): 1; ('623', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('welsh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James 1.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Newgate', 'ORG'): 1; ('627', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('green', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christe Deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mihi nulla salutis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nego', 'PERSON'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('besi•es', 'NORP'): 1; ('628', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fleetwood', 'ORG'): 1; ('Fernham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Richardson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('palmer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('J.', 'ORG'): 1; ('Traiford', 'ORG'): 1; ('Thomas Witton', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lombardstreet', 'GPE'): 1; ('bowyer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cooper', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Berard the Frenchman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Monday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bartlet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Elizabeth Clark', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anna', 'GPE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hanna', 'ORG'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('629', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Copes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('every hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Suffolk', 'GPE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Henry the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('ten day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Fecknam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two day', 'DATE'): 1; ('31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('Harding', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Judah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('nourish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Babylon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israelite', 'ORG'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Amicitia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi inter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('publican', 'NORP'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Julian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Spira', 'GPE'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1"
A70635,14 | 13342,night sister lady Katherine testament end send sister book trim,god: 0.35; life: 0.35; christ: 0.35; death: 0.35; lord: 0.35; hand: 0.35; mercy: 0.3; priest: 0.2; church: 0.2; blood: 0.2; payment: 0.15; paul: 0.15; pharaoh: 0.15; persecute: 0.15; people: 0.15; penitent: 0.15; plague: 0.15; outcry: 0.15; page: 0.15; possession: 0.15; sin: 0.15; fox: 0.15; body: 0.05; vol: 0.05; night: 0.05; book: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 2; ('Harman', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Katherine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('midnight', 'TIME'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('deliverer', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 1; ('four hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('60', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('h•dierna mihi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 1; ('nil nocet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('H. Haggar', 'PERSON'): 1; ('A. 1520', 'DATE'): 1; ('44', 'DATE'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bristol', 'ORG'): 1; ('892', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('these two year', 'DATE'): 1; ('A. 1557', 'DATE'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('catholic', 'NORP'): 1; ('Hallewin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cornelius Hallewin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antwerp', 'GPE'): 1; ('Cont', 'GPE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Flemish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Cornelius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amsterdam', 'GPE'): 1"
A70635,15 | 13423,letter mr. Pa. Throgmorton love God move son bring eye,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; church: 0.5; christ: 0.5; death: 0.5; lord: 0.5; mr: 0.5; word: 0.5; pa: 0.45; law: 0.4; thing: 0.05; bring: 0.05; people: 0.05,"('Pa.', 'GPE'): 9; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('hus', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Hierome', 'GPE'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Herwyn', 'ORG'): 2; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Hierome', 'PERSON'): 2; ('a hundred year', 'DATE'): 2; ('830', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('fox', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Roger', 'PERSON'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('holland', 'PERSON'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 2; ('268', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('inn Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('155', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Brimston', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julian Hernaudes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('spanish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('spanish', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('John Herwyn', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ba•liffe', 'NORP'): 1; ('Houscot', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bailiff', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('10.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('brethren', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nov. 4', 'DATE'): 1; ('1560', 'DATE'): 1; ('524', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('William Hierome', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stepney', 'GPE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('527', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('528', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Prague', 'GPE'): 1; ('Constance', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 1; ('832', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bohemis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Pa. 833', 'GPE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('834', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('he may 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('1416', 'DATE'): 1; ('835', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Plato', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anaxagoras', 'GPE'): 1; ('Zeno', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Boetius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Baptist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Stephen', 'GPE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('836', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('g•d', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a•', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Londy', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hussi', 'GPE'): 1; ('837', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cap', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pa. 838', 'GPE'): 1; ('Clarks Mart', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eccl', 'GPE'): 1; ('223', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John Hus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hist', 'ORG'): 1; ('539', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Poggius', 'ORG'): 1; ('the council of Constance', 'ORG'): 1; ('Leonard Aretine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three hundred and', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one hour', 'TIME'): 1; ('Poggius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('152', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('holland', 'GPE'): 1; ('Roger Holland', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Holland', 'GPE'): 1; ('kinsman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('875', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bonner', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Felix', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('876', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nicholas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elias day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Baal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pa. 877', 'GPE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Swithfield', 'GPE'): 1; ('878', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('John Hooper', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Somerset', 'GPE'): 1; ('1547', 'DATE'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this many year', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 4.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('testimon•es', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 11', 'LAW'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John describe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apocalypse', 'PERSON'): 1; ('animantibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('salva•n', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Basil , Ambrose , Epiphanius , A•gustine', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1"
A70398,12,regard assembly title pope reverence assembly complea exhortation power hypocrite,king: 0.5; covenant: 0.5; parliament: 0.5; conscience: 0.5; word: 0.5; protestation: 0.5; scruple: 0.45; consent: 0.4; argument: 0.3; assembly: 0.3; god: 0.25; bishop: 0.15; oath: 0.1; liberty: 0.05,"('second', 'ORDINAL'): 13; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 12; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Scotland', 'GPE'): 4; ('England', 'GPE'): 4; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Oddy', 'PERSON'): 4; ('m. Kaye', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 4; ('Ezra', 'PERSON'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Nehemiah', 'PERSON'): 3; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('quae', 'GPE'): 2; ('Scot', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jacobs', 'ORG'): 2; ('sixthly', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Germany', 'GPE'): 1; ('cratche', 'ORG'): 1; ('braseni', 'NORP'): 1; ('Timothy be ordain', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Neb. 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('mer•z curse', 'GPE'): 1; ('Anabaptists', 'NORP'): 1; ('Zanchius', 'ORG'): 1; ('grati•n', 'ORG'): 1; ('Apostole', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('coll•quiis', 'ORG'): 1; ('magistratu habentur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('supreme judicatory .', 'ORG'): 1; ('suprem•cy', 'DATE'): 1; ('bona verba', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isaac', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Esau', 'GPE'): 1; ('frigidum afflare', 'FAC'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scots', 'ORG'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Conira', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Neh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.36', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('37', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('th••', 'ORG'): 1; ('supreme judicatory', 'ORG'): 1; ('scottish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prelacy', 'PERSON'): 1"
A77290,4 | 14579,mention ministry ordain God place fall ministry church name witness,god: 0.5; ministry: 0.5; church: 0.5; time: 0.5; gospel: 0.5; thing: 0.5; word: 0.45; witness: 0.4; bishop: 0.35; part: 0.35; lord: 0.3; antichrist: 0.1; spirit: 0.05,"('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 7; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('ten', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11.7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('William Sawtrey', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Walter Brutus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('God , 1260 day prophetical year', 'DATE'): 1; ('12.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('their day', 'DATE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('17.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('•h•ch', 'GPE'): 1; ('John Huss', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Sawtrey', 'PERSON'): 1; ('English', 'NORP'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('Thomas Arundel 1399', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Maryes', 'GPE'): 1; ('Maniple', 'LOC'): 1; ('Paten', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Crosier', 'PERSON'): 1; ('another day', 'DATE'): 1; ('16.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about 1393', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('Apocalypse', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Merlinus Calcedenius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Joannes Wolfius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('genitus', 'ORG'): 1; ('aequus Pastor', 'ORG'): 1; ('coeli', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bridget', 'ORG'): 1; ('italian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Scissa', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Paris', 'GPE'): 1; ('Savanorala', 'PERSON'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 7.1', 'LAW'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the ministry of Edmundsbury', 'ORG'): 1; ('one half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antichristus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ecce ego mittam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Prophetam', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eliah', 'ORG'): 1; ('Elias', 'PERSON'): 1; ('pope', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1"
A70351,3,Caesar throne sword justice Jehova arm danger harm angel legion,god: 0.4; ceremony: 0.4; worship: 0.4; man: 0.4; religion: 0.4; treatise: 0.4; word: 0.35; commandment: 0.25; warrant: 0.25; sign: 0.2; minister: 0.15; question: 0.1; print: 0.1; pride: 0.1; protestation: 0.1; proposition: 0.1; pronounce: 0.1; printed: 0.1; puritan: 0.1; prince: 0.1; precept: 0.1; presbyter: 0.1; king: 0.1; doctrine: 0.05; surplice: 0.05; effect: 0.05; nature: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('1605', 'DATE'): 4; ('1604', 'DATE'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 2; ('Whigs', 'PERSON'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 2; ('Positions Archiepiscopal', 'ORG'): 2; ('England', 'GPE'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lev', 'PERSON'): 2; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jehova', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pursell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('jack', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('William Bradshaw', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sidney', 'ORG'): 1; ('Chattam', 'GPE'): 1; ('1601', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('English Puritanism', 'NORP'): 1; ('Puritan', 'GPE'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Oxford', 'ORG'): 1; ('Westminster', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1660', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('29.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26.5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('outward', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 15.9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('outward gesture', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mat 5.14', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Sect', 'PERSON'): 1"
A77236,61,treatise cross baptism contract syllogisme use idol God service use,idol: 0.4; cross: 0.4; image: 0.4; worship: 0.4; sign: 0.4; use: 0.4; god: 0.4; christ: 0.4; church: 0.3; lib: 0.15; cap: 0.15; idolatry: 0.15; portiforium: 0.1; popery: 0.1; prince: 0.1; precept: 0.1; power: 0.1; posterity: 0.1; profess: 0.1; picture: 0.1; place: 0.1; proof: 0.1; service: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 2; ('John', 'PERSON'): 2; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Tertullian', 'GPE'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Bellarmine', 'GPE'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the year 1660', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 5.21', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Idoli', 'GPE'): 1; ('10.15 10.13', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gideons', 'LAW'): 1; ('crown', 'ORG'): 1; ('religionis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 1; ('England Homil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('16.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ursin', 'GPE'): 1; ('martyr loc', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hooper', 'FAC'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bagington', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Allen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Psal', 'NORP'): 1; ('idol', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('68', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('de Idololatria', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Epiphanius', 'NORP'): 1; ('johannem epūm', 'ORG'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('115.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('50.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bellarmine', 'ORG'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Portiforium', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Reynolds', 'PERSON'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('hart', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('hart no', 'LAW'): 1; ('Andra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aquin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aquinas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Costerus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Coster Enchri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Andradius', 'ORG'): 1"
A76178,21 | 17255,Thes. sovereign heretic man infidel heathen obey thing obedience authority,authority: 0.5; god: 0.5; power: 0.5; law: 0.5; man: 0.5; prince: 0.5; obedience: 0.4; sovereign: 0.35; thes: 0.3; king: 0.25; thing: 0.25; act: 0.2; case: 0.15; office: 0.1,"('nec', 'ORG'): 5; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('senate', 'ORG'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('330', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('331', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('f•r', 'NORP'): 1; ('22a', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. a. 10', 'PERCENT'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('ten thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('half', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('332', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Gunther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ligurin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('376', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cogitet', 'ORG'): 1; ('primaevi temporis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Num Petrus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Clemens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Sceptra Latina', 'PERSON'): 1; ('erat', 'NORP'): 1; ('jura Latini', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vel cuiquam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tantum cuiquam jus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romanus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vana figuris', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Otho', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hroswithae Histor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('101', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Reuberi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qualiter', 'DATE'): 1; ('zeli', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rectoris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('333', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('England', 'GPE'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Henry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('seventh', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('334', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('335', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('336', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('337', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('338', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('339', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('340', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('341', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('that|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('342', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('343', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('344', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Civit', 'GPE'): 1; ('li', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec jure fieri', 'ORG'): 1; ('jura dicenda', 'ORG'): 1; ('vel putanda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quaelibet iniqua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Quocirca', 'ORG'): 1; ('juris consensu', 'PERSON'): 1; ('populi', 'GPE'): 1; ('sed qualiscun', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('digna non est', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Respublica', 'PERSON'): 1; ('juris sociatus non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('two mile', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1"
A70781,18 | 19495,thing widow betroth person question use authority Sanchez sort person,pollution: 0.5; thing: 0.5; self: 0.5; desire: 0.5; sin: 0.5; page: 0.45; sum: 0.45; oblige: 0.45; man: 0.4; use: 0.35; theft: 0.2; person: 0.05; restitution: 0.05; opinion: 0.05; effect: 0.05,"('Jesuit', 'NORP'): 5; ('Sanchez', 'ORG'): 4; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Lessius', 'ORG'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Escobar', 'GPE'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('tenetur', 'GPE'): 2; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Filliur', 'NORP'): 1; ('extendunt ad omnem volupraris affectionem', 'ORG'): 1; ('etiam simplicis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. d .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('104', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('697', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bonum finem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('carnls', 'ORG'): 1; ('interdum', 'NORP'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('772', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('luxuria num', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('449', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('95', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('154', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Inchoatam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non ob delectationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec peceatum quidem', 'ORG'): 1; ('contra', 'ORG'): 1; ('105', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('R•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quidam volunt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('etiam de ipsa', 'ORG'): 1; ('licet', 'PERSON'): 1; ('licet de ca gaudere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('teneri neminem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ab equitation•', 'ORG'): 1; ('150', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('se honesta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('morem patriae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quando sine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Laicis', 'GPE'): 1; ('secularibus', 'GPE'): 1; ('necessaria est', 'GPE'): 1; ('nimio', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quam', 'NORP'): 1; ('contra', 'NORP'): 1; ('Layman lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('day', 'DATE'): 1; ('the night', 'TIME'): 1; ('procul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tambourin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jesuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('si nulli est domino', 'PERSON'): 1; ('usui futura', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sa verbo furtum', 'ORG'): 1; ('292', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quidam probabiliter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quando non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('totam summam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tenetur totam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('161', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('non ad totam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui notabilem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non teneri', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mortali totam restituere', 'PERSON'): 1; ('tom .', 'DATE'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('47', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('441', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ab ecdem domino', 'ORG'): 1; ('levem materiam usurpat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('peccat mortaliter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('233', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('257', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('chapter 10', 'LAW'): 1; ('143', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bauny handle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Emanuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('french', 'NORP'): 1; ('•um', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 13', 'LAW'): 1; ('185', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('186', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A75801,3,see writer subject learn accomplishment art observe practice experiment time,fruit: 0.45; man: 0.45; art: 0.45; tree: 0.45; argument: 0.45; thing: 0.45; profit: 0.45; work: 0.4; labour: 0.4; pleasure: 0.3; practice: 0.2; time: 0.05; god: 0.05; pleasantness: 0.05; place: 0.05; practic: 0.05; porch: 0.05; poet: 0.05; praise: 0.05; plant: 0.05; perfect: 0.05; phil: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'DATE'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('9.25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('twenty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('L. Ba.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('usus meditando', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Turpis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('86', 'DATE'): 1; ('Austen', 'PERSON'): 1; ('rob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('eight divine', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Uzziah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Susanna', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('5.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. Psal', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22.2 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five divine', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('Amos 4.9', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28.39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'DATE'): 1; ('29.5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Amos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Neh', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven divine', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Argum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.8 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A73533,2,write Christ hand heart injury count seducer judge traitor Caesar,jesus: 0.5; christ: 0.5; name: 0.5; god: 0.5; man: 0.5; saint: 0.5; saviour: 0.45; salvation: 0.4; glory: 0.4; title: 0.3; jew: 0.2; soul: 0.1; lord: 0.05; king: 0.05; cross: 0.05,"('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 45; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 10; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 9; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('Nazarenus', 'GPE'): 7; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 6; ('Nazareth', 'PERSON'): 6; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jew', 'PERSON'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Rex Iudaeorum', 'ORG'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('4.12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Iehoscua', 'ORG'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('1.47', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cyril', 'ORG'): 2; ('10.30', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 2; ('Caesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('Cruce', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ludibrium', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('23.24', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christiani', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pilate', 'ORG'): 1; ('three divine', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Salvator', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Floridus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Messiah', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Nazarenum', 'GPE'): 1; ('hebrew', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('greek', 'NORP'): 1; ('latin', 'NORP'): 1; ('grecian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Latines', 'ORG'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isaak', 'GPE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('mell', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Melos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Iubilus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Corde', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('insipidus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Sirach', 'GPE'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.29 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4.29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Elisha', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mount Carmel', 'ORG'): 1; ('magna miseria superbus homo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('humilis deus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'NORP'): 1; ('49.18', 'MONEY'): 1; ('Simeon', 'GPE'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2.30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 3.17', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mei percussi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ambr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('qui nihil habuit', 'ORG'): 1; ('pro se doleret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Romish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Sceva', 'ORG'): 1; ('19.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('sanguinem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quem de matre accepit', 'ORG'): 1; ('alligavit fortem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Carne', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Thomas', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20 28', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Jericho', 'GPE'): 1; ('Samaritan', 'FAC'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('affectibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('threefold', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 1.14', 'DATE'): 1; ('1.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sed nomini tuo da gloriam .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Turk', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus of Nazareth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gabriel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Nazarites', 'GPE'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A75732,4 | 20858,law judgement property law consequence person age nation law judgement,power: 0.5; law: 0.4; christ: 0.4; god: 0.4; king: 0.4; judgement: 0.4; realm: 0.4; angel: 0.4; britain: 0.35; man: 0.3; kingdom: 0.15; place: 0.1; peter: 0.1; pope: 0.1; point: 0.1; prince: 0.1; perfection: 0.1; person: 0.1; psal: 0.1; persuade: 0.1,"('Britain', 'GPE'): 7; ('Lucius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('22.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Europe', 'LOC'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Eleutherius', 'GPE'): 1; ('fox', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('169', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eleutherius Papa', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucio Regi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ad correctionem regis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('god grace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the council of your realm', 'ORG'): 1; ('deus judicium tuum', 'GPE'): 1; ('regi da', 'PERSON'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('concord', 'GPE'): 1; ('Eleutherius', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('the three century', 'DATE'): 1; ('a hundred year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'ORG'): 1; ('forty day', 'DATE'): 1; ('he|will', 'NORP'): 1; ('19 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 44', 'DATE'): 1; ('2. 10 , 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand and six hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1"
A76967,4,joy prayer need thank obtain need ill sadness sin use,man: 0.5; heart: 0.5; action: 0.5; time: 0.5; god: 0.5; work: 0.45; body: 0.45; passion: 0.3; lord: 0.3; psalm: 0.3; soul: 0.25; joy: 0.15; way: 0.15; mirth: 0.1; duty: 0.05,"('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 8; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('James', 'PERSON'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('135.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('147.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('5.25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'GPE'): 1; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('100.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('107', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('64.51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('35.21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('25.11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Samuel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wttnesse', 'ORG'): 1; ('12.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('14.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('liquorem', 'GPE'): 1; ('payday', 'DATE'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('57.20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one day', 'DATE'): 1; ('24.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cicero', 'ORG'): 1; ('laetari', 'GPE'): 1; ('contristari', 'ORG'): 1; ('Interior', 'ORG'): 1; ('it|be', 'ORG'): 1"
A76967,5 | 22664,affliction think misery thing mercy condition bless man afflict Eliphaz,soul: 0.45; man: 0.45; body: 0.45; thing: 0.45; god: 0.45; affliction: 0.45; lord: 0.45; psal: 0.45; part: 0.35; heart: 0.2; time: 0.1; spirit: 0.1; way: 0.1; plenty: 0.05; place: 0.05; prepare: 0.05; prayer: 0.05; pract: 0.05; power: 0.05; poverty: 0.05; poet: 0.05; price: 0.05; pleasure: 0.05; say: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 2; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 2; ('5.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a very few minute', 'TIME'): 1; ('Rome', 'GPE'): 1; ('8.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'DATE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('all this year', 'DATE'): 1; ('next year', 'DATE'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('equidem', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quam vinculum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('libertati meae', 'ORG'): 1; ('65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Terreni', 'NORP'): 1; ('11.1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('that day', 'DATE'): 1; ('6.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anaxarchi', 'ORG'): 1; ('Beatrice', 'ORG'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('138', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3', 'DATE'): 1; ('thou', 'NORP'): 1; ('11.12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('4.8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('25.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('12.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('69', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('121.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10.3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13.7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psal 63.10', 'LAW'): 1; ('thou', 'GPE'): 1; ('41.2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Catech', 'NORP'): 1; ('D. Hammond', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('84', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('34.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1.10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a penny', 'MONEY'): 1; ('A. Gellius', 'NORP'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('multis', 'NORP'): 1; ('illis', 'GPE'): 1; ('Homer', 'PERSON'): 1"
A76394,3,reader reason print copy intercept Cavaleeris God love man man,covenant: 0.35; god: 0.35; discourse: 0.35; man: 0.35; grace: 0.35; reader: 0.3; right: 0.25; truth: 0.25; marge: 0.25; way: 0.15; heart: 0.15; please: 0.15; pointing: 0.15; paradise: 0.15; part: 0.15; paul: 0.15; peace: 0.15; persuasion: 0.15; perusal: 0.15; piece: 0.15; place: 0.15; subject: 0.1; self: 0.1; scripture: 0.1; day: 0.05; blot: 0.05,"('9', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('31', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('24', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('l.', 'PERSON'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Cavaleeris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Barret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('R.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jonathan Robinson', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the golden lion', 'FAC'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the apostle day', 'DATE'): 1; ('our day', 'DATE'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Tim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thirteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Pag', 'ORG'): 1; ('225', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('297', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Laert', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Socrate', 'ORG'): 1; ('111', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Aeschines', 'ORG'): 1; ('Socrates', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8.5 .', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jehu to Jehonadab', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('J. B. Addenda', 'PERSON'): 1; ('corrigenda', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('niti', 'GPE'): 1; ('61', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. 2', 'PERSON'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('div', 'PERSON'): 1; ('76', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('93', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. ult .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('137', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('152', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('162', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('cur', 'ORG'): 1; ('164', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('174', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ac', 'ORG'): 1; ('213', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('232', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('guileless', 'PERSON'): 1; ('233', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('235', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('245', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('247', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('253', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('279', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('282', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. •13', 'PERSON'): 1; ('285', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('300', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('306', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('307', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('321', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('322', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('326', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('424', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('429', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quatefaciendam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('405', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('maymony', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('385', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('l. 4', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Baxt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bapt', 'ORG'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('99', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2.17', 'MONEY'): 1; ('the day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('ibi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('alia mihi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('totius', 'NORP'): 1"
A77245,42,T. H. postscript argument man wit learning contrary opinion thing,god: 0.5; error: 0.5; christian: 0.5; man: 0.5; religion: 0.5; truth: 0.5; faculty: 0.45; word: 0.4; manner: 0.25; ear: 0.25; world: 0.2; justice: 0.2; action: 0.15; nature: 0.05; cause: 0.05,"('T. H.', 'PERSON'): 6; ('christian', 'NORP'): 5; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 2; ('Galieni', 'NORP'): 2; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Heb', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('dulce canit', 'ORG'): 1; ('volucrem dum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('decipit auceps', 'PERSON'): 1; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Molech', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tophet', 'GPE'): 1; ('million', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tophet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1.27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Salomon', 'ORG'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12.13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('28', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('14.19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('caesaris jussum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quod colit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('factorem dominum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('finis', 'NORP'): 1; ('ARMILLA CATECHETICA', 'PERSON'): 1; ('John Arrowsmith', 'PERSON'): 1; ('D.', 'NORP'): 1; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 1; ('Regius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('the university of Cambridge', 'ORG'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'DATE'): 1; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1659', 'DATE'): 1; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Fleetstreet', 'ORG'): 1; ('Dunstan', 'GPE'): 1; ('London', 'GPE'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('3. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A75616,8,aphorisme IV. goodness greatness attribute multitude divine perfection exercitation Exerc.,god: 0.5; mercy: 0.5; lord: 0.5; grace: 0.5; goodness: 0.5; bowel: 0.5; world: 0.5; man: 0.45; love: 0.45; heart: 0.35; sin: 0.25,"('thou', 'GPE'): 11; ('§', 'NORP'): 10; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 3; ('Hos', 'ORG'): 3; ('Isai', 'ORG'): 3; ('Jerem', 'PERSON'): 3; ('17', 'DATE'): 3; ('grace', 'PERSON'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Exerc', 'ORG'): 2; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 2; ('145', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jehovah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Jonah', 'GPE'): 2; ('2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Ephes', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('103', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Titus 2', 'LAW'): 2; ('12', 'DATE'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 2; ('aphorisme IV.', 'ORG'): 1; ('34. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('bowel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jupiter', 'LOC'): 1; ('optimus maximus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('one hundred forty five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('every day', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('egyptian', 'NORP'): 1; ('thou', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('63', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ludovic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('Elohim Abarbanel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Joann', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Buxtorf', 'NORP'): 1; ('Dissertat', 'GPE'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'DATE'): 1; ('viscera recepit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('33. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Benjamin', 'ORG'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Admah', 'GPE'): 1; ('63.', 'DATE'): 1; ('49.', 'DATE'): 1; ('eighteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('18. 1', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ezekiel', 'GPE'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('4. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('Bernard .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Erasmus', 'ORG'): 1; ('concione de misericordia', 'ORG'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('lo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('whereunto', 'NORP'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeremiah', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hosea', 'GPE'): 1; ('14. 3', 'DATE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('27. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('24. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('R.', 'NORP'): 1; ('87', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'DATE'): 1; ('6. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Esau', 'GPE'): 1; ('33. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Ephesians', 'NORP'): 1; ('1. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ibid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('Barnabas', 'ORG'): 1; ('21.', 'DATE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('15.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Eph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('16', 'DATE'): 1; ('Arminian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Familist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nine hundred ninety', 'DATE'): 1; ('nine', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('tota repellitur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi tota', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('elegit ab aevo', 'ORG'): 1; ('acta synod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4o', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('293', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 1; ('Gratia', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gloria sola', 'PERSON'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jericho', 'GPE'): 1; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Gentiles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('more than thirty year old', 'DATE'): 1; ('fifty', 'DATE'): 1; ('sixty year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Habakkuk', 'GPE'): 1; ('2. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'GPE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A75616,9,aphorisme V. goodness greatness God manifest decree election preterition work,god: 0.5; person: 0.5; man: 0.5; life: 0.5; act: 0.5; decree: 0.5; election: 0.5; world: 0.4; say: 0.4; name: 0.2; thing: 0.15; faith: 0.15; divine: 0.05; christ: 0.05; saint: 0.05; predestination: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 13; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 11; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 8; ('§', 'NORP'): 8; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 8; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 5; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('Tit', 'PERSON'): 3; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 3; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Grotius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11.', 'DATE'): 2; ('1. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 2; ('25', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('48', 'DATE'): 2; ('lin', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 2; ('34', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Erasmus', 'PRODUCT'): 2; ('thou', 'GPE'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('greek', 'NORP'): 2; ('aequalibus', 'ORG'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('saint luke', 'PERSON'): 2; ('three thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('one day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 2; ('aphorisme V. the', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Exerc', 'ORG'): 1; ('election describe', 'PERSON'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 24 , 25', 'DATE'): 1; ('Aph', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae deus occulta esse voluit', 'ORG'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('monifesta fecit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('illis', 'GPE'): 1; ('istis damnabiliter', 'NORP'): 1; ('de vocar .', 'PERSON'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('243', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('278', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('46', 'DATE'): 1; ('T. P.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('97', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Electi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 10. 26 ,', 'PERSON'): 1; ('28', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'DATE'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('11. 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('Arminius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Titus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Johns', 'ORG'): 1; ('John 17', 'PERSON'): 1; ('as many as thou', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('vitam aeternam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('e•m', 'ORG'): 1; ('etiam paciscendo de ea', 'ORG'): 1; ('David Dicson Exp', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Tit', 'GPE'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('l. de Praedestin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Timothy and Titus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Scotish', 'NORP'): 1; ('Austin', 'GPE'): 1; ('facti sumus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('electi sumus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('st luke', 'PERSON'): 1; ('st John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apocalypse', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('6. 10 , 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('a little season', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('about one hundred and twenty', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('seven thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('morrow', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Novit', 'ORG'): 1; ('9 15 , 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 19', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('Josiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('three hundred and', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Scultetus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Esai', 'PERSON'): 1; ('45', 'DATE'): 1; ('623', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('one hundred and', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Procopius Procopius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Misdates', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 1; ('persian', 'NORP'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('st Peter', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('35', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hephzibah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Persona', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Seneca', 'GPE'): 1; ('Proserpina', 'ORG'): 1; ('tuo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('63', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Conclus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Leviticus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Levit', 'GPE'): 1; ('18. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet righteous judgement', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet Rom', 'ORG'): 1; ('98', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('157', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4o', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('maxim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('dvobus', 'ORG'): 1; ('quem praescivit pluribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('gravionibus', 'ORG'): 1; ('relicto', 'PERSON'): 1; ('leviora', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1am', 'TIME'): 1; ('51', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('injusta', 'PERSON'): 1; ('circumstantiam quae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('causam meriti', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vero deus', 'ORG'): 1; ('justiti•e', 'ORG'): 1; ('aut aliam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('licet mihi quod velo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Davenantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Praedestin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Reprobat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('133', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nihil vident', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chrys', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter ministry', 'ORG'): 1; ('Paul', 'ORG'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luke', 'PERSON'): 1"
A75616,9 | 24782,product election happiness object decree God appoint wrath salvation lord,god: 0.5; election: 0.5; thing: 0.5; say: 0.45; lord: 0.45; grace: 0.45; love: 0.4; book: 0.4; choose: 0.35; decree: 0.3; life: 0.25; man: 0.2; name: 0.15; sin: 0.05; favour: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 11; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 10; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 9; ('§', 'NORP'): 8; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 8; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 7; ('thou', 'GPE'): 7; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 4; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Ephes', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Leah', 'ORG'): 3; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('11', 'DATE'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('1. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('•um', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14', 'DATE'): 2; ('Christum', 'GPE'): 2; ('Jesus 1 Thes', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pilate', 'ORG'): 1; ('19 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('2.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 24', 'DATE'): 1; ('25', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'DATE'): 1; ('Christianity', 'NORP'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('10. five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('quod quaeris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('homil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('38', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Melancthon', 'GPE'): 1; ('dulcescet nostra de predestination', 'ORG'): 1; ('impiae rationis judicium spiritus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11. 55', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hieron', 'ORG'): 1; ('dignare', 'ORG'): 1; ('tu ista nescire', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quae', 'GPE'): 1; ('sed ta•e', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non judica', 'GPE'): 1; ('sed audi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'GPE'): 1; ('9 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('hoard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('God', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Exerc', 'ORG'): 1; ('hominem de cunctis', 'ORG'): 1; ('thirteenth', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('secreti huius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('17. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('9 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('egreditur', 'GPE'): 1; ('Calvin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 1; ('Esau Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Rachel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('30 , 31', 'DATE'): 1; ('Esau', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('quantum', 'ORG'): 1; ('1.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Peter Lombard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi forte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('sententiarum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dist', 'NORP'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('13. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('10 , 13', 'DATE'): 1; ('15', 'DATE'): 1; ('John 10', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('20. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('english', 'NORP'): 1; ('Davenant', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Cambridge', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ann', 'PERSON'): 1; ('1641', 'DATE'): 1; ('John bishop', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Salisbury', 'GPE'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('1. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Thess', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ephes', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('1. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plato', 'PERSON'): 1; ('eight', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Noah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 8', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sodom', 'ORG'): 1; ('Gomorrah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 19', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('1 Thess', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('20.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cor', 'ORG'): 1; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Fr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('19 four', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('8. 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vocatio', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tertius', 'GPE'): 1; ('Justificatio', 'GPE'): 1; ('Quartus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Tom 7.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('177', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('chapter 31', 'LAW'): 1; ('Zacheus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jericho', 'GPE'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Chaldeans', 'NORP'): 1; ('Nicodemus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dionysius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Damaris', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Athens', 'GPE'): 1; ('8.', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zechary', 'GPE'): 1; ('Joshuah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Zechar', 'GPE'): 1; ('3. 34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('behold', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Satan', 'FAC'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('1. 3. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('John 6', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the last day', 'DATE'): 1; ('Hom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('46', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A75616,9 | 24828,pattern man make call image So God Gen. create man,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; image: 0.5; spirit: 0.5; soul: 0.45; world: 0.45; lord: 0.45; prosperity: 0.4; dust: 0.35; gen: 0.3; body: 0.3; adversity: 0.1; thing: 0.1; son: 0.05; saint: 0.05,"('2', 'CARDINAL'): 10; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 8; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('§', 'NORP'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('the day', 'DATE'): 4; ('§', 'PERSON'): 4; ('wherein', 'PERSON'): 4; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 3; ('Theodosius', 'ORG'): 2; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('third', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('six', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Nehem', 'GPE'): 2; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 2; ('11', 'DATE'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 2; ('Ezechiah', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14.', 'DATE'): 2; ('2. 11', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 2; ('27', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('mos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hebraeis', 'ORG'): 1; ('videantur', 'GPE'): 1; ('epitheti significationem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Andr', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Exercit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('similitudinem', 'GPE'): 1; ('9 6', 'DATE'): 1; ('James', 'PERSON'): 1; ('James 3', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Antioch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Theodor', 'ORG'): 1; ('5.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Placilla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Macedonius', 'NORP'): 1; ('one hundred', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Colos', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Heb', 'LOC'): 1; ('1. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christ', 'GPE'): 1; ('the six day', 'DATE'): 1; ('41', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Manilius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('apud Lip•', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Physiolog', 'GPE'): 1; ('English', 'LANGUAGE'): 1; ('Charron', 'ORG'): 1; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('twelve', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Amatorium', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('601', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Trinity', 'ORG'): 1; ('3 19', 'DATE'): 1; ('18. 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('Abraham', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Bernard', 'PERSON'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('Divinae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('aurae', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Elizabeth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 18', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Exerc', 'ORG'): 1; ('chapter 10. 11', 'LAW'): 1; ('Eccles 7', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mephibosheth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ziba of half', 'ORG'): 1; ('19 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'DATE'): 1; ('Sparta', 'GPE'): 1; ('174', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Plutarch', 'GPE'): 1; ('Persia', 'GPE'): 1; ('sepulchre', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Valens', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('arrian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Theodoret lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. 8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Christians', 'NORP'): 1; ('66.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Josephs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('105', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('41', 'MONEY'): 1; ('42', 'DATE'): 1; ('43', 'DATE'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('4', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'DATE'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('19', 'DATE'): 1; ('20', 'DATE'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('wherein cross', 'ORG'): 1; ('diverse year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the fourteenth year', 'DATE'): 1; ('one hundred eighty five thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Chap', 'ORG'): 1; ('20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('fifteen year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jonathan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Haman', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mordechai', 'NORP'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('— medio de fonte', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Lucret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('surgit amari aliquid', 'ORG'): 1; ('Librat', 'NORP'): 1; ('Antithetis', 'LOC'): 1; ('Eccles', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 4', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('Oxymel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 1; ('the black night', 'TIME'): 1; ('Levit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ainsworth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('a very fair day', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Nemo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('meliora lapsus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Trag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2 Cor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mordechai', 'NORP'): 1; ('Esther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 2', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('61. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Galat', 'GPE'): 1; ('22', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephes', 'ORG'): 1; ('4.', 'DATE'): 1; ('30', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('sanctam hilaritatem', 'ORG'): 1; ('Heinsius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Drusius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Praeterita', 'ORG'): 1; ('Hebrves', 'ORG'): 1; ('Corinthians', 'NORP'): 1; ('15. 15', 'DATE'): 1; ('17. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('the red sea', 'LOC'): 1; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 1"
A75616,10,proposition viz. divine providence affair method sake affair I. family,god: 0.5; man: 0.5; lord: 0.5; church: 0.5; king: 0.45; providence: 0.45; time: 0.45; thing: 0.4; land: 0.35; way: 0.3; host: 0.3; saint: 0.15; mean: 0.05; temple: 0.05; place: 0.05,"('thou', 'GPE'): 8; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 7; ('§', 'NORP'): 5; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 5; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 5; ('Joseph', 'PERSON'): 5; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('Israel', 'GPE'): 4; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 4; ('christian', 'NORP'): 3; ('nonlatinalphabet', 'GPE'): 3; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Jew', 'NORP'): 3; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 3; ('8', 'DATE'): 2; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('8', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 2; ('four', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('seven', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('15', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('August', 'DATE'): 2; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('David', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Haman', 'PERSON'): 2; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Haggai', 'ORG'): 2; ('6', 'DATE'): 2; ('french', 'NORP'): 2; ('Anabaptist', 'NORP'): 2; ('10', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('16', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('I.', 'ORG'): 1; ('1 Sam 2', 'QUANTITY'): 1; ('quisquis Cristianum', 'PERSON'): 1; ('humani hostis', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Orat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('39', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('135', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Phil', 'PERSON'): 1; ('4. 22', 'DATE'): 1; ('Cesar', 'ORG'): 1; ('Christian', 'NORP'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet vir', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet foeminam', 'ORG'): 1; ('nonlatinalphabet ignis', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ga•akers Serm', 'WORK_OF_ART'): 1; ('Eleazar', 'GPE'): 1; ('24. 12 ,', 'DATE'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('14', 'DATE'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('3. 17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('kingdom', 'GPE'): 1; ('15. 6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('the season', 'DATE'): 1; ('239', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Anastasius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Justine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('divina', 'GPE'): 1; ('Desport', 'ORG'): 1; ('Daniels', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Apocalypse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Britain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Saxons', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Danes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Normanes', 'ORG'): 1; ('Isaiah', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jeremy', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hear David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('18. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('32', 'DATE'): 1; ('33', 'DATE'): 1; ('34', 'DATE'): 1; ('39 40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('battle', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Antichrist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 17', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Tit', 'GPE'): 1; ('Fabritius', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jesus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('S. Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Julian', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pelag', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('J. G.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Red', 'ORG'): 1; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('moribus', 'ORG'): 1; ('106', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('45. 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ophir', 'GPE'): 1; ('Exerc', 'ORG'): 1; ('deuteron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('11.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Musculus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Jacob', 'GPE'): 1; ('Austin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ursin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Isaiah 27', 'DATE'): 1; ('Deuteronomy', 'GPE'): 1; ('11. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Canaan', 'GPE'): 1; ('the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the end of the year', 'DATE'): 1; ('the catholic church', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philip', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('6. 26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('B. Andrews', 'ORG'): 1; ('60.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('2. ii', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('105. 17', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('Josephs', 'PERSON'): 1; ('bush', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Egyptians', 'NORP'): 1; ('Pharaohs', 'LOC'): 1; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 1; ('3.', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Joshua', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Solomon', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Ahasuerus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Mordechai', 'NORP'): 1; ('Mordechai', 'GPE'): 1; ('Esther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'): 1; ('Herod', 'ORG'): 1; ('Josephus', 'GPE'): 1; ('interrumperetur aedificatio pluisse', 'ORG'): 1; ('Judaic', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('almost ten year', 'DATE'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Hagg', 'PERSON'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'): 1; ('virgin marry', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Bethlehem', 'ORG'): 1; ('the year 1573', 'DATE'): 1; ('rochel', 'GPE'): 1; ('288', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('Wolfangus Musculus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Melch', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Adam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Theol', 'GPE'): 1; ('373', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('the next morning', 'TIME'): 1; ('Bucer', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Jacob', 'PERSON'): 1; ('32', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('jordan', 'GPE'): 1; ('27. 9', 'DATE'): 1; ('71', 'DATE'): 1; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('totius', 'NORP'): 1; ('Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Id.', 'GPE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zacharius Ursinus', 'ORG'): 1; ('nisi hospita', 'PERSON'): 1; ('40', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('ult', 'ORG'): 1; ('deliverer', 'ORG'): 1; ('Jerem', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 7', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Ephraim', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Matt', 'PERSON'): 1; ('10. 30', 'DATE'): 1; ('10. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('139', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Mal', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 16', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('S. Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 1; ('8. 28', 'DATE'): 1"
A75616,10 | 24897,virulency bitterness spirit way people God harden act evil way,god: 0.5; thing: 0.5; heart: 0.5; man: 0.5; lord: 0.5; way: 0.5; people: 0.5; israel: 0.45; providence: 0.3; say: 0.3; hardness: 0.2; world: 0.15; hand: 0.05; time: 0.05,"('Israel', 'GPE'): 11; ('2', 'CARDINAL'): 9; ('5', 'CARDINAL'): 6; ('Pharaoh', 'PERSON'): 5; ('one', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('1', 'CARDINAL'): 5; ('§', 'NORP'): 4; ('3', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('12', 'CARDINAL'): 4; ('three', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Isa', 'LOC'): 3; ('harden', 'PERSON'): 3; ('Deut', 'PERSON'): 3; ('4', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('two', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('7', 'CARDINAL'): 3; ('Julius', 'PERSON'): 3; ('thou', 'GPE'): 3; ('17', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('Rom', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Pharaoh', 'GPE'): 2; ('Twiss', 'PERSON'): 2; ('the day', 'DATE'): 2; ('Satan', 'GPE'): 2; ('Judas', 'PERSON'): 2; ('first', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('Psal', 'PERSON'): 2; ('Zech', 'ORG'): 2; ('4.', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('nec', 'ORG'): 2; ('6', 'CARDINAL'): 2; ('second', 'ORDINAL'): 2; ('35', 'DATE'): 2; ('19 9', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Paul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('9 18', 'DATE'): 1; ('11', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('harden', 'GPE'): 1; ('Matth', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13. 12', 'DATE'): 1; ('Moses', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('Aaron', 'PERSON'): 1; ('29', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Egypt', 'GPE'): 1; ('this day', 'DATE'): 1; ('S. Austin', 'PERSON'): 1; ('quando non', 'PERSON'): 1; ('excoecare quando', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de Praed', 'PERSON'): 1; ('non indurat', 'PERSON'): 1; ('impertiendo mal•tiam ,', 'PERSON'): 1; ('gratiam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Aug. Epist', 'PERSON'): 1; ('105', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('impart malice', 'PERSON'): 1; ('14', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psalm', 'GPE'): 1; ('Esai .', 'DATE'): 1; ('quod', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Velle', 'GPE'): 1; ('nolle', 'GPE'): 1; ('Austin', 'GPE'): 1; ('Miro', 'ORG'): 1; ('quod etiam sit contra', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nisi sineret', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nec utique nolens sinit', 'ORG'): 1; ('Aug. Enchir.', 'PERSON'): 1; ('160', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nisi omnipotens etiam de malo', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Evangelical', 'NORP'): 1; ('Isal', 'ORG'): 1; ('6. 10', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Pharaohs', 'ORG'): 1; ('94', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('potentiam cogendi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('utiam suadendi', 'PERSON'): 1; ('16.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Saul', 'PERSON'): 1; ('13', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('it|be', 'PERSON'): 1; ('81. 11', 'DATE'): 1; ('Vid', 'PERSON'): 1; ('vindici', 'PERSON'): 1; ('94', 'DATE'): 1; ('daily', 'DATE'): 1; ('9 34', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Zechary', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hircino', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('mollis erit', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Pharisee', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Leviticus', 'GPE'): 1; ('Hugo de S. victor', 'PERSON'): 1; ('lib', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de sacram', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Hugo', 'EVENT'): 1; ('Exerc', 'ORG'): 1; ('Melancthon', 'GPE'): 1; ('nihil curate', 'PERSON'): 1; ('de ira dei', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Judaeus Apello', 'ORG'): 1; ('Lactantius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Horace', 'PERSON'): 1; ('113', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('6', 'DATE'): 1; ('7', 'DATE'): 1; ('8', 'DATE'): 1; ('earth', 'LOC'): 1; ('nec magna', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('nec parva', 'ORG'): 1; ('Molin', 'GPE'): 1; ('23', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('five', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Monendus', 'ORG'): 1; ('Philippus', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('wolf', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Luther', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Maximilian', 'NORP'): 1; ('aeterne nisi vigilares', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Historia Pontificum', 'GPE'): 1; ('259', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Natur', 'PERSON'): 1; ('73', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('13', 'DATE'): 1; ('18', 'DATE'): 1; ('John', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Gaius', 'PERSON'): 1; ('3. 65', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('house', 'ORG'): 1; ('worth many thousand', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Prov', 'ORG'): 1; ('10. 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('nulla', 'PERSON'): 1; ('miseria quam', 'PERSON'): 1; ('nihil infelicius', 'ORG'): 1; ('32.', 'DATE'): 1; ('David', 'PERSON'): 1; ('37.', 'DATE'): 1; ('36', 'DATE'): 1; ('winter', 'DATE'): 1; ('Mammon', 'PRODUCT'): 1; ('§', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Frenchman', 'NORP'): 1; ('Richelieu', 'GPE'): 1; ('Ludov', 'ORG'): 1; ('166', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33. 29', 'DATE'): 1; ('26', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('33', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Psalm 127', 'GPE'): 1; ('15. 3', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('Isa', 'ORG'): 1; ('52.', 'DATE'): 1; ('Spain', 'GPE'): 1; ('Bristol', 'ORG'): 1; ('Madrid', 'GPE'): 1; ('Stephen Marshall', 'PERSON'): 1; ('five thousand year', 'DATE'): 1; ('Daniels', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Daniel', 'PERSON'): 1; ('Dan', 'PERSON'): 1; ('2. 19 , 20', 'CARDINAL'): 1; ('21', 'DATE'): 1; ('Augustine', 'PERSON'): 1; ('mund•s', 'ORG'): 1; ('evertatur mundus', 'PERSON'): 1; ('benedicam domino', 'PERSON'): 1; ('August', 'DATE'): 1; ('Anselm', 'ORG'): 1; ('Ʋrbanum Pap', 'ORG'): 1; ('Canterbury', 'GPE'): 1"
